<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="pr_faith_1t">
Отче!
\nБудь ласка, дай нам зрозуміти серце Ісуса, який змушений був залишити своїх улюблених учнів і, йдучи шляхом хреста, мав піти до вічного світу, і, будь ласка, дозволь нам відчути і пережити серцем Ісуса Христа, який зібрав своїх учнів біля колін і з великою турботою та щирим проханням звертався до своїх улюблених учнів, які йшли за ним, розділяючи радість, гнів, смуток та насолоду протягом трьох років.
\n\nМи щиро сподіваємось і бажаємо, щоб ти дозволив нам стати улюбленими дітьми, які здатні смиренно принести себе в жертву заради однієї Волі, і, розуміючи це розумом і відчуваючи всім тілом, дозволь нашим серцям, які здатні відгукнутися на Його заклик, проникнути до небес, і якщо Його серце рухається, дозволь нам рухатися разом з Ним, впливаючи на людей землі.
\n\nБудь ласка, дозволь нам відчути і пережити серце Ісуса Христа, який, перебуваючи в цьому гіркому людському світі, бачив, як усі натовпи, що йшли за ним, відступили, і залишилося лише дванадцять апостолів; але Він відчував, що навіть серед них незабаром Юда зрадить його. Ми щиро сподіваємось і бажаємо, щоб ти дозволив нам сьогодні пережити і відчути через наші серця і тіла серце Ісуса Христа, коли все, що залишилося від його трирічного шляху публічного життя, сповненого праці та віри у людей, була така самотня ситуація.
\n\nОтче! Дозволь нам сьогодні пережити і відчути біль серця Ісуса Христа, який говорив із небесами, дивлячись на шлях розп\'яття. І ми щиро сподіваємось, що ти встановиш нас як дітей, здатних стати об\'єктами втіхи для Його серця, як живі жертви, що схиляються перед тобою, Отче.
\n\nМи молимося в ім\'я Господа.
\nАмінь.
\n23 травня 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_2t">
Любий Батьку!
\nСкільки разів Ісус сподівався на покаяння від народу Ізраїлю, від фарисеїв і людей єврейської релігії, які не вірили в Нього?
\n\nДозволь нам стати людьми, чиї серця і тіла торкнені шляхом Ісуса, якого вигнали і переслідували, і який не міг спокійно спати, і дозволь нам стати людьми, які не можуть не відчувати серце Ісуса, хочемо ми того чи ні, і які не можуть не почати уподібнюватися Його серцю, хочемо ми того чи ні. І більше того, чи не є це Волею, яку Ти шукаєш, і надією, яку ми прагнемо, щоб таке серце з\'явилося серед нас?
\n\nДозволь нам відчути, що тепер ми маємо відповідальність взяти на себе шлях, який пройшов Ісус Христос, і послання Євангелія, яке залишив Ісус, і відповідальність повернути Тобі, Отче, славу перемоги, борючись із мільярдами сатан.
\n\nДозволь нам стати дітьми з такими установками, які здатні стояти твердо, і які вірять у Твої слова життя і Твої слова істини, з впевненими манерами, як у Ісуса, який вірив у небо і стояв твердо перед натовпами всіх зібраних.
\n\nБудь ласка, не дозволь нам сьогодні хвалитися перед Ісусом, і не дозволь нам сьогодні говорити про наші ситуації перед Тобою, Отче. Будь ласка, веди нас так, щоб ми могли представляти Твоє серце, Отче, і могли зайняти те саме положення, що й Ісус. Якщо це Твоя воля, Отче, щоб ми з\'явилися без вагань перед людьми в будь-який час, у будь-яку годину, щоб представляти Волю Ісуса Христа, то, Отче, будь ласка, прийди до кожного з нас і дай нам вказівки щодо кожної речі.
\n\nЯ щиро сподіваюся і бажаю, мій Отче, щоб Ти привів нас до того, щоб стати святими, які мобілізуються для виконання Твоєї Волі, і які здатні виступити і боротися, представляючи Ісуса Христа, щоб здійснити Твою Волю, Отче.
\n\nТепер, оскільки ми будемо твердо проголошувати Твою Волю всім людям, Отче, будь ласка, встанови нас як воїнів неба і встанови нас як Твоїх дітей. Будь ласка, дай нам вказівки, порадь нам, поклич нас і встанови нас у положенні, яким Ти можеш пишатися.
\n\nЩиро сподіваючись, що Ти полюбиш нас і направиш нас, ми смиренно молилися в ім\'я Господа.
\nАмінь.
\n27 травня 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_3t">
Ми відчули у наших серцях історію праці нашого Отця, який здійснював провидіння, встановлюючи закони небесної моралі, щоб створити в усьому космосі призначені відносини з життям відновлення.
\n\nОтче, будь ласка, веди нас до того, щоб ми стали людьми, які глибоко усвідомлюють, що Ти трудився протягом 6,000 років, щоб встановити світовий рівень цінності життя.
\n\nОскільки ми зрозуміли, що це небесний закон, що Ти не можеш вести релігії, які не утворюють зв\'язки від індивідуального рівня до цілого, будь ласка, дозволь нам тепер жити життям, якого прагне Ісус Христос, і ми щиро сподіваємося і бажаємо, щоб Ти дозволив нам пізнати цінність любові Ісуса Христа.
\n\nОскільки ми усвідомили, що і ми повинні мати рішучість життя, яку мав Ісус Христос, будь з нами, щоб ми могли відганяти вторгнення Сатани і перемагати на полі битви, де можемо знайти цінність нашого індивідуального життя.
\n\nОскільки ми зрозуміли, що звинувачення Сатани існують щодо нашого проходження курсу відновлення цінності життя, яку залишив Ісус Христос замість себе, будь ласка, веди нас так, щоб ми не були тими, кого звинувачує Сатана, щодо курсу, який ми наполегливо продовжуємо і йдемо вперед від рівня нашого індивідуального життя до життя світу і життя космосу.
\n\nМи щиро сподіваємося і бажаємо, улюблений Отче, щоб Ти дозволив нам твердо блокувати звинувачення сатани в нашому повсякденному житті, і мати рішучість блокувати його з погляду історії, і будь ласка, дозволь нам виконати цю відповідальність.
\n\nОскільки ми тепер знаємо, що повинні уподібнюватися досконалому характеру Ісуса, який мав владу над усіма речами творіння, улюблений Отче, будь ласка, веди нас, щоб ми могли уподібнюватися характеру Христа. І оскільки ми, незалежно від того, ким ми є, перебуваємо у положенні, де маємо йти шляхом боротьби, Отче, будь ласка, веди нас так, щоб нас не звинувачував Сатана щодо нашого життя у суспільстві, щодо нашого характеру або щодо любові.
\n\nБудь з нами, щоб реалізувати любов Христа, який щиро прагнув реалізувати любов нашого вічного Отця.
\n\nЩиро сподіваючись, що Ти будеш володарювати над нами, щоб ми мали цінність життя, яку встановив Христос, і усвідомили цю цінність на цій землі, ми молилися в ім\'я Господа.
\nАмінь.
\n6 січня 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_4t">
Отче!
\nТурбуючись про нашу власну нинішню негідність, ми, звичайно, повинні стати людьми, які можуть плакати, але ми щиро сподіваємося і бажаємо, щоб Ти направив нас стати синами і дочками, які здатні плакати, турбуючись про плоди, що були волею Ісуса. У той самий час, коли ми повинні стати людьми, що плачуть, усвідомлюючи власну неповноту, будь ласка, дозволь нам стати людьми, які здатні каятися і проливати сльози, побачивши спокуси Сатани, який кричить і ображає Ісуса, і усвідомивши, що світ став злим і не виконав волю Божу.
\n\nЗавжди відчуваючи погляд Бога на собі протягом свого життя, Ісус, щоб завершити шлях відновлення через відшкодування, приносив себе в жертву для відновлення до самого моменту своєї смерті. Точно так само, незалежно від того, в який день або в який час Ісус приходить до нас, будь ласка, не дозволяй нам забути його погляд, звернений на нас, або його кроки, що наближаються до нас. Дозволь нам зрозуміти, що досі було незліченну кількість разів, коли ми ігнорували погляд Ісуса та його кроки, коли він наближався до нас.
\n\nОтче! Дозволь нам стати людьми, які каються за кількість сліз, пролитих перед небом, і за те, як мало ми втішали серце Ісуса, який незмінно приходив до людства, хоча ми зраджували його не один раз, а навіть два чи три рази.
\n\nО Отче! Оскільки твої самотні сини і дочки знають, що час світового суду недалекий, і сад вселенської Голгофи вже перед нашими очима, будь ласка, направ нас не йти шляхом віри, зосередженим на нас самих.
\n\nОскільки наші життя не належать нам, і життя, яке ми проживаємо щодня, не належить нам, і наші надії та бажання не належать нам, будь ласка, направ нас не жити щоденним життям для себе, і, улюблений Отче, ми щиро сподіваємося і бажаємо, щоб Ти дозволив нам не мати наших здібностей, прохань і бажань, всі ці речі для себе.
\n\nНавіть якщо ми підемо шляхом розп’яття замість Ісуса, ми щиро сподіваємося і бажаємо, люблячий Отче, щоб Ти направив нас стати синами і дочками, які нарешті пізнають незмінну віру Ісуса; які здатні каятися, проливаючи сльози в присутності Ісуса до того, як настане день суду Голгофи, так само як Петро плакав у своєму серці та проливав сльози як вірянин у Бога, коли бачив Ісуса, що ніс хрест; і які здатні відкрити свої провини та плакати перед Тобою, узявши на себе всесвітнє покаяння.
\n\nОтче! Оскільки ми йтимемо слідами Ісуса замість нього, Отче, будь ласка, дай нам місію рятувати нещасних людей цієї землі, і дозволь нам пройти залишок шляху Голгофи.
\n\nІ коли ми переможемо Сатану всюди у світі та здійснимо основу слави перемоги, ми щиро сподіваємося і бажаємо, щоб Ти повів нас так, щоб ми могли вшановувати воскреслого Ісуса за наше життя.
\n\nМи смиренно молилися в ім\'я Господа.
\nАмінь.
\n10 лютого 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_5t">
Батьку!
\nТи послав Ісуса Христа на землю як Господа, що має владу над вічним ідеалом, і як Господа, що має владу над вічним добром, щоб скоротити відстань, яка збільшилася між нами через падіння людських прабатьків. Пробач людству, яке не змогло прийняти Ісуса як Господа, що прийшов як уособлення, що представляє Тебе.
\n\nМи знаємо, що через недосконалість наших прабатьків Ісус переживав страждання, і ми усвідомили, що страждання Ісуса все ще тривають через нашу недосконалість сьогодні. Тому, будь ласка, дозволи нам стати здатними виконати Твою надію, щоб ми постали гідними перед усім створінням, успадкувавши дорогоцінну працю доброго пастиря.
\n\nІ дозволь нам бути здатними реалізувати надію Ісуса, і дозволь нам стати такими, щоб носити Твоє життя і Твою любов, а також життя Ісуса і любов Ісуса. Ми зрозуміли, що якщо ми не станемо такими, то в майбутньому у світі людства ми ніколи не зможемо вирішити болісну ситуацію Ісуса Христа, який прийшов як добрий пастир.
\n\nТому, відкриваючи двері наших сердець, будь ласка, направ нас бути здатними почути голос доброго пастиря, який кличе нас. Тепер, коли ми знаємо болісну ситуацію нашого Отця, знаємо Твою самотню ситуацію, знаємо ситуацію нашого Отця, який так багато працював, ми глибоко соромимося себе. О Отче, будь ласка, направ нас не ставати людьми, що просять, нещасними, які покладають усі свої печалі, самотність, праці та страждання на Ісуса.
\n\nТепер, коли ми знаємо всі таємниці Сатани, Твою внутрішню ситуацію та внутрішнє серце Ісуса, ми щиро сподіваємося і бажаємо, Отче, щоб Ти дав нам силу взяти на себе відповідальність за Твою ситуацію, за сум, самотність, страждання та обмеження Ісуса, і бути здатними боротися з мільярдами сатан.
\n\nОтче! Дозволь нам бути здатними дивитися на Ісуса, який працює, сповнений смутку, і який турбується про нашу ситуацію, і дозволь нам усвідомити, що навіть сьогодні Ісус відчуває біль від розп’яття через нашу зворушливу ситуацію.
\n\nМи не знали, що коли ми в скорботі, звертаючись до неба, у печалі, звертаючись до неба, і в самоті, звертаючись до неба, Ісус приходить, щоб відчути ще більшу самотність, більший смуток і більше страждань, щоб втішити нас. Тепер, навіть якщо наші страждання більші за страждання Ісуса, і наші печалі більші за печалі Ісуса, і наші труднощі більші за труднощі Ісуса, будь ласка, допоможи нам стати справжніми синами і дочками, які здатні турбуватися і благати, щоб забрати печаль Ісуса.
\n\nІ ми щиро сподіваємося і бажаємо, щоб Ти дозволив нам стати здатними йти за добрим пастирем і втішати палке серце доброго пастиря. Ми щиро сподіваємося, щоб Ти дозволив нам стати людьми, які беруть на себе місію Ісуса від його імені і які здатні боротися і боротися з Сатаною, навіть якщо невидимий Сатана створює страждання і страх, атакуючи нас безпосередньо в нашому житті, і ми щиро сподіваємося, щоб Ти встановив нас знову як синів і дочок, здатних успадкувати життя Ісуса.
\n\nМи молилися про все це в ім\'я Господа.
\nАмінь.
\n31 березня 1957


    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_6t">
Ми знаємо, що Ісус Христос, який був посланий Тобою, наш Отче, Який трудився протягом 4000 років після Адама, прийшов як Твоє втілення, як плід сліз, поту і крові, і Він прийшов із місією проливати сльози за Тебе, проливати піт за Тебе, проливати кров за Тебе, і з місією вирішити Твою ворожнечу.
\n\nКоли ми думаємо про те, що Ісус Христос ішов шляхом сліз, представляючи небо, ішов шляхом важкої праці без хвилини відпочинку, представляючи всіх людей, і йшов важкий шлях Свого публічного життя, Отче, дозволь нам щиро замислитися над тим, чи стали ми людьми, які здатні зустріти такого Христа.
\n\nКоли Ісус ніс хрест на своїх плечах і йшов до гори Голгофа, у далині були жінки, які ридали і голосили за Ним, але Ісус обернувся до них і сказав: “Дочки Єрусалимські, не плачте за Мною, а плачте за себе і за своїх дітей”.
\n\nСьогодні, будь ласка, дозволь нам відчути і глибоко усвідомити в цей час палке серце Христа, коли Він говорив це. Оскільки ми знаємо, що людина, яка не знає ситуації хреста, не може отримати спасіння від хреста, і що людина, яка не вміє відчувати і глибоко усвідомлювати серце Ісуса, коли Він ішов на хрест, не може стати на бік істини, Отче, зглянься на Своїх синів і дочок, які зібралися тут у цей час.
\n\nНавіть якщо ми нічого не маємо і нічого не можемо Тобі запропонувати, Отче, ми щиро сподіваємося і бажаємо, Отче, щоб Ти дозволив нам стати захисниками доброти, які, закарбувавши у своїх серцях самотність Христа у Гетсиманському саду, зустрічають і борються з ворогами, які наступають і вторгаються.
\n\nМи знаємо, що настав час, коли сьогодні ми повинні пройти вершину світового Голгофи, і ми повинні закликати до цього світу, який схожий на пустелю, останній заклик, який Ісус проголошував у місці під назвою Гетсиманія. Тому ми щиро сподіваємося і бажаємо, Отче, щоб Ти вів нас, щоб ми не стали синами і дочками, які живуть для себе і тримають Христа на відстані.
\n\nОтче! Дозволь нам стати людьми, які, представляючи серце Ісуса Христа, першими беруть на себе відповідальність за труднощі, коли є труднощі, і першими беруть на себе відповідальність за скорботи, коли є скорботи, і які, навіть якщо ми впадемо після страждань, якщо це є Твоя Воля, зможуть боротися і йти вперед, охоче підкоряючись цьому.
\n\nМи молилися в ім\'я Господа.
\nАмінь.
\n30 червня 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_7t">
Любий Батьку!
\nМи щиро надіємось і бажаємо, Отче, щоб Ти дозволив нам стати настільки єдиними в розумі та Волі, щоб, коли Ти нерухомий, ми також були нерухомі, а коли Ти рухаєшся, ми також рухалися.
\n\nБудь ласка, дозволь нам відчути серце Ісуса в той час, коли він зустрічався з недовірою на землі та турбувався, втішаючи зболене серце Бога і був розчарований. І ми щиро сподіваємось, що Ти дозволиш нашим розумам не залишатися бездіяльними у цей час, а навпаки, бути здатними рухатися, з\'єднаними з Твоїм серцем і історичним серцем Ісуса.
\n\nБудь ласка, дозволь нам відчути Твоє зболене серце в наших думках і дозволь нам глибоко відчути серце Ісуса Христа, який страждав, щоб спасти людство, і ми щиро надіємось і бажаємо, возлюблений Отче, щоб Ти дозволив нам спокутувати всі гріхи темряви, які залишаються в наших думках.
\n\nОскільки ми знаємо, що перед нами сатана завжди діє, щоб блокувати Твою благодать, Отче, будь ласка, дозволь нам стати людьми, які, розуміючи, коли і в якій ситуації приходить Твоя благодать, здатні подолати атаки сатани та бути обійнятими у вічних обіймах Твоєї любові.
\n\nМи щиро сподіваємось, що Ти дозволиш нам відчути Твій дотик милосердя, дотик нашого Отця, який шукав нас і, виконуючи провидіння протягом 6 000 років, не відкинув нас, навіть коли ми були нерозумними та недостатніми.
\n\nМи молилися в ім\'я Господа.
\nАмінь.
\n12 січня 1958

    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_8t">
Батьку!
\nМи знаємо, що для того, щоб відновити Адама та Єву, яких було втрачено, після того як ти працював 4,000 років, ти послав Ісуса на цю землю як людину в зовнішній подобі Адама. Чим більша була твоя праця до народження Ісуса, тим більшим джерелом гордості для неба мав бути Ісус, який народився завдяки цій праці, і він повинен був стати гордістю людства і всього творіння. Небо знало цю істину, але земля була неосвіченою і не знала; небо вітало його, але сьогодні ми не можемо не соромитися за те, що, не знаючи, земля його не вітала.
\n\nРоздумуючи над сумною правдою, що надійний погляд нашого Батька, який так тяжко працював, змушений був зупинитися на бідному Ісусі, який лежав у яслах, ми гостро відчуваємо, що наші предки не мали віри, і наші предки не мали вірності. Оскільки ми знаємо факт, що помилка гріхопадіння Адама та Єви знову була продемонстрована людством у тому місці, сьогодні ми не можемо не бути надзвичайно засмученими і відчувати цю сумну історичну правду у своїх серцях.
\n\nМи щиро сподіваємось і бажаємо, щоб ти дозволив нам мати можливість утішити твій смуток, Батьку, замість вибраного народу, народу Ізраїлю, який не зміг утішити тебе в минулому.
\n\nОскільки минуло близько двох тисяч років з моменту приходу Ісуса, але ми знаємо, що світ серця перевершує час. О Батьку, який перевершує історію, дозволь нам у цей час стати здатними обійняти і прийняти серце Ісуса Христа, який пішов на небо з сумним серцем.
\n\nМи щиро сподіваємось і бажаємо, Батьку, щоб ти дозволив цьому стати часом, коли ми зможемо вшанувати в наших серцях образ Ісуса в момент його народження, знаючи ненависть, що пронизує і залишається на землі і на небі до сьогодні, та муки 2,000 років після приходу і відходу Ісуса.
\n\nБатьку, будь ласка, благослови цей момент сьогодні, коли ми святкуємо цей день, і дозволь, щоб смуток Ісуса, який прийшов і пішов 2,000 років тому, був вирішений через цей один день, відкривши славу радості, на яку сподівався Ісус. Оскільки ми, хто знає всі найглибші серця, хочемо святкувати цей день, дозволь, щоб усі муки минулого, про які людство не знало і залишило позаду, були відшкодовані завдяки цьому часу, і ми щиро сподіваємось і бажаємо, щоб, дозволивши нам стати перед тобою, Ісус був щасливий, і ти був утішений, Батьку.
\n\nМи щиро сподіваємось, щоб ти дозволив цьому бути святим часом, коли ми зможемо знайти джерело щастя, вирішуючи через нас горе, залишене тисячоліттями, і щоб те, що ми приносимо з об’єднаними думками тобі, Батьку, стало історичною жертвою, яка вирішує горе.
\n\nМи молилися в ім\'я Господа.
\nАмінь.
\n3 січня 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_9t">
Батьку!
\nНіхто з людей на землі не знає цього дня, і ніхто не усвідомив муки небес, і ще менше вони знають про твоє нескінченно скорботне серце. Ми не можемо не дякувати тобі за те, що дозволив нам благодать слави святкування, як день народження Христа, цей день, про який люди не знають, даруючи цей день нам, які не знають жалюгідної правди того дня, Отче.
\n\nБудь ласка, дозволь цьому святкуванню сьогодні стати можливістю втішити серце Ісуса, який був у муках протягом 2000 років. Дозволь цьому стати часом роздумів над Христом, який народився у становищі страждання, прожив своє життя понад 30 років і не уникав шляху Голгофи; і стати часом прийняття його старих битв як незавершених справ. Ми знаємо, що не можна обійтися без того, щоб у цей час ми не успадкували, як наше завдання, велику працю, яку він залишив під час свого життя.
\n\nО, Отче! Люди на землі не знають, що ворожнеча, залишена Ісусом, досі залишається на землі. Дозволь умам і тілам твоїх синів і дочок, які зібрані тут зараз, бути охопленими твоїм серцем, і дозволь нам зрозуміти серце Ісуса, яке було таким, і бути здатними втішити його, зрозумівши про серце Ісуса, що зустріло смерть.
\n\nОскільки це важливий день, коли не обійтися без того, щоб залишити свідчення перемоги перед тобою, встановивши умову, навіть якщо це буде через вшанування нової волі в цей дорогоцінний день, будь ласка, пам\'ятай цей день.
\n\nПоки ми щиро просимо тебе, будь ласка, прояви себе через радість, ми покірно молилися в ім\'я Господа.
\nАмінь.
\n3 січня 1959

    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_10t">
Батьку!
\nЧи був хто-небудь на цій землі, хто знав би розум Ісуса? Оскільки не було жодної людини, яка бачила Ісуса, сповненого тривоги, і яка б відчула та глибоко усвідомила скорботу неба, що проникала у її розум, ми знаємо, що небо не могло не журитися через людей, які були такими.
\n\nУ цей час дозволь нам відчути через наші серця сумний факт, що, не маючи жодного учня, який би, знаючи серце неба, назвав його "Господи", Ісусу довелося йти життєвим шляхом, всіяним сумнівами, і, більше того, зустріти кінець свого самотнього життя, сповненого сумнівів. О, Отче! Дозволь нам стати людьми, які можуть осягнути самотнє серце Ісуса, який зібрав своїх учнів перед собою та повинен був сказати їм, що незабаром його життя на землі закінчиться, і він піде в царство свого Отця.
\n\nЯкщо розглядати це в рамках часу, між Ісусом і нами є період у 2,000 років, але оскільки ми знаємо, що світ серця може перевершувати час, будь ласка, дозволи відбуватися актам прямого досвіду та глибокого відчуття, щоб, зворушені до сліз самотнім серцем і виснаженим виглядом Ісуса, ми змогли сьогодні побачити його святий образ, який звертався до нас слово за словом. Така сцена є сценою, яку ми, як людські істоти, не можемо не прагнути.
\n\nІсус обіймав ревне серце неба, обіймав всю роботу неба і прийшов до людства, але людство ставилося до Ісуса, який був такою людиною, як їм заманеться, і повністю відкинуло його. Вони поставили його в абсолютно самотнє положення.
\n\nАле дозволь нам дізнатися про самотню ситуацію Ісуса, який не мав навіть одного учня, якому можна було б довіряти в присутності похмурого серця Ісуса, який думав, що, щоб відкрити єдиний шлях до саду життя, не можна було обійтися без того, щоб вести їх до Гефсиманії, і не можна було обійтися без того, щоб вони йшли шляхом хреста на Голгофу. Дозволь нам дізнатися, що навіть ідучи без сперечань через місце скорботи і навіть будучи сповненим скорботи, Ісус не міг залишити людство, яке було таким.
\n\nСьогодні дозволь нам бути здатними спілкуватися з серцем того часу та звертатися до неба, думаючи про ці істини, і вигукувати до неба, кажучи: "О Отче!" з серцем Ісуса, який був у положенні, як сирота.
\n\nМи щиро сподіваємося і бажаємо, Отче, щоб ти дозволив цим людям стати учнями, які відкривають свої серця і можуть вірити, і щоб ти дозволив цим людям стати тими, хто може свідчити про Ісуса.
\n\nМи щиро сподіваємося, що ти дозволиш нам співчувати серцю Ісуса, який мав залишити учнів, які не знали, яким великим був його смуток, і серцю Ісуса, який був у положенні, коли потрібно було завершити своє життя, не побачивши його плодів, незважаючи на те, що він прожив усе своє життя заради людства. Дозволь нам співчувати розуму Ісуса, який турбувався про небо з надзвичайно сумним серцем.
\n\nМи смиренно молилися про все це в ім\'я Господа.
\nАмінь.
\n11 січня 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_11t">
Oh Father!
\nThe closer that the time comes to meeting the Lord of resurrection, the more hesitant our minds become. As the time comes closer, please let us imagine even more Jesus Christ, who embraced the sorrowful destiny of death.
\n\nWe have come to know that he who died at the seat of punishment, passed on with enmity in his heart. Since we have come to know that the mount of Golgotha that he walked upon was a peak of the tears of destiny, we know that the blood and sweat he shed have lived on in the history of destiny until today, and they are being resurrected and are going into the innermost hearts of each human being.
\n\nBecause of the blood and sweat that were shed in the center of the Will of the historical providence of destiny, we know that all these things will move forward through that blood and sweat, until that destiny conies into existence. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become people who are filled with that kind of heart today, and who are in that kind of state.
\n\nThe Lord who passed on like this, the Lord, who was the bridegroom, said that he would go through a history of destiny and come again. Since we know that the Lord inclines his mind and body towards us and that the heart of the Lord earnestly desires to seek and establish us, please allow us to have minds that earnestly desire to be our real selves and to be proud of our adorned appearances before all people.
\n\nAs we seek to go that way, we find an evil world; since the way that the Lord walked remains, we must walk over the remaining peak of the people, and we must walk over the remaining peak of the world by enduring, and enduring, and enduring again. We have come to know for the first time that it will not do unless we maintain, by enduring, a history of martyrdom, which can go over the peak of the cross, which remains on the earth now.
\n\nNow please let us feel that destiny with new minds, and anticipate it with new minds, and be able to go forth until the day that we are able to cling to you and weep, Father, while enduring with new minds, and please allow us to become able to go beyond the destiny of accumulated sorrow. While earnestly requesting that you will let us become sons and daughters who are able to tread upon the authority of death by enduring and remaining until the time that we can boast of the destiny of joy, and sing of the glory of resurrection.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 29, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_12t">
Father!
\nWhat was the hope John the Baptist held in his heart as he preached in the wilderness for 30 years eating locusts and wild honey? We know that his entire hope was greeting the Messiah who was coming.
\n\nHe, who had borne witness to the Messiah, had a destined relationship of heavenly morality such that it would not do unless he became one with the Messiah. By reflecting everything Jesus had in John the Baptist`s heart, John the Baptist should have realized a unity that said he is in my mind, and I am in him; his things are my things; his heart is my heart, and his life is my life; but he could not do that.
\n\nWhen he was imprisoned sorrow and loneliness, from a position of not being able to help lamenting his lonely situation, and remembering that he had raised up his hands and borne witness that this was the son of heaven in front of the crowds at the Jordan River, John the Baptist sent his disciples to the Messiah he had borne witness to, to the Messiah heaven had borne witness to and established, and he asked him, "Are you he who is to come, or shall we look for another?" We have come to know that this scene was a historical, sorrowful scene; it was a scene filled with anguish which was difficult for heaven to go through.
\n\nThe course of John the Baptist remains in the flow of history just as it was. Please allow those of us who are hoping to find a new belief, who are preparing, while anticipating a new history, to become people who know how to consider things having put ourselves in John the Baptist`s position.
\n\nSince we have come to know through history the fact that the people of heaven rejected heaven`s Will, please take dominion so that we will not become people who follow in those kinds of historical footsteps, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will not allow us to become people who lose the Will that was prepared and refined in the wilderness.
\n\nPlease allow us to realize that today our minds and bodies have no honor before you, Father. Please let us be able to hear your words of advice and inherit the sorrowful heart of Jesus Christ, and we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow our minds and bodies to be able to embrace the sorrowful, heavenly heart and to greet the new central figure of the new belief, whom humankind does not know.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow this to become a time when we can be concerned about who the central figure is who will take care of this age and which people is the people who will be able to remain in this age, and when we can be filled with sorrowful hearts and long for those who are like that.
\n\nNow the time has come when we, who live inclining our ears to the words we hear and the voice we hear, and who live in concert with that and respond to that, must look back on the path we have walked and come to our senses anew.
\n\nPlease let us go beyond the position of being concerned about our own selves, who are in a position of having to determine whether to live or die, while being in the midst of confusion and chaos. We know that the society cannot be trusted, and the world cannot be trusted, and the time has come that we must be submerged in the world of the doctrine we can believe, and we must come to our senses on our own and be able to form a destined relationship with the world of that doctrine, and recognizing ourselves, we must cling to heaven, and we know that the time has come that it will not do unless we have a revolutionary change of mind.
\n\nPlease guide us to be able to pursue a new self, remembering that we are in such an environment, and please let us become people who are able to greet the appearance of joy, by going over the peak of sorrow filled with enmity, and please let us be able to long for that appearance, to be led by that world, and to harmonize with that world.
\n\nPlease give us the strength and courage to be able to block and fight, and to consider it pitiful that today the social environment is not free and that it is filled with sorrow. If there is a heaven that is eternal and absolute, we earnestly ask that you will give us the power to be able to cast aside the entirety of sin.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nApril 12, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_13t">
Father!
\nWe long for the holy majesty of Jesus of 2,000 years ago. We would come to realize that the desolate world lay before Jesus who was conveying the word, and there were people who were centered on themselves and sought to lift themselves up, but through the gaze of Jesus who looked upon those people there was an infinitely sorrowful heart flowing.
\n\nOh Jesus, who looked upon Judaism, in which the religious sects were fighting each other, and upon the reality of the believers who argued with each other! When we reflect on the nature of that era when people struggled to push themselves to the forefront by hiding their faults and revealing others faults, we understand the infinite sorrow of the mind of Jesus, who truly had come to take responsibility for that world and that age.
\n\nWe can measure the heart of Jesus who, in spite of that, called out, "Ask, and it will be given you; seek, and you will find; knock and it will be opened to you." The ones who had to ask, seek, and knock were the people, the religious orders, and the individuals, but those who had to ask did not know how to, and those who had to seek did not know how to, and those who had to knock did not know how to.
\n\nJesus, who was watching that, was in a position such that it wouldn`t do unless he asked representing humankind, and he was in a position such that it wouldn`t do unless he sought representing humankind, and he was in a position such that it wouldn`t do unless he knocked representing humankind. This was a sorrowful thing, Father.
\n\nThe Messiah, who was sent and longed for humankind to seek him, was instead in a position where he had to seek, and heaven, which hoped that humankind would attend him, had made preparation through the long course of history, but he was in a position of not being attended by humankind. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow this to be a time when we feel the lonely heart of Jesus.
\n\nAs Jesus related to humankind on the earth, the situation was such that he could not help but weep and lament, but nevertheless he hoped that the earth could become such that you could bless it. Please act to manifest the holy majesty of Jesus here before us today, and we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will let us become a group of people who are able to hear his voice which is commanding us; who are able to adore, experience and feel keenly his heavenly heart which is silently flowing in his innermost self; and who are able to bow down and weep.
\n\nSince we have raised up our hands and have appeared as naked people before you, Father, please have mercy on us. Please do not allow anything other than you in our minds, Father, and please do not allow our hopes, or our desires, or any conditions that we request to be anything other than what is yours. We earnestly hope and desire that you will let us become sons and daughters who are able to live clinging to minds which are filled with your infinite heart, and to live experiencing and feeling keenly those minds, and fight together on the side of those minds. We have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nApril 26, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_14t">
Oh Father, who has carried out the providence in order to greet the day of hope you have anticipated and waited for, you could not cast away faithless humankind, and in order to embrace the many lonely groups of people, you gave the blessing of Israel, and led history forward, and on the day that you sent the being you had promised, heaven should have been filled with your glory, and through the rejoicing hearts of all the people, both heaven and earth should have been filled with joy but Father, we know the greatly mortifying historical fact that the sorrow of 4,000 years was imposed on the one person of Jesus.
\n\nHe was born in a stable, and the more than 30 years he lived were so wretched and so lonely, and there were so few places he could depend on. Today we know that Jesus, who had so few people he could trust, died as the leading character of enmity, and was not able to open his innermost heart to people or express his earnest heart on the earth.
\n\nThere remained heavenly advice he had to give, but because the people who had to receive it did not believe in him, he could not say everything, and he died with the sorrow of it still being in his heart. Please forgive all humankind who do not know that sorrow of Jesus 2,000 years ago. Nevertheless, we have heard the prayers, the words of advice and the requests he gave to the disciples he gathered and who followed heaven.
\n\nWe know the mortifying historical fact that the moment when his destiny and heaven\'s destiny met, the joy of heaven should have been created, and furthermore a new kingdom should have been built on earth. But the moment that those destinies collided with each other, joy disappeared, lamentation and anguish began, and the path of the cross of enmity came into being.
\n\nOur ancestors became indebted to heaven, and we, too, are indebted universally to heaven, so we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will pardon the fact that we are a group of people who are seeking our own comfort and who do not know how to indemnify that.
\n\nFather! How many sons and daughters do you have on this earth, who have minds that have experienced and felt keenly your grieving heart, who are concerned about the earth, and who are concerned about heaven? Father, we know that they are very rare. Our Father, who has passed through the ages, counseling our lonely selves while not minding putting forth a great deal of effort in order to save all the pitiful people, please establish a new covenant with us. If there is a heavenly Will to give to these people a new covenant and a mission of the new age, Father, please carry out that work.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMay 17, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_15t">
Today we know of and believe in Jesus who was born and died in history, but there is no one who knows of and believes in Jesus and his heart when he was rejected and driven out, and wandered to that town when he was driven out of this one and to that village when he was driven out of this one. We have not been able to find in history a person who knew Jesus, who appeared representing the heart of heaven.
\n\nThe people of Israel, who were awaiting the Messiah, had the hope of meeting the Messiah in their hearts, and they struggled and endured through several thousand years, and they anticipated wondering in which age the Messiah would appear. But we cannot help but recall that when that goal appeared in reality, they were fast asleep, without knowing the heart of heaven because they leaned towards the environment they were in and their own situations.
\n\nIf today we have the responsibility of resolving the enmity that has penetrated your heart, as we recall that there was that kind of lamentable history, please allow us to be able to cope with and resolve, in their stead, the sins of Israel which did not recognize Jesus who came. Please allow us to be able to take responsibility for the mistake of Israel which caused Jesus such sorrow and to repent in its stead. Jesus had a life of more than 30 years of sorrow.
\n\nFurthermore, there were the three years of his public life, but who knew his heart and who knew his situation? There was not even one person. And more than that, the disciples who attended him as their master, who shared his joys and sorrows, who were sad together when he was sad, and were lonely together when he was lonely, they did not know, either.
\n\nThe disciples, who should have clung to heaven and appealed with earnest hearts, concerned that their master might go the path of death, were instead in such a state that they were asking who Jesus was. Therefore, if it is the case that there was sorrow in the heart of Jesus who felt that his three years of devoted work were in vain, where could there be sorrow greater than his, and if he felt pain, where could there be pain greater than his?
\n\nThere are Christians who know how to adore and attend the Jesus who wielded power, but there are no Christians who seek to hold onto and live the footsteps of Jesus who was stepped upon and driven out. Father, we cannot help but appeal with bitter tears that among the people of the world many sons and daughters who are able to come forward will do so, holding on to the heart of Jesus who was so miserable.
\n\nOh Father who lives controlling the background of history! We know that you quietly teach us the way to go. Oh Father, please do not allow us to become people who long for the Jesus of the past; we earnestly hope and pray that you will allow us to become able to struggle in order to testify to the Jesus of this age.
\n\nNow please let us be able to sympathize with the heart of Jesus, who should have gone before you, and bow our heads before that heart, and if there is something that Jesus wanted and which would make him happy, please allow us to become able to realize it for him. We earnestly hope and desire that you will guide us to become sons and daughters who are able to be filled with and form a relationship with the heart of Jesus who should have resolved the problems of life of humankind two thousand years ago.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 19, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_16t">
We know that your sorrowful tears remain on this earth where you lament wondering where Israel has gone which used to live within your realm of blessing, and boasted of being the chosen people and boasted of its authority as a chosen people.
\n\nIn spite of the fact that while enduring historical loneliness, you went forward holding on to the chosen people of Israel throughout 4,000 years of history in order to send the one Messiah, they left the Messiah behind and were embraced in the bosom of Satan. We have come to know the truth that because of that, the sorrow you felt as you watched was not a loneliness of that time alone, but it has remained as a historical loneliness for billions of years.
\n\nWhen we reflect on the fact that at that time the chosen people of Israel did not know this kind of fact, today we cannot help but be sorrowful that it is our responsibility to have to reveal the nature of the historical sin as we bow down our bodies and compose our minds, and repent in their stead for that historical sin.
\n\nToday we know the fact, which has been hidden in the shadows of historical sorrow, that Jesus came with the lonely heart of heaven to the people who were collapsing and overthrown and dying, and taking compassion upon them he came to them without holding back even his own life. But the people of Israel, who called themselves the chosen people, did as they pleased to the messiah who was sent by heaven and to John the Baptist who was prepared by heaven.
\n\nPlease allow your sons and daughters who are gathered here today to know that it was not because the people of Israel at that time were less than us, that they betrayed heaven, and it was not because their desire to live for the sake heaven was not as great as ours, that they forgot heaven.
\n\nPlease allow us to realize that they were lacking in hope about the new age, and they had a concept about the new messiah, and they thought that the new Lord to come would be very great, but because the messiah who appeared in reality was too haggard, and pitiful and unimpressively small, they rejected him.
\n\nPlease allow us to consider what kind of position we are in now, and today we commonly speak ill of the historical people of Israel, and like to criticize the situation at that time, but please let us know that there is no difference between the situation today and the situation at that time.
\n\nPlease allow us to have minds that admit that if we had been alive at that time, we would have been the same as them, and if we had been alive at that time, we would have been in the same position as they were. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to realize that we are people who have within us the traces of that kind of historical sin, and that Satan\'s evil influence is stalking our bodies.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 22, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_17t">
Today the course of our lives is a miserable course, and since the living environment is very complicated, we are living in a state of confusion where we are unable to distinguish between good and evil.
\n\nWe know that heaven struggled in this kind of land in order to pioneer the path of one life, and many prophets came to this earth and died in order to introduce to humankind the aspect of a true person, and a true concept, and the true aspect of the cosmos.
\n\nThe time has come when we must long for his idea which filled his heart which flowed out from the sacred image of Jesus Christ who was able to pray for the blessing of all people even though, among all of the prophets, he came to the earth as the messiah for all people and disappeared worthlessly like a bit of straw on the cross.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will pardon that in spite of this being a time when we should disregard ourselves, we have raised ourselves up and disregarded all the things of creation, and we have established ourselves and disregarded heaven.
\n\nIf we want to move towards true minds and true goodness, please let us realize that we are people who are indebted to heaven and earth, and we are a tribe of sin which has been wounded in an inexpressibly savage-looking way in the course of human history. Now since the only things we need are a mind that is able to search for you and fidelity that is able to search for our original selves, Father, please allow us to have them.
\n\nWe cannot deny that the course of life Jesus lived was a path of miserable tears, and we know that each and every page of past history continued on as blood-curdling, bloody battles. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will let us know that we are in the position of the stragglers of universal history who are not able to have anything to be proud of in this age, and cannot clarify anything historical when we establish ourselves. Therefore, since a true leader, a leader who has a true life and a true heart, is needed, we believe that the person whom heaven has sent to humankind is the savior and the messiah.
\n\nBut please let us grope and consider on our own whether we have the constancy, fidelity, and heart that are fitting before him in order to go before the person who is the messiah.
\n\nWe know that in relation to receiving the messiah, heaven is anticipating that humankind will offer its greatest fervor, it greatest loyalty, and its greatest sincerity, and we know that heaven is demanding burning hearts and absolute devotion which do not take sides with Satan. Now we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will guide us to become humble young sons and daughters, who, even if we have not reached such a position, will be able to have at least minds that long for such a position, and who hope for the grace of forgiveness on bended knees.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 19, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_18t">
Oh Father!
\nToday, this time is a time that has a historical distance from Jesus. But we know that even though there is a distance in history, there is no distance in the world of heart. Therefore, please do not let us become people who believe in the historical Jesus; please let us become people who are able to know and believe in Jesus directly through our hearts.
\n\nPlease allow our minds and bodies to be filled with awe-filled minds, earnest minds, moved minds which are able to hear the voice of that time which appealed to us, and to bow down our heads before him and feel sorrow through our minds while imagining the anxious majesty of Jesus who spoke.
\n\nPlease let us become people who call you "Father" without even realizing it, and who, without knowing when we do it, thank you while feeling the ecstatic grace of the Lord. Please let us feel sorrow over the ghastly road he went after appearing on the earth, even though the messiah whom you sent was a being whom heaven should have protected and supported, and please let us be concerned over his toil and angry over his anger.
\n\nBy our heartistically taking over today all the things that our ancestors of that time could not do, please let us become people who console and people who comfort Jesus in their stead, and please let us become objects of hope to him.
\n\nHow pitiful a person was Jesus? His mind could not help but lament when he looked at the people, and there was nothing for his heart to do but weep aloud when he looked at the religious bodies. Humankind could not understand his situation of having the responsibility of the providence of heavenly destiny.
\n\nThere was no one who understood his heart as he wandered in the mountains alone at night, putting behind him humankind, with whom he should have communicated his heart, the religious bodies, with which he should have shared his heart, and the people, with whom he should have lived together. Today, please do not allow us to become like the people who follow Jesus without knowing him, and who believe in Jesus without knowing him. Earnestly hoping that you will allow us to become people who cling to his pitiful heart, who are able to weep endlessly for it, who are able to be endlessly concerned about him, and who are able not to mind even the place of death for his sake.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 18, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_19t">
Father!
\nPlease let us consider what the situation of Jesus must have been like when he came alone and died 2,000 years ago. In order to save all the people on this earth, even if he would offer his entire self as a sacrifice, and even if he would collapse, he was concerned, and he calmly received those miserable difficulties, and he even enjoyed going to lonely places. Please let us feel sympathy for that loneliness of Jesus.
\n\nWe know that Jesus did not fight in order to realize a personal goal; rather, he fought shouldering the heavenly mission of saving the people of the world who have become sinners and at the same time he shouldered the mission of leading this world which was in the realm of death into the world of heaven, that is, the world of light.
\n\nAt that time, there was not a single joyful thing in Jesus` entire living environment. Everywhere he went there was persecution, and everywhere he went false accusations blocked his way, but he did not grieve. Even when facing a desperate situation, he never despaired.
\n\nWe know the will for which he endured while watching your dispensation for the sake of a world of hope and for the sake of the Kingdom of Heaven of the future.
\n\nEven though the sons and daughters who are gathered here are at a historical distance of 2,000 years, we must become sons and daughters who are able to heartistically communicate with the heart of Jesus of 2,000 years ago, and relate to you from a position of taking the heavenly responsibility of heaven.
\n\nAnd we earnestly hope and desire that you will let us become sons and daughters who cling to your lonely heart, and comfort you in place of all humankind on the earth, and who, appealing to this people and all humankind on the earth, bring them to form their destined relationship with you.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 12, 1960
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_20t">
Father!
\nWe are reflecting on the day of the historical anguish of Jesus, when he, who lived for over 30 years, faced the day of his grief-filled destiny, having the Will of the providence of salvation of the earth in his heart and having heaven in his heart, but without having found a single person who related to him as the Savior, without having found a single family that attended him as the Savior, and without having led a single people who followed him as the Savior.
\n\nJesus had to go the path of the cross at a time he did not want to, and he had to bring his mission to a conclusion when it was not yet time, so he couldn`t say everything he had to say; and without having been able to carry out the heroic decisions and determinations he had set in his heart, he left behind grief, and took it with him when he went; but where is the person who knows his heart?
\n\nOh Father! Today we have not known to the marrow of our bones that anguished tears for all of humankind were brimming in Jesus` eyes as he looked up to heaven, and the worn-out external form he had while facing death was representing all of humankind, and there was no one among the people of that time, either, who knew that the person going through such ghastly suffering was the son of God.
\n\nSince the people who should have known and attended Jesus opposed him instead and acted violently in order to drive him to the way of the cross, how pitiable was Jesus who had come embracing the Will?
\n\nIn spite of their being the people who should have communicated with the heart of heaven and communicated with the heart of Jesus, Jesus had to be concerned for them instead, and while looking at those people, who were in the realm of death, playing in the hands of the enemy, without knowing the sorrow of Jesus, who was being dragged away by the enemy, Jesus had to pray and say, "Father, forgive them; for they know not what they do." We earnestly hope and pray, Father, that you will let us become able to seek and feel the heart of Jesus who had to do that.
\n\nWhen we have spoken of the cross, we have known it by name only. We did not know that the mount of Golgotha was hell for Jesus, and was the place of the execution of his death. But now when we think of the cross, please let us know that the tearing sorrow of the heart of grief of God which had accumulated over 4,000 years was so much greater than the pain of the tearing of Jesus` body. Please let us become people who are able to know that it was more sorrowful for Jesus to have wrung out his heart than it was to have his flesh ripped and his blood flow on the cross.
\n\nDo you have any true sons and daughters among the group gathered here today? Is there anyone who is hoping to receive the blessings of heaven but ignores the blood Jesus shed? Is there anyone who seeks to relate to the Will of heaven, but steps on the heart of Jesus?
\n\nPlease let us become a group that is able to weep endlessly over the death of Jesus and remember that one day of sorrow which cannot have its grief resolved even though we weep and weep, and weep again.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 21, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_21t">
Father!
\nHow frustrated, grieved, sorrowful, and painful must have been the heart of Jesus Christ who, while looking at the Last Days of Israel, which you had worked hard for 4,000 years to lead, could not speak words of congratulations to that people and could not help but speak words of lamentation.
\n\nFather! We know that the frustration of heaven filled his entire being, the innermost heart of Jesus, as he watched the many people who were struggling on the verge of death, when they did not listen even though he advised them and when the ignorant crowds were not able to be enlightened even though he sought to enlighten them. And we know that the more that frustration filled him, the more his mind wanted to resent this earth. But there was no one on the earth who knew the heart of Christ who suppressed that and endured.
\n\nWe have come to know that it was historical grief that, while attending the holy majesty of Christ who worked so hard, like a brother and like a father, in order to pioneer his lonely course, and while becoming one mind with him, we did not weep together when Jesus Christ was weeping, or starve together when he was starving, and that we were not dressed shabbily together when he was dressed shabbily, or beaten together when he was beaten, or driven out together when he was driven out, who, by finding and entering the foundation of heart now, are able to hold and embrace the internal character of Christ, and who, by becoming heartistic friends able to communicate with his circumstances, are able to rush towards the mount of Calvary in Jesus` stead.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to experience and feel keenly that if we are sons and daughter like that, we are friends of Christ, and people who attend the son of heaven going beyond history. Jesus came to this earth and shed countless tears, but no one knew about that, and with a grieving heart, shedding bitter tears, he appealed to heaven, but there was no one who knew that, either.
\n\nFather, today we thank you for having trained us by driving the Unification believers into pitiful positions.
\n\nWe thank you for having united us in the midst of hunger. Father, please let us become sons and daughters who are concerned about the Will, even if we are dressed shabbily, and who are concerned about you, even if we are beaten.
\n\nWe know that this is your desire, Father, and it is your Will to establish people like that about whom you can boast before this people. Now since the time has come to fulfill the mission of finding and establishing people like that, please do not let us be cowardly while facing this mission, and please do not let us hesitate while facing this mission. Earnestly desiring that you will let us become sons and daughters who are able to leave results before you by giving all the love and sincerity we have, and who are able to be remembered in your heart.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJuly. 17, 1960
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_22t">
At the same time that this morning is the first Sunday we greet in this new year of 1965, it is also the day on which we greet the 1,965th year since the incarnation of the Lord. Many people decided, according to what they thought, and have celebrated the birthday of the messiah, but they did not even know after the messiah came to this earth what kind of destined relationship and value were decided together with humankind, together with the world, and together with the universe, and remembering only his fame, they have celebrated the messiah`s birthday.
\n\nBut the small group of us which has gathered like this today cannot help but sympathize in our hearts with the situation of Jesus who had been sent 2,000 years ago through your mighty, sublime will and sacred administration, but who faced a miserable situation, and we cannot help but feel pain to depths of our bones that at that time the people of Israel did not fulfill their mission.
\n\nWe know that that person who was born as your precious son, was a person sent in order to resolve your sorrow over having lost Adam, who turned his back on the ideal of creation of heaven and earth.
\n\nAs for the messiah, Jesus, whom you sent in order to achieve the desire you had for a world of joy which you wanted to realize through him, the glory you wanted to receive through him, and the Will you wanted to realize through him, from the day he was born, he lived in a wretched environment.
\n\nMany people anticipated the messiah, but they did not know the one who really came as the messiah. When we think that the messiah alone had God`s heart in his heart, and his living situation was such that he had to live with the hope of God and without others knowing him, he appeared as a humble person, was nailed to the cross through pitiful circumstances, shed tears and blood, and died, we cannot help but apologize at this time for our ancestors having been unworthy, and we cannot help but apologize for Judaism which had the responsibility but did not fulfill its mission completely and for Judaism`s sin of having betrayed God.
\n\nPlease let this become a time when we once again deeply seek in our hearts and think and repent for the history of sin which made successive generations of our ancestors shed blood, and for all the sins of the many people who have betrayed God.
\n\nFather! We must consider your loneliness, and we must sympathize with the situation of Jesus who was falsely charged, and we must become people who are able to realize the lonely, miserable situation of his disciples who have gone a course of blood until now Please do not let us forget that today our entire purpose for commemorating the birth of the messiah is in order to comfort as individuals, to comfort as families, as peoples, as nations, and furthermore, to comfort as a world, Jesus who died with sorrow in his heart.
\n\nTwo thousand years of history have gone by. During that time, how many sorrowful situations have there been? We know that you have been sorrowful, Father; Jesus has been sorrowful; the Holy Spirit has been sorrowful; and the Christians have been sorrowful, too. And we know that the final day of the Last Days, that is to say, the Day of Judgment, which is to resolve that kind of sorrowful grief, is near.
\n\nThe believers in these Last Days, who are in the position of having to greet once again the messiah who comes in order to resolve your grief which has piled up over and over again, Father, must not just long for the messiah without having minds capable of being obedient to the messiah who is coming and without preparation like the people of Israel who longed for the messiah; therefore, we earnestly hope that you will let each one of us be aware of these kinds of things.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the holy name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 3, 1965
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_23t">
Father!
\nTwo thousand years ago you chose the people of Israel and you sought to have them experience and feel your heart keenly through their minds and bodies, but we know well that that your Will has still not been accomplished.
\n\nWe know that there were many people who were unfaithful, but there were no people who had the life of heaven as they related to the Will of the providence. Jesus came to this earth and sought to reveal the life of heaven, but since there was no one who followed him, he died alone. But today we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will guide us to become a group that is able to inherit the mission of Jesus and that is able to inherit the will of Jesus by becoming a lamp to all of humankind.
\n\nOh Father! Until now you have endured while watching the social environment of fallen faithlessness and now we thank you that out of concern for the world you have chosen us, and that you have allowed us the grace of being able to stand before heaven more constantly as the world becomes more evil. We cannot help but think about the position of Jesus Christ who could not help but be subjected to sorrow due to the faithlessness of Israel. We know that he spoke representing the sorrow of heaven, and his actions were due to his faith, and were centered on you, Father.
\n\nPlease guide us to attend you with our minds and bodies by connecting with your dream and by restoring through indemnity the sins of humankind now in the Last Days. On this earth there are many people who believe, but just as there were no people who truly followed you among the people of Israel, today Christianity, which must represent the new Israel, is not able to take responsibility for the entirety of the Will of the providence due to not knowing your Will. Oh Father, please let us be able to realize that Will, and by guiding us please allow us to be able to remain eternally after having been called by you.
\n\nWe know that when you chose us, it was not for ourselves alone that you chose us; you chose us for the people and for the world; therefore, please guide us according to your Will.
\n\nEven if we are beaten many times, torn apart, and persecuted, if it is the case that there could be one life such as you anticipate, we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will guide us to become people who are able to endure as long as necessary and to offer you the victory.
\n\nFather: Please let this become a precious time in which we pledge that we will accomplish your Will by connecting our hearts with the heart of heaven now. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that, having allowed the Will of the providence, you will allow us to be able to go forward taking responsibility for your Will with love, and that you will allow us to be able to go forward for the sake of the way of the Will alone by experiencing and feeling keenly the heart of heaven.
\n\nEarnestly hoping that you will allow us to be able to live centered on your will alone by clinging to you whether we live or die, if it is your Will, and by our minds searching for your life, and our bodies searching for the path of your life, we have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nApril 6, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_24t">
Father!
\nWhen we reflect on the path that the Unification movement has walked, we realize that this movement is a movement that no one at all has loved; the nation opposed it, the established churches opposed it, the parents opposed it, and that position of having been opposed by each individual has been just like the position of Jesus who was driven to the way of the cross.
\n\nAs for the 2,000-year course after being driven out and dying on the cross, Jesus has sought individuals, has sought families, has sought tribes, has sought peoples, has sought nations, and has sought the world, but he has sought them on the spiritual level alone. We have come to think that it was the ardent wish of the hope you held to bequeath this spiritual standard and to connect it to a substantial level, and it is the result of the toil you went through for six thousand years.
\n\nThe path that the Unification Church has walked until today was in order to find once again individuals, families, tribes, and churches by inheriting the destined relationship with the grief-filled innermost heart of Jesus and not dying even though we have been driven out substantially by this people.
\n\nWhen we have ideas like this, as for this nation and this people, we have come to realize that they have come to an age where they are able to stand in an even higher position than Judaism by having the same standard among the religious bodies. The group that became one through the gospel of Jesus was in a stronger position than the group centered on Judaism which opposed Jesus. When we think that you have established us in just that kind of position now, we truly want to thank you.
\n\nWe must realize that there remains before us a lifelong mission in which it will not do unless we go beyond the church and go up to the level of the people, and we must clearly realize that no matter what kinds of difficulties we encounter, and no matter what kinds of sacrifices we have to make, it is only if we go beyond this path that there is a way for us to live and to settle down. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to be able to determine once again that we will invest all manner of devotion for this alone, whether we are asleep or awake.
\n\nWhen we think that a day of certain victory is coming in the not too distant future, we must give the love that Jesus could not give, and we must receive the love that Jesus could not receive.
\n\nWe are very grateful for the historical fact that your grief and the grief of Jesus will be resolved through us because this kind of thing is happening in the Unification movement, and please do not allow us to lose this precious opportunity which comes only once in a lifetime.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 25, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_25t">
Father!
\nThe Jewish religious bodies and many priests were people who said that they were establishing the standard of heaven by demonstrating the internal destined relationship of heaven in their lives and attending heaven on their own.
\n\nBut we know the fact that in relation to Jesus Christ, who appeared as the center of life, as the crystallization of life, as the center of love, and as the crystallization of love, they ignored him so coldly, and among the Jewish religious bodies which were spiritually responsible for the nation of Israel, there was not a single person who was on Jesus` side. When we think that that was the result of the 4,000 years of suffering of our indignant Father, we cannot help but face you with tears, Father.
\n\nFather! There was not a single brother who stepped forth to block the history of sorrow and enmity, or cried out putting his life on the line by standing on the side of Jesus, who was filled with grief as he left on his final journey. And when we consider the fact that not even his mother said, "I\'ll go in his place," in relation to Jesus` path of death, we see that Jesus was truly to be pitied.
\n\nWhen we reflect on the fact that Jesus` end was so regrettable and tragic, we want to curse the nation of Israel and Judaism of the past with minds filled with enmity. But Jesus did not curse them; rather, for fear that the realm of Israel, which God had gathered together by working so hard for 4,000 years, would collapse, he had to ask for blessings for them even while he was on the way to death; therefore, we absolutely must come to know the indignant heart of Jesus who had to do that.
\n\nWe must earnestly feel that Jesus, who did not receive any sympathy even while on his way to death, was in the situation of a lonely orphan. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to realize clearly that it is we, it is the Unification movement alone, that remains in this very historical age as the group in the position of having to become the friend of Jesus who was like that, having to become the relative of Jesus who was like that, having to become the religious body of Jesus who was like that and beyond that, of having to become the sisters and the bothers of Jesus who was like that.
\n\nFather! Today, when Christmas comes, many people are praising the fact and spreading the news from person to person that Jesus was the person who was born with the mission of the messiah who had to save all people. But when we come to know the real situation, if we think that Jesus was a person who was born in such a lonely way in the midst of historical sorrow, we must become people who weep, and who are able to comfort and weep over the pitiable nature and feelings of the sorrowful inner heart of Jesus who was like that.
\n\nFather! From the day that we came to know the Will, we knew that it was our responsibility to have to resolve the sorrowful grief of Jesus, and because we knew that we would have to resolve your sorrowful grief, until today we have gone forward fighting and have built up this Unification movement today. When we think of the fact that you can teach and reveal your full, sorrowful story like this, and for the first time in the history of the world there have appeared a destined relationship and a foundation that can listen to it, since we must not forget that this place is really a place that is able to receive your hope, please do not allow us to forget that your heart is hoping to be linked here again.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 3, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_26t">
Father of Love!
\nThank you for having come to us. Today you have come to us in joy, but we are afraid that as you leave tomorrow you won`t be able to promise a day to recite poems of joy when you leave. We have come to know that your complicated course, as you have been dealing with humankind, has been one where you met people in joy but where the days of departure were departures in sorrow.
\n\nPlease allow us to have more longing for you tomorrow than today, and please allow us to be able to long for you even more as we enter our old age than in our youth. In that way please allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to go forward step by step to the profound and sublime world of the heart.
\n\nFurthermore, please allow us to comfort your heart of enmity, to resolve the grief of the enmity of Jesus, and to resolve the grief of the enmity of the historical ancestors, and we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that because of us, the final mission of today, the heavenly resolution of grief, will be accomplished and offered to you.
\n\nToday we have come to know that Jesus came with the heart of a pioneer. Why was his glory turned into pioneering? It was because John the Baptist betrayed him; it was because the religious bodies betrayed him; it was because the people betrayed him; and it was because all the people of the world betrayed him.
\n\nAs long as we know that this is the historical reality left behind in the Christian history of today, please allow internally determined hearts to soar up on the foundation of our minds, like the determined heart of Jesus who started from the preparation period, went through the period of accomplishment, and went up towards the standard of perfection.
\n\nJesus faced enemies on the level of the people and enemies on the level of the nation, but since today we have the responsibility to face enemies beyond the people, on the level of the world, and enemies on the level of the cosmos, that is to say, since we have a responsibility such that it will not do unless we cope with the mission of the final pioneer, please give us ability, Father. Earnestly hoping that you will allow us to become sons and daughters of victorious glory by enthusiastically walking to the end of the path of the world-level Golgotha and by carrying this responsibility by ourselves.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 1, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_27t">
We hope that you will allow us to become children who can make you happy, Father, and who are able to follow your voice which is calling us and run out onto the field of battle, in order to realize the hope you desire, while looking up at heaven and at all the things of creation.
\n\nWe must know your lonely historical grief, and we must know the truth of how anxious and grievous your footsteps have been as you have sought this world. When we think that our bodies must be your footholds as you go, Father, and must be used as the materials to smooth out a level path, we come to know that even though we fall over, struggle, and shed blood because it is a path of thorns, the mission of having to pioneer this path is the true mission and the responsibility that we must fulfill.
\n\nPlease allow us to pave the way this people will go by offering our minds and bodies, and by this people`s being established, please let them be able to pave a straight way on which all people can go towards you, Father. We earnestly hope that you will allow this people to become able to receive this kind of grace of love.
\n\nFather! We have walked a path that others have not known and that others have not welcomed. There were many sad times and there were many lonely times. But because it was the path that you have been going, we welcomed it with tears and grateful hearts, and we know that we have called out to you millions of times with voices reflecting hearts filled with tears, and we know how precious is the fact that together with our voices which called out to you and together with our tears, you also shed tears.
\n\nPlease remember the names of the earnest and admirable Unification workers who did not mind going the way of hard work in order to go that path, because they knew it was that kind of path, and who struggled along the path of asceticism, and who went forth taking as their standard the world-level course of Golgotha in order to greet the day of joy when they could call out to you. Today is there anyone who is tired of being devoted to your Will? We earnestly hope that you will love them again by reaching out with your heart of mercy.
\n\nSince we must now walk again on the path of grief-filled restoration, please consider those footsteps as holy, and please remember how they look. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who are able to be placed by you personally in front of many people by having received your protection and authority, by having a hundred victories for every hundred battles wherever we go, and by establishing a foundation of glory before you, and who are able to have you praise us, saying, he is my son, and she is my daughter.
\n\nEarnestly hoping that only the glory of victory will remain before the Will which you are planning on the remaining path of restoration.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 26, 1965
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_28t">
Father!
\nPlease look with mercy on your children who have gathered here today. All of your children here will have to go and find the nation of the original homeland. Who could have known that this path which leads to the nation of the original homeland was such a difficult path?
\n\nFather! Please allow us to step on this foundation of enmity, on this grief-filled world of lamentations, and by kicking it aside, please let us have an explosion of new minds which are able to fly like missiles to a new stage. Please allow us to have the explosive power and driving force of heart. Since we know that in order to do that, it will not do unless we have your love, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become people like that.
\n\nWe know that it doesn`t matter even if someone blocks and opposes this path. The way we must go is pressing, and because it is pressing we cannot rest even if we want to, and since we know that we are unification children who are facing the destiny we must go and that we must urge ourselves on, please smooth the way in front of us and please let us determine to fight at each peak on the path we are going. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will please not allow there to be anyone who falls down after having gone up.
\n\nPlease remember those who have endured and gone along suppressing their sorrowful breasts along the many courses of history, and please do not allow the light of apprehension, despair, or defeat to shine on their faces. Father, we have had that kind of past, but please allow us to be able to go forward in the midst of the hope of tomorrow with hearts that are bursting, overflowing with hope, and overflowing with joy.
\n\nFather! Please allow us to have hearts that are able to report form a position of not deviating from the ideal world, and please allow us to become victors in our daily lives day by day. Please allow us to become victors in our daily lives year by year.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become the heroes of the establishment of the nation who are able to build the nation of the original homeland which is the foundation of joy which you want to allow to us by letting us become victors in our course of life. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who are able to attend you by having built the kingdom of peace, and who are able to live and die there for thousands and thousands of years.
\n\nPlease allow there to be peace on the days which remain, and please allow your divine protection to be over the joy-filled course of your children. As for their going forward having determined all kinds of loyalty and sacrifice, while earnestly requesting that you will allow your heart of mercy to overflow in the center of their lives always.
\n\nWe have earnestly and humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 10, 1968
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_29t">
Father!
\nWe thought that being your sons was only good, and we have lived forgetting the fact that to the extent that we are your sons, the cross is placed on our shoulders.
\n\nBut now we have come to understand, Father, that our being different from the people of the world is this kind of difference, and we are able to receive your love because of this aspect, and our being able to shoulder the burden of history is because of this, too.
\n\nToday, when we look at the world of Satan, we come to know the truth that in order to search for a second beginning, your love has been accompanying us deeply throughout the course of history and now in this age. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who are able to be grateful for this.
\n\nAs for our going the absolutely necessary course in front of us, which we must go now, we must go the path of the individual Abel, and we must go the course of the family, tribe, people, nation, and world-level Abels. Please let us realize that until we have gone the whole way on this path, we will become busier and busier. Please go together with us along this path we are going while being so busy that we have no time to eat even though we want to, and we have no time to sleep even though we want to.
\n\nWe know the fact that you can look at us and finally take a rest when not only we, but also the Cain world we have saved, return to you, Father. Please allow us to become people who fulfill this kind of responsibility completely, who make efforts and offer all our devotion without any lack, while indemnifying your indignation, Father. Requesting you to please be together with us personally in everything.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nApril 5, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_30t">
Father!
\nHaving written Christian history over thousands of years, you have related to history on the solid foundation of your unchanging innermost heart. We know well that the historical story of your having carried out the providence until now is a story of your having shortened the complicated stages of the sinful elements along that course by having paid indemnity.
\n\nWe have come to fathom that it is the way of your Will that for thousands of years good people have been sacrificed in order to prepare the beginning about which you can say, "This is it," at a starting point that resulted from that shortened history. Along that way, many people shed blood, but we know that there was no person who shed blood while standing in the position you truly wanted. Because that was your grief, Father, in order to resolve that decisive starting point you sent Jesus, but we know that even Jesus died with the sorrow of not having been able to find that starting point centered on the earth and the spirit world.
\n\nThen the history of toil of our Father, who carried out the providence even by having extended history, went forward having fallen down to being a miserable path with the added burden of the cross. We know that then, in order to resolve that in the historical Last Days, once again you prepared this kind of awesome starting point by establishing the Unification Family. But we must know clearly that this starting point definitely is not realized from a reckless position. We must realize that it is accomplished only if we have unchanging content following certain sound, fundamental rules.
\n\nWhen we think about what you will request of us at this point, we come to think that it is not the widening of a foundation of external power; rather, it is the building up of one individual, one family, and one tribe which have been transformed by the Principle on a solid foundation. We must realize the truth that, that movement is more precious than anything else.
\n\nWhen we think of things like this, if we reflect once again on how important we have considered a view of life that is in accord with the Principle up until now, we cannot help but realize that we are people who have been disloyal to you, Father. When we think that until now we have gone forward from a position of each of us going our own ways, leaving the Principle as the Principle and our daily lives as our daily lives, please allow each one of us to admit once again that we have not been loyal or filial to you, our Father, who has worked so hard for each of us.
\n\nPlease pardon the sorrow of the past when we could not have sovereignty where we could become one with you from a position of the Principle and our daily lives having become one. And furthermore, please demolish our selves which are facing such a present situation. Then we earnestly hope and desire that you will once again let us realize that it will not do unless we become people who have principled characters, who are confident that you can dwell at a starting point, at the same time that we can represent you eternally.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nApril 26, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_31t">
Beloved Father!
\nWe have realized that you are seeking princes and princesses of victory who praise the glory of the victory of tomorrow while enthusiastically seeking the world of the springtime culture in their hearts, having the substance which is able to go through a destined relationship of all four seasons with our Father who is the eternal subject.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will let us become your children who are able to be aware of how holy our own selves appear who have been called to this holy fate. A person comes and passes away once. However precious life may be, we know that it cannot he compared to the bloom of youth.
\n\nOh Father, when we enter our prime of life, we have burdens to carry, and if we fight and cannot keep up, we know that our descendents, who are the fruit of that, will be miserable. Because of that, we know that only if we live vigorously during our prime of life, and while going through our old age are a family which has in its bosom descendents who are able to greet the new spring and see the new summer season, then later we will be able to overcome without difficulties the winter season which will come to us.
\n\nThe more we understand that three billion people of the world are standing on a line now that determines their final destiny in front of the abyss of hopelessness due to the fall, we come to know that the winter season can be overcome in the world of humankind only if there are princes and princesses of heaven here who are able to represent the spring of tomorrow and who are able to represent the summer of tomorrow. Judging from this we come to know the fact that God`s providence accomplishes its decisive beginning which is able to have victory over the realm of death by connecting the destined relationships to other destined relationships from that point.
\n\nOh Father` Please let us kick aside the grief of our ancestors who died leaving behind sorrow, and please let us kick aside the stronghold of the enemy which bore the fruit of enmity with humankind, and please let us be able to have the hope of tomorrow in our breasts.
\n\nHaving passed through springtime and summertime, we are the substantial fruits of the autumn season; therefore, we must become people who are not unworthy of inheriting the world of hope of the future. Then we must become sons and daughters who appear as heavenly princes and princesses who do not fear the approaching winter season and who are able to survive as the frame of reference of your victory. Earnestly hoping that you will let this insignificant group of people gathered here become those kinds of sons and daughters.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMay 3, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_32t">
Father!
\nWe long for your voice which gave directions to us. Please let that touching voice which told us to head towards the greatest goodness once again move our minds at this time.
\n\nWe long for the earnest appeal of our broken-hearted father who advised us to go the way of historical misfortune by going over the path of persecution, the path of suffering, the path of difficulties, and the mount of Golgotha, which the Lord left behind. Father: Please have mercy on us since we are bowing down our heads before the awesome grace of your having told us to resemble the internal character of our extraordinarily sublime Lord, after having gathered us together, your children who have grown up as we wished, have lived as we wished, and are as we wish.
\n\nWe offer our thanks to you, our Father, who has called and gathered us, and has given the immeasurable grace of the blessing to us, your children, who are filled with sin, and who, even though we analyze our original natures or characters, have nothing to offer to you. Please let us experience and feel keenly and verify the broken-hearted situation and heart of our Father who earnestly asks only for faith and heart alone.
\n\nFather! We do not want to listen to the words of a person. We have already heard many words and seen many people. We have related to many people, and we have visited places that were inspiring, but they have all passed by without having formed relationships with us. The inspiration passed by as inspiration; the people passed by as people; and we who are left are like historical orphans who are all alone. Because of that, we are hoping that a new spring breeze will come. How much you must be longing to be able to allow grace like that, Father! Please let us become people who gather before your holy majesty with thirsting and eager minds and hearts which report truthfully. Father, we earnestly hope for and desire this.
\n\nWhat shall we say? Before speaking, please let us experience and feel keenly a deep inspiration which moves our minds without our even knowing it, and please let us be able to weep aloud and shed tears, and have our minds become overcome with grief without our knowing it. We know that such a state of mind does not occur unless heaven causes it, and we know that one experience is more valuable than millions of words.
\n\nSince we unworthy people have come before you, Father, please let us go back to having the minds of children. The people who say they have learned and know, how much do they really know, and those who say themselves that they have something to be proud of, how much do they have which they can put forward in heaven? We know that they have nothing.
\n\nWe know that more than excuses, the truth, and more than the truth, experiences of the heart are what will he collected after we die, and they are what will remain. Therefore, please personally manifest yourself to us, your children, who must be the central figures of history.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 11, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_33t">
Oh Father!
\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow this to become a time when you can make your appeal go through by building bridges between your mind and each mind and by connecting your heart with each heart, and when we are able to experience your heart and feel it keenly.
\n\nIn the course of history so many saints and sages have come and gone, but they did not know what the circumstances of heaven were, and they did not know what the heart of heaven was like.
\n\nPlease allow us to know that the closer the Last Days come, the problems that have to be discussed and solved are the circumstances of heaven and the heart of heaven.
\n\nPlease allow this to become a time when we how down deeply to you, Father, and when we can determine ourselves to go forth with joyful minds even if we sacrifice everything in order to solve these problems. Please let us realize once again that it will not do unless we become sacrifices. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow this to become a time when we hope for your power, Father.
\n\nWe know that even if heaven has prepared everything, it will not do unless we ourselves have a foundation of preparation in our minds and bodies that corresponds to that preparation. Please do not allow us to let anything remain of what has been in our minds up until now, and please allow us to be able to return to the hearts of children, and once again form our destined relationship with heaven through the touch of your gentle heart.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will let this become a time when we are able to harmonize with heaven by being immersed in the grace commanded by you, Father, and when you personally discuss with us, and you can establish a new covenant with us.
\n\nPlease allow this to become a time when through the words of the new covenant we are able to once again determine and pledge ourselves to you, and while earnestly hoping that you will allow this to become a time when we can establish a purified standard before you while repenting for everything of the past.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 11, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_faith_34t">
Beloved Father!
\nOur minds have all sorts of forms and figures, but please let your character appear in our daily lives, and please allow us to become beings of righteousness who are able to move when you move, and who are able to be still when you are still.
\n\nSince you know, Father, that we, who are weak, are kneeling down before you, and are going towards the heavenly castle, even if our bodies are blocking the mercy of our eternal Father by being trapped in secularity, please allow your external form to appear through our minds and bodies by our bodies` subjugating everything that is secular Please act, Father, to let us be able to feel through our minds and to sense through our bodies that the Will of that kind of providence, and the grace of the providence, and the love the providence are connected with us.
\n\nWe feel that today also our minds are running towards absolute goodness, but our bodies are counterattacking our minds continuously in order to obtain secular things. Therefore, Father, please allow our minds and bodies to become one centered on your Will. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will completely remove the footholds through which Satan can work in our minds and bodies, by breaking down the distance between your heart and our hearts.
\n\nUntil today, heaven has sought to embrace and love our bodies which were centered on our minds, but we still have not been able to appear as complete object partners of beauty in the presence of the internal character and external form of the innermost heart of our Father. We know that this causes historical sorrow and lamentation. Since these are minds and bodies which cannot help but kneel down before you, and are minds and bodies that have been stained by sin, and are inadequate minds and bodies which are longing to be filled by your overflowing grace, Father, please, take hold of all of our minds and bodies now.
\n\nPlease let us be able to appear as people who return joy to your internal character and respond to your mind. Now please allow us to be able to kneel down in front of your majesty and return glory to you by having the standard of hope for which you have longed for six thousand years, and we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow this to become a time when we can reveal your internal character to you, so that you will be able to rest.
\n\nWe know the fact that all the ideologies, doctrines, and the rights that people have, all these things will disappear. But we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will let us have in our minds power which comes and explodes anew, and eyes of resurrection through our minds and bodies having entered into the fundamental position which can exist eternally, and please let its cast aside our daily lives centered on ourselves, and please guide us to lead our daily lives centered on the cosmos. We earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to become able to experience and feel keenly your mind as our mind and your heart as our heart.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 9, 1958
    </string>
</resources>