<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">True Parents</string>
    <string name="app_start_name">TF PRAYER</string>

    <string name="advert">Advertising</string>
    <string name="info_text">Hello. I`m Vadym. \n\nThe application is designed only for the prayer list. On the main page there will always be True Parents. The "Prayer List" menu allows you to add, edit and delete items. You can select the item for whom/what you pray for. There is also a chronometer that counts the time. After 3, 7, 12, 21, 40 minutes, a signal will sound with a message that expired according to the time. \n\nThe "Father's Prayer" menu is a collection of prayers that are in translation to russian for the time being. \n\nYou can always unsubscribe to me according to the wishes of the application. If you want, you can express gratitude by transferring the money. \n\nAs for the development of the project, at least it is planned to implement the ability to download the finished list.</string>
    <string name="private_policy"><a href="https://drive.google.com/open?id=1wsbkQ0TLdPWQ9WFKnp6_Yw7wYDpgAWNSxViHhmjoI3Y">Private policy</a></string>
    <string name="coffee_gift">Coffee gift</string>
    <string name="about">About app</string>
    <string name="share_by">Share:</string>
    <string name="share_body">I want to share "TF PRAYER" application.</string>
    <string name="empty_list">Empty list</string>
    <string name="author">Author: Vadym Gryganskiy</string>
    <string name="email">E-mail: vadym.adv@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="explanation">Value of prayer</string>
    <string name="explanation_text">Explanation kido</string>

    // App rater
    <string name="rate">Rate "TF PRAYER"</string>
    <string name="later_rate">Remind me later</string>
    <string name="no_rate">No, thanks</string>
    <string name="to_rate">Take a moment to rate the TF PRAYER app. Thanks for the support!</string>

    // Dialog
    <string name="add_new_person">Add new person</string>
    <string name="add_person">Add person</string>
    <string name="edit_person">Edit person</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="task_cancelled">Task canceled</string>
    <string name="something_wrong">Not write. Check your enter data</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>

    // Timer
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="reset">Restart</string>
    <string name="min_3">It`s been 3 minutes</string>
    <string name="min_7">It`s been 7 minutes</string>
    <string name="min_12">It`s been 12 minutes</string>
    <string name="min_21">It`s been 21 minutes</string>
    <string name="min_40">It`s been 40 minutes</string>

    // drawer navigation
    <string name="home_page">Main</string>
    <string name="tp_photo">True Parents</string>
    <string name="tp_mPhoto">True Parents</string>
    <string name="tp_kido">Prayers of Father</string>
    <string name="tp_mKido">Prayers of True Father</string>
    <string name="mense">Family Pledge</string>
    <string name="kido_list">Prayer list</string>
    <string name="communicate">Contact</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="send">Write to the author</string>
    <string name="donation">Read</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    // TP kido books
    <string name="pr_nadezdy">Prayers of Hope</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy">Prayers of Victory</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca">Prayers of Heart</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty">Prayers of Filial Piety</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya">Prayers of Resurrection</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya">Prayers of Entreaty</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty">Prayers of Determination</string>
    <string name="pr_faith">Prayers of Faith</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty">Prayers of Loyalty and Filial Piety</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration">Prayers of Restoration</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion">Prayers of Devotion</string>
    <string name="pr_unification">Prayers of Unification</string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_1">1. Please reveal the beauty of Your original nature, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_2">2. Please let us return glory to You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_3">3. We bow down respectfully before You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_4">4. Please let us become children who find and return glory to You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_5">5. Please let us return glory to You while shouting out hosanna</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_6">6. Please establish us as our original selves in the original garden</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_7">7. Please let the day come when we have become completely one with You</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_8">8. Please let us become beings of love which go in all four directions</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_9">9. Please let us have the joy of resembling the original external form</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_10">10. Please let us become original people who atone for the sorrows of history</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_11">11. Please let us become beings who sing praises to You eternally Father</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_12">12. Please let us have hearts of hope heading towards You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_13">13. Please let us become fruits of joy who establish a day of rejoicing</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_14">14. Please let us seek and enter into Your world of heart</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_15">15. Please let us become children who open the age of Your glory</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_16">16. Please let us become children who build the original homeland</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_17">17. Please let us long for the original world</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_18">18. Please let us know heaven through our hearts</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_19">19. Please allow us the destined relationship of Father and son through our hearts</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_20">20. Please let us long for heavenly families</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_21">21. Please let us harmonize with You through our minds and bodies</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_22">22. Please let us harmonize and become one through our hearts</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_23">23. Please let our hope and Your hope correspond</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_24">24. Please let the ideal world of creation come quickly</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_25">25. Please let our new determination become the foundation of Your glory</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_26">26. Please let us realize that You created all things to receive joy</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_27">27. Please let us fulfill completely the mission of the victorious lord of dominion</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_28">28. Please let us become children who seek the original homeland</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_29">29. Please let us realize the precious value of families where the love of heaven is putting forth shoots</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_30">30. Father! Where are you dwelling?</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_31">31. We want to become lights of joy before You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_32">32. Please let us long to have the destined relationship of father and son with You</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_33">33. Please let us appear as symbols of You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_34">34. We thank You that we were born in this new historical age</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_35">35. Please let us make a nation of hope</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_36">36. Please let all of our emotions long for things of original nature</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_37">37. Please realize a family that can become the beginning of the kingdom of heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_38">38. Please establish us as Your eternal substantial object partners</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_39">39. Please let us become the unification movement which realizes the ideal world of love</string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_1">1. Please let us become the elite troops of heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_2">2. Please let us follow the example of Jacob`s course and return the glory of victory to You</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_3">3. Please let the glory of Zion come</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_4">4. Let us break down the walls of resentment and become courageous, victorious people who are moving forward</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_5">5. Please let us become harvest workers who have been grafted to the love of heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_6">6. Please let us become heaven`s elite troops who maintain unchanging fidelity</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_7">7. Please let us have victory in this final battle</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_8">8. Please let us become the elite troops of heaven which have victory over satan</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_9">9. Please let us attain the third Israel</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_10">10. Please let us realize the world of true freedom, liberation and unification</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_11">11. Please let us become those who remain with You to the very end, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_12">12. Please let us become brave men of heaven by overcoming all things</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_13">13. Please let us become the elite soldiers of heaven who are strong and of good courage</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_14">14. Please let us bear the final fruit by making an effort and enduring to the end</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_15">15. Please let us bear good fruit</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_16">16. Please let us become brave soldiers of heaven who rush towards Canaan</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_17">17. Please let us push forward bravely for the sake of victory over the world of satan</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_18">18. Please allow us to be those who remain the same on the final battlefield until the end</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_19">19. We have gone forth determined to die</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_20">20. Please allow us to become brave people who advance bravely towards the world</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_21">21. Please Let Us Go Forward With A Clear Sense Of Purpose</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_22">22. Please Let Us Become The Young People Who Are Establishing Your Nation, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_23">23. Please Allow Us To Become The Children Who Offer The Final Victory To You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_24">24. Please Let Us Be The Pioneers Who Establish Your Nation Of Victory</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_25">25. Please Allow Us To Overcome The Trials And To Be Victorious</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_26">26. Please Let Us Go Forward With Brave Courage Like David</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_27">27. Please Let Us Be Strong And Of Good Courage, And Please Let Us Win The Victory</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_28">28. Please Allow Us To Push Through Adversity And Be Victorious</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_29">29. Please Let Us Realize The Completion Of Your Will Through Home Church</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_30">30. Please Allow Us To Be The Young People In The Forefront When Following Your Will</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_31">31. Please Let Us Be Aware Of Being The Elite Troops For Building The Kingdom Of Heaven</string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_1">1. Please allow us to become filial children who comfort You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_2">2. Please allow us to become children who completely fulfill our responsibility</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_3">3. Please allow us to become children who resolve Your heart of enmity, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_4">4. Please let us become heartistic sons and daughters who are strong and of good courage</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_5">5. Please let us fulfill our responsibility completely from a bride-like position</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_6">6. Please let us become true children who represent the cosmos</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_7">7. Please let us become children who are able to comfort You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_8">8. Please let us find the rest that comes from Your love, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_9">9. Please let us become children who respect Your counsel</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_10">10. Please let us move only as Yours</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_11">11. Please let us lead the way in the resolution of historical grief</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_12">12. Please command us through the original heart</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_13">13. Please let this become a path of faith where we attend our sorrowful Father</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_14">14. Please let us search for Your course of suffering</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_15">15. Please let us be able to sing of your liberation</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_16">16. Father! We are in deep awe</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_17">17. Please let us become children who do not leave behind grief</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_18">18. Please let us walk the path of loyalty and filial piety while attending You</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_19">19. Please let us become true sons and daughters who serve You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_20">20. Please let us become true filial children who attend you offering all our devotion</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_21">21. Please let us become true filial children and fulfill our responsibilities</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_22">22. Please let us have the qualification of true sons and daughters</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_23">23. Please let us welcome in the original spring together with You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_24">24. Please let us become children who comprehend through our hearts</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_25">25. Please let us become children who are able to be held in the embrace of Your Heart</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_26">26. Please let us inherit Your path of sacrifice</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_27">27. Please let us become children who are able to say we will go forward for Your sake alone</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_28">28. Please let us be children who do not forget our destined relationship as parent and children</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_29">29. Please let us possess the features of children who are able to represent You</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_30">30. Please let us become children who are able to take over Your great work</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_31">31. Please let us stand as fitting children before You</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_32">32. Please let us become able to testify that we are Your children</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_33">33. Please let us realize the precious value of True Parents and attend them</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_34">34. Please let us comfort the situation of heaven which has suffered unjustly</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_35">35. Please let us become children who are concerned about our parent`s heart first</string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_1">1. Please let us be aware of Your heart</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_2">2. Please allow us to experience Your heart</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_3">3. Please let us bow our heads before Your course of sorrow</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_4">4. Please allow us to become leading figures who inherit the sorrow and suffering of heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_5">5. We want to become true sons and daughters will comfort our Father\'s heart</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_6">6. Please enlighten us about Your heart though Jjesus</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_7">7. Please let us testify to the sorrowful heart of our Father</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_8">8. Please let us feel Your sorrow in place of You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_9">9. Please let Your situation and heart become ours, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_10">10. If the path leads to the heavenly palace, we would follow it even though it be a path of tears</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_11">11. Please let us comfort heaven for its hard work in the course of history</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_12">12. We long to become humble people who understand Your sorrow</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_13">13. Oh, sorrowful Father, please let us comfort you</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_14">14. Please let us be close to the wellspring of Your heart</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_15">15. Please let us communicate with Your lonely heart</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_16">16. Please let us communicate with Your heart</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_17">17. Please let us form our destined relationship of heart with You</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_18">18. Please let us become true sons and daughters who know how to hold on to You and weep</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_19">19. Please let us share Your heart</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_20">20. Please let us be moved by the heart of heaven and shed tears</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_21">21. Oh Father, who has walked through this course of history of lamentations</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_22">22. Please let us fully realize the intricacies of the sorrowful history</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_23">23. Please let us consider how much pain You feel as You sent out Your children</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_24">24. Please let us become Unification church members who comfort our sorrowful Father</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_25">25. Please find the destined relationship of heart and accomplish the completion of restoration</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_26">26. Oh Father, You have carried out the providence from a position of more suffering than I</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_27">27. Please forgive this pitiful group that has gone against You and betrayed Your confidence</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_28">28. Please let us become children who experience Your Heart of love</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_29">29. Everything was because of Your love</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_30">30. Now that it is over, we see thai everything was love</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_31">31. Please relieve the 6,000-year history so interspersed with grief</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_32">32. Please bless this day as the day of the complete resolution of historical grief</string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_1">1. Please make us resemble your external form</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_2">2. Please re-create us</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_3">3. Please allow us to become embodiments of goodness through the word</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_4">4. Please resurrect us as substantiation of Your goodness</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_5">5. Please allow us to become true children of truth, life and love</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_6">6. Please let us become true sons and daughters of the eternal True Parents</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_7">7. Please protect us through your touch of re-creation</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_8">8. Please let us have lives of heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_9">9. Please allow us to clear out the root of evil and go forth on a new path</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_10">10. Please restore us as original human beings</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_11">11. Thank You for letting us come to understand our original value</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_12">12. Please allow us to awaken from our sleep of ignorance, having forgotten our original appearance</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_13">13. Please take dominion over our minds and bodies</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_14">14. Please look at us with compassion and carry out Your work of re-creation</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_15">15. Please let us form relationships with You, trough our new hearts</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_16">16. Please lead us to become the true ancestors of humankind</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_17">17. Please graft us to Your heart of life</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_18">18. Please let us realize that we are beings who have formed relationships above and below, front and back, and right and left</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_19">19. Please allow us to possess the justification of children and the glory of children</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_20">20. Please establish us in a position united with Your standard of heart</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_21">21. We thank You for having chosen us and formed a relationship with us</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_22">22. Please allow us to realize the precious value of being Your children</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_23">23. We offer thanks and praise for Your having chosen us</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_24">24. Please allow us to leave the satanic realm and become one with You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_25">25. Please form a relationship with us through original love</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_26">26. Please cut off the root of sin through the power of the original nature</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_27">27. Please let us cast away the traces of sin caused by the fall</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_28">28. Please allow "me" to become someone who shines in history</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_29">29. Please let us cut off our relationship with the realm of satan and find our original Parents</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_30">30. Please establish a new order of love through the grace of the blessing</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_31">31. Please bless us to become sons and daughters You are able to embrace</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_32">32. Please allow us to become the children You hoped for</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_33">33. Please let us be reborn into a life thai is one with the will</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_34">34. Please take dominion through Your touch of re-creation</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_35">35. Please allow us the authority of sons</string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_1">1. Father! Please bear with our unworthiness</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_2">2. Please allow us to become living sacrifices of goodness alone</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_3">3. Since we will humbly take on everything, please go ahead and act</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_4">4. Please keep us and take dominion over us</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_5">5. Since we have repented for our unworthiness, please assert Your dominion over everything</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_6">6. Please enlighten us in this hour</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_7">7. Please grant us Your love and the grace of Your compassion</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_8">8. Please let us have an universal idea and truth</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_9">9. Father! Please become our center</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_10">10. Please allow Your work of sanctification</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_11">11. Please guide us to be children who fight with satan and are victorious</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_12">12. Please allow us to become one with Your mind</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_13">13. Please allow us to find the true path even in the midst of confusion</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_14">14. Please let us open our hearts and feel Your existence</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_15">15. Father! Please take pity on us</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_16">16. Please seek us reaching out with love</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_17">17. Please allow us to make a new beginning in the midst of this new shock</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_18">18. Father! Please have compassion</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_19">19. Please let us have meek and humble minds</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_20">20. Please allow us to realize that we are in a miserable situation</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_21">21. Please allow us to have a substantial feeling</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_22">22. Please allow us a foundation of security and Your outstretched hand of protection</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_23">23. Please bear with our mistakes of the past</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_24">24. Please allow us to feel deeply ashamed in front of You</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_25">25. Please allow us to become aware of the mistakes of the past</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_26">26. Please allow our minds to long for our original home</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_27">27. We long for You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_28">28. Please allow us to have minds that long for You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_29">29. Please allow us to become children longing for our real Father</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_30">30. Please allow us to go forth with childlike hearts</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_31">31. Please allow us to become those who can be together with goodness forever</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_32">32. Please allow us to consider on our own the situation with which we are faced</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_33">33. Please allow us to realize through experience the existence of our Father who is always near us</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_34">34. Please allow us to walk the path of life together with You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_35">35. Please allow us to live lives of gratitude</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_36">36. Please allow us to become children who cherish the pulse of Your life</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_37">37. Please set on fire our hearts of adoration for You, ether</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_38">38. Please allow us to become new shoots</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_39">39. Please allow us to pursue a true life with a gentle, humble attitude</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_40">40. Please allow us to be those who are able to be sorry even if we have given limitlessly</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_41">41. Please allow our meeting to be centered on heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_42">42. Please let us go the path of living for others</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_43">43. Please let us know the time of our life</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_44">44. Please establish us as children of whom You can be proud</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_45">45. Father! We did not know in time</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_46">46. Please allow us to become true</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_47">47. Please let us realize that on the path of faith our own selves are our enemies</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_48">48. Please allow us to become substantiations of Your hope</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_49">49. Please allow the fallen realm to be overcome by Your heart alone, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_50">50. Please remember your children who are working hard for the restoration of the world</string>

    <string name="pr_reshimosty_1">1. Please let us realize the will centered on heaven alone</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_2">2. We will run forward for the sake of God`s will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_3">3. We will go the way of the will gratefully</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_4">4. Please let us become children who can be entrusted with Your will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_5">5. Please let us become substantial beings who realize the will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_6">6. Please awaken us to our historical destiny of accomplishing Your will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_7">7. No matter what kind of suffering it is, please let us win over all of it</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_8">8. Since we have come to know Your will, please let us act on it</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_9">9. Please let us dash forward constantly towards the will today as well</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_10">10. Please let us go the way of the will of our Father sincerely</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_11">11. Please protect Your children who are fighting for the will in each place</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_12">12. Please let us go all the way on the path we must go</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_13">13. Please let us become a movement that remains by having endured and endured</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_14">14. We thank You that we have come to participate in the way of Your will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_15">15. Even if there is a path of the thorns of suffering, we will go for the sake of the will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_16">16. Please let us become unification church members who realize your will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_17">17. Please let us become children who are able to go directly toward the will alone</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_18">18. Please let us become people who can save the world</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_19">19. Please let us accomplish the realm of the will for the sake of the establishment of the ideal world</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_20">20. Please let us all walk the family-level course of responsibility for the will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_21">21. Please let us fulfill the missions of people who are going the way of the will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_22">22. Please do not let us be inattentive for even a moment while going the way of the will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_23">23. Please let us have humble minds while bowing our heads before You of our own accord</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_24">24. Please let us become victorious sons and daughters who are able to go straight towards the will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_25">25. Please let us live together with the will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_26">26. Please let us be able to cope with the way of Your will on our own</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_27">27. Please let us walk a course of life that corresponds with the will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_28">28. Please let us overcome the suffering way of the will by taking Your example</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_29">29. Please let us walk the way of public righteousness for the sake of humankind</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_30">30. Please let us become a movement that is able to advance altogether towards the way of the will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_31">31. Please let us straighten out and go the way of heaven by offering ourselves completely</string>

</resources>