<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_1t">
Beloved Father!
\nWhen we come to know that the path of destiny which remains before us is in the heart of the mountains, on high steep mountains, we realize that the range of our belief is far too limited. We cannot help but confess to you that we are people who have followed the way of your will too narrow-mindedly, too passively, and too inadequately.
\n\nFather! Please allow us to receive the dominion of our Father who is leading the entire providence of heavenly morality. Father, please grant us your compassion so that we may be able to look upon your external form, and please hold on to us and establish us. We earnestly hope and desire, our Father, that you will allow us to become original substantial beings who are able to distinguish between good and evil naturally as people who are not inadequate to represent the things of creation on this earth.
\n\nOh Father! Please let us now forget the concept of "myself," and please let us remove from our bodies any of Satan\'s authority of ownership. Please let us be restored as unchanging individual beings who relate to all things, and who, in our minds, have God alone, call out to God alone, and are proud of God alone.
\n\nWhen we return glory to you, Father, all the things of creation are in harmony and the millions of saints in heaven are in harmony, and when one shout of gratitude and hallelujah goes up together from heaven and earth, we know that Satan will surrender voluntarily. Therefore, please lead us so that can happen, Father.
\n\nPlease allow the complete nature of your dominion to settle in our bodies. Please allow us to be able to sing hosanna and songs of victory in your presence. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become heroes of testimonies and children of victory who represent heaven in the midst of the harmony of all the things of creation. We have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 27, 1956
    </string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_2t">
Oh Father of creation!
\nYour beauty has been revealed in all of creation, and all of the external forms which You have touched are overflowing with the beauty of your profundity and manifestation.
\n\nPlease allow us to be able to experience and feel keenly through our minds and bodies your broken heart which even today is seeking without rest the beauty of humankind which is the purpose of creation, and please allow us to be able to relate to your love with beauty.
\n\nPlease allow our minds to appear like the original minds of the time when you created us, and please allow our bodies to reveal beauty like the bodies just after creation when they were not stained by sin.
\n\nPlease allow us to stand with minds and bodies of the original nature, completely free of any defects, which can represent your love and heart. And if you, our God, move, we move, too, and if you, our God, are at rest, we are at rest, too. We have come to understand that this is one of the standards you have had as you worked hard going through the history of the providence of restoration until now.
\n\nSince what we must find now are our own minds, and what we must complete are our own bodies, please let us find them and complete them. Then please establish us as beings who are able to bow down representing the original beauty of our Father.
\n\nPlease allow us to be able to offer songs of gratitude and glory to you, Father. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to be able to feel deep in our bones and flesh that this is the purpose of our father who has worked so hard.
\n\nBecause we have inherited the blood lineage of the fall, without our realizing it we have left heaven and lived lives putting importance on ourselves, and we have left behind heavenly morality and acted centered on ourselves. Therefore, contrary, to that, please allow us to be led by the call of our original mind which is able to relate to heavenly morality. And please allow us to find our original selves which heaven prefers by our original minds motivating our bodies.
\n\nAnd we earnestly hope and desire that you will establish us as children who are able to resolve the lamentations of the myriads of people, resolve the lamentations of heaven and earth, bow down before you humbly, Father, and receive your love. We have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 10, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_3t">
On this day you have permitted, we have prostrated ourselves before you in order to bow down respectfully before you. Therefore, please penetrate deep into our spirits and raise up minds that are without flaws.
\n\nPlease allow the respectful bows we are offering at this time to be able to become bows that comfort your lonely heart. And we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow this to become a time in which you are able to command us and give as responsibility for the Will which you are administrating.
\n\nOh Father! We know that it was you who called and gathered us, and you counseled us, and it was also through your works that we acted in the realm of life. Therefore, please allow us the fire of the Holy Spirit which you promised, and please help us not to be inadequate to appear as joy for the whole with each one\'s mind and body in harmony. And we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow the totality of our divine natures which you are requesting to be revealed at this time.
\n\nFather! Please bestow your compassionate love upon us, and please move us through the works of the Holy Spirit to be able to have our entire minds lean towards the glory of heaven. And representing the people and representing humankind, and representing all the things of creation of heaven and earth, we all open the door of the holy of holies and go in seeking to be close to you. And we earnestly hope and desire that you will receive this time of offering respectful bows as the offering of living sacrifices of victory.
\n\nThrough these respectful bows please allow this people to be established close to you, Father. And we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow all humankind to furthermore be removed from the realm of sin and to have the opportunity to be able to come over to the world of the realm of goodness over which you have dominion.
\n\nNow at this time we have put before you our entire minds and bodies, minds that are able to bow before you and minds that prostrate themselves in obedience. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will command us without reservation all the Will that you will promise and will accomplish.
\n\nHoping that you will grant the works of the Trinity to pour down upon all of our heads, we have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 1, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_4t">
Beloved Father!
\nIn that place where tears are exchanged with tears, please let us communicate with the heart and mind of heavenly morality from which we cannot separate ourselves even if we want to. We know that the destined relationship of love which has been hidden in heaven is to appear by connecting the destined relationships of life in that place where the love of heavenly morality communicates. And we also know that it is the law of heavenly morality that this relationship must he linked throughout the earth.
\n\nFather! We also know that the restored garden that you desire is entirely a garden of love, it is a garden of victory, and it is a garden of glory. We also know that in order to establish that kind of garden through our lives of service today, at the same time that we seek again for the lives, love and glory that can give joy to God; it will not do unless we straighten out ourselves as well.
\n\nTherefore, Father, please establish through us the standard of the ideal of restoration which you have had in your heart since the creation. Then with that standard as a foundation please establish your reign of a thousand years, and allow the people on the earth to be able to completely move and receive your innermost heart which will influence us for billions and billions of years unto everlasting eternity by going as far as the realm of your ideal.
\n\nPlease guide us to be able to not leave behind any condition whatsoever about which Satan can accuse us as beings that represent heaven and earth, and to bring to completion the total accomplishment of restoration. Please allow us to become children who are able to offer you the entire glory of your value.
\n\nPlease let us realize that that kind of work will not be brought to completion if we cannot become heroes of victory in relation to our minds, in relation to our life force, in relation to the course of love, and in relation to our lives which people do not know about. Please let us realize that that kind of work will not be brought to completion unless we are victorious in the battle with Satan until the end.
\n\nNow as we go through the course of the entire battle from the beginning, as we stand before you in order to bring your mind into ours and receive it, please lead us to be able to respectfully report words of blessing. And please allow us to be able to represent your will by forming victorious destined relationships. We earnestly hope and desire that the Trinity will cooperate with us and that you will protect us, Father, until we become people who have the qualifications of victorious heroes who have completely restored all the things of creation, and who are able to inherit your glorious unfinished work by facing and fighting Satan and being victorious, and who return everything we have to you as yours.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 3, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_5t">
Father!
\nPlease take dominion over all of your sons and daughters who have gathered here. Please allow your Will of joy to be revealed through our minds and bodies. Through what you manifest, and through your actions, please remove our improper thoughts, our improper ideologies, and our improper concepts. And through us, Father, please allow there to arise in all of us works of inspiration which are able to liquidate at this time all the indignation caused by us, which fills your heavenly castle.
\n\nPlease let works of repentance rise up in our minds. Please strike our bodies with works of power, remove the evil elements, and please allow us to blamelessly reveal good elements alone in the presence of our Father who exists eternally. In that way, we can harmonize with your love, and respond to your goodness though our original character and original nature. At the same time that you see the reality of this kind of beauty and rejoice in it, even the saints in heaven will be in harmony at this time through us, and bless all of us to be able to offer up songs glorifying you.
\n\nWe earnestly hope for and desire this, Father. Oh Father! Today at this time please allow us to engrave on our minds the fact that the mission you have given us was not given for the salvation and liberation of ourselves alone. Please let us realize that the destiny of this people depends on us today. Today through us please allow all the people of the world to be able to establish conditions for appealing to heaven and earth.
\n\nFather! While we are standing on this solemn, serious path of life and death, holding on to heaven with our right hands and striking Satan with our left hands to win the victory, please hold on to us, Father, until we are able to return glory to you while shouting out "Hosanna!" with both hands raised.
\n\nPlease do not allow your lonely sons and daughters to become exhausted in their battle with Satan as they face the Will of this age when the time is not yet full. Oh Father, who has protected us until now, we are still able to hope for your grace which protects us from this time on as well. Therefore, please allow us to be more than equal to the task of representing your Will in any place whatsoever, and of resolving the indignation that has filled you.
\n\nEven if all of us offer our lives as sacrifices, please allow us to he able to bow respectfully with gratitude before heaven and embrace your indignant heart. We earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to become people who are able to accomplish the «ill of heaven quickly, leaving nothing out, and that we will become beings of beauty in whom you delight and who return glory to you while shouting "Hosanna."
\n\nEarnestly hoping that at this time you will cause only your Will of joy to act, we have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 2, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_6t">
Beloved Father!
\nIn the garden of our minds, please allow your joy to be planted! Please allow your life to be planted; please allow your love to be planted; and please allow your glory to be planted!
\n\nPlease allow your joy, life, love and glory to become the foundation of our eternal minds, and please allow us to trample down and stand victorious over all the unhappiness of the earth. Please allow us to trample down and stand victorious over this world of darkness, and please allow us to trample down and stand victorious over this world with its terrible divisions and strife.
\n\nSince we must become sons and daughters who are able to trample down and stand victorious over sighs, interference and weeping and we must become people who are able to spread joy to many people, please guide us even though we are inadequate.
\n\nFather! We know that today we ourselves must stand before you as true children, and we must not enjoy happiness from an evil position, or enjoy happiness centered on ourselves. Furthermore, we know that the life Christ lived when he carne to the earth was not a life centered on himself. Therefore, Father, before ourselves being happy, please let us first make our brethren happy; and before enjoying something ourselves, please let us be able to let our brethren enjoy it.
\n\nPlease let us have minds that are able to walk the cosmic course of life and go beyond ourselves. Please allow us to be able to love each other and to relate as true brothers and sisters through goodness alone while taking the example of Christ's course of life. Please allow us to be able to have God's joy, life, love and glory as our own, and we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will establish us as one center from which we cannot leave even if we wanted to, centered on the destined relationship of true brothers and sisters.
\n\nWe know that if there is a person who truly loves others, the original garden will reveal eternal value through that person. Therefore, please, please lead us to be able to sing songs of your glory without being ashamed by having become the sons and daughters of heaven you have been hoping for within the realm of your love.
\n\nPlease allow us to be able to bow down respectfully with gratitude before you and your glory, and to reveal our individual values as object partners of beauty to you. And while earnestly hoping and desiring that you will please allow us to become eternal children of victory, we have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 9, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_7t">
Father of love!
\nUntil now we thought only the front existed, but the back does, too; we thought only about today, but tomorrow exists, too; and we thought only about the top, but the bottom exists, too. We have come to realize that at this time.
\n\nAnd we have come to realize that if those things are connected centered on the eternal Will, then even if the right side becomes the left side, and the left side becomes the right side, that is to say, even if the front and back, or right and left switch their positions, they can stand before you, Father. But in addition, we have come to feel that because until now we have not been able to pull out the fundamental root of sin which is in humankind, today in this age the front and back, the right and left, and the top and bottom have each been confused and are not able to have give and take properly.
\n\nOh Father of love! Now please allow a day of joy to come quickly in which the front and back, the right and left, and the top and bottom have become completely one centered on your eternal idea. Now we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to realize that if up until now we have had a mind to establish ourselves and have not had a mind to empty ourselves, we will not be able to avoid your judgment one day. And we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to become your true sons and daughters who are able to sing songs of your glory and who can be proud before you by our having realized indivisible relationships in which the top takes the place of the bottom, and the bottom the top, and the right takes the place of the left, and the left the right.
\n\nFather! We know that today in this age there are many paths nearby that are blocking our ways. Therefore, please allow us to become your sons and daughters who are able to comfort you by realizing the victorious day of the Will, by having gone forward in silence towards heaven and by distinguishing between those paths.
\n\nPlease allow to appear quickly on the earth the day of your joy which will bear the fruit of that one purpose and complete that one purpose, and complete everything about that one purpose for which we have hoped and gone forth. While earnestly hoping and desiring that you will allow us to rejoice as well, moved by your heart which is rejoicing, we have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 1, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_8t">
Father!
\nWe know that our individual selves represent God, represent couples, represent parents, represent children, and represent brothers and sisters in front of humankind who are wandering, searching for truth. And we know that we have an absolutely necessary historical course that through our individual selves we must realize in the universe a place of rest for our minds that can determine this kind of great fundamental position of the individual.
\n\nNow as for each individual, we know that the men are looking for true elder sisters and younger sisters; they are looking for true mothers; and they are looking for true mates. And the women are also looking for true mates. We know that people who are wandering looking for the same idea, people who are in the same position, people who cannot become enemies are the people who must become involved in the idea of creation.
\n\nBut through the fall of humankind, the love of parents was broken, the love of couples was broken, and the love of brothers and sisters was broken. Accordingly, in order for us to go forth and find these things today we must first feel the emotion of love for each other as brothers and sisters. Furthermore, we have now realized the fact that only if, representing the six thousand years of the sorrow of God, we find a mate whom we can love is the principled standard restored which can represent heaven and earth.
\n\nToday we are not just simple beings. Rather, we know that because we are beings who must not lack in any direction and must have natures that go in all four directions, it is a sorrowful thing for us if we do not have brothers and sisters; it is sorrowful if we do not have friends; it is sorrowful if we do not have parents; and it is sorrowful if we do not have children.
\n\nIt is a principle of natural law that people love each other with natures that go in all four directions. Because that is the first standard of life which God allowed us through our eternal original mind, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow your sons and daughters who have gathered here to realize that if we forget that kind of principle in our daily lives, we will become sorrowful.
\n\nNow please let our hearts represent the Holy Spirit and embrace humankind, our minds represent the Son and embrace humankind, and our minds represent God and embrace humankind. Please allow us to be able to embrace them as children of heaven. Please allow us to become people who are able to think of heaven and earth with those kinds of minds.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to receive quickly a day of joy which can be restored as a center before the eternal world of all things, and a day about which we can rejoice even while we are suffering and in sorrow. According to this kind of absolute, ironclad rule, please allow us to be able to realize from our two-dimensional selves, beginning from our bodies, the parents of our bodies, the brothers and sisters of our bodies, and the couples of our bodies; and from our minds, please let us realize the parents of our minds, the brothers and sisters of our minds, and the couples of our minds; and from the eternal world of idea centered on spirit the parents of our spirits, the brothers and sisters of our spirits, and the couples of our spirits, that is to say, the three types of the three kinds of parents, the three kinds of brothers and sisters, and the three kinds of couples.
\n\nNow we must search around for the true parents of our bodies, the true parents of our minds, and the true parents of our spirits; but the parent of our spirit is you, Father; the parent of our mind is the Lord who comes again, and our physical parents are the parents who gave us birth.
\n\nTherefore, please allow us to be able to find our children, brothers and sisters, and mates who are relative to them. We have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 21, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_9t">
Oh Father!
\nPlease have compassion for all the people living on the earth. We know that the day is coming near when we must bring the Will to completion. We know that that day is the day your indignation will be resolved, it is the day of hope of Jesus Christ, and it is the day for which humankind has been earnestly longing.
\n\nWe know that the time has come that it will not do unless, having met the day of glory, we attend you in our minds, and the time has come that it will not do unless we avoid the history of sin before facing the fearful Day of Judgment. Therefore, Father, please now mold our minds once again, and let us have heartistic natures that are able to bring you joy. We earnestly hope and desire that you will please mold our bodies again and let us becomes bodies of the external form that you are able to move.
\n\nThen please allow us to become true sons and daughters who can be claimed as your own, who are able to sing songs of the original hope as the minds and bodies you had created.
\n\nIn the midst of that glory we will become one and at the same time that your happiness will be our happiness, and our happiness will be your happiness, it will also be the happiness of billions of saints in heaven, and through the happiness of all the things of creation a day can appear; and we are earnestly hoping that that day, the day of your hope, the day of your glory, and the day of your joy will appear quickly on the earth.
\n\nIf there are people whose minds fall short, please allow them to dash forward following your original mind, and if there are people who do not have the original human external form created to represent your internal nature, please allow them to expel all the evil elements and subjugate their bodies.
\n\nWe desperately long to be sons and daughters of heaven who are able to harmonize and move with your heart through their minds and bodies when you move, Father. Therefore, oh Father, if our minds are not able to move with your original mind, please remove those minds, and if there are bodies not resembling the original external form, that cannot become bodies of your external form which can move with your heart, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow those bodies to become bodies that are not inadequate to appear as bodies of beauty, that are able to have the original external form through having been subjugated.
\n\nSince we now offer all our minds and bodies, Father, please accept them and take dominion over them, and please remove entirely any elements Satan may take advantage of. Father, please personally command, and please allow us to be able to reveal the glory of goodness and to be able to be transformed.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 11, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_10t">
Father!
\nHumankind must awaken from its deep sleep, from darkness and from the power of total darkness. But people do not know they must awaken. No matter what kind of barriers block our path please let your compassionate concern appear to us so that we may be able to dash towards the new banner of light.
\n\nFather! We know of the historical toil you have gone through for us, your young children. And we know that we are people who cannot help but be sorrowful about ourselves, who have natures of darkness latent within us, just as you have looked at the earth and felt sorrow, today it will not do unless we feel sorrow when looking at ourselves.
\n\nFurthermore, we know in our hearts that there still remains before us the responsibility that we must go beyond ourselves and pay off our debts in relation to all the things of creation which are in sorrow, and that we must comfort the heart of our Father, who is in sorrow. But please pardon our having come to this position today without having been able to cope with this responsibility.
\n\nYou sought to establish a history of joy and substantial beings of joy, but the history of sorrow was taken over by sorrow and substantial beings of sorrow ended up arising from it. Since the resultant substantial beings were beings of resentment and lamentation, how could it not become your sorrow, and how could it not cause complications in your heart?
\n\nWe are in a pitiful situation such that it will not do unless we hope that you will mold us again through acts of reanalyzing and recreating our wretched selves which are like this today. Father, today please take even more pity on us and take us as yours, and please take us as substantial beings who can be remolded by your idea, Father. Please mold our minds and bodies again according to the original laws of creation, so that we may have the beauty of the original nature of heaven as the Will you desire. Heavenly Father, we earnestly hope for and desire this.
\n\nPlease allow us to be able to rejoice over attending you, Father, who created the entire universe, and to be able to sing a song of joy over having found the Lord of the entire universe; to be able to sing hallelujah; and to be able to look at the bright light of the new morning after having broken down the barriers of sorrow and come out of misery. And we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to be able to have the original pride and be able to long for the original nature while relating to everything you created.
\n\nWe know that since people fell even the things of creation have been sorrowful and have lamented and we know that they are hoping to be able to stand in the position of the original things of creation through the touch of true sons and daughters. When we think that we have the mission of having to restore the things of creation to their original position and of comforting you, today we humbly report to you how inadequate we are; and we ask you to please pardon that we are in a situation such that we cannot survive unless we can hope for your help and hard work once again.
\n\nWe know that each one of us has the responsibility that we must resolve your indignation, and we must bring to an end the lamentations that have happened during the last six thousand years by realizing the hope of all the things of creation and your hope at least. Therefore, Father of compassion, Father of love, please do not allow our minds to move a long distance away from you.
\n\nPlease do not allow us to become people who move far away from your internal nature and external form. Because you created us, we know that we have the destined relationship of creation that we are able to communicate with your mind, Father, and that we are able to communicate with your body, too.
\n\nTherefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will establish us once again as beings of original nature, and that you will lead us into the realm of authority of your original power. Father, even though we have even less worth than specks of dust or micro-organisms. And please allow us to become bright lights to this dark world as sons and as daughters who are able to establish the prestige of heaven and be proud before you, Father. And please allow us to become herds of lambs who are able to appear representing the light of the East, and who are able to convey the joy of the new heaven to this dark earth.
\n\nPlease allow us the strength to be able to take on this entire mission and responsibility. We have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 15, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_11t">
Unworthy as we are, we have come before you, Father, who has dominion over our lives and deaths. Therefore, please accept us, and please take us according to your proper Will.
\n\nWe want to sing praises to you while belonging to the realm of life, but our natures of sin which belong to the realm of death are still enslaving us today. Oh Father, who has been carrying out the providence of salvation, in order to guide us into the new realm, please manifest yourself and remove the power of death and allow us the grace of life and resurrection.
\n\nOh eternal Father! Please allow us to move as beings of life that have the value of creation, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow those of us who have bowed down to become people who are able to sing your praises, who are able to praise your extraordinary beauty and who are able to sing of your extraordinary goodness.
\n\nWe know the fact that through the fall of human ancestors the destined relationship of life of heaven and earth was cut off; and through the betrayal of heaven by the archangel who should have sung your praises representing the angelic world, he was not able to fulfill his responsibility of singing your praises. Since you have called us today, through us please resolve your indignation which has built up due to not having had your praises sung. Please discuss with us these internal situations you could not discuss, and please establish us as beings of a destined relationship that is able to connect all people and heaven. Father, we earnestly hope for and desire this.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will lead us to become able to form our destined relationship with you as substantial beings of life who cooperate with you, and who offer all our loyalty to you, our Father, who has been looking forward to sharing the joy of creation with us.
\n\nPlease let us realize today the fact that heaven is looking forward to our standing before you as object partners, who are extremely cooperative today, and the fact that heaven is looking for people who will sing your praises with deeply devoted hearts.
\n\nPlease allow us to become people who are able to stand as beings of endless grace, as beings who sing endless praises, as beings of endless cooperation with you, and as beings who have groped for and found the heart of our Father who established the idea of creation and has worked so hard until now in order to let us have dominion over everything.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 8, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_12t">
Father!
\nWe know well that Jesus came to this earth, and from the day that he knew the truth and the more time passed, his hope went beyond the family, went beyond the people, went beyond the nation, beyond the world, and even went beyond the infinite spiritual world, having to become one with you, Father. He knew that everything from the beginning to the end had to move together with you, and he went a difficult path, a sorrowful path, the path of the cross, without minding them. Father! All the things we see in front of our eyes look beautiful, but please allow us to realize that those things are merely phenomena that are passing by with us.
\n\nWe know that the things of the world that we like, that we believe in, and that we depend on are of no help in the world of our mind or in the eternal world of hope. Oh Father! Please allow us to cast aside all these things, and allow only hope centered on you to become the entirety of our lives; and we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow it to become the totality for our entire lives.
\n\nWe know the fact that we cannot become your sons and daughters if we are not people who go out to the battle and hold on to the fact that living for you and the hope of heading towards you are more precious than anything we have and more precious even than our lives. Please allow us a powerful hope that is able to laugh at even a peak of death and overcome it.
\n\nPlease do not allow that to remain, just as hope alone, but please let our minds, which are burning with the impact of this hope, to be able to become even stronger. And we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become sons and daughters whose minds and bodies are able to dash towards that path. Please let us realize the fact that unless a person has a strong idea of hope that is for you, unless a person has hope that can overcome even the path of death, you cannot believe in him.
\n\nAs for our hope today, we know it is not a hope we shall hold on to for a few years and then give up; rather it is a hope we shall hold on to for eternity. And furthermore, we hope and desire that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who know that without this hope, life is not rewarding.
\n\nOh Father! The more we think of you, the more we earnestly hope that you will allow us to have hearts of hope that long for you, hearts of hope that long for your life, and hearts of hope that long for your love.
\n\nAnd until we are established as sons and daughters who can be blessed together with your promise, please do not allow our earnest minds of hope to be taken away in our daily lives along the course of our lives. Since we know that many satans are attacking us in order to take this away, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to return glory to you, by holding on to the mind of hope you have permitted and by fighting to the end.
\n\nWe earnestly hope that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to return glory to you, by having held on to your hope and by having fought with many satans and won on the final battlefield which remains.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 22, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_13t">
We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will lead our minds and bodies to the position of being able to he recognized as your body and limbs.
\n\nMany people are leaving and heading for the heavenly castle, but when we think about how many true sons and daughters are going while looking towards your heart, we cannot help but stand before you with minds that are worrying.
\n\nYou have been calling us and seeking us for six thousand years. As the Lord of creation, you have called us and sought us personally, but when we think on our own about whether we have come before your knees as appropriate fruits of joy, we realize that it will not do unless we repent once again before you for all of the things we have done in our lives in the past. It will not do unless we also reflect on all our everyday actions. Please pardon that we are in a position where it will not do unless we repent while taking this opportunity today to look with melancholy at the totality of how we will act tomorrow as well.
\n\nThe original people that heaven looked forward to were people of glory, and the people heaven sought were people heaven could be proud of; but today we could not become those kinds of people, and we have not become original true people whom you can call, Father. When we discover that we cannot help but feel grief about our own selves, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to have at least earnest minds which repent that we have no honor before you.
\n\nNow we know that you are longing for true sons and you are longing for true daughters who are able to shed tears looking on this land while holding hands together with you, Father. We know that many people, even though they had held your hand, have gone our and turned their backs on you, and they think they have been forgotten by you. But today we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will let us become sons and daughters who are able to remain and report our situation to you, and hold on to your hand, having offered our lives and commanded our bodies with sincere hearts that are heading towards heaven.
\n\nEven though many people resent heaven, exclude heaven, and stand in a position of betraying heaven, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow at least us to become sons and daughters who seek the day of rejoicing in which you can find joy, and who have unchanging hearts.
\n\nPlease do not let us become people who move through our minds alone. We earnestly hope and desire that you will let us become sons and daughters who are able to reveal your glory by offering our bodies as holy, living sacrifices to you, Father. We have come to know that the original homeland which you have left behind remains only as an ideal. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will now allow us to have your heart in ourselves and to come to know that the responsibility and mission of accomplishing that ideal on the earth in reality still remains.
\n\nYou have gone forth in order to save our unworthy human selves. Now please do not allow any changes in our minds which are praying, as we head towards the one final day of victory, and while earnestly hoping that you will not allow us to stand in the position of children lacking filial piety, we have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 29, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_14t">
Oh Father, who has not cast us aside and who never rests while guiding us through new love! Even if we do not seem appropriate in relation to your Will, and we do not please you, please relate to us with a mind of compassion. Even so, we have earnest minds that are seeking to enter your world of heart and are avoiding the sinister world. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will come into our minds and pardon them, adding your compassion as you look at our minds.
\n\nSince we know that you will not cast away a person who appears and is concerned about your heart, and who has gone forth seeking you with an earnest heart, please allow our minds to dash forward towards your mind, Father, and please allow our bodies to dash forward in order to be held in your embrace. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will please incite our minds and bodies, and that you will let our minds and bodies be filled by a movement that can appear and kick aside the angry, lonely, regrettable history of sin.
\n\nNow our minds long for your internal nature; our bodies want to look upon your external form; our hands want to hold your hand, and we want to hold your body, Father. We know that it is your central hope in relation to humankind that you want to have sons and daughters who are able to sing of your love, to have that kind of true sons and daughters.
\n\nTherefore we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will let this become a time in which at least our minds and bodies are filled with that kind of heart. We know that only if our lonely heart, which rebukes what we have done wrong in the past, and which reproaches how insufficient we are today, explodes from within our innermost heart and calls out to you, only then will you hold on to us, will you look down upon us, and will you embrace us.
\n\nTherefore, Father, please allow us to have that kind of heart. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that by allowing us to be filled with that kind of heart and to recognize how inadequate we are, there will appear in us an earnest mind that is able to offer everything to your majesty.
\n\nEven if we are faced with an environment where we cannot find a place for our body to stay, and our minds which must head towards heaven are wandering in the midst of chaos, we know that you will not cast us aside and you will lead us into your embrace through your touch of grace. Therefore, earnestly hoping that you will raise up minds that are able to bow down and appeal before you, we have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nApril 12, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_15t">
Oh Father, who has endured and fought throughout the long course of history in order to seek the glory of heaven! Please allow the day in which you alone may enjoy the glory of the providence, to appear quickly in heaven and earth. We know well the fact that from the day that our human ancestors made a mistake, the original Will which you established, has been trampled upon ruthlessly by countless satans.
\n\nWe did not know the situation of heaven which was faced with being in a position of having to find a person who could cope with that Will, because the Will, which had to be realized centered on humankind on this earth, had been trampled upon. We know that because there was no person coping with the Will, you have suffered going a course of so much lonely toil, and the history of your inexpressible toil for the sake of conveying the Will which filled your heart toward humankind, is the very providence of salvation up until today.
\n\nOh Father! Now please allow us to become sons and daughters of heaven who are able to offer all our devotion for the sake of finding the path of glory of our Father, and to have in our hearts the Will which is able to bring you joy through the course of history, and through the Will of the providence of salvation which has appeared. We know that your Will is to seek true sons and daughters. Therefore, please now be together with us as true sons and daughters who make you happy, and please let us he able to realize the nation, world and cosmos that are able to attend you. And please let us realize that this is the Will you are hoping for, the nation you are hoping for.
\n\nWe know that it is the greatest hope and joy of our Father who has struggled for six thousand years to have true sons and daughters bring all the things of creation into harmony and sing his praises. And it will not do unless we become sons and daughters of heaven who are able to offer everything and go forth for the sake of establishing that nation.
\n\nFather! Today we know your Will, and we know that we are the sons and daughters you have chosen and established in the center of your Will. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become sons and daughters of heaven who are able to offer our lives and go forth not minding the path of struggle, the path of being unjustly accused, or the path of death today or tomorrow.
\n\nPlease allow this to become a time in which we are able to bow down respectfully to you, Father, and attend you as true children who embrace the true Will. We know that the power of countless satans are invading each place where people gather to accomplish this Will. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will let us establish your age of glory as living beings in your magnanimous embrace, and please remove the forces of darkness which invade and enter into each one of our minds and bodies. We have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nApril 26, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_16t">
We know the fact that your ideal of building the original garden, and embracing the original true children that you were to enjoy through the original heart has still not appeared on this earth.
\n\nPlease pardon that there has never been a time that we human beings sang of heaven with original hearts from the day we were enslaved by death until today. Please pardon our pitiful selves who have not been able to stand in a position of glory and call out to you as original individuals, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will take pity on the fact, Father, that we have not been able to be moved and call you, "My Father," with earnest hearts, with original hearts.
\n\nHumankind, who lost the original garden, fell down to the world of death, has been fighting darkness, has been enslaved in the hands of their enemies, has been lamenting and despairing. But in their consciences in which traces of their original minds remain, they have been longing for the original homeland.
\n\nEven while going through the historical battle, through the touch of heaven which we could feel moment by moment, we went forth looking for the lifeline of heaven. We thank you, Father, for the cooperation you gave. Father, since you know that we, who are extremely young and unworthy, are struggling and becoming exhausted along this course, please reach out to us in compassion once again. Please allow us the power of recreation, and please let us restore our original hearts. We earnestly hope and desire, our Father, that you will hold on to us so that we may go close to you as original people.
\n\nEven if we cut off everything of this world, it will not do unless we go towards the original world which heaven desires. Therefore, please allow us to have earnest minds which are filled with longing for the original homeland, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will push us out, Father, to the point where we will run to the original homeland even if our bodies and legs become tired.
\n\nPlease allow our bodies and minds to become one and to yearn for the heart of heaven. Please build through us the garden of happiness which you can finally enjoy together with us human beings. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become able to push and go forward with minds of love, even if billions of people of this age oppose us.
\n\nSince we are fallen people, at any rate, we know that it will not do unless we find our original selves by going through the course of restoration. And we know that it will not do unless we find the original homeland, we attend our original father, and we build the original world. Today we, who are fallen, have not known your heart of love; we have not known the original homeland; and we have not known our original personalities or our original selves.
\n\nTherefore, oh Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will establish us as people of glory who are worthy of living while attending you by having all the elements which allow us to become beings of original nature once again through your word, through your personality, and through your heart of love. We know that in order to block this kind of work, along this historical course many enemy satans have attacked, starting with our ancestors up until ourselves today, without distinguishing between the age or time.
\n\nHaving gone forth knowing that it is our responsibility to reject and restrain them, we now earnestly hope and desire that you will let us become true sons and daughters of heaven who are able to align ourselves with your heart, arm ourselves with your word, and go forth imposingly to face the enemy.
\n\nNow it will not do unless we find and go to the original homeland ourselves. We know that our families, our society, all the thirty million people living in this land, the many people living spread out on this earth, and even the many spirit people in the spirit world are wandering, looking for the lost original homeland. Therefore, Father, please let us become the people responsible for being able to build the original homeland which communicates with your heart.
\n\nPlease let us become the elite troops of heaven, the workers of heaven who are able to build the original garden by finding true sons and daughters in the enemy world and gathering them together.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 14, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_17t">
Oh Father!
\nWe know that if there were people who had true minds, then there wouldn\'t be anyone who did not long for the original world; and if there were people living who had true bodies, then there wouldn\'t be anyone who did not long for life in the original world.
\n\nAs for the way the original Adam and Eve looked when they could relate directly to you before the fall, heaven appeared, the earth appeared, and after all the things of creation appeared, after Adam and Eve had been created as human beings for the first time, how happy you must have been over how they looked! How precious our ancestors must have appeared since they had been placed in a position of glory where they could relate to you.
\n\nNow please let this time become one in which we are able to admire the original world through our minds. We have come to intensely long for hearts of goodness which are able to make your heart respond, Father, and we have come to intensely long for the look of goodness of the original homeland where we can hold your hand. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become people who are able to long for the ancestors of the original nature.
\n\nIf we know while living on the earth that in the world of heart there are no historical distances, and there are no limits of time and space, even though we are groping around having lost our way and are asleep in the realm of death now, please allow us to long for the way our original ancestor looked who was born through the heart of infinite love, and to long for the way our original selves look.
\n\nPlease allow us to become people who are longing to find our father who created us like that, and to become people who shed tears dispiritedly longing to look like that, and we earnestly hope and desire, my Father, that you will allow our minds and bodies to experience and feel keenly in this moment beauty itself which is able to harmonize together with the atmosphere of that world, the circumstances of that world, all the things of that world, and all things in the universe, even if we look shabby.
\n\nFather! We call out to you, and we have been happy to call out to our Father who has worked so hard along the historical course of the Fall, but we did not know how to even imagine our original father rejoicing in the garden of goodness without the sorrow of the Fall, and there was not even a time when we wandered searching for that father. And in relation to believing in the true savior, we human beings have known only the Jesus who hung on the cross; please pardon the fact that we have not been able to believe in Jesus who could have appeared as the Lord of glory and not gone through the suffering of the cross, and not been persecuted or in pain.
\n\nFather! Today please allow our minds to overflow with longing for the world of harmony where we can live together with our original selves, centered on the original ideal and the original goodness. Our Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will please allow us a place of joy where we can call out to you through our original hearts.
\n\nPlease let us come to understand the innermost heart of Moses who wanted to lead the multitudes of the 600,000 Israelites who were suffering in Egypt, and please allow us to realize the fact that Moses related to the people with a grieving heart. Today the Christians of the world must inherit the blessing of the second Israel which is spread throughout the world.
\n\nWe have the responsibility of announcing that the blessed land of Canaan which they are looking for still remains. Since we know that the responsibility to fulfill this mission belongs to us today, oh Father, please allow the indignation, exasperation, and mortification which remain to penetrate deep into our flesh and bones. We earnestly hope, Father, that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who have the fidelity of heaven and who will finally take vengeance upon your enemies even if our minds and bodies collapse and die a hundred times.
\n\nAs we receive the command you have given and go forth, we have come to realize that the course of the cross remains. Since these are your lonely sons and daughters who have gone forth of their own will on this difficult path, please be a friend of their minds. We know the fact that when you become our center forever and ever, our minds and bodies take your example, and as unchanging central beings we will he able to represent you. Therefore, now please once again personally take our minds and bodies as your own.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 28, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_18t">
We earnestly hope and desire that you will not let us become people who know heaven by having received the word; rather, please let us become people who know heaven through our hearts. Please guide us to not become people who seek to be saved through the word, but rather people who are saved in the presence of our Father through our hearts and can sing songs of life. Then, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become people who are able to first see how much you have worked and suffered, and who are able to bow down our heads and comfort you.
\n\nIf we have a goal in life, please let us pursue that goal of life through our hearts; and if we must have content in our daily lives, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will let the content of our daily lives be your heart alone.
\n\nSince many people have come before you, Father, please let them find on their own, for whom they are staying here, for what they are working, and to what place they are heading. If there were a person who could be recognized by your saying, "You are a person who will stay with my heart forever," we know that there could be no one happier than that person.
\n\nFather! We know that you come to us with eternal life, with an eternal ideal, and with a heart of eternal love; and what you are longing for are sons and daughters who can sing and enjoy being centered on the idea that we are not two but one, with your things being ours, and our things being yours, and you being together with us in our innermost hearts.
\n\nWe too are looking forward to the arrival of a time in which we are able to attend you, and to be proud and rejoice throughout the whole world after having found and offered you all the elements of glory. Since you know all these things, Father, by connecting our minds and bodies, and by moving all the past things of heaven and earth, please transform all of them in the world of heart. And while earnestly hoping and desiring that you will let us be able to decide and determine ourselves in a state of joy and impact which is able to stimulate glory, we have humbly, prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 26, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_19t">
Father!
\nIf we insist on any kind of ideologies centered on ourselves, or any concepts that we feel or are conscious of, please remove all of them.
\n\nWe are facing a destiny of having to be recreated once again, and we have not been able to resolve our grief over needing to be restored. Therefore, we have realized that even if we have something that we can insist about imposingly before heaven, before you, Father, that cannot become any kind of condition or object partner. We know that no matter how we excuse ourselves before heaven and insist on our difficulties, we are sad and pitiful beings who cannot he compared to our Father who has worked unceasingly.
\n\nNow if we have realized that we do not become ourselves by ourselves, and that we are not ourselves, please let us long for the being of the original nature who has let us become ourselves, and please let us be able to penetrate into the mind of the original nature and to bow our heads before that master of the original nature.
\n\nOur minds know that there is an absolute master of the universe. Furthermore, when we realize that this master is restraining all of our actions, please allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to feel in our minds that we are not beings who are facing a destined relationship without any purpose; rather we are beings who are facing a destiny of having to go through the course of a restricted environment according to an absolute purpose.
\n\nNow we have gathered at your knees and are imagining in our minds your glorious throne, but since we do not know where our minds will wander, or in which direction our minds are heading, Father, we hope that you will please guide us in the direction where we as beings of the original nature are able to rejoice together with heaven.
\n\nEven if our faces are ashamed and we are ashamed to look up, please allow this to become a time in which we are able to long for your heart, to look up at you, and to bow down our heads before you. We earnestly hope and desire that this will become a time in which you promise that even if we reach out to you with unworthy hands you will take hold of our hands, Father.
\n\nAll we want is the reality of life of that one promise that we can cling to your heart alone, Father, and that we can live together with you. Since we have bowed down before you hoping that those things will become the targets of glory about which we will be able to boast forever and ever, even if there are inadequate things about us today, please pardon us, Father.
\n\nEarnestly hoping and desiring that you will form with us a destined relationship of father and son which cannot be broken by establishing the hearts you want to establish.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nAugust 9. 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_20t">
Father!
\nWe must become people who are able to realize and weep over the sorrow of our father who was not able to find the sons and daughters he wanted to find on this earth, but please pardon us, for we have been in the pitiful situation of wandering around searching for our own satisfaction.
\n\nJesus, too, looked at his mother and younger brothers who were in this kind of situation, and said, "For whoever does the will of my Father in heaven is my brother, and sister, and mother." We are people who do not have parents of the original nature, who do not have brothers and sisters of the original nature, who do not have children of the original nature, and who have not become couples of the original nature.
\n\nSince what we must hope and long for now are parents of the original nature, brothers and sisters of the original nature, children of the original nature, and couples of the original nature, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who long for parents of the original nature, who long for brothers and sisters of the original nature, who long for children of the original nature, who long for couples of the original nature, and who forget our own prestige and wander looking for them.
\n\nPlease let a movement of people begin in heaven and earth in which they are able to enjoy the lives of heavenly families which attend you directly. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that in heaven and earth you will let a heartistic revolution, a revolution of love arise, which we cannot help but respond to even if we don't want to, and we cannot help but go to, even if we don't want to, as we are transformed by that ideal and enjoy it. Earnestly hoping that you will allow us to take that as our guiding principle of life and to have it become a turning point in our lives.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nSeptember 27, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_21t">
We cannot help but worry whether our natures dare be offered to you, Father, and when we reflect on our own about whether our minds and bodies are such that they can receive the purpose you have allowed, we cannot help but bow our heads with embarrassed minds. Therefore, please take pity on us, Father.
\n\nWho is there who would dare to stand before you, Father, and who is there who has the confidence to be able to stand before you? We know that the farther we go, the more we know there could be no one who does not feel the sorrow of heaven which seems to cut right through us. There has been no one who knew that there are traces of your toil, that you have a heart, and that your awesome internal nature exists which makes us not know what to do with ourselves, and makes us unable to lift up our faces.
\n\nBut you have raised us to be able to know about those kinds of facts, and we thank you for that. To whom is this due? This did not happened because we are so wonderful, and it did not happen because we have everything we should have. Please allow us to know that it happened because our many ancestors, who admired goodness throughout history, formed with heaven a destined relationship which affected us without our even knowing it.
\n\nPlease allow us to know that we of today are not just we ourselves alone. Please take dominion over us so that we will become people who are able to respect that destined relationship and rejoice together in that destined relationship; and please do not let us become people who betray that relationship.
\n\nFather! In what kind of position are our minds? Please let us think on our own about what our bodies are waiting for, why they are moving, and where they want to he placed.
\n\nPlease let us feel through our minds that in the midst of silence, at this time, too, you are urging us to feel the value of life. And please let us know that you are our Father who cannot help but feel sorrow while looking at humankind because of the tragic reality of their struggling to hold on to their lives alone.
\n\nOh Father, who rules the world of our hearts and minds, please come personally, and rule over us all at this time according to the original nature, and take dominion over us according to the true nature. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us new words, and that you will let us stand in a position where we are able to harmonize with you through our minds and bodies, having become people who are in harmony with the words of goodness, and who enjoy relating to goodness, to people of the original nature, and to people of the true nature.
\n\nWhere are there good-looking people, and where are there ugly people? Since we know that we are one through our hearts, please allow us to be able to move and be still and to harmonize and comply with the heart of heaven. And please let your glory alone appear in front of all of our lives, and please act to let the grace of your life penetrate deep into our innermost hearts.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that by moving our minds and hearts, you will allow this to become a time in which new decisions and determinations to resolve the grief of restoration and to pioneer the course of eternal life, explode out of our innermost hearts. At this time please allow the right of life to all the multitudes who are bowing their heads here, and while earnestly requesting that your many sons and daughters who are in heaven will harmonize with us, too, and cooperate in establishing the foundation of victorious glory.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 25, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_22t">
Father!
\nSince we who adore you have gathered together on our unworthy bended knees and we are looking forward to being able to meet you, attend you, and discuss together with you, please do not leave us alone. Oh Father! Please harmonize together with our minds, and please form a destined relationship together with our bodies. Please do not let the flow of your earnest heart remain as yours alone. Please let this become a time in which that flow of life itself which exists is able to penetrate deep into our minds.
\n\nPlease allow us to become people who are able to be submerged in longing for you, and who are able to be held in the embrace of love of our infinite father, while looking up at the majesty of our father who is directing billions of saints. Please let this become a time in which we are able to call out to our father with minds and bodies that bow our heads of our own will, and in which we are able to thank heaven that we are in this warm home of nature.
\n\nFather! We know that before being the father who called us, worried about us, and sought us, along the course of the battle, you are the father who, in the midst of silence from a place deep in your heart, could not help but feel even when you did not want to, and could not help but think, even when you did not want to.
\n\nAnd we know that within our lifetimes, we must absolutely form a destined relationship in which you are able to call us your children, and we are able to call you our father.
\n\nHave we ever discussed something with you even once in private? Has there ever been a day when, intoxicated with your glory and your gentle voice, we didn\'t know whether we were in our bodies or outside of our bodies, and we bowed our heads and bowed down to you? We have come to know that in the course of faith we definitely need to have those kinds of moments. And we have come to know that in order to bless us with those kinds of moments, you have toiled until today.
\n\nTherefore, please allow this to become a time in which our minds and bodies are able to enjoy attending our original father, are able to enjoy attending our father of the original nature, and are able to enjoy attending our father of the true nature. You are not a father who relates to us having set up certain conditions; rather, you are a father who flows together according to the flow of your mind, and who moves together according to the movement of your mind.
\n\nTherefore, we know that the hope and the ideal we must have while living on this earth are only harmonizing with the original feeling, and the original emotion while we have our lives. We have come to know that you are our father, who is working so hard in order to show results while directing everything from a place that cannot be seen; our father, who exists but seems not to be there; our father who has dominion over our minds but seems not to have any relationship with us; our father who governs the infinite world. Since we long to be people of the original nature who are able to harmonize, to be still, and to move with the movement within that governed realm, within that realm of dominion, oh, Father, please do not leave us alone.
\n\nIf there are people with the doors of their hearts closed, please open those doors, and if there are people who are suffering physically or heartistically through being enslaved by shadows of death please take pity on them as well. Father, please do not leave us alone, and if there are no minds that sincerely long for our father who truly exists, please allow us to realize on our own that we are shameful people before you, who are our father who truly exists, who are our father of heaven.
\n\nToday, even though each of our minds is different, even though each of our situations is different, even though each of the environments we are facing, our internal customs, and the concepts, ideologies, and viewpoints we have in our innermost hearts are different, in the world of the original heart, the minds that want to harmonize are the same, and evil people and good people can harmonize there. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will lead us to he able to do that at this time.
\n\nEarnestly hoping and desiring that this will become a time of grace in which we are able to mold ourselves anew through the word, and we are able to attend you, Father, by having found our original hearts through selfless hearts that have confessed everything to you.
\n\nFather, we have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 1, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_23t">
Father!
\nWe know that it is lamentable that our minds have lost the place where they can dwell, and it is lamentable that they have been deprived of their qualification of being able to discuss their value together with the entire world and cosmos.
\n\nWe know that the original human beings had a direction to go, and in an environment of freedom where they had formed a relationship with you, Father, the great Lord of heaven, they should have sung songs of your value, sublimity, and goodness, and they should have enjoyed harmonizing with you through your heart.
\n\nHuman beings are searching around in order to find again the original position they lost, and they are taking great pains today also in order to find again the original value they lost.
\n\nOur hope is to sing eternally together with the Lord in the garden of the purpose where we are able to rejoice by having harmonized our minds and bodies and having linked our hearts. From the day we move our footsteps in the direction of that garden, no matter what kind of difficulties or sorrows we run into, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who will not hesitate until the day we obtain all those things. We earnestly hope and desire at the same time that you will decorate with an unchanging value that is more than adequate to move the entire world of beings in heaven and on earth; at least our hearts, which are sincere in relation to you, are like the pine and bamboo, and are always boiling up.
\n\nIf there is a Lord of creation, we can know even through reasoning that such a being is to be longed for, and we know that: this is your hope also. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who are adequate to win over the dangerous world of sin, the fallen world, and to form a relationship with you on that kind of standard.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord,
\nAmen
\nApril 10, 1960
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_24t">
We know that the time of hope you have longed and longed for is close at hand. Father! Please let your sons and daughters who have gathered here return to having the hearts of little children. We have realized that although human beings know something, it cannot be compared to the things of heaven.
\n\nWe know that only if we have the satisfaction of a moment of being held in your embrace, will we be able to feel joy eternally while transcending the concept of time, and be able to feel gratitude eternally while transcending the concept of time, and be able to sing of happiness eternally. We also know that that kind of world, the ideal world of creation you hoped for, must be realized on this earth.
\n\nToday we are being injured by the complications which arise from society, but since we are looking forward to the world of eternal freedom, happiness, and peace, which is able to transcend time and cover those things, please allow us to have a destined relationship with that kind of world.
\n\nWe know that you are leading us to that kind of world, and we know that we must determine to make all kinds of sacrifices and go forth in order to make that kind of world. Therefore, please let our footsteps go forth for the sake of accomplishing that world. Please guide us so that we will not be unworthy to receive your blessing, and we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will please allow us not to fail to accomplish our moral obligations of having become your children.
\n\nNow we need a lifeboat that can push its way through this environment where waves of death are dashing against us. Please let us ride that lifeboat and be able to sing songs about the glory of salvation, and please let the day come quickly when songs of victory ring throughout heaven and earth.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 19, 1960
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_25t">
When we think that so many complications remain for heaven because of our being descendants of sin, who have not been able to remove the traces of death, we do not qualify to give you assurances, suggestions or pledges as we greet the New Year once again.
\n\nBut because there remains peak after peak of the grief of restoration so that we must pledge and go, and pledge and go again, we feel that it will not do unless we make a new pledge from daybreak before we see the sunlight of the new morning of brightness once again today. Since we pledge that we will fulfill the mission of the pioneer, and the responsibility of men of vision, and the responsibility of people in the vanguard while representing this people and all humankind with new hearts and new minds in this new year, please allow this pledge we have made to move heaven.
\n\nPlease let us become new selves who are able to have the authority of love with the power of heaven, each time we face the forces of darkness. And by establishing the light of this pledge today, please allow all of the 365 days of one year become like this day today.
\n\nPlease let these new decisions and new determinations of this year become the foundation of your glory, and please let us become the helms of the sailboats crossing the rivers of suffering in this world of death. Then as for reaching that blessed land, the garden of hope you desire, we earnestly hope that you will not let us suffer any losses or feel any difficulties.
\n\nSince at daybreak, too, there are family members who are facing this place while embracing your Will and calling your name, please embrace them. Please let the new light of brightness dwell with those people who are greeting the New Year with hearts filled with tears. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow your day to come in which light shines forth and the foundation of your glory is raised up high.
\n\nPlease pardon the sins of the past of this people through the Unification Movement. Considering this people, please forgive the sins of all the people of the world. Considering the people of the world, please pardon the sins of all the sad spirits in heaven and earth. And please forgive the sins of our ancestors who have come and gone from the past until now.
\n\nPlease watch and protect us until we and this people reveal your day of glory as the light of life in all the nations of the world. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will let the day of victory which remains to come to us quickly, and the dangerous conditions of the battle which remains to disappear through the light of life.
\n\nHoping that your glory will fill the cosmos and it will be together with the blessed couples, this people and all of humankind, we have prayed in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary I, 1964
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_26t">
Father, who created all the things of heaven and earth for your glory! Please allow us to feel once again that your heart of hope, joy, and love fills all of the things of creation. Please let us become sons and daughters who are able to realize that there is not one single being that your hands have not touched for the sake of that lofty and precious hope. Please do not let us forget that there was that kind of day of joy that you created all the things of creation for your eternal nobility and glory, and all the things of creation carne into being in order to be held in your bosom of grace.
\n\nPlease do not let us forget that there was a foundation of eternal love, a foundation of eternal happiness on which you and all the things of creation, having joined into one, could have lived, and could not have been separated even if you and they had wanted to, by your having established the source of eternal life and the authority of eternal life.
\n\nHaving all things filled with the hope you anticipated, the glory you hoped for, and the love you looked forward to eagerly, was your hope and the purpose of creation, but who could have even imagined that that hope would bear fruit of sorrow and despair? Who could have known that you who should receive glory would be in the regrettable situation of being ridiculed by your enemies?
\n\nWho could have known that, in spite of having to reveal the glory of victory and praise the glory of heaven and praise the glory of earth in front of your infinite love, with tears of sorrow we would shed blood and our flesh would he ripped, for the sake of the historical course of the restoration of grief? In this way today, there is no place on this earth for the world of hope to go, and in heaven and earth this kind of foundation has disappeared without remaining anywhere, and it has become filled with sorrow. When we come to know that, we, who imagine your mind today and who are feeling your heart, cannot help but be bitter about the past days, and we cannot help but sneer at the miserable history of humankind.
\n\nPlease let us realize how regrettable a fact it is that we are in this kind of position. In spite of the fact that this is the universe you wanted to embrace and these are the children you wanted to love, today the things of creation all over this earth have become symbols of sorrow, and the people are descendants who have betrayed your love, and are descendants who have trampled upon your foundation of heart. When we come to know this kind of fact, please let all of your young children who have gathered here at this time, feel in our minds how precious a thing is each one's responsibility of having to comfort your sorrow, and please let us be able to pledge that we will become beings who are able to comfort your sorrow and repent for all the sins of the past on bended knees.
\n\nWhile earnestly requesting that you will allow this heaven and earth to become a happy one where we can live with and attend our original father, we have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 15, 1964
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_27t">
Father!
\nWe know that you and our ancestors have toiled in order to go against the current of the course of truth which had become false while going through the long course of history.
\n\nWe know that the long course of history includes the labor of our ancestors for the sake of establishing a standard for the character which had become false. Accordingly, we cannot help but thank you, Father, for having directed our many ancestors up until now towards the true truth, towards the true character, and towards the world of the true heart. Father! We must spread the words of the truth of heaven in this land where truth has run dry, and we must establish many destined relationships in this land with true children of heaven.
\n\nThrough your beloved children, we have come to the stage of forming new families, new tribes, new peoples, and new nations. And we know, oh Father, that centered on the true kinship formed by the destined relationship through your heart, it will not do unless there occurs a new beginning of the people or a great move of the people which will be a new part of world history. Therefore, please be together with us.
\n\nNow in these Last Days, in this world, please let us be able to subjugate the historical enemy Satan through the true words of truth, true character and true hearts, and through this standard, please let us be able to purify the evils of society. Please allow us the grace of being able to represent the overall authority of heaven, and we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will add to us the strength and power to be able to establish the authority of the victorious Lord of dominion.
\n\nWe know clearly that you will, without fail, hand over and bequeath the entire universe to your beloved children. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will not let us become exhausted in that process, and you will let us be people who endure and remain until we can sing a song of victory to you, our glorious father.
\n\nSince we are now beginning this year, please bless us, Father. We know that there will be many sad things, and we will run into lonely and difficult situations. We earnestly hope that you will lead us to the garden you are hoping for and that you will embrace us with the glory of victory in this year.
\n\nAsking that you will let the rejoicing of the victory you are hoping for and the glory of eternity be with us, we have prayed in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 1, 1966
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_28t">
We must recognize anew and respect of our own accord the fact that we exist in order to seek and offer the joy that you desire and the victory that you desire. And through all the beings we must realize an environment that is able to glorify you. Since in order to do that, it will not happen unless we have something of the subject partner nature. Oh Father, please protect each of our minds which feel your love.
\n\nAs we look at the remaining course of restoration, please let us feel that you are anxiously appealing at this time, too, Father, asking who will take responsibility for this course. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who are able to sing songs of victory before you, having carried this responsibility to the end, no matter what sacrifices accompany it on the field of battle.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who can be praised by you, as you stand us up before all of creation and all the people, after we have taken the glory of victory on the battlefield of restoration. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow each one of us to feel that we must not just sit here like this; we must advance along the course of the battle with grim decisiveness and determination, which is able to mobilize heaven and to mobilize the earth.
\n\nPlease let us be able to find the land of our original homeland, and please let us he able to find our original brothers and sisters. And please let us become your sons and daughters who are able to have parents and children of the original nature. Please let us become your sons and daughters who are able to realize for you the purpose of joy which you hoped to govern through love.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the true Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMay 28, 1967
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_29t">
Father!
\nWe started out with bare hands, but now we are in a position where we envy nothing. We do not need money; we do not need power, either; and we do not need any kind of worldly culture. More than those things, what we need and are thirsting for are the love of God, the love of parents, the love of couples and the love of children. We are seeking after families centered on our Heavenly Father in the original homeland that we have longed for and about which heaven and earth can rejoice.
\n\nFather, in this whole world, could there be anything with more value than this kind of family? Even if there were a mountain of precious treasures such as gold, what could be more valuable than the destined relationship of a family centered on the parents love, the destined relationship of brothers and sisters centered on the parents?
\n\nSince we know that this is what you have been seeking, Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to clearly know that we are Unificationists in order to become leaders who are able to connect our motives in order to be able to build history, having enjoyed ourselves here and determined ourselves here in order to leave behind infinite value.
\n\nFather! In the long course of history, sorrowful tears have been shed. We know that in every circumstance where men and women have met, sorrowful situations grazed them, and the critical paths of history evoked the lamentations of heaven. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that today you will allow us to become a beachhead like iron and stone which is able to defend against the enemy and resolve your grief, by men and women becoming true couples and establishing families.
\n\nFrom that kind of position we must find ourselves, find families, find tribes, find peoples, find nations, and run towards the world of which we are newly aware. Therefore, please do not allow us to be lacking.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 8, 1968
    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_30t">

    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_31t">

    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_32t">

    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_33t">

    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_34t">

    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_35t">

    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_36t">

    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_37t">

    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_38t">

    </string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_39t">

    </string>
</resources>