<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_1t">
Today even if we see something evil, we don\'t sense anything, and today with hearts that are unrighteous and incomplete and frozen by suffering while facing the will of heavenly fortune, we are unable to feel our responsibility. We have been people who have not experienced heartbreak penetrated by sorrow and have not had minds to cast aside the enemy; we have been people who have not been able to bring results in battle, or to believe in the Almighty God. We did not know the filial devotion of Jesus Christ in relation to heaven.
\n\nYour will to raise up Jesus Christ and to be proud of him has passed through history through the disciples and connected to us today. Please let us know that you are hoping that your Will shall bear fruit through us. And please allow us to realize that today, in addition to the joy of having received life, we also have a central responsibility which can be welcomed by myriads of saints.
\n\nNow please allow us to become sacrifices to resolve the enmity of heaven and earth, of all things of creation, and of Jesus Christ. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become children with filial hearts who devote ourselves heart and soul.
\n\nFather! Please allow us to realize that today it is each one of us and all of us together who have the responsibility to resolve the grief of heaven, and we are in a situation where it is through ourselves that we must bring to an end the battle to resolve the enmity of heaven. Since we have realized this, please allow us to have minds that seek to accomplish more than anyone else, minds that are able to be grateful to you alone, Father.
\n\nPlease allow us to be grateful even if we are carrying a cross, and please don't allow us to become unmanly fellows in front of you, Father, even if we fight: with billions of satans. Please lead us to become children who can say, "Father, I'm here, so don't worry," even if we are carrying a cross and standing in a difficult position. We earnestly hope that you will allow us to become children who are able to offer comfort to our Father who is in sorrow over seeing his children in difficult situations.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMay 16, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_2t">
Father!
\nSince a rugged path still remains before us, we earnestly hope and desire that you will personally hold us and allow us the strength to be able to remain to the end, even if we go over all the paths of death.
\n\nPlease embrace these foolish children who are only gazing up at you, and please allow us the courage to be able to push forward along this way to realize the will of heaven alone. We earnestly hope and desire that you will help us to be able to go forward as heroes of heaven and as the children of heaven who have been called.
\n\nPlease help us not to be found lacking while fulfilling the mission we are shouldering as believers who have the responsibility of awakening all your sleeping children and guiding them to you. Please help us to become children who walk the proper way responding to your grasp, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will help us not to become children who are the objects of Satan`s derision. Please help us not to be foolish people who calculate heavenly morality centered on ourselves. We earnestly hope and desire that you will help us to become children who can exalt your grace on this earth and reveal your glory alone.
\n\nSince we have the mission to find and bring before you the four billion people of humankind who are sleeping, oh Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will help us become children who are able to exalt your glory and joy, high on the earth by letting flames of life rise up everywhere we go and by bringing about the work of resurrection when we go out confidently with the Word you have given us,
\n\nPlease allow us to believe clearly that it is our responsibility to relieve the lamentations of Christ, who has been appealing to you for our sakes, and to relieve the earnest heart of Christ, who has been working for the sake of the people of this earth for thousands of years until today.
\n\nPlease help us not to become children who drop back onto the earth the mission we have already shouldered, and by establishing us as your children of ability, as your beloved children who can reveal your glory to the end, we earnestly hope and desire that you will help us not to leave behind any unresolved grief.
\n\nFather, please carry out your work and personally embrace your children who are raising up a lonely altar in the midst of a difficult environment and are crying out to and appealing to you. And we earnestly hope that you will allow us to become heaven's children who are able to receive your extraordinary Will and go forth.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMay 23, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_3t">
Father of love!
\nWe have come to know that you lament that there is no person to bring to a conclusion the history of struggle which remains as the enmity of heaven. Humankind must pull out the original root of the fall which was planted because of humankind, but since in spite of passing through a long history, humankind still has not been able to pull out that original root of sin, Father, please allow us to be able to pull it out. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us all to be filled with your heart and to become one with it.
\n\nPlease allow us to resemble your frustrated mind, and please allow us to have once again the hope that you are hoping for. Please allow us to become brave people who appear representing heaven, who are able to fight with the billions of enemy satans and take responsibility for the remaining history of enmity, and please allow us to become brave people who are able to go forth representing the earth.
\n\nOn the remaining field of battle, please allow each of us to be able to take responsibility and to go forth for your Will until we realize the garden of joy where we are able to share with each other the heart of love of our eternal father. We earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to become your dauntless sons and daughters who are able to fight with Satan, each one of us representing your entire Will.
\n\nPlease allow our minds and bodies to experience and feel keenly the grace of your joy, and please carry out your work of re-creation centered on us. And we earnestly hope and pray, beloved Father, that you will allow us to become children who are able to return glory to you and experience and feel your love keenly due to having taken hold of the root of sin and fighting and winning over it.
\n\nNow pouring out the fire of your holy spirit like water which is pouring down, please act to let your chosen children gather into one, and be able to face and fight against this dark world, and we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who go forth and conquer all evil representing your heart of the enmity of 6,000 years.
\n\nNow on the remaining field of battle, please do not allow us to become people who are indebted to you, Father, and please allow us to be able to be equal to the grace of eternal victory. We earnestly ask you to allow us to be able to establish your will and go forth with the hearts of indomitable heroes until the ideal garden is built which can reveal your heart of blessing on the earth.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 7, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_4t">
Beloved Father!
\nPlease let those of us who are here become heartistic sons and daughters who are able to bear the heart-rending appeal shouted out by Abel. And through our senses and through our blood, please let us relieve the heart of Christ which was pierced by enmity over not having been able to say all he had to say to the people when, representing the blood of Abel, he offered himself as a sacrifice of blood on the mount of Golgotha.
\n\nWe thought that the footsteps of the many saints and sages who have come and gone in the course of history were their footsteps alone, but now finally we have realized today that those footsteps are the very footsteps we also must take today. There are many people on earth, but since you have come to us who are so unworthy, please guide us to become sons and daughters who know your situation, oh Father, as you hope we will resolve the grief of 6,000 years for you.
\n\nOn this earth there are many distinguished people, and there are many outstanding people, and there are also many people of ability, but you have come to us, even though we are so inadequate. -We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will guide us to become sons and daughters who are able to experience and feel keenly your forlorn situation as you ask us to understand the situation of heaven.
\n\nJust as long ago Joshua was strong and of good courage, today representing the people, we must be strong and of good courage, and representing the world, we must be strong and of good courage, and representing the earth, we must be strong and of good courage. Therefore, Father, please be with our inadequate selves. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will lead us to be able to indemnify and go beyond all the sufferings of history through our own selves.
\n\nFrom among the Christians of the world, please allow there to appear quickly many people who are strong and of good courage like Joshua and Caleb who said they would have to go into the promised land of Canaan even if they died over and over again. We earnestly hope that you will lead us to be able to quickly greet a day of glory when we can harmonize with you, Father, and feel the throb of your life, the throb of life of resurrection through hearts based on heavenly morality.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 23, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_5t">
Father!
\nPlease bear with our having been disloyal and unfilial people who have not known your heart which is worried about our lonely selves, but rather have appealed to you to resolve our frustrations up until now.
\n\nNow that we have realized how pathetic and frustrated the heart of heaven is, please let us understand that we dare not tell you about our own situations.
\n\nFather! Since that alone is not sufficient, please allow us to be able to resolve your worries and your concerns through our own selves today, and we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who can offer everything we have to you.
\n\nSince today we are attempting to establish valuable conditions for the sake of heaven in the realm of our real daily lives, Father, please be with us.
\n\nIn establishing heavenly conditions with the value of the whole, we have been showing ourselves to be unworthy by not being able to be happy about our sacrifices, but since from now on we will become sons and daughters who have minds that can enjoy it even if we are used for you without limit. Father, please allow that. Since we know that even Satan cannot block our footsteps, we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will help our minds not to change today or tomorrow.
\n\nFather, if we seek to become the brides of Jesus who is the groom, please allow us to realize that we are in a position such that if the groom is worried, we too must be worried, and if the groom fights, we too must fight together, and whether we live or die, we must move together with the groom. Please establish us in the position of brides who experience and feel keenly the joy of the groom who, having finished the course of the battle, sings of your glory in the grace of liberation.
\n\nIn that way everything that has been lost will be found, and we earnestly ask that you will allow a day when we are able to sing praises to your glory with joy to appear quickly in the courses of our lives, in our daily lives, and in our hearts.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 4, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_6t">
Father of love!
\nI had thought that Jesus came to the earth for the sake of finding me alone, but that was not all; I had thought that he came for the sake of my family, but that was not all; and I had thought that he came for the sake of the chosen people of Israel, but that was not all. He also was not a person who came for the sake of any one denomination.
\n\nWe have come to understand that at the same time that Jesus was the hope of the created world, he came representing its entire value. Father, what kinds of minds do we have today in relation to Jesus who had the mission to restore everything like that? Please do not allow any of us to become a person who says, "I will die clinging to my family." Please do not allow any of us to become a person who says, "I will die clinging to my people, my nation, my world." We earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to become people who are able to live risking our lives for the problem of the life and death of the cosmos, that is to say, even if I live, I represent heaven and earth, and even if I die, I die representing heaven and earth.
\n\nToday if there remain the sounds of the shouts of lamentation among the things of creation because the will Jesus had to restore was not accomplished, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become true sons and daughters who are able to give Jesus and you rest by letting us eliminate that, and please let us be able to form an eternal, destined relationship with you and even penetrate into your heart.
\n\nAnd please work together with us, Father, in order to resolve all historical enmity and to be able to receive the comfort of that resolution, and please allow us to be able to go forward together with you. Earnestly hoping that you will allow us to become true filial sons and filial daughters who are able to forget everything and praise heaven.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 23, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_7t">
Father!
\nIf we have life, please do not allow the driving force of that life to limit itself to my one being, and if we have the power of the word, please do not allow the word to remain in our own individual selves.
\n\nAnd furthermore, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become people who can make the power of the word and life go beyond the people and move heaven and earth by swaying the world.
\n\nWe who have gone forth seeking you now did not know that you are not just a father of glory as we had thought; rather, you are going through crises of crucifixion. Today there are many people who are waiting for the Lord of glory, but since there are no people who have a true will to follow the Lord of suffering, Father, please bear with these pitiful human beings.
\n\nFather! Now we are those who must go over the peak of sacrifice, but when we realize that you have struggled indescribably before us in order to find us, we come to feel that we cannot help but go this way whether we want to or not.
\n\nSince we know that today we have the entire mission of having to indemnify all the historical debts that remain, if we are unworthy, please eliminate that, and please allow us to be able to be capable of carrying out the mission given to us.
\n\nFor the sake of this people, and for the sake of the world, and for the sake of heaven and earth, please allow us to be able to establish this people first before you, and we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who can do that and much more.
\n\nWe, who hear the sounds of the screams of sin which are left from the course of the 6,000-year history, know that we are standing in a position of having to break through from now on as new ancestors of goodness by going through the positions of Adam and Eve. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will establish us as heavenly workers who build a new world stepping over all of the present realities.
\n\nUntil now we sought you, our father, who comforted us, and we sought you in order to be comforted, but now please allow us to become people who represent you, the father who is comforting us, and attend the Lord instead. And we are earnestly hoping that you will guide those of us who have sought to be capable of fulfilling this mission so that all our power will be able to remain until that hope in our minds is realized.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of our beloved Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMay 4, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_8t">
Father: Many people do not know the flow of history, but we know that you have been personally directing the Will of the providence.
\n\nToday please allow your sons and daughters who are here in this place to critique on their own the kind of situation they are in now. Is there anyone who is living for the sake of finding rest for his or her body? Is there anyone living only for the sake of finding rest for his or her mind? We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will now allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to find the rest that comes from your love.
\n\nWe have come to realize that this is the inevitable course of restoration humankind must go. Because humankind lost that due to the fall, please allow us to stand up imposingly before human history which has groped to find faith, substantial beings, the Word, and love, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to go forth unblamable with heavenly hearts, heavenly love, and heavenly hope before all the things of creation on this earth.
\n\nFather! Earnestly requesting that you will eternally embrace our minds and bodies with eternal life.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 14, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_9t">
We know that it was you who blessed this chosen group and it is you who will make them succeed. We know that the origin of our mind is goodness, and that we move through goodness, and we know that the purpose of goodness, the historical purpose, and the providential purpose all become one centered on you, Father.
\n\nAccordingly, please allow the ideological apex which we are longing for to bear fruit through spirits of goodness, and we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow this time to become one when we establish ourselves as people who go forward steadily in order to become this ideology itself.
\n\nPlease allow us to take a good look at the direction our minds are heading and our bodies are heading. Now please allow our minds to be able to devote their entire energies to longing for you and to admiring goodness. And please allow our bodies to be able to struggle in order to hold on to goodness and to thirstingly, urgently fold our hands and call out to you, Father.
\n\nSince we know that the history of 6,000 years is a history through which we have held on to you and appealed to you, Father, we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow this to become a moment when we are able to reveal ourselves honestly and bow down before you, and report to you truthfully about all our situations, and receive the counsel of your bidding.
\n\nSince it was you who drove us out along the way to which others said no, and it was you who guided us along the way that was so difficult to go, please take responsibility for this way, Father. We have not moved in accordance with any kind of human mind, and we have not been pulled along by any kind of human situation. And since we have come to this point led by the power of the mind and could not help coming whether we wanted to or not, please lead us not to be lazy.
\n\nSince we do not know your words of counsel which urge us on, please give us hour by hour the stimulation of your power to realize your word and to head out in the direction of that word. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will not let any person fall behind on the course going towards you at long last.
\n\nPlease allow us to place everything we have before you now, Father, and please do not allow your altar to be defiled because of us, and we earnestly hope that you will allow this to become a time of our bowing down to make an offering to you with complete sincerity.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 18, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_10t">
Please do not allow us to become people who think that we belong to ourselves. Our minds are not ours, and our lives which are in motion are not ours; and as the desires we are longing for are not ours please do not allow us to relate to heaven with minds that consider things centered on ourselves. Since we began as yours, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow this to become a time when we are able to move only as yours.
\n\nSince we know that our minds must become yours, and our bodies also must become yours, and our ideologies and opinions must become yours, please do not tolerate anything that is not yours. If there are elements of evil which you do not want in our minds and bodies, please eliminate them, and we earnestly hope and desire, oh Father, that you will allow this to become a time which moves as yours alone through your having eliminated all the ideologies and opinions that are not yours.
\n\nWe know that uncountable satans are stalking our minds and our bodies. If the bitter root of sin, which you cannot tolerate, remains, oh Father, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will bring about heavenly acts that will give us the ability to subjugate our minds before you, and that you will appear and bring about heavenly acts of re-creation through the authority of your power.
\n\nWe know the fact that when heaven moves, the earth cannot help but move, and when the earth faces heaven and requests something, heaven cannot help but accomplish it for the earth. Today are there sons and daughters of heaven who are struggling with sincere minds and true hearts in order to grasp heaven as their own? Is there any person who has lived his or her entire life thinking of all of heaven's situations as his or her own situations, thinking of heaven's work as his or her own work, thinking of the ideas of heaven as his or her own ideas, and struggled while seeking to grasp this, been treated contemptuously while seeking to grasp this and been driven out while seeking to grasp this? If we have not been in that kind of position, please allow us to be able to report truthfully that we are criminals who cannot be tolerated by heaven.
\n\nNow we have realized that heaven exists, and we have realized who our heavenly Father is. Since we know that there remains the necessary condition that we must form a certain kind of destined relationship between you and us, Father, today please allow us to form a destined relationship with you, our heavenly Father, through this kind of heart, and to feel your anguish as our anguish, and your deep regret and sorrow as our deep regret and sorrow. Please allow there to appear before this people and please allow there to appear in this land a heavenly march which goes forth to fight a fierce battle against Satan.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to be able to drive out from the earth the enemy satans who have faced heaven and accused it for 6,000 years, in order to resolve your grief and to build as soon as possible the ideal garden you have sought.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 15, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_11t">
You are the father of hosts, you are the Lord of the entire universe, and you were the central figure who had all authority under heaven, but because of the mistake of your son and daughter, you are facing a miserable situation like this. Therefore, please allow us to understand your heart at this time. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will not allow us to become weak like defeated people as we look up at the peak of enmity of the providence which remains.
\n\nOh, Father of compassion! Oh, Father of love! If your promised Will is alive in our hearts, please protect us. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become loving sons and daughters who build up an altar of heart while kneeling down wailing before you.
\n\nWhen we have come before you, Father, we have been able to experience and feel keenly the lonely heart of Jesus who had determined to go forward not caring about all the difficulties. Now since the time has come to speak proudly about the hope that we, who have gone out with determination, are embracing, please let us stand on the side of heaven and lead the way, and please let us leave behind what heaven wants to leave behind.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will help this true group of people be able to comfort you and fight for you, Father, adding our hearts together.
\n\nSince a trend towards the historical turning point has appeared before us today, please let us become a group of people that resolves the grief of history. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to feel we are inadequate in relation to the Will you have established, and are able to represent the heart of Moses who sought to build an altar for you and believe in you even in difficult circumstances.
\n\nWhat we are going through cannot even be compared with your worn, your suffering, and your toil. Please allow us to become people who are able to see the circumstances you went through as you walked the course of unending troubles, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become people who are able to see your majesty as you walked the unending course of suffering.
\n\nPlease let us be able to go beyond all the unjust accusations we are encountering, all the criticism we are receiving, and all the persecution we are encountering today. Please guide us to be able to go forward for you, Father, without getting bogged down, no matter what kind of position we are in. We earnestly hope that you will enlighten us to know deeply about all these things, and please counsel us through your heart which is concerned for us, and earnestly hoping that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who do not mind all these things.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 29, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_12t">
Father!
\nPlease allow our minds and bodies to be permeated by your heart. Please let us become able to feel that we are being pulled into your heart which is permeating our original minds. In our minds and bodies, please allow hearts to blossom that are moved and can go forth running to you who are joyful, and embrace you.
\n\nWe have realized that you appear faintly in the midst of dimness and you do not move until we open our hearts. Even though our minds may have become dirty, since our true hearts are still heading only towards you, Father, please come to us through these hearts, and command us through these hearts. Please allow earnest hearts to well up which can call you "My Father" while shedding tears we do not even perceive, having realized that our past lives were disloyal.
\n\nWe have come to know that heaven does not hesitate to protect anyone, and we have come to understand that heaven does not hesitate to become the friend of those who are seeking heaven, and we have come to know that heaven enjoys appearing as the friend of people who shed tears wailing to heaven, and as the father who will live with us eternally.
\n\nFather! We long for your voice which counseled us quietly and we long for a sense of the amazing love with which you embraced us gently. We long for a moment when we can call you "Father" through our minds which are like that, and we want to raise our hands and exclaim and boast that you are our father.
\n\nWe thought that you were a father who was far, far away, but it was a joyful moment when we found that you are in our hearts. When we said you were far away, you were in our hearts, and when we were confident that you were in our hearts, you were the father who had called to us from afar, but today humanity does not know how to match this heart beat. Please let us repent at this time for ourselves of the past which did not realize that the place where we thought you had abandoned us was the place where you were close to us, and that the place where we thought you were not with us was the place where you were together with us.
\n\nWe did not know your mind which does not want to leave in places of suffering your sons and daughters whom you want to call "my beloved son" and you want to call "my beloved daughter." We, who don't know your complicated heart, thought that you, who sent us out on the path of toil, were a hardhearted and cruel father, and during that time, there were many times we complained to you and there were many times we felt bitter. Since we did not know about the complicated walls that blocked the way between you and us, Father, please bear with the fact that we have felt bitter, have rejected you, have been coldhearted to you, and have not had faith in you.
\n\nWe have come to know that this was because of the aspect of the sin committed by our ancestors due to the fall, and this was because saints and sages died leaving behind stains of the blood of enmity in human history.
\n\nToday is the level of our minds in a high place? Please burn away those minds by fire. Are we waiting impatiently to put ourselves and our authority forward and to appear in your place? We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who, realizing that you are in a miserable position, are able to call you "Father," and are able to smite our shameful breasts in front of your majesty.
\n\nFather! Now as we come to realize that there remain times of suffering which will continue endlessly along the remaining way as well, we cannot help but report our disloyalty of today to you with our heads bowed. It is my desire that you please allow this one being to carry the sorrow of history, and please allow heaven to tread upon and go over all the suffering remaining, having taken this being as a sacrifice.
\n\nI long for the moment when you can rest and cast aside all lamentations, Father, and we can have a moment of joy embracing each other when I can call you my father, and you can call me your son. As long as we are living on this earth, no matter how miserable we are, no matter how resolved we are, or how much we sacrifice, please allow us to become your sons and daughters who are able to establish at least sincere hearts of unbending loyalty on this earth and then disappear.
\n\nSince we have resolved to go that kind of path, Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will drive us out and lead us until we don't mind those things. We earnestly request, Father, that this will become a time when we are able to pledge and determine ourselves with new minds and bodies.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 29, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_13t">
Father, you have rejoiced in revealing yourself in silence, and you have not minded revealing yourself in the midst of difficulties. When we realize again that historically it was you, Father, who fought personally on our side with us on the battlefield and who was together with us at the point of despair, and when we think that it was you, Father, who was always with us, and who always fought on our side with us, and who always longed to live together with us, please let us repent for our course of faith of the past in which we rejoiced in rejecting and excluding the earth even while living on the earth.
\n\nOur Father whom we joyfully attended as being far above the earth was a father of glory, but we have come to know that our Father who appeared on the earth is miserable, and worn out, and lonely. And furthermore, we learned and came to know that you have come to us and related to us in that way through the course of history.
\n\nNow we should not rejoice in and attend our Father who has appeared in glory; rather we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to stand in a position of glory by being able to rejoice in and attend our father who has been wounded on the earth and has been afflicted with difficulties, and who has struggled to find a true son.
\n\nIf we seek to attend you from that kind of position, we know that we will first have to go a path of tears, we will have to walk a path of thorns, and we will have to go beyond the path of the suffering of the cross. We know it is only in that way that we can know the fact that you exist. We cannot help but think that this kind of lonely course of faith is remaining for us.
\n\nHeaven has warned us that now is the time to wake up from sleep. Heaven warned us that it is the time when we should hold up a bright light in this dark night, but are our minds immersed in darkness? Are our bodies bound by the chains of death? Please lead us to cut and cast these aside in order to be able to run towards heaven, to be able to fight in the place of heaven, and to be able to take responsibility in place of heaven. We know that it will not do unless we become sons and daughters who by doing that can call you "Father" and who long for our father to come; therefore, if there are people who are inadequate to stand before the will, Father, at this time please encourage them.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will let us know that the time and the age are at hand, and not let us become people who are judged, or swept away by the shadow of death, and that you will let us become sons and daughters who know how to run forward towards the garden of freedom seeking your bosom and led by the call of life, even if we have the grief of our bodies being ripped apart and even if we face the grief of death.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nApril 19, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_14t">
We know that the place where you dwell, Father, is the world of infinite patience, and it is a place of infinite toil.
\n\nWe, who know your heart and will which dealt with all the sins committed until now since our ancestors, cannot help but bow our heads with ashamed hearts before our father who has walked a path of so much endurance and a path of so much toil in order to find a being of the original creation.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to be able to broaden our minds at this time and bowing down our bodies, attending you in our minds and holding on to you with our bodies, oh Father, who has struggled in order to hold on to humankind, who has gone forward fighting together on the side of our ancestors, and who has endured together with our ancestors, during the long ages as though they were a day.
\n\nWe have come to know that among the many people who are living on the earth, while there are many people who avoid the path of toil, there are extremely few people who seek and go forth on the path of toil knowing your situation in order to have your heart in their minds and bodies. When we come to realize that there are very few people who offer loyalty for your sake, who prepare an altar for you, becoming sacrifices for your sake, or who reveal your enduring heart on the earth, we come to realize that you are terribly miserable,
\n\nFather! We cannot help but feel that you are a father who toils and worries about humankind, and even while loving humankind, you are lamenting.
\n\nOh, my Father! Now please let the day come soon when you can convey what your situation is like to humankind who are living on the earth. We are earnestly looking forward to your situation which is like that, being able to be sunk deep into the hearts of each and every person.
\n\nFather! On this day, on this holy day there are many people who are looking forward to receiving blessings bowing their heads and kneeling down to you, but please let us become people who know that blessings belong to heaven and humankind must take responsibility for the course of toil, suffering and endurance.
\n\nIf we have joy, please let us return it to you as yours, Father, and if we have hearts of happiness and gratitude, please let us return them to you as yours also, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who take charge of your sorrowful course filled with grief and enmity as though it were our own.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMay 24, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_15t">
Father: If we recollect your sorrowful historical course, we cannot suppress our fearful minds, and each time we relate to the majesty of our Father who has toiled so hard, we cannot suppress our awe-stricken minds. Now please establish these people as sons and daughters who are able to stop and take over your toil by offering their minds and bodies as sacrifices.
\n\nYou have eagerly awaited the coming of a day of victory when we can sing of liberation from a position of joy which you are able to enjoy, but it is not you who is to realize that will of liberation; we know the fact that it will not do unless it is done by us, human beings who are so disloyal and struggling in the realm of death.
\n\nPlease bear with humankind who are in an important position like this, but who are languishing along the course of death without knowing their own value as human beings. Please awaken in us earnest minds which are able to sing praises of your heart of glory by holding up a new standard for the restoration of the original heart in ourselves now. Please let us have original internal characters and original external forms, and please let us appear as true sons and daughters and be able to sing of your liberation, Father. We know that you know the fact that this has been our hope for thousands of years.
\n\nFather, we earnestly hope and desire that you will lead those of us who know that there will be a day of victory to a position of the level of victory, and that you will lead us to be able to become sacrifices in front of the great will that you want to give us responsibility for. Father! Please allow us to be living temples binding together our inadequate devotion.
\n\nSince we know the fact that you are notifying us that it will not do unless each of us individually becomes a sacrifice for the victory, please eliminate everything which is not proper to you, and Father, please raise up a new authority of re-creation by reaching out with your almighty hand. Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will have the internal character and you will have the external form of re-creation which is able to eliminate everything which is not yours.
\n\nAnd now, my Father! Please awaken this people which is sleeping, and by taking humankind, who are wandering in dire misery, in your hands, and gathering them together in one place, please lead them into your original garden, into the garden of goodness which is your ideal. No matter what kind of persecution or misfortune humankind must go through, we earnestly hope and desire that you will quickly lead humankind into the midst of the garden you desire.
\n\nFather! Since we know that humankind has a responsibility that must be fulfilled in order to do that, oh Father, please command your beloved sons and daughters. If they have the responsibility to have to go out and find the remaining lands of sin and the remaining people, we earnestly hope and desire that you will please raise them up and command them, and please allow them to be commanded and sent to the place that you desire as ardent laborers, as chosen warriors of heaven who are able to build the garden of victory.
\n\nWe have prayed these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 28, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_16t">
Father!
\nWe are in deep awe. Having gone this path, we have come to understand that it is a magnificent path to go, and the more that we experience it, the more we know that it is a path of sorrow which cannot be stopped no matter how much we smite our breasts.
\n\nOh Father, who sought us not for just a day, and not for several years, but for the long time of 6,000 years! Please let this be a time of realizing just how insane the position was that we put you in, and just how angry a position we let you stay in, and furthermore just how unfilial a position we were in. Please let us realize that we, who wept and cried over the things of this world before forming this destined relationship, are sinners among sinners.
\n\nWhat is the hope of those of us who have come here? We did not come here to find someone wearing good clothes; we did not come to find someone of authority; and we did not come for the sake of some desire. Since we have come merely longing for your love, longing for your affection, and longing for a destined relationship with you, Father, if you have tears, please allow us to have those tears also, and if you have suffering, please allow us to have that suffering, too.
\n\nPlease let us realize that it will not do unless we become princes who indemnify and in your place take responsibility for the history of sorrow and suffering, and we must not become princes who wander searching for a history of joy. We know that you are longing for sons and daughters who are victorious in a position like this, and sons and daughters about whom you can boast before heaven and earth.
\n\nAnd furthermore, we have realized that the goal of God's having toiled for 6,000 years was to establish beloved sons and daughters. We earnestly request and desire that you will allow us to become equal to the duty given us and to be able to fulfill the responsibility given us today. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to become filial sons among filial sons, filial daughters among filial daughters, and loyal subjects among loyal subjects.
\n\nThen, we earnestly request that you, the father of history, may become our father; that you, the father of the present age, may become our father; and that you, the father of the future, may become our father; and that you will protect and embrace these people, Father, until the day of joy comes when we sing songs of joy mobilizing the entire universe.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 11, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_17t">
Father!
\nWe will go. We will be proud. We will overcome. We will collapse embracing this will.
\n\nNo matter how many people there are who oppose us, please allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to say, "Who could possibly destroy your and our relationship which is united heartistically or the fact that we are your sons and daughters, and you are our father? We want to be confident of this honor alone. We want to leave behind this honor alone for a thousand years."
\n\nFather! We are in awe of the grace you have told us about. We arc ashamed in front of our ancestors who were ignorant but obedient, and we are in awe of the martyrs. And we are in awe of Jesus, your only son who died. Even though we are inadequate and have no qualifications, you have given us such grace that it is difficult for us to be equal to it. Please bear with the fact that we have not been able to shed tears of gratitude.
\n\nWe have realized that we must become your children while we are living, and we have realized that before we die we must praise your love highly. Therefore, please allow us to be able to die not having left behind any grief, and having attended you, at least one time, Father, as those kinds of sons and daughters.
\n\nPlease let us realize that this is our hope, and it is your hope, too, Father, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to realize that this is the way to avenge you and to wipe Satan out of existence.
\n\nWe earnestly request and desire that you will let us become sons and daughters who go forth and fight while praying even if we collapse enduring, sacrificing, and yielding until the dominion of heaven is established, and even if we face grief which chokes us up for the sake of the day in which this will is realized. Please be with us personally so that we can unite and be more than equal to the responsibility that you have given us in front of the world.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the lord.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 17. 1960
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_18t">
Father!
\nPlease pardon the fact that we have shed endless tears because of our difficulties. When we had difficulties, we often smote our breasts and gnashed our teeth. Please let us realize how unpardonable this behavior was in front of our father.
\n\nFather, please let us realize that this kind of act could be expected from a traitor who had forgotten the sorrow of heaven, but it is an unreasonable act even in our dreams for a group that knows the sorrow of heaven. We have realized that being joyful even when in sorrow, and being joyful even when in difficulties, and being grateful even if we die are only fulfilling our responsibility at least a little in front of our father, and they are ways to avoid being ashamed in the presence of our father who comes to us.
\n\nNow the problem is the kind of position we are in. Have we ever even once greeted our father who came to us, or fed our father who was hungry, or given a drink to our father who was thirsty, or dressed our father who was in need of clothing, or gone to see our father who was in difficulties, or visited our father who was ill? You have said that those positions are where we can always attend you, Father.
\n\nWe have realized that we must become sacrifices for the whole, and we have realized that it is an ironclad historical rule that the smaller must be sacrificed for the larger. Furthermore since we have realized that great sacrifices must be made in order to establish the will of the heavenly providence, please let us suppress our own sorrows and be more concerned about your sorrows; let us suppress our own worries and be more concerned about your worries; and let us suppress our own unjust suffering and be more concerned about your unjust suffering. Please let us realize that if we become sons and daughters like that, the heart of heaven comes to be together with us.
\n\nWe were those who forsook you when we had suffering, who reported to you when we were in sorrow and who appealed to you to take care of it when we went through unjust suffering. We have realized that this is not the duty of filial children or the duty of loyal subjects and faithful women.
\n\nWe have come to realize that if you are going through unjust suffering, it will not do unless we seek to shoulder that unjust suffering even if we come face to face with a sorrowful position or the position of death, and we have realized that we are the people who must not let you stay in that kind of position if you are in that kind of position, even if we come to stand in a difficult position here on the earth.
\n\nFather! Please open the doors of our minds and dwell in us, and please release your grief which has formed during the course of restoration, and please let the joy and glory of attending you with our minds be able to reach and affect this world even to all the created things of heaven and earth. Since we have realized that you are infinitely longing for that day, Father, please let us become people who fight and fight, and weep and weep, going forward for the sake of that day.
\n\nWe earnestly request that you will allow us to become people who know how to run forward to the altar of glory where we attend you by establishing a standard of heart that says, "I will be loyal to you in that way."
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMay 22, 1960
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_19t">
Father!
\nWe really want to know your hope, your situation, and your heart. From that kind of position we can call you our father, and we know well how much you have longed for and sought for sons and daughters who pledge to find and establish the nation where we can serve you eternally. And we also know that it was only Jesus Christ, who lived and died on this earth, who called you "Father" from that kind of position of hope.
\n\nHe knew your hope, knew your situation, and knew your heart. He knew that your hope was destroyed in the course of history, and it was ostracized in the circumstances of the ages, and it remains as a difficult hope while pioneering the circumstances of the future. Your situation is a situation of pathetic tears, and it is a situation placed in an environment no one can sympathize with even if they want to, and he went the path of death together with humankind.
\n\nHe felt from your position that it was a situation he had to struggle with, and he felt your indignant and angry heart at the time you lost Adam, and your frustrated heart when you sent the messiah. And we know that he did not lose your hope, your situation or your heart, and while hoping for your mighty will and doctrine, he quietly went through a period of preparation, determined to die, pledged before you, and went forth on the path of the pioneer.
\n\nWe have come to know about the heart of Jesus who faced the cross with the hope he could not realize remaining in his heart, and even though feeling his situation was bleak, in order to not be called an unfilial child he sought to fulfill the duty of loyalty and to carry out completely the duty of filial piety. How much have you longed for true sons and true daughters who can call you father from that kind of position? How much have you longed for true sons and daughters who subjugate the enemy through the hands of those sons, and who bring the enemy to ruin through the hands of those daughters, and for children who gather together serving you and singing praises of your victory, "May the resolution of your grief and your hope for this land of great grief be realized! And may you receive glory!"
\n\nWe know that you have looked forward to having those kinds of sons and daughters call out to you in your name from that kind of position. We all hold on to you alone, Father, and we hope to become loyal subjects and faithful women who establish your dignity by offering all our filial piety and by offering all our loyalty to you. We are earnestly hoping that we will be able to call you our father from that kind of position, and be able to attend you as our father.
\n\nWe want only to become true sons and daughters who can really call you "Father," and true loyal subjects and faithful women who are able to really love you. This alone is our treasure; this alone is the purpose of our lives. Until now for the sake of this way we have lived dealing with all kinds of trials, and we are going this way today as well. Since from now we must go forth again, please let us become people who do not pass our sorrow on to you even if death blocks our way.
\n\nWhen we are in a sorrowful position, we should consider that as your sorrow, and we will have to be able to embrace and comfort each other, and we will have to become people who are able to long for and find such a father and such a son. Even if a person like that is dressed in ragged clothes, and he disappears through meeting his final death from a position where he is being ostracized, he cannot but be your son. Therefore, we know that the appearance in heaven and on earth of that son and the father whom that son calls, is the end of the fallen history, and the hope of the course of restoration.
\n\nWe have realized that it is the ideal of the second coming to have one son come to the earth who can be established as a world-level son and who can take responsibility for all of heaven and earth as unfinished works.
\n\nTherefore, from that kind of position, please let us be able inherit your innermost heart, inherit all your external circumstances, and to inherit all of your unfinished work as true sons and daughters. Please allow us to be able to direct the world here on earth, lead the rest of the people, and guide them to you, and please let us be able to sweep away the remaining enemies and be able to judge again.
\n\nEarnestly hoping for and desiring this, we have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 3, 1965
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_20t">
Father!
\nWe must not become a group that is just following. We earnestly hope and desire that you will let us become people who appear as those who are leading the way, in front of you, in front of our people, and in front of humankind.
\n\nFather! You have the grief of having worked so hard in sorrow for many grief-filled days, and since it was the grief of many people betraying heaven and becoming enemy groups, we know well that it is we who must take on the burden of this grief-filled day and these grief-filled situations.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will let us become your sons and daughters who are able to rejoice of our own volition about offering ourselves as heavenly sacrifices for the sake of the universe and all things of creation by taking on the responsibility for that burden.
\n\nNow at this time we are hoping that we can report honestly about everything of our past days and on the foundation of pure and clean minds, we hope that our minds can be filled only with hearts that long for you and affection that adores you. By doing that, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to be true filial sons and true filial daughters who are able to attend you with devotion, and not mind no matter what kind of situation you are in and no matter how you appear.
\n\nNow we earnestly hope that at this time you will let each one of us have earliest minds which bind together all our various kinds of devotion and offer them, and bow down humbly and are able to call out to you, and are able to weep endlessly held in your embrace.
\n\nThe father who has come to us until now has not been someone else's father. Since we have understood that you are my father and our father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will once again hold in your embrace these sorrowful children who are standing on the way of the destiny of restoration and who have to form a destined relationship with you, Father.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 12, 1966
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_21t">

    </string>
</resources>