<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_1t">
Father, please reveal yourself to us through your words of potentiality, and remold our entire beings. Beloved Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will begin your work of re-creation.
\n\nAs you have called and established each one of us individually out of difficult circumstances, now we will pass over the peak of our difficulties and trials. Now the time has come to raise up a song of triumph out of the struggle of the remaining real battle. Oh, Father, please add your power to our power, and add your ability to our ability, and please reveal yourself as the power of resurrection.
\n\nPlease allow the spirits that have been imprisoned in darkness to be liberated, and resurrect them with the fire of hope. Please allow the fire of your life to brighten far beyond the garden of truth which was blocked, far beyond this world which has been dominated by evil, and far beyond this site of your enmity of 6,000 years. My Father, I earnestly hope for and desire this.
\n\nWe know that the new history begins centering on you, Father. And we know the fact that if the standard of history is not set in heaven it cannot be the standard of history for the whole. Oh, Father! Since you have established us, please let us realize the new history.
\n\nPlease establish us as the elite troops of heaven of the new age, and allow us the blessing of being able to return glory and joy to You by building a new garden. We have broken down the walls of the battle, and we have entered upon the path which the saints and sages walked.
\n\nWe have entered the path called the difficult way. We have entered upon a path from which we cannot turn back even if we want to. We know that the time has come when we must fight with independent courage towards our unilateral goal. Please allow us to become the elite troops of heaven who can charge at Satan, who can go with fervor to the very end and raise up the flag before others.
\n\nFather! Until we can transform the alter of the remaining struggle into the altar of victory, into the alter of rest, and into the altar of glory for You, please, Father, protect our way as we go, sanctify the places where we stay, and guide us so that we may do even more than set up the white flag of the joyful victory in front of this people and all humankind.
\n\nI have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nApril 8, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_2t">
When we realize that the course to realize your Will is a lonely course which none of the people of the world knows, and when we think that the life of 21 years that Jacob walked is the path of faith which remains for us, we ask You to take pity on us and to help us walk the way of the Will by following the example of the course of Jacob who walked to Laban\'s house when he faced the wilderness of Haran, and we ask you to be our friend along the way. Please protect us along the way.
\n\nWe know that there are many Satans blocking the path that we are going. We know that the powers of darkness are blocking the way. Oh, Beloved Father, in the hearts of your children, who intend to follow the course that Jacob walked, please let there remain only one unchanging center like an iron will. Please let us become children who can rush forward forgetting all about our physical circumstances, keeping only the will of heavenly destiny in our hearts, and devoting ourselves with sincere hearts.
\n\nAnd now since we cannot help but endure and go through the battle until we offer the final song of victory to you, Father, oh, heaven, please give us strength and give us ability. As we inherit the lonely heart of Jacob, please allow those of us here the blessing of seeing the glory of the ladder reaching from earth up into the far reaches of heaven with heaven's angels ascending and descending it.
\n\nLet us come to know that heaven is with us and cooperating with us to the end. Let us come to know your heart of patience, Father, and until the day of realizing your eternal Will, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us as brave soldiers of battle, as brave soldiers of patience to fight to the end and to have victory.
\n\nWe offer these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 3, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_3t">
Father!
\nIn order to find and establish the one center of Zion, up until now so many of our ancestors have struggled and shed blood in order to pay indemnity for the acts that have indebted us and have caused You to worry.
\n\nOh, Father! Please let the glory of Zion come into our hearts and bodies now, and please let the joy of Zion where you can dwell eternally fill our hearts to overflowing.
\n\nWe know that if we become sons and daughters of glory whose minds and bodies can be dominated by you, there is nothing more that we could desire, and there is no hope greater than that.
\n\nBut if we cannot respond to our eternal father of love who is reaching out to us, there would be no people as miserable, no people as pitiful or as lonely as us.
\n\nWe have come before you, Father, with our wounded minds and bodies just as they are. So please take pity on us and let our wounds from being struck in battle be healed, and let us discover the taste of the love that you have harbored in your heart. Then let us resemble the heart of heaven, and centered on the glory of heaven, let everyone be able to sing, and centered on the glory of heaven, let everyone be able to enjoy, and for the sake of the will of heaven let everyone bow their heads. My Father, we sincerely hope for and desire this.
\n\nPlease let us be moved by the love of our Father which we feel from today and by the hope that we will have from today on and by the grief we will have from today on, and with hope let us pass over the peaks of the struggles of tomorrow, and while going through the course of our lives let us go over the walls of the curses of our many enemies.
\n\nAnd then let only a mind of peace become the center of our hearts. And let only our hearts which are longing for victory become the centers of our lives, and do not let us be lacking to go out and carry the flag of the battle representing this people. We know that this is the time of the Last Days, and we do not need the words of man, and we do not need any words that come through man, and we do not need any will centered on man.
\n\nWe know that we need only the words of love of our Father which come through the pulse of eternal life. Therefore, even though we are in an insecure position where we cannot experience love, Father, please work and inspect us with your eyes like fire, and bring out the core of joy that has been hidden in our hearts. Let us who are surrounded by so many kinds of fears become your children who come before you and repent.
\n\nIf there is anyone who has taken your hand, and who knows how to be grateful for your blessings, let him keep that heart without any changes. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will make us into sons and daughters who more than qualify to be recognized as sons and daughters of love in front of you, our Holy Father.
\n\nJust as the movement of life was one, and the movement of blessing was one, and the manifestation of glory was one, oh, Father, build a fence around the altar which has been scattered, and, centered on your Will, gather and establish us, and quickly set up the altar of joy that can make this people become one.
\n\nEarnestly desiring this, we pray all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 11, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_4t">
For thousands of years our ancestors have been building up walls of sorrows, and as the days go by, these walls are not getting lower; rather, through his many deceptions Satan has been making the walls higher.
\n\nToday all the people of the world have the responsibility to take down the walls of resentment that their ancestors have built up, and furthermore, we, too, must understand that we have that responsibility as well.
\n\nWe thought that Jesus himself having gone the path of anguish was just his own anguish, but when we realize that his anguish remains as ours, we discover ourselves to be those who must now go towards heaven with tears flowing.
\n\nNow, when we look at the walls of all the sins our ancestors committed with our hearts breaking over those sins, we realize how weak we are. Oh Father, please let us inherit your strength which can push all this away.
\n\nFather! Even if we are in a lonely position, please let us reclaim the wall of tears and realize a garden of harmony. Father, now that we know you are concerned about us in your heart please let us leave our hesitations behind and appear before you as those who are going forward without rest.
\n\nSince we have now received your command and have begun on our way, please let us become good sons and daughters of heaven who can run hard along the path to realize your desire, determined to go whether we live or die. Father, we earnestly hope for and desire this.
\n\nNow we can respond to the words which Jesus said, "Leave everything and follow me." Let us become the sons and daughters who can respond to that call.
\n\nIn front of the Will which gives you joy, Father, when you command us towards the garden of desire which you want, we must become the sons and daughters who can come forward and not waver having made all preparations without hesitation, and who can be embraced and loved by heaven.
\n\nAnd since we have the responsibility that we must fight with Satan and be responsible for the six thousand years of historical resentment, please let us become courageous men of victory who can fight with good hearts, with indomitable spirits which have made new determinations, new decisions and new pledges.
\n\nEarnestly desiring these things, we have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 23, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_5t">
Father!
\nThrough your words we have come to know that heaven and earth are like one body. When we come to realize that heaven is the subject and we are minor details, we realize that we are beings who cannot live even one day or one moment without receiving the sap of life and love of heaven.
\n\nAnd when we realize that our being is such that we should live as one of the branches and leaves of heaven receiving the sap of love flowing out from the eternal God, we ask you to forgive us for not having lived like that. Father! It is the Last Days, and at this time which is announcing the Day of Judgment, we ask that you will allow each of ourselves to be grafted to your love centered on Jesus Christ who is the perfect root.
\n\nWe know that you are longing to gather from each of us fruits of love born through the love of our eternal Father and through the love of Jesus and the Holy Spirit. But for us to arrive at that point by ourselves, we are so insufficient, so incomplete, and so immature that we worry that we might become obstacles to your scything of the harvest.
\n\nSince we now commit ourselves to you, Father, oh please, Father, raise us and take care of us. In the midst of trials and tribulations place us in the pulpits and allow us to become complete as mature fruits. And please allow us to become people who bear fruit and who realize the eternal Kingdom of Heaven by joining hands with the love of our eternal Father, and please let us become harvest workers who can bring in the harvest for you.
\n\nPlease let us come to realize that you are pressing for the realization of the Day of Christ through us now. Please let us understand that this is the time that you want to show the love of Christ by raising us up.
\n\nAnd furthermore, please let us realize that you have raised us up and you are waiting for us to embrace the sufferings of Christ now in this 20th century. Father, please lead us so that our steps which are running towards the castle of heaven are not centered on ourselves, and please do not let anyone remain in a state where he prays centered on himself.
\n\nPlease allow us to come forward and cast out all the elements that evil can attack. In order to realize the Will that you desire and you are directing please take hold of us, Father, and help us to endure and continue going even on paths where we could not help but collapse and be disappointed or on paths with any kind of serious struggle. Father, we earnestly hope for and desire this.
\n\nFather! We pray when in place of Jesus we do the work that he could not accomplish completely on this earth, even if we are persecuted by this people, please help us to be able to cope with all these things.
\n\nAnd when we live for the sake of heaven, even if we are insulted by the people on earth and have difficulties and experience anguish, please let us overcome everything capably and remain to the end.
\n\nSix thousand years have passed until today. Since Jesus has been longing for this day of harvest, and is calling us, through us please wipe away the stains of the blood and tears of the cross and historical anguish, and lead us to become the shields of victory. Please do not let us forget that Jesus who was the incarnation of hope is waiting for us to become qualified people who are able to take dominion over Satan.
\n\nIn that way, today also we must fight in place of heaven, holding the joyful Will of our Father in our hearts. We are earnestly hoping and desiring that you will let us become sons and daughters who are determined to subjugate the enemy Satan. And if we dedicate the course of our lives to this work, and we are not able to complete the mission, the work of our Father, then let us be determined to complete it even through our descendents.
\n\nWe offer all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 30, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_6t">
Please let us feel, oh God, that at the same time that you are the commander of love, you are our one and only commander-in-chief who is facing and fighting with evil. Please let us become saints who can make you proud by following the example of the course of devotion of Jesus Christ and by resembling the external form of our Father who has been continually fighting without resting for six thousand years.
\n\nPlease don\'t let us, who are in the process of fighting today, become foolish people who ask Jesus and the Holy Spirit to center on ourselves, or who ask you, God, to center on ourselves.
\n\nWe know that we should appear as the elite troops of heaven who fight heaven\'s battles representing heaven and who can be victorious there. We must not become the elite troops centered on any people or the elite troops centered on any specific world.
\n\nTherefore, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will let us become the elite troops of heaven, who maintain unchanging fidelity for the will of heaven, for unchanging love and for the eternal ideal of heaven.
\n\nFather, at this time please let us come to understand that when you, who have endured for six thousand years, give us a command, if we are not people of character with value who can fathom your heart, then you cannot directly command us.
\n\nAnd if someone is not true, righteous and law abiding, and is not a person who qualifies for glory with an unchangeable aspect which can represent heaven, then Jesus Christ, who has been working for 2,000 years, cannot directly command him, either. Please let us come to understand this. Father, we are earnestly hoping for and desiring this.
\n\nNow if there is a cosmic hope that still remains for us, please let us come to realize that our hope is to become elite troops who can take total responsibility for everything in the universe and liberate all the things of creation, and give joy to all humankind. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will let us become intoxicated with our sense of mission, and receive heaven's commands and fulfill our responsibilities completely.
\n\nIn order to establish heaven's will on this earth, Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will let us be sons and daughters who know only how to fight, who do not know how to rest or change, and who, knowing the laws of heaven and the laws of the battle of the universe, will represent the unchanging center, until the glory of the restoration and the ideal of the eternal God are revealed in all things of creation.
\n\nPlease lead us to become the elite troops of heaven who, transcending everything, rush forward not caring even if we are on the path of death for the sake of your joy and your glory alone, Father.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nApril 4, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_7t">
The hope that our minds have been longing for is the garden of the ideal of our eternal father. All our bodies have been longing for is to reach the day when we can speak with pride in front of our Father in the glory of victory after fighting with Satan. Then our minds would be filled with the glory of our Father, and our bodies would resemble the external form of our Father. We earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you would please allow us to appear in glory; and allow our minds and bodies to become the objects of your joy.
\n\nWe are those who should take on the external form of sons and daughters of that kind of victory, but with our minds in front of your glory and our bodies in front of your internal character, please let us reveal everything about ourselves. We ask you to please fill us with awe and lead us to be able to reflect on and repent about our inadequate selves of the past.
\n\nFather! If we truly admire your love and desire to resemble your character, then we know that your present anguish must become ours, and your frustration must become ours. Therefore, beloved Father, please work to make us like that.
\n\nOh, Father of love! Among us are there any sons or daughters who, although they know their minds and bodies are going the way of darkness and death, are not yet able to repent? Oh Father, please show your capabilities. Oh Father, please show your power.
\n\nOh Father, please bring about your work of resurrection and re-creation. In that way please let our minds and bodies have the ability to rush towards and enter your heart of infinite love. Beloved Father, we are earnestly hoping for and desiring this.
\n\nFather! Please let us realize the fact that as time passes, the day of the final battle is coming right before our eyes. Please do not let us become people who lose heart on that battlefield. Beloved Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will please let us become the elite troops of heaven who will go forward and fight and fight again until we have established the one standard of the final victory representing you, Father.
\n\nUntil now you have been sad together with us; you have fought together with us; you have gone through difficulties with us. Now since we know that there is a new battle left for us to fight while looking towards your one day of hope, oh, Father, please act by giving us limitless ability so that we can win that battle, and please do not let us prove inadequate.
\n\nIn that way, this people can be embraced by your heart of love, and furthermore, through this people please let the many people on this earth be able to greet your glory daily. And through humanity may one, not two, worlds be realized, harmonizing with even the millions of saints in heaven. We earnestly hope and desire that you will act so that we can realize quickly here on earth a new restored garden where we will praise your glory and experience your love.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 13, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_8t">
When we reflect that a history of struggle remains for us which even if we die we cannot help but inherit as the work you have left to us, please let all of us who are here open ourselves before you and ask ourselves whether we are truly the elite troops of heaven who can fight - the elite troops of heaven who can fight and bring the victory. Father, we earnestly hope for and desire this.
\n\nWe know that the enemy which we must fight against is not some certain person on the earth, but Satan who grasped the authority of the skies and raised the banner of rebellion against God and has been accusing God throughout the long course of history of 6,000 years.
\n\nWhen we think that today we have the responsibility and mission to subjugate this tremendous enemy in front of you, Father, we realize that basking in your grace we have desired only to receive your love and until now we have wanted such easy lives. Father, please bear with us.
\n\nUp until now we have been forgetting that in order to subjugate our enemies, even facing the adversity of the cross or terrible troubles and battles, we are in a position where our minds and hearts must not change.
\n\nBut from now on, beloved Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will please let us become the elite troops of heaven who will hold on to our unchanging hearts and be able to fight millions of Satans all alone.
\n\nAre there any sons or daughters exhausted by the struggle while going forth supporting this Will? Oh, Father, please give them strength. Are there any who are hesitating? Please give them your courage. Then they will be able to rush towards the goal of victory. Beloved Father, we earnestly hope that you will let them become loving sons and daughters who can dash at and run straight to goal of the battle.
\n\nSince we have the responsibility to go over the peak of Golgotha to victory through hand-to-hand combat in the very end, we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will let us become your sons and daughters who have your strength, heart, resolution and determination, who can rush towards the site of every battle, and who, while feeling your grief, can win the victory.
\n\nPlease let us lay open before you the place where our heart dwells. Please let your will appear as a concrete objective. And oh, Father, are there any weak people among your sons and daughters who have the mission of standing up to Satan and showing your standard? Please give them strength. Are there any who pray to you and squeeze out the grief of heaven?
\n\nOh Father, please give them happiness. Are there any working hard to find heaven? Please appear to them as goodness and public justice.
\n\nNow please let us be your sons and daughters who can go forward towards your will taking responsibility for it alone even though walls block the way in front of us along this course of struggle that we must go.
\n\nWe earnestly hope that you will let us be able to establish the standard of your sons and daughters who can win the victory even if we have to offer our very last breath following the example of Jesus' victory as he overcame infinite suffering on his way to the cross.
\n\nWe offer up all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 27, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_9t">
In the spirit world things are organized in the name of the second Israel. But today Christianity which is spread widely throughout the world is not able to set up the order of the second Israel. Father! Please awaken this sleeping people, and awaken the Christians of the world who are sleeping.
\n\nPlease give to us the authority of the chosen people who can build the third Israel throughout the world today, and who can become one with the spirit world and establish order on the earth, giving the blessing in place of the second Israel.
\n\nThen please let us take over the heavenly mission which must go up through the tribes which have been set in order though the people, through the nation and through the world, and please let us take over the course of Moses struggle.
\n\nAnd please let us take over the course of Jesus struggle and cast out Satan\'s criticisms and accusations, and beyond that, let us attend you, Father, and let us receive your glory. Father, we earnestly hope for and desire this. We earnestly hope that you will establish sons and daughters of joy who can win over the sufferings of the chosen people of Israel whom you have selected.
\n\nPlease let us achieve the course of restoration of the world-level Canaan. And now please let us band together into one and be victorious in the course of the struggle with Satan. Please don't let us become a group that rebels against the one central will of Jesus, and don't let us become a group that causes you to suffer.
\n\nNow we sincerely ask you to let us become sons and daughters who will more than fulfill the third Israel and who will not cause heaven to worry.
\n\nWe offer all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 9, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_10t">
Father!
\nPlease take pity on humankind who has lost the garden of freedom, on humankind who has lost the garden of liberation, and on humankind who has lost the garden of unification. We thought that all the things that were lost could be resolved only in the external world, but we have come to understand the historical sorrow that although things went forward with one external standard, internally they were divided.
\n\nPlease let us have overflowing strength of ideology, strength of love, and strength of life facing God, which can win the world of internal freedom, the world of internal liberation, and the world of internal unification which are the problems now. Please establish in our hearts one standard of heart that will allow us to tread upon and go beyond resentment, sadness and suffering while laughing even at death.
\n\nFather! When we look at the historical world of today, we realize that it is moving and going forward centered on material things, and it has a form that externally looks like it is unified while it promotes division internally. But when we look internally, we understand that history has flowed in the opposite direction in order to avoid a lack of mind, in order to avoid a lack of life, and in order to avoid a lack of love.
\n\nFather! Today in the hearts of humankind who are living on this earth there is not just material scarcity and exhaustion; we are not just being pressed hard materially; we are being hit by mental exhaustion and are being pressed hard mentally.
\n\nTherefore, to fill this, please grant us the fire of the Holy Spirit and your life, Father, and the strength of your love. And please grant to us all internal life which can be obtained only in a place which is exploding, and your heart of freedom, Father, your heart of liberation, and your heart of unification which can absorb even the ideology of freedom which we have pursued.
\n\nIn the face of the course of history of searching, wandering and working, please now let your heart, Father, explode in our hearts. Please let us possess your life force, your ideology, and freedom based on lives centered on your love, freedom based on ideology, freedom based on love.
\n\nAnd furthermore please let us possess the entirety realized by the liberation and unification based on all those things. And while we say, "Oh, Father, please be comforted now. We now know what Your heart is like," please let us come to possess the foundation of heart that can fulfill your desire, Father, you, who have worked so hard in the course of history
\n\nThen we will attend you, Father, and from a position where we can sing of life, and ideology and liberation and you can receive glory, we will relieve even the heart of our Father who has been carrying out the providence to restore the freedom which relieves the lamentations and suffering of restoration and the anguish of restoration. We earnestly hope that you will please let us become your sons and daughters and please let all the people of the world attend you, Father, and be able to sing of freedom, and be able to sing of liberation and be able to sing of unification.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 12, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_11t">
Today we have gathered once more at your knees, Father, but we are worried that we might not be able to offer glory to you, our anguished Father. We are worried that absurd charges might appear in front of the Will which you desire. Oh Father, if we are not suitable, let us go of our own will to a low place, and please let us at least have hearts that sincerely desire your pity.
\n\nIf you don\'t care for us, Father, then how could we see your glory on this earth? If we cannot become those who can remain in your heart, how can we … see the will of the garden you allowed? Oh, Father! Please let us become a group that can remain in your mind, a group that can be transformed in your heart, a group that can live together with you. From the very beginning we have yearned for that, and watching that Will, we have gone forward.
\n\nPlease let this be a time when we question whether we, who have pledged before you, who have determined ourselves before you, whether we have become those who can obey your commands.
\n\nThe last days are approaching, and we know that you must be lamenting that there is no group that will take responsibility for you. We have found you and have seen your glory, and we fancy ourselves to be your sons.
\n\nWe know that you are lamenting because you see no group appearing that can take responsibility for any one area of your will which remains, of the providence you permit, or your course of struggle. Oh, Father, at this time please let us once again be able to shed tears of bitter repentance and raise up an altar of redemption before you.
\n\nWe know about the people of Israel who collapsed in the wilderness while they resented you and their minds wished for rest during the course in the wilderness. Today in order for us to not become like that we are now attending you and seeking to take your hand, so, beloved Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will lead us to become a group that participates in your glory.
\n\nAt this time when you are searching for your sons and daughters who will work for the earth, please do not let us be people who remain clinging to ourselves when facing you, Father. We ourselves feel our inadequacies; we are so inadequate that we dare not appear before your altar, Father. But please let us become your sons and daughters who can keep to the very end, even to death, the path of Golgotha for the sake of this Will. And we earnestly hope that you will let us be a group that remains to the end.
\n\nWe have offered all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 19, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_12t">
Father!
\nWe know that in order to move eternal life, life must be moved by life, and love must be moved by love. Therefore, Father, you who are the subject of life, please appear as life, and you who are the subject of love, please appear as love.
\n\nWe are suffering the drying up of life, and we are suffering the drying up of love. And while that is happening, we are at a poverty-stricken point in all doctrinal aspects, and we are so inadequate that we cannot even protect our lives for one day. Betraying heaven and earth we are holding in our hearts the resentment of the fall which lost your ideology and this day, too, we bow before you in sorrow, Father.
\n\nPlease embrace our pitiful appearances, Father. It you say you do not know us, who would take responsibility for us? And if you do not hold on to us, who would hold on to us? As we have no leader before us and no teacher before us, we earnestly hope and desire that only you, Father, will be together with us.
\n\nWhen we come to realize that you work so hard to comfort our hearts each time we stiffer a difficult experience or have a sorrowful experience, we cannot help but report to you that we are ashamed before you. We are sorry, Father, that you have shed tears watching us go along the path of persecution as we follow the way where you told us, "Go."
\n\nResponding to your call when you tell us, "Come," we follow in your footsteps. Since we have even determined to go the way of death, Father, when the path of death appears, please don't let us retreat before it, afraid of the line of death.
\n\nEven if we run into the pain of our bodies being ripped apart or our hearts being torn to shreds, as long as your sighs remain, your desire remains, your love remains, we earnestly hope that you will let us become heaven's true sons and daughters, heavens true brave hearts who can overcome all things.
\n\nWe have prayed these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 21, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_13t">
Now the time has come when we must resolve the course of history of universal sorrow and create a new history of joy. Father, our strength is insufficient, so please give us powerful strength, and please let us have powerful ambition. We earnestly hope, Father, that you will let us be the figures of the elite troops of heaven who can go forward with confidence to the goal with new valor.
\n\nYou said, "Be strong and of good courage," to Joshua and Caleb who were looking at the land of Canaan. Since the standard you established for Joshua when he faced his enemies was to "Be strong and of good courage," today we cannot help but fully attack the capital of Canaan with strength and good courage.
\n\nAt this time when the battle of the final judgment is right before our eyes, we know that you need sons and daughters who can face the forces of darkness and take responsibility and fight on the earth. Father, we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will let your sons and daughters who are gathered here become those kinds of responsible people.
\n\nPlease take dominion of each of the hearts of your sons and daughters who are gathered here.
\n\nIs there anyone who is insisting on establishing himself today? Is there anyone who is relating to you, Father, through some ideology, or thought system, or concept or understanding? Then he is one who does not know your absolute authority, Father. He is someone who does not know the suffering behind you.
\n\nPlease let us be able to break down the wall of death which has been blocking us for six thousand years through enmity and sorrow. Then millions of saints can be mobilized, and please let the many spirits of the spirit world centered on the Triune God offer a welcome of joy at this time. We earnestly hope that you will let this be the time when we can promise the day of liberation and restoration to all the beings of the universe.
\n\nWe offer this in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 21, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_14t">
Until now many people have come and gone for the sake of your Will, but we know that your having called us who are so insignificant and gathering us in this place is a great blessing. And we know that your having gathered us means that you have something to request of us. Oh Father! We earnestly hope and desire that at this time you will pour your words of life and your grace of life into each individual soul.
\n\nAs we gaze at the garden of hope, we realize that today and tomorrow a battlefield remains where we must pioneer the route of the battle. Therefore, please guide us to be able to drive out and sweep away the wave of death with minds and bodies that are strong and of good courage. And, Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will let us become your sons and daughters who have the power of life and the grace of resurrection.
\n\nBeloved Father! Please bless the many religious bodies who gather representing this people. And Father, please especially pour out your grace of blessings on the family members who are praying earnestly on bended knees before you in loneliness. Please protect them and reach out to them with endless blessings, and counsel them through endless works.
\n\nOn the remaining battlefield of the final battle with Satan, we earnestly hope and desire that you will not let us be defeated and that you will let us become your sons and daughters who will sing loudly the triumphal song of glory and your sons and daughters whom you can praise.
\n\nOh Father, we know that many have made efforts for you, Father, but because they could not endure to the end and could not win their efforts and work could not bear fruit. Therefore, we earnestly hope that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who can endure and strive to the end until we realize the final fruits for you, Father, and please let us go forward today and tomorrow, staking our entire lives regardless of what kind of battle there is.
\n\nWe offer all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 22, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_15t">
Father!
\nUntil now we have not known what your will was. We did not know your will for history; we did not know your will for this age, and we did not know your will for our lives and our daily activities. But it is awe-striking and we thank you that you have allowed us the blessing of being able to know your historical Will. We truly thank you, Father, for the blessing of teaching us the heart of the age, the heart of life, the heart of daily activities, and even the heart of time.
\n\nEmbracing these hearts we will have to go through the gate of the apostles, and following the path that Christ went, we will have to go through the narrow gate. Then we will become those who can fight and win at the point of death and more than receive the blessing of resurrection, and we will leave on this earth once again resurrected tribes of goodness. We know your words that it is only by bearing fruit that we can avoid the judgment.
\n\nSince you have said that every tree that does not bear good fruit is cut down and thrown into the fire, we must become good trees. Please allow us to become good trees and to be people who bear good fruit.
\n\nIn order to gather good fruit, Jesus, too, has been struggling for two thousand years. Therefore, please give us the grace of resurrection today and allow us as good trees to be able to bear good fruit. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to be sons and daughters who know how to sow seeds on the earth.
\n\nThis is your will, Father; this is the purpose of our Father who has come to the earth. We know that this is the content for which you have struggled. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to be able to cling to you and fight, and to be able to live with that content, that will, and that purpose deep in our hearts.
\n\nWe earnestly request you to let us become the most filial sons and daughters who can comfort you and who can comfort the Lord by having accomplished the will which was left and by having run to the end of the path.
\n\nWe offer all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nApril 26, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_16t">
Father, we humans are surrounded by misery with the waves of death rolling over us. But you have been carrying out the providence of the history of struggle while being falsely accused, and you have been working so hard during that long period of time in order to bring about the day when you could take pity on the earth. We realize that we could not establish our dignity before you and that we are sinners whom you cannot believe even though you want to.
\n\nNow please deliver us from this six-thousand-year history which has been like the affliction in Egypt. Thank you for your promise of the day and the age of glory. Through history we know well that you had many saints and sages walk the path of tears and blood before others, and it was more than a few times that you ordered the direction they had to go, telling them the path would be like that.
\n\nOh Father of pity! Oh Father of love! We know that it is difficult for you to hold on to this earth and to take our hands. We are unprepared and disloyal, but as we have come before your majesty adoring your mercy and longing for your love, please bear with us.
\n\nPlease have pity on us who are living our lives on this earth where sorrow and lamentations remain. Please have pity on us who are struggling in the realities of daily life. Even though we should be those who are concerned with the heart of heaven, we cannot help but look at this land with tears and sorrow. And we cannot help but lament over our hearts which cannot help but weep loudly for the sake of heaven.
\n\nI pray that, filled with the kind of heart that longed for the restoration of Canaan, you will clear away, Father, the realm of lamentations of this history of six thousand years of tribulations like the course of the affliction in Egypt.
\n\nHumankind has hoped and believed and followed. We know that the path has been a course of toil, and the footsteps demanded sorrow. Because it was humankind who committed the act of the fall which caused resentment, we must go whether we want to or not.
\n\nEver since humankind, which is struggling in a pit of despair, knew of the promise of heaven, we have been struggling in order to get out of this pit of death. But we know that we have not been able to get out from under Satan's command even up to today. And furthermore, we know that even more than anyone else, we ourselves are among them.
\n\nNow the time has come that in order to live we must call out to you alone, to our living Father, and the time has come that it will not do unless sons and daughters who give their full loyalty appear for the sake of our Father who has established the Will of the providence.
\n\nTherefore, please allow us to have at least earnest hearts which proclaim they will struggle to establish that nation, and today and tomorrow please let us reproach our unprepared selves, deplore our incomplete states, and strike our disloyal selves. Beloved Father, we earnestly hope for and desire this.
\n\nOh Father! We know well that when the 600,000 people of Israel escaped from Pharaoh's palace, their shout of joy rose up to heaven, but later, when the soldiers of Pharaoh followed them, they lamented and reproached heaven as they went their way. Today when we come before you, Father, are our hearts filled with joy? We are afraid that contrary to that heart, a heart that reproaches heaven will grow within us.
\n\nEven if we have the sorrow of running into some kind of sadness or some kind of crookedness, and even if our enemies dig pits of sin and lie in wait for us, we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will not let us lose the fidelity which becomes the elite soldiers of heaven.
\n\nOn the way there will be mountain peaks, gravelly fields and wastelands, and there will be times when enemies plot against us. Therefore, we earnestly hope and pray that you will allow us to become brave soldiers of heaven who can each feel responsibility in our hearts and charge forward and not reconsider the determination we have already made, and today and tomorrow develop the straight road of the battle until the promised land of Canaan is liberated.
\n\nWe pray all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMay 17, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_17t">
Father!
\nWe who have gone through the course of history send our reflection out to the world, and we hold in ourselves the reflection of the world. Accordingly, please allow us to become filial and loyal sons and daughters who can attend you, Father, who are moving the world. We have realized that this is your hope, Father.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who can gallantly stand before the Will of heaven and with new determination pledge that we will sacrifice ourselves for the Will from now on.
\n\nEven if the path before us becomes rough and persecution is continuous, we will think of you, Father. And even if tears rise up out of loneliness, we will think of you, Father. And even if we don\'t know what to do with ourselves because we are pierced by vicissitudes of grief, we will think of you, Father. And if we think that this way is the way I must go, that it is my life\'s work, then we know we will not be destroyed.
\n\nWe know that if we are like that, through us the time will come when this people will know a new direction, and the time will come when a new level of culture of the people of the world and a new beginning point will be established. Please allow us to become brave people who will march blowing our trumpets loudly in order to establish the garden of the heavenly heart with relationships of heavenly affection.
\n\nPlease allow us to become your sons and daughters who march into the enemy camp in order to see the end of Satan. In that way we will find the children whom heaven lost and return them to the heart of heaven. Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who can do even more than sing a song of victory.
\n\nWe earnestly request and desire that you will embrace us and train us so that we may not be inadequate to take on the great work of this age, this great world-level work, and furthermore, this great cosmic work which heaven wants to give us.
\n\nWe offer all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 16, 1960
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_18t">
Father!
\nWe have arrived at the place you told us to go to. Since coming here we have realized that the final battle still remains. Just as the Jordan River was blocking the way of the Israelite people who had gone out in joy looking forward to the restoration of Canaan, the promised land, we have come to understand that the final battle remains before us.
\n\nWe know that when the time carne for the Israelites to cross the Jordan River which was in front of this people who had received the commandment to go to this area and who had gone towards that site of hope, there was a three-day course of struggle.
\n\nWe know that today you must remove from us the blood lineage of the gruesome history which has continued unbroken until today, and that this is the victory. Father! Now we know that this is a serious moment when we must walk solemnly towards the throne of God our Father with firm resolution, having received a final special command. We have realized that our minds and our bodies are not our own. Whose are we? And for whom have we come to this place? We are yours, Father, and we have come here for you.
\n\nWe have realized that the place where we are replenished is not the earth. The place where our bodies are replenished goes out in four directions, but we understand that the place where our spirits are replenished is in poverty, suffering, sorrow and grief.
\n\nHaving arrived at the final rampart which we must overcome and then establish ourselves, we realize that this is the moment that we must await your final order to make the assault. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that at this moment you will allow us to come to have a firm resolution, pledge and conviction to finish the work and then collapse.
\n\nPlease let us become people who know how to fear you, Father. You struck the people who betrayed the Will and increased the sorrow of the sorrowful course of history. Even if there is resentment which tears away our flesh and breaks our bones, please let us be those who remain to the very end and do not change our set determination. If we all offer our minds and bodies for the unchanging center, what resentment could we have?
\n\nWhether we are asleep or awake, eating or starving, please do not let us forget that we are the elite forces of heaven who must maintain God's frontline.
\n\nEven if our situation is like that of diseased wanderers who are thirsting and starving, we earnestly hope that you will not let us become a group that goes back on the promises we made to you, Father. May your Will be realized, Father. And may you please allow the Will that you have given us to bear fruit through us.
\n\nWe pray in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 11, 1960
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_19t">
Father!
\nEven if the poverty of this age comes near us, and the starvation of this age comes near us, and the despair and lamentations of this age come near us, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become unification workers who, safely overcoming these things, become the sons and daughters of heaven who have the power of resurrection from the world of death and who are able to raise up the flag of victory.
\n\nIf among us there is anyone who is inadequate and cannot: move according to your Will, Father, then even if you have to strike him, please establish him in the land of hope that you desire. Since we know that the Will of Heaven is to establish the victory even through death, please do not let us cast away our conviction to follow you or our determination to die.
\n\nWhen the Israelite people were marching to the land of Canaan, if Moses had taken a rod and even beaten those who were collapsing in order to get them to go through the wilderness, the 600,000 people would not have become food for vultures in the wilderness.
\n\nWe know only too well that the time has come when a people\'s movement must be carried out with individuals who can pledge and determine to ask to be guided, even by being struck by a rod.
\n\nSince our Unification Movement has come forth already determined to die, Father, please guide to the land of Canaan, even if you need to take up the rod and strike us to do it. We must become those who say that even if we die we will have to go and die in that place.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will not allow us to become those who follow in the footsteps of our ancestors who collapsed and became food for vultures in the wilderness, left a stain on history, and left behind grief for thousands of years.
\n\nNow we have inherited heaven's Will and are going forth holding up the standard of the new Israel. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become heaven's sons and daughters who know how to take responsibility for and pass over the peak of the cross which they were not able to pass over.
\n\nPlease don't let us be held prisoner in habitual concepts of faith, and as the days go by please allow filial piety and loyalty to you to flow deep in our hearts. We earnestly hope and desire that the more perilous the environment, the more you will bless our true, earnest hearts to be able to have dominion over ourselves.
\n\nWe have offered all these things in the name of our Lord.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 23, 1962
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_20t">
Father!
\nPeople thought that this historical event which occurred in a corner of Korea would be pursued and driven out, and that it would disappear like flowing water. But now it has spread out to the world and is creating controversy in Japan, America, Germany, and in the entire world.
\n\nBut we know that this is not something to destroy the world; rather, it is something to destroy Satan\'s world. We know that it is a historical event in order to banish the very being of Satan from this land. Since we are the brave people of heaven who are carrying the mission of this kind of awesome restoration, please, please allow us to be strong and of good courage.
\n\nFather, please be with us always. We know that behind us there are always thousands and thousands of saints who are ready to fight to the end. For us there will be nothing but advancing; we must go forward for this nation; we must go forward for this world; and we know clearly that we are on a course of restoration today that includes the awesome mission of liberating even the spirits who are in the entire cosmos. Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to follow this way to the end.
\n\nFather! An awesome, historical, new path of righteousness has appeared on the earth. A new order has begun to be extended over this earth. Therefore, the whole world should be drawn into a whirlwind of inspiration, and the world that praises you, Father, while holding up the flag of victory, which should come quickly.
\n\nSince we are people who have determined to invest our lives and everything we have for that, please give us directions and orders according to your desire, Father. We will cross the oceans without hesitation and will walk across continents.
\n\nAs we go our way, please reach out to us with your peace. We know that the shield of victory is near us; therefore, we earnestly hope that everywhere we go you will allow many incidents to happen that will reveal your real nature and your glory.
\n\nEach time that we visit many other nations, we understand how rushed and how busy our mission is; therefore, we must offer more devotion to you, Father. Now the time has passed for living for this people. The time has come for living for the world and for the cosmos.
\n\nTherefore, we earnestly ask that you will allow us to become the victors by connecting ourselves totally with you in our realms of life by going beyond our individual living circumstances and by centering on you, the source of life, the source of love, and the source of the ideal.
\n\nWe have offered these things in the name of the True parents.
\nAmen.
\nMay 4, 1969
    </string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_21t">

    </string>
</resources>