<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_1t">
Father!
\nSince many members are thirsting for life and have gathered here before this altar, please allow them to represent your glory; and representing the altar of joy please let them know your deliberations and dilemmas; and please allow them to be able to experience your heart. We know that you are in a position where you cannot help but believe in these insignificant beings as you relate to them, and we know that you are in a position where you cannot help but carry out your works through them.
\n\nEven though we know that up until today heaven has been in a position where it must believe us, believe in and establish us, we ask you, Father, to please bear with our faults of the past which made you unable to believe in us.
\n\nWe humans beings have not been able to fulfill our responsibility to become people you can trust, so Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will bear with us at this time. Please allow us to become those who believe you and trust you, and can give up our lives for you, and can honestly offer our daily lives to you. My beloved father, we earnestly hope and desire that you can take us as sacrifices proper for you to accept. Oh, Father! Since you have called us who are so unworthy from among so many people, please accept us and embrace us with your compassionate love.
\n\nWe offer our minds and bodies to you, so please allow us to experience your anxious mind, and our beloved Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become children who are able to accept and carry out your desire. Your heartbreaking situation formed throughout six thousand years has continued until today, and when we consider your history of lamentation which has continued until today, and consider that today, we ourselves are the very source of your lamentations, we ask you to please bear with us.
\n\nPlease make us into the realizations of the life and the idea you desired, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will make us into roots of life which can give you joy. We have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMay 23, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_2t">
Oh, Father of love!
\nOh, Father of compassion! By ourselves alone, with just our strength, we cannot possibly separate goodness and evil and raise goodness up to be goodness. Therefore, please reveal the power of goodness which heaven has sheltered and the power of love which heaven has hidden, and please work through the power of resurrection.
\n\nPlease allow us to be able to reveal a power capable of being good even in our unworthy position. And our beloved Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to be able to have the glory of resurrection, and to be able to bow before you, having given our minds and bodies fully for you and to be able to reveal glory having spent our minds and bodies completely.
\n\nFather! Please purify our minds, and please work with your purifying touch in the soul of each one here. Please reveal what is in the mind and body of each one, Father, and purify each thing. Since it will not do unless all the improper elements are divided out and cast away, oh, Father, please personally become the master of separation and the master of our hearts.
\n\nI earnestly hope and desire, my Father, that you will allow us to be able to separate good and evil and then do away with evil, and to be able offer ourselves through one center before the majesty of our father as living sacrifices of goodness alone.
\n\nOh, Father! Please allow us to recognize the unworthiness of ourselves in front of your manifested external form, and to discover that we ourselves are in the realm of death, having received the power of the sins of the past. In front of you, Father, in front of the altar of the glory of goodness, please let us be able to reveal ourselves and please eliminate any improper habits from the past and any concepts that keep us from believing you.
\n\nPlease allow us to receive a new stimulation of goodness and to feel anew the value of your internal nature and to feel an impact in our minds and bodies. We earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will carry out a work of repentance and inspiration. Father! Please accept us and take dominion over us. Please don't allow even one person among us to be dominated by Satan.
\n\nAfter going through your almighty works and your works of efforts for recreation, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to cast away the force of today's habits. Please eliminate at this time, Father, all the unacceptable, improper elements of sin, and by personally intervening, please act to fill all of us with only the elements of glory that you can take dominion over, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will completely take dominion over us.
\n\nWe humbly pray this in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 11, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_3t">
Father!
\nPlease, you alone protect everything, and you alone take over and take dominion.
\n\nPlease let this become a time of knowing that not even our lives are our own, and not even our knowledge is our own, nor are all our concepts our own. Please allow us to be on the move only if heaven is on the move and to decide something only if heaven decides, as people who have entrusted ourselves only to you.
\n\nPlease let us understand that even if a concept is considered outstanding in the world, it cannot avoid the destiny of heaven. Please let us realize that the ignorance of the world has penetrated this land, and please allow us to understand that the shadow of sin has formed a relationship with the entire world. Beloved Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to be awakened to our unworthiness and to be inspired by the movement of destiny and to feel awe-stricken as we deal with the whole.
\n\nFather! Please command us. Please advise us and tell us what you want. Please reveal the power of resurrection, and allow the power that can push aside the wall of darkness which is blocking us to explode. We earnestly hope for and desire this. Since the spirit is willing but the flesh is weak, please reveal a power that can go beyond this weak body, and please move according to the authority of your touch, and please allow us to be able to truly accept being molded by your touch, by the blessing of recreation which you shower upon us. We earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to become gentle, humble people who can be molded into an external form of glory.
\n\nSince today you have called us though we are worthless people, please allow us to be able to fulfill your desire. Please allow a living altar to appear for the sake of finding a way for this pitiful people to live, this people who are in the midst of distress, who are dying. Please place our individual beings in front of you today Father, and allow us to stand in a position of being able to receive answers to our questions, and please allow us to be capable of receiving and carrying out the mission heavenly destiny asks of us.
\n\nPlease allow us to be able to fight with all evil and separate it out, and please allow us to separate good and evil and to stand in the position of goodness.
\n\nPlease allow us to believe that Satan's evil will be liquidated, and things of goodness will remain, and please allow us to become those people who enter on the straight way and live in the midst of your glow.
\n\nWe pray in the name of the lord.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 19, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_4t">
We are praying earnestly to you, Father. First, we know that our minds and bodies must become sacrifices like the gold, frankincense and myrrh given by the wise men from the east.
\n\nWe know that it will not do unless we become sacrifices. Please allow us to offer our minds and bodies. Beloved Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will not allow us to become abominations before the altar.
\n\nThe more that we understand what you have chosen as your purpose of goodness and righteousness, and the more we think about your having once again sought out our unworthy selves, we cannot help but be contrite about our insufficiency in relation to you. We have let go of all our rituals, concepts and insistence on ideology, and since we have bowed down before you, Father, please help us.
\n\nFather! Please take responsibility for everything. Please receive our minds and bodies completely and take dominion over them, and please allow us to become people who are able to embrace the history of six thousand years and comfort your anguished heart. Beloved Father, we earnestly hope and desire that we will be able to unite, and as a unified sacrifice be able to bow before you in joy together with the many saints, and that you, the living God, will take dominion over the entirety of our minds and bodies.
\n\nFather! Please take pity on this people. We know that you have toiled through the long course of history in order to be able to love this people. We know that when you chose us, in order to reveal your will you had toiled in ways known to none.
\n\nWe know that the enmity of this people has penetrated into heaven, and we know that the enmity of all humankind on the earth has also penetrated heaven. Since we know that heaven is lamenting because there is no one to become a sacrifice representing the anguish of heaven and earth, please allow us to become sons and daughters who entreat you to resolve in your stead the enmity penetrating the entire universe today. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who will come forward and fight Satan in your stead.
\n\nPlease allow us to be able to sing your blessings unified around your one will by bringing our minds and bodies into harmony. And we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to be able to bow before you in gratitude for your blessing of liberation.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 12, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_5t">
Beloved Father!
\nOn this lonely course of restoration which cannot help but be trod whether one wants to or not, who is there who will shoulder again the burden of the destiny caused by the fall?
\n\nThrough the fall of our human ancestors, you came to embrace grief early, Father. And enmity remained in the minds and bodies of humankind. And we know that through the sinful history of the unfaithfulness of the Jewish people, this enmity came to affect the entire world. At this time when heaven and earth are permeated with complaints over this enmity, we earnestly hope and desire that you will open before us the path for us to go.
\n\nIn order to go on the path you will lead us, first we must find a place where our lives can be at rest. After that, our minds and bodies must become your place to find peace, and then we know that your love for which we long must dwell in our minds and bodies.
\n\nOh, Father of compassion, Father of love, benevolent Father, oh my Father who has worked so hard to reveal your will, please reside in the midst of us! Since we have come before your knees, ashamed, Father, with our defiled minds and bodies just as they are, please bear with us.
\n\nIf you do not bear with us, if you do not become our standard for going forth, then there is no one more pitiful than us. Oh, Father! Because you have been our eternal ideal, our eternal hope, and our eternal life, and you know the situation we are facing today and the entire will we are hoping for, it will not do unless you appear to us and take dominion personally.
\n\nFirst, please allow us to become people with elements of the original nature and essence which can receive your dominion, and please allow our minds and bodies to be able to be captured by your words of bidding and your work of construction. And then, in front of your glory, please allow to be revealed your direct works of power which will make us unable not to surrender even if we don't want to.
\n\nAnd we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will take dominion over all our minds and bodies and that you will remove from us the roots of sin which you cannot endure. Since the waves of death are trying to sweep us away, please block all those things. And if personal enmities have permeated us, please remove them.
\n\nAre there any minds, or wills, or thoughts, or insistence on ideologies left that are centered on ourselves? Oh Father, please appear as the reality of power and please only you take dominion and assert yourself, and mold all our minds so that we may be able to resemble your external form.
\n\nWe earnestly ask you to allow this, and we have prayed these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 3, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_6t">
Father!
\nWe know that at this time it will not do unless our minds and bodies resemble you completely. So please embrace us to your eternal bosom and in order to realize your will, please let us inherit your heart which has loved billions of people. And please allow us to realize that this is the time when we must appear with hearts like yours.
\n\nThis land is the land where you toiled and shed blood, and because we know that this land is the land where humankind went the difficult path of the cross, the land where the people of the world went the course of Golgotha, Father, please lead us to come to realize by ourselves what kind of situation we are facing today.
\n\nIf we are going to acknowledge that we are following the footsteps of Jesus thirty-year life of suffering, then please lead us to clearly understand what kind of environment we are living in and what we must hope for and desire.
\n\nAt this time when the remaining battle of the cross has come right before our eyes, as individuals we know that we must have hearts that are aware that they can push aside all these sufferings and enmities, so, Heaven, please have pity on us at this time.
\n\nPlease lead us to feel our unworthiness, and guide us to feel our inadequacy by ourselves, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow this time to become a time when we can shed tears of anguish in front of you, Father, lamenting our own incompleteness.
\n\nAsking you to take dominion over all things, we have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 10, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_7t">
Oh Father of compassion! We earnestly hope and desire that you will bear with our situation of not being able to think of the authority, honor or situation of our Father who has such an aching heart, but rather we are living by receiving the power of your compassion.
\n\nSince we, who are here on this dark earth of death, know that without grace and the power of life, we would never be able to offer the glory of victory to you, oh Father, please allow us your promised grace. We earnestly hope and desire that as you turn out the providence, you will reveal your entire will and that you will reveal it to us.
\n\nInadequate as we are, how dare we show ourselves before you? How could we raise our heads before heaven? Even if we died a hundred million times, we are beings who deserve it. We are held prisoner by the chains of sin, and we are people who deserve to go through the suffering of the judgment.
\n\nTherefore, we hope for your merciful love and hope for your grace, and since we have prostrated ourselves before you with minds that report truthfully on their own, we have laid out before you everything that we have. Please allow us to do away with anything that is not proper, and to maintain the mentality you grant us, and we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will guide us to be able to appeal to heaven for your mighty grace.
\n\nFather! Please take pity on us. In order to find and go this way which others deny, we remember times that filled our minds with sorrow, and we know that there were times filled with worries and trials; accordingly, Father, even if this is a position that others deny, may the grace of your recognition alone pour down on us.
\n\nBeloved Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you alone will embrace us, that you alone will comfort us, and that you alone will counsel us. Among ignorant humankind if there is a person who can understand the anguish of heaven, oh Father, even if he were struck with the distress of anguish a hundred million times, we know that he would be victorious without fail.
\n\nPlease let us be sons and daughters who experience your anguish through our minds and bodies, and please let us experience the concern your heart felt when dealing with the earth, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will establish us as sons and daughters who can fulfill our duties.
\n\nFather! Please do not let us remain, in our ignorance, in a position that can lead to ruin. Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will give us the grace of being able to wait impatiently for your love and compassion alone and being able to eliminate the stronghold of evil by exploding it ourselves. We earnestly ask that you will allow our minds and bodies to be captured by the grace of your love and the will you have bid us.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in die name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nApril 14, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_8t">
Oh Father!
\nPlease don\'t leave us only to ourselves. We know that this world is an environment of failure where humankind has walked a historical course. We know that faith alone is not enough, nor are we alone enough. We hope that you will let us have a universal ideology and truth which will allow us to find the origin of our lives and to transcend ourselves.
\n\nAnd at the same time that we have truth, we know that we must establish a standard where heaven can be present with us. Please guide us to be able to go forth from the position of being able to call you "Father," Father, from a position of knowing that completely through a course of absolute faith.
\n\nJesus told us to seek him through the relationship of the bride and bridegroom. Internally, it is the heart that can understand circumstances, and if it is the word that allows circumstances to be understood internally, then please let us understand the word; and through that word, please let us know truth and heart. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to form a relationship, Father, which through a heartistic ideology allows us to know even your heart.
\n\nFather! Today please do not allow us to remain in our terribly narrow circumstances. Please don't allow us to become foolish and lose the totality of our value by leaning towards small works. Please allow us to see your greater heavenly nature while we adore your greater grace.
\n\nThat nature has not yet appeared in any form on this earth. And if heaven is hoping to reveal that nature through us, please allow us to move and go forth before you with a bit greater standard of faith and a proper mentality and feeling. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will guide us to be able to fulfill that responsibility.
\n\nFather! Please pour out the final grace that you wish to allow at this time. Through sacrificial lives, as the sons and daughters of our father of glory, please let us receive our eternal father's entire ideology of faith as the ideology for our daily lives today. We earnestly ask you to guide us to become victorious people who are able to be proud in front of all people of having accomplished that.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nSeptember 8, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_9t">
Please, may your deep internal nature of love be present in our minds and bodies. Since we have been embraced in your bosom, Father of love, please pour out upon your sons and daughters the joy of love which is hidden in the fullness of your life.
\n\nIf it seems we are not able to experience your preciousness and your heart, Father, we know that we will not be able to erase all our relationships of sin which are not proper. Oh Father of compassion, now in this one moment please allow us to be submerged in your love alone, Father, and please allow us to give our full devotion to your providence.
\n\nMy Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become loving sons and daughters who adapt ourselves to your having dominion, and whose minds can experience the original will and can feel the original heart, and who can more than fulfill our entire responsibility which has been established on the earth.
\n\nWhen we walked along rugged paths until today, when our hearts were sorrowful, we know that you were sorrowful before we were, and even when we were lamenting on our own in the pits of despair, we know that in our stead you were reflecting on all our sins and you were fighting in our stead in the instances of Satan\'s accusations.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire beloved Father, that you will allow us to feel in our minds and bodies that even if we offer our entire mind and body as a sacrifice to you at this time, Father, there is no way we can repay the grace of our Father who has worked so hard until now.
\n\nOh Father! From among many people, you have called and raised up our unworthy selves. How dare we present ourselves in front of you who have called and raised up this people, from among the many peoples. We have nothing to be proud of. Now what we want is to become people who are able to feel anguish together with you when you feel anguish, and who can feel joy when you feel joy, and whose minds and bodies explode for the will when you desire it.
\n\nFather, please protect us. May you alone be our center, May you alone be our Lord. Even though we have nothing to be proud of on the earth, and the place we are standing is a lonely place, since we know that the path we are on is rough, Father, please accept as and take dominion.
\n\nEven if we collapse in the battle of the Last Days, please be comforted through the sound of our voice calling, "Father."
\n\nSince we are your sons and daughters who have received the counsel of your love, and have determined and pledged to go out and fight again,
\n\nFather, please do not turn our minds and bodies over to Satan.
\n\nPlease embrace us in your realm of love, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will hold and lead us to the end, Father, so that through us you will be able to realize the garden you desire and bring into being the day when all people can rejoice. We are earnestly hoping that you will allow us to remain as centers who can be proud in relation to your will, and who can become like light in relation to your will when we offer everything we have now.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nSeptember 22, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_10t">
If it were not for you, Father, we could not be comforted. And we know that you cannot allow us your glory. By any chance are our minds moved by sin and sometimes asserting ourselves? We know the historical truth that acting centered on oneself became an act that betrayed the moral laws of heaven.
\n\nAccordingly, we lay everything out before you and earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to receive the grace of sanctification. And then please allow our mind to manifest itself as your mind and our body to manifest itself as your body. And please let the desire you have take the place of our desire, and today please allow our fighting minds to be together with your mind which is fighting for the will you desire. And we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will give us the blessing of being able to serve your one will alone with an indomitable spirit.
\n\nUntil now the lives we have lived have been worldly, and we know we have not been able to come out front the midst of the falseness of sin. Now please allow us to find absolute value which transcends time and space, and through one center please allow us to offer everything we have to the will through which you seek to reveal that value.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to establish a reciprocal standard where our minds can be harmonized in front of that will and that we will be able to have the joy of being able to sing in the midst of heaven's glory.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 20, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_11t">
We know that because humankind is living buried in sin, it is easy for us to consider everything centered on ourselves, and it is easy for us to establish wills which are not the Will and to follow them as if they were the Will. Oh, Father, please make us completely realize that we are like that.
\n\nThen please allow us to establish complete centers for ourselves and to go forward on the path of your eternal life. And we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who can fight with Satan and go forward rejecting everything for the sake of the Will you alone desire.
\n\nWe still do not know where the standard is that can guide ignorant humankind. We know that there have been many times we have worried about ourselves and prayed. Oh, Father, please make us realize how unworthy we are.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will guide us to be able to go forward to the final point of victory following the laws of the principle. We know that at this time, too, Satan is confusing us through intrigues and slander in order to block the blessings you want to give us.
\n\nOh, Father, please lead us to be those who can push aside all those things and fight with Satan and go forward. And furthermore, we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who are able to form an intimate relationship with you within the realm of the providence and go forward.
\n\nFurthermore, since we have to face the last days, please allow us to have a new sense of discrimination which can distinguish all things. Please allow us to realize that everything in the environment centered around ourselves is something to test us. And please do not allow those things to become satanic elements. We earnestly request and desire, Father, that you will guide us and protect us so that we will not be unworthy to reveal your glory by ourselves treading upon and going over those things.
\n\nIn order to find and establish the day of victory that can reveal your glory, Father, at this time please allow us to be able to have in our minds and bodies the power and strength that can face Satan and fight with new resolution and determination. We earnestly hope and desire that your infinite love and care will be revealed to all the people of the earth and to this country and this people. We have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 11, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_12t">
We know that if your mind and Adam\'s mind had become one, and your will and Adam\'s will had become one, today\'s anguished history with the two worlds fighting would not have happened.
\n\nToday your anguished and sorrowful mind is in our minds. Our original minds recognize this, and only the fallen nature, which is centered on itself, is denying that this is true. Since we know that we are always facing this kind of battle between our original minds and evil minds, please allow us to control our own minds ourselves and become one with your mind, Father. Since the time is coming near for the struggle of having to control our own wills and become one with your will, oh Father, please bear with us if we have a mind that cannot become one with you. Please allow us to make effort to forget everything and to become one with your will and mind alone.
\n\nWe know that a mind that is one with your mind could not be exchanged for hundreds of millions of dollars. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will lead us to be able to fight and go forth, and hold on and go forth to attain that one thing, even if we have to sacrifice everything.
\n\nFather! This time now is a very difficult time, and Satan is blocking our minds which want to become one. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to establish a new condition of sacrificing ourselves for others for the sake of establishing your will.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to be equal to the providential history which can broaden the glory of your will and that we will be able to fight while looking up towards your will. We earnestly hope and desire that you will please allow us to realize our desire for our minds and wills to appear as one before your altar as another condition for a relationship with you and as a condition to subjugate Satan.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nNovember, 10, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_13t">
This time now is like the time when the Israelite people were in confusion 2,000 years ago, the time when the Messiah had to come. We are now facing such a time, and we know that we are facing a time when it will be difficult to discriminate between what is true and what is false.
\n\nUntil now there have been many teachers who worked hard in the course of past history, and we have followed many leaders, but today we have lost the center of our minds on which we should depend. We know that you know that today humankind is facing confused living circumstances. Therefore, Father, please control our lives, please control our minds, and please control our ideas so that we may have a joyful time when we can live depending on our natural disposition.
\n\nToday as we live in such a confusing world, please allow our minds and bodies to spread this idea. Please let our bodies witness to it through our daily lives, and please allow us to be grateful in our minds. And we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to be able to receive the blessing of being your sons and daughters who have fulfilled the mission of restoration, and be complimented as the sons and daughters you desired. Father! Please supervise our minds.
\n\nMore than anyone else, our minds know better the way we must go. Since our minds desire to go along the original true path, Father, please grant to us the truth and the religion that are able to realize our mind's desire, and please guide us to be able to accomplish the will of the providence of salvation. Since the entire religious world is divided into many denominations, and is in confusion, Father, please take pity on it.
\n\nWe know that the problem here is not which religious body, or which group, or which denomination. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to understand that the main point of truth and the entirety of truth is having an internal heart that you are able to recognize and going forth with an earnest heart that can experience your mind. Now even if we run into adversity, the time is near when your will must be realized. Therefore, please allow us to go through the adversity and to have minds and bodies that can see your glory. And we earnestly hope and desire that you will guide us to become your sons and daughters who even alone win over adversity and while worrying about your heart, unknown to others, raise up an altar, and offer everything in order to resemble your mind and in order to experience your heart.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMay 18, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_14t">
Father!
\nWe know well that without even knowing the direction they must go, many people have struggled along the terribly anguished course of history in order to find you.
\n\nYou appear to exist, and then seem not to exist. You seem to be living together with history, and yet, Father, we have not been able to have a clear understanding that you really exist. You seem to be together with our minds, but with deeply sorrowful minds, we are looking at you as our father who cannot establish regulations like a real being. We know well that you created the entire universe through an idea of goodness, and you gave humankind a true conscience, and you gave us the amazing blessing of being able to experience that idea of goodness through the faculties of intellect, emotion and will.
\n\nAnd we also know well that the fact cannot be denied that the nature of your existence comes to be felt within the time limits of a certain age. Each time we long for your internal nature which comes to our minds, we cannot help but be captured by an anguish we ourselves don\'t understand. We can only lament over our wretched appearance. We know that you have led us into this situation, as a historical, heartistic action to lead us to eternal life.
\n\nWe want to know you, Father, who behind die scenes in history sought us through your heart and mind in order to arrange history into one realistic ideology. We are eagerly looking forward to establishing your mind as the ideology for our lives and our daily lives. But because we do not clearly know the value of your existence, we do not know the value of our daily lives, and without knowing the value of our lives we are faced with the wretched situation of having to struggle today and tomorrow. Therefore, please take pity on each of us who are wandering on the brink of death.
\n\nNow, Father, we know that the time has come that it will not do unless you stretch out your hand of love. That wave of love will have to reach the situation around us and even into our hearts. We know that this is the time when we must restore the authority of your heart, the leading authority you alone have. We know that we will reach the time when we must fight centered on mind, so please allow us to become people who have tolerance and can open our closed minds.
\n\nThe time has come when we must become sons and daughters who are ready to bend our bodies and bow before you. Therefore, we earnestly hope that you will allow us to become people who see your outstretched hand manifest before us and that you will allow us to be able to hear the voice of our father who is knocking at the door of our minds.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 18, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_15t">
Oh Father!
\nPlease take pity on us. Without your grace we are pitiful people who can do nothing but die. Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will not cast us aside and leave us, but will embrace us in your bosom of mighty love.
\n\nUntil now your sons and daughters who have been following have not thought this path of struggle was difficult; but if it were not for your love, we could only have wandered, so please take pity on us. And please embrace us in your mighty love and please let us be able to experience the grace of glory which you permit to us.
\n\nWe know that everything centered on humankind has an end, but every act centered on you continues forever, Father. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will remove everything centered on humankind and allow only things centered on you alone to appear out of the gardens of our hearts.
\n\nThe more our earnest minds search for you, Father, and the more we long for your internal nature and as we desire more to go closer to your mind, there are many times when we forget the fact that your great love is here among us without our knowing it.
\n\nPlease do not allow us to forget the fact that you are always together with us, to say nothing of when we are busy or in a hurry.
\n\nAnd we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will not allow us to forget the fact that you are always living together with us.
\n\nFather! Please look upon us with compassion. Please take responsibility for our lives and take responsibility for our hope. If you would grant your hope to us, please grant us the strength to be able to fight together with you until we make that garden of hope our own. And we hope and desire, beloved Father, that you would protect us so that we do not become exhausted in the battle with the enemy.
\n\nSince our hands and feet have been wounded while we made our way through the world of death, at this time we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will join hands with us and embrace us. Because we know that if you say you do not know us there would be no one more wretched than we are, Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will please hold and comfort us.
\n\nIf it were not your command, we would not have been able to give up even our lives; but we have followed the command you have given and gone forth because it is called a true path. "Therefore, Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will not cast us away but rather embrace us at this time. Father!
\n\nPlease look upon us with compassion. Please allow us to feel to our very bones that if it is not you, nothing will be accomplished, and if it is not your will, it will not be accomplished, and if it is not your work, it will not be accomplished.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to keep in our lives the work that you left, the will that you left, and the hope that you left, and that you will allow us to fight to the end, and to appear as your high-spirited sons and daughters.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 22, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_16t">
Greeting this holy day we come before your being, Father, with bowed heads. Oh father of love, father of compassion, father of magnanimity, please bear with us.
\n\nOur minds want to resemble your mind, and our bodies want to resemble your external form. We are not able to accomplish that because we don\'t know how. Therefore, please inform us through our minds and give us experience through our bodies. We earnestly hope to be able to bow before you, Father, as those who have taken the example of your internal nature.
\n\nIf it seems there are sons and daughters who are not proper before your will, please seek them out personally and instruct them. Our ears are dim, and our eyes are dim. We do not know how to hear your words, and we do not know how to look upon you. Please let us sense in our minds and bodies that having to make us hear and having to make us see is more sorrowful for you than for us, more heartbreaking for you than for us, and more frustrating for you than for us.
\n\nYou have beckoned to us hundreds of millions of times, but we did not know how to respond, and you called out to us tens of thousands of times, but we did not know how to hear you. Then how could we not be ashamed to stand before you? Even so, we hear your voice calling us to come, and even so we know that you are beckoning and calling to us, and we fall down on our knees. We are the pitiful people among the pitiful. We believe that you know that we are those who more than anyone else have no place to depend on. "Therefore, even though we appear crude, you will have to seek us out and hold us, reaching out with love.
\n\nOur eyes are dim and our bodies wounded, and even though we are in a position of not being able to know the essence of life, Father, please embrace us personally with love. We earnestly hope and desire that you will stop our tired footsteps, turn our minds from dejection to joy, and comfort us.
\n\nEven as sorrow is handed down, we know it is because this is a fallen world that you are caused to feel sorrow. Satan is blocking our path, and because you know that he is sweeping away the world through the power of death, you did not leave the responsibility up to us, but have taken on the responsibility alone and have gone forward facing and fighting the enemy, Father.
\n\nThe more our minds revere you as that kind of father, the more your mind will want to forgive us and forgive our faults. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that through that heart, you will once again seek us out.
\n\nWe regret having become sinners, and we weep. Our hearts are indignant hearts and our tears are flowing, and when with earnest hearts our minds repent, we realize that you have borne with us for 6,000 years, Father, and today at this time also you seek to relate to us with a heart of compassion.
\n\nPlease knock on the doors of our hearts as we weep. Please remove the thoughts and assertions of all the ideologies that have been stained by sin until now. And please let us sense your life in our minds and bodies. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow this to be a time when we can experience heaven's heart of painstaking circumstances, heaven's heart of love, and heaven's grace of love which we have not been able to feel, and we can form the kind of relationship where you can call us your sons and daughters.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nApril 19, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_17t">
Father!
\nWe have realized that when we are trying to think of a new work, we are not able to even think about it in the places where we have been doing things until now. We have realized that until we stop the flow of history and take a moment when we can think, we cannot awaken ourselves even though we want to.
\n\nWe know that we cannot be aroused from this sleeping appearance without receiving new stimulation. Therefore, Father, please continuously shock us anew so that we may be able to put aside the historical relationships we have. We know that we will not be able to be awakened if we do not have stimulated minds; therefore, please allow us to become beings who find such minds and know how to respect them.
\n\nIn each age you sent a responsible person who could awaken us, Father. You looked upon fallen humankind, and since you held on with your sorrowful heart and let them live and go, Noah lived and went that way, and Moses, too, and Jesus also did that.
\n\nOh Father! Please give us the shock of a new feeling at the bottom of our hearts. Please let us go beyond ourselves and experience your sorrow, and please give us minds that can be concerned for the people who are being swept into the world of death. If there is a person with this kind of mind, he is a person who can obtain the liberation of the people.
\n\nAnd furthermore, if there is a person who has a mind that is clinging to the world and worrying about it, he is a person who will obtain the grace of worldwide liberation. And furthermore, if there is a person who knows how to be worried about cosmic liberation, he will not be ruined together with history. We know that he is a person who will leave a new history to the world.
\n\nTherefore, today please do not let us become people who reveal our feelings and cling to ourselves and cry. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become people who represent your earnest heart as you look at us, Father, and please let us go towards the good for which the whole is hoping.
\n\nPlease let us feel in your stead the mind that was anxious that we might not follow and that humankind might fall. Please let us follow your example and let us know how to look at the people and look at the world, worried that those who are following might fall, and worried that those who have fallen might collapse and die.
\n\nIf there were sons and daughters who could look at you and say, "Father: I am here, and I have taken responsibility for your heart, so please rest," we know that kind of scene would mean that history is going in a new direction. Please let us become those people who know how to go forward having made all sorts of preparations to be able to begin in a new direction, and please let those of us who should begin in that direction, who must awaken make a new decision and determination and pledge in our minds according to the appearance of the historical screams of misfortune. We earnestly ask you to let us become those who know how to be awake as heaven is awake, and sorrowful or joyful together with the moral laws of heaven and with history.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nApril 19, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_18t">
Father of compassion! Father of love!
\nIf you just leave these pitiful people as they are, they will never be able to get out from under the shadow of death. What is there for those of us in this situation to be proud about and how can we come before you saying we are right? What do we possess that we could come before you defending ourselves?
\n\nWe have nothing. The only thing we have is our inadequacy, and the only thing we feel is our awe-stricken mind. Therefore, please have compassion, Father, for these people of death who are hoping for your compassion, your benevolence and your mercy. All of us are looking towards heaven, eagerly waiting for your hand to reach out to us. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will have compassion for us.
\n\nThe time of the providence is hastening the Last Days, and the waves of death have swept around us and without any exception seek to swallow us. We know that you know we are faced with a chaotic environment, and your heart which worries about us remains on this earth, as do the footprints of your hard work. We know that as you look at all this, your mind is inexpressibly anxious; therefore, Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will lead us and have compassion for us at this time.
\n\nIf we have lonely hearts, let us empty them out at this time and we must change them and take on your heart. If we are sorrowful and have inexpressibly frustrated hearts, we are in the pitiful situation of having to exchange them for your heart of joy and life.
\n\nOh Father who knows this, in spite of our being those who should take responsibility in your stead and relieve you of your difficult position, you are taking care of our difficult situation. And we earnestly hope and pray, Father, that you will bear with the fact that we are within the fallen realm and have to receive strength from you again.
\n\nFather! Please allow our hearts to be able to communicate with each other. We, who have been languishing in the realm of death and who had no destined relationship and were not acquainted, have gathered together referring to each other as the members of one family. Since we have gathered together adoring the idea of your heavenly providence, Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will have compassion and come to us.
\n\nCould anyone have confidence in front of you, Father? Since you have said that you have confidence, we have hoped to have confidence, too, and since you have said that you feel this wav, we too hope to feel that. If this is false, Father, please bear with us, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will personally take dominion.
\n\nEven when coping with a sad situation relating with humankind, your sons and daughters could not have a situation where they could speak out their minds, and even when faced with a difficult situation, they had no family members with whom they could open their hearts. We earnestly hope and desire that you will take pity on them.
\n\nWe know that in the world connected to your heart, we move transcending the distances of time and space. Therefore, at this time also, connected to that same heart, if the mind of heaven moves please let our minds be moved as well. Please inspire us by reaching out with your grace for all, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will connect us to your heart again.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 7, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_19t">
Before we report anything to you, Father, you already know our hearts. Please allow us to feel that this is a time when heaven is observing everything about us.
\n\nOh Father! You have gone through a historical course of such toil. Today please appear right in front of us and groom us through new words. Please relate to us with a new heart. We intend to sweep away every unfaithful aspect, and with childlike minds offer everything we have before you, our Father, whom we respect.
\n\nWe lay down before you, Father, all the rituals, ideologies and concepts of the world, and we ask that you will allow us to have meek, humble minds like those of children. May we have humble minds which are able to be molded as you would mold us, and since we seek to offer ourselves before you, please accept us. May the triune God act.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and pray that you will allow this place where we are bowing to you with rejoicing hearts, guarded by heavenly forces and angels, to become an altar of wondrous blessing which can lead our whole lives to victory.
\n\nWe have left everything up to you. Please let us open our hearts and all the ideologies we have before you. We hope that in that way you will allow us to be able to change everything we have into your things.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 5, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_20t">
Father!
\nWe see that although the many people living on the earth are at the point of death, the present state of affairs is that they are pushing themselves forward and they are busy bragging before the universe.
\n\nIn this kind of world, can one dare to be proud of oneself? Can one assess one\'s own value highly? When we recall our hearts and weigh them in silence, we will not be able to deny that we are faced with a false situation.
\n\nFather! Today what are our minds imagining, and what are we seeking to rise up to? The time has come that we must realize that now our minds are not able to be ours and our bodies are not able to be ours either. The time has come that we must recognize that we are in a miserable situation where we cannot put ourselves forward and be proud of ourselves.
\n\nWe cannot make the final decision about the value of our minds and bodies. Please allow us to feel how miserable we are who cannot lead even our own selves to the goal through the course of the situation that has occurred. If we have life, it is not because of us, and if there is an ideology that leads our minds in the direction of goodness, please allow us to feel the fact that it also originates not in ourselves but in something else.
\n\nFather! Today please allow us to realize that you are searching for a victorious person who knows how to take mastery over his ego and how to rid himself of the conceit which made him want to put himself forward and raise himself up and which made him intent on establishing and justifying himself. We have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 19, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_21t">

    </string>
</resources>