<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="pr_unification_1t">
Father!
\nThis people has been a people that has gone hungry, that has had no place to lean, that has had no hope, and that has had nothing to speak proudly about. Each time this people has depended on something, they were captured by it and trampled upon by it. For these reasons we cannot deny that your sorrow must have been great while dealing with this people.
\n\nWhen we look at the history of this people, through the invasions of other peoples there were so many complicated and twisted situations. At each of those times, the common people were torn apart, trampled upon, and pursued, and you know that they were placed in terrible circumstances
\n\nWe, who have inherited the flesh and blood of this people, are gathered here. The time has come for us to appeal to heaven to heal the grief of this people. This people has been placed in wretched circumstances, and at this crossroads of life and death, the people are running around in utter confusion. In this situation who will become the central figure?
\n\nThe time has come for us to sing the song of liberation and raise up a beacon of new hearts. We know that we have reached the era when we must sound the bugle to march. Father, please gather together the young people who understand your will.
\n\nGather together your sons and daughters who are shedding blood and tears while wailing for this people.
\n\nWe are not a group that appeals to others while following some system of thought. More than that, we look forward to being the first to die so that we could become the fertilizer that will allow new shoots to rise above this people.
\n\nWe pledge before you that we will become that kind of people. Therefore Father, before we speak, please let us experience your heart, and may our eager hearts be filled only by you; please melt our hearts. Please allow each of us to reappraise ourselves to determine our point in existence, and to appear in a new resurrected form.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 19, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_2t">
Father!
\nPlease take pity on and extend the benevolence of your mercy to this people. But if through this group which is being driven out and pursued you have something you desire to realize, then please drive this people out and have them pursued even more.
\n\nWe know that in the midst of this situation you are hoping that a group of young people will appear who will have a sense of responsibility to take on the suffering of this people and to take on their difficulties in their stead.
\n\nPlease allow us to know the loneliness of this people and this nation and your loneliness which moves you to tears as you see humankind struggling on the frontline of death. This loneliness has been pent up in hearts. Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will please let us realize that a frightful time is coming to this people, a time of heaven`s grief, together with sighs and weeping joined by blood.
\n\nWe know that before this people should go through difficulties we should go through them first, and before humankind should go through difficulties, we should go the way of the cross first. In the midst of a chaotic environment Jesus also walked the path toward the palaces of heaven, and he told us to take that path.
\n\nWe know that this is the content of the Gospel which Jesus left us, and as we stand at the vanguard of the course of history, please let us become those who can take responsibility for everything. Don\'t let us be those who collapse or fall apart when we collide with something. Each time we collide with something please let us form a strong heartistic relationship with you, Father. We earnestly pray that you will help us become those who can appear before you.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 11, 1960
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_3t">
Until you found this Korean peninsula, we know that the course of history which you struggled to establish was a history stained by tears and sweat and blood.
\n\nWithout others knowing, you chose this people, and we know that our having been driven into a pitiful position was due to the will of your mighty providence. We know well that we must attend you as our Father in front of all your peoples.
\n\nPlease allow us to realize once again that we are those who must know that each time this people walked a difficult course of history, the father who held and wept over his many collapsing children as their eyes filled with bitter tears, that father is our father; that sorrowful father is our father; that suffering father is our father.
\n\nYou have personally connected to us, reaching out with life and love; you have sought your sons and daughters; you are the pioneer of pioneers; you have done works in person as the king of pioneers, but today the 30 million people of this nation do not know you. This people should be looking forward to the day of attending you, but they are not. Please bear with them.
\n\nWe know well that in the past and the present the people who were called by you, our Father, have left behind historical stains as we passed through each age.
\n\nPlease forgive the fact that although the more this people repents for the course of its history the more it should be able to receive your heart, it is not in a position to do that. We cannot help but feel that we cannot even raise our eyes before you because we know how great your efforts were to find this pitiful people.
\n\nFather! Please create a relationship of life with this pitiful people. Please let us be able to be proud of having been a people who suffered; please let us be able to be proud of having been a pitiful people. Please let the day come quickly when this people, who had nothing to be proud of and had nothing at all to depend on in the world, can be proud together with heaven.
\n\nWhile earnestly hoping for and desiring this, we have humbly prayed these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 1, 1961.
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_4t">
Today when you look at this world, Father, is there a place somewhere that gives you joy? Humankind is not thinking about which place will become that kind of central point. Moreover, this nation, this people who should take responsibility for all the historical problems and who should lead, this people does not know.
\n\nFather! Multitudes of people are looking for their own happiness, and many nations are seeking their own nations` profits. All those things are being realized in ways that do not follow your will; rather, they are increasing your sorrow and enmity, and are ravaging your heart. We earnestly hope and pray, Father, that you will take pity on these nations and people who don`t know what they are doing.
\n\nYou know that historical sorrow and historical grief have sunk deep within this people and us. Because your desire remains to resolve these historical resentments, we know that we who understand this cannot help but come forward. I know that there is no one seeking to make a new history for this people or weeping for the sake of this nation and this people.
\n\nBut now that I have gathered unification workers who seek to take on this task, Father, please carry out your providence through them. Even though they may not seem like people you can believe, still they have heard your voice calling in the new age. With trembling and sincere hearts, with impatient hearts, they worry that they might once again bequeath grounds for grief which you do not desire. Because of that, Father, please look upon them with compassion.
\n\nFather! You must remember the grief of this people. You must take responsibility for the wretchedness of this people. I earnestly hope and desire that you will not take back from this people the promise that you made to them. I earnestly hope and desire that the tears of this people and their suffering will become conditions resolving the grief remaining in restoration.
\n\nFather! Because the time is coming when a final decision will have to be made through us about the will and idea that you are hoping for in the Last Days, I earnestly hope that you will not allow us to be found lacking during the remaining course of restoration while we are carrying out this mission on the level of the people.
\n\nI have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 27, 1964
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_5t">
Father!
\nYou have to remember many peoples. But because this Korean people is to be pitied, please give this people your blessing at this time. By comforting this devastated Korean peninsula, please make its people able to go forward towards the new world and gather them in the realm of the side of heaven.
\n\nKorea is the nation of the new covenant, the nation where you can come. We know that it is the nation that must prepare the altar of Abel in relation to your new will, your desire for this nation is for it to offer total devotion to you, Father, and that is the duty of this nation in relation to you.
\n\nWe know well that that is the duty of this land, the many nations and the many good spirits. Please pour out your love and compassion so that this people and this nation may stand properly in relation to your Will. We earnestly hope that you will make this people become a people necessary to the building of the Kingdom of Heaven as the third Israel of hope.
\n\nMay all nations follow the example of the duty of loyalty and filial piety towards heaven which this nation has established. We know how much you have longed for the day to come when humankind will offer its loyalty to you, your many children who are gathered here feel those things deeply in their hearts and are eagerly desiring for that Will to be realized.
\n\nFather, please protect and raise them up to be victorious in the final battle. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow this people and this nation to able to attend you when you come into your glory.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow them to become a nation and people like that. We know well that the people on earth, of course, and centered on the earth, the many spirits in the spirit world are participating in the returning resurrection, and they are eagerly anticipating the resolution of their grief.
\n\nIn that way, with their cooperation, we will attend you, Father, in the place where Cain and Abel have become one and where the world of your glory is realized. Please let the entire heavens and earth come to live in the midst of your love and joy. We earnestly hope and desire that you will give us greater strength and ability so that in a place of peace we can realize a nation and a cosmos that celebrates your glory.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 2, 1966
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_6t">
Father!
\nWe know that Korean history has been a continuous flow of sorrow. We know that you have been directing us along this path of the worst Golgotha from the beginning until now because that was the destiny of this nation.
\n\nFather! When we think that each time this people appealed to you and each time their eyes could have been opened their history has continued on as a history of defeat, we think that from the August 15th liberation until now, we have overcome difficult circumstances and we have entered a realm where we can give ourselves to you completely.
\n\nThere is no new hope in front of this people, and if you had not been their source who established their beginning, you would not have been there for them, and this people would have met a tragic end.
\n\nFather, you have allowed this people to lose their nation, and have allowed them to lose righteousness, and furthermore, you have divided this people completely at the 38th parallel. But we have come to know that all this was your will in order for us to be able to find absolutely everything.
\n\nWe know that behind this people is your providential guiding hand. Now once more, please allow us to straighten ourselves up and to raise before you an altar for our atonement, and after we have received forgiveness for all the sins of our ancestors, please allow us to appear before this age in new full attire.
\n\nEarnestly hoping that you will allow us to appear as people of courage in this age when the Promised Land is calling, we have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 13, 1966
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_7t">
Father!
\nPlease remember this nation of 30 million people. This people is a people with deep internal feelings, a people with so many situations tangled together. It is a people that can harmonize with your love, Father, and can long for you.
\n\nFather, please do not let the stains of the blood and tears your young children have shed while being persecuted all over this Korean peninsula become foundations for the accusation of Satan. On those holy foundations, raise up descendents whom you can call one by one and greet the day of glory. We are earnestly hoping and desiring that you will let us be able to sing praises for the victory of joy and attend you, Father, having prepared a holy sanctuary.
\n\nBecause this is our hope, we will have to devote ourselves to it today and tomorrow, and we will have to devote ourselves to it for the rest of our lives. Therefore, even if we die, we will have to die at the point where we have offered ourselves totally. But because we know that we should not be worrying about the problem of whether we live or die, we are earnestly hoping and desiring that you will make our concern for the Will which has not been realized be our everything.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nAugust 13, 1967
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_8t">
Father!
\nFirst, we would like to thank you that among the many peoples and lands you remembered this pitiful people who have been driven out so many times. We thank you that for your holy Will you chose the lonely mountains and rivers of this Korean peninsula, and we thank you that you are making Korea the focus of your providence.
\n\nThe more we think about the fact that there are so few people who are able to devote themselves completely to this Will, we cannot help but feel more and more ashamed. But when we think about the fact that a father`s loving heart rests more with a handicapped child, we are hoping that you will forgive this people which has a historical background that could only cause you worry.
\n\nFather! The Unification children have gone through a history of struggles shedding blood and tears which others did not know about, having put up a boundary line of seven years until today. At times they were driven out; sometimes they wept smiting their breasts, or they held their empty stomachs; and sometimes they wept endless tears discussing your situation, Father.
\n\nLike this, all of the patriots of the past started with tears, but we could have a day when we could thank you for having reaped laughter rather than reaping tears. When we realize that it is because of your protection and all of your help, we cannot help but be even more grateful.
\n\nWe appeal to you with one heart to realize quickly the heaven and earth of freedom where we can attend you, Father, and when we can speak out our hearts which we want to proclaim proudly. We are earnestly hoping and desiring that you will accept all of our situations as we are bowing to you.
\n\nNo matter what anyone says, we are lonely people who have nothing. Only you are on our side; you alone are all that we have. We must realize that our living for you is a high and noble thing impossible to exchange for any amount of money in the world.
\n\nFather! Please let us be sincerely grateful for the fact that even though we are ugly, we have been placed in such a position today through the benefit of the age and the foundation of merit laid throughout all the lives of our ancestors.
\n\nWe are earnestly hoping and desiring that you will make us able to be grateful not from our own personal positions but rather from a historical position which extends through the past, present and future.
\n\nWe sincerely ask you to extend the glory of our victory and grace to all things, and we have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 24, 1967
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_9t">
Our Father of love!
\nSince the day that Adam fell, how great have your efforts been to find one person whom you could believe? And how much have you sought a person who would take responsibility and fight for you? How much have you longed for and sought one person who could inherit your full authority? We cannot help but feel again painfully that it was your anguish, Father, and the grief of human history that there was no such person on the earth.
\n\nFather, you have walked the path of such sorrowful historical turning points for the long time of 6,000 years. When in sorrow, you endured the sorrow, and from the position of taking responsibility for everything, you have continued until today without a moment of rest, humankind has been struggling along a dark, night path, but please let us remember again that you have been taking great pains for the providence of human history in a much greater darkness than that.
\n\nAnd we are earnestly hoping and desiring that you will wake us up to the fact of our shameful and sorry selves. And please let us realize how full of grief your way has been as you wandered and searched along the way of history for 6,000 years.
\n\nWhen we come to understand the fact that your toiling footsteps, which were driven out by so many nations and peoples and wandered and searched in this country and that country, in this city and that city, have stopped today here in the mountains and rivers of Korea, we feel once again that we are truly ashamed of ourselves in front of you.
\n\nThis people did not know the fact that centered on the Korean peninsula and its 30 million people, you were reaching out through your providence. Even our good ancestors who lived in this land and passed on did not know. But now we have reached the time when we can understand the fact that you have reached out through your Providence centering on this people.
\n\nWhen we think about this, we cannot help but confess that from the past until today this people stands in shame before you, Father. Even though we are unworthy to even dare to relate to you, you reached out to us in compassion and love, and you established us in your realm of the grace of love. Therefore, we sincerely request that you will let us become your children who humbly bow to you representing this people, these mountains and rivers, and all humankind.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 31, 1967
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_10t">
Father!
\nYour noble, precious and holy providential history has traced its path through the long history of humankind. Father, today once again you have raised us up. Please let us feel how pitiful and lonely your position is as you seek to take responsibility for the world.
\n\nWhen we think about the fact that now even at this moment there are groups all around the world who, out of concern for this teacher, are earnestly appealing to you, Father, with tears, while longing for this one distant corner of Korea, we come to realize clearly how frightening and terrible is the responsibility of the Unification Movement of Korea.
\n\nFather! Please pour down your blessings on those of the Unification Movement who are longing for Korea. Respecting Korea as their fatherland, they are shedding sweat, blood and tears for this land. When we think that they are together with us in the unification ideology, and these many groups desire their bones to be buried for the sake of this land, we realize we must unite them together into one and establish the one nation which you desire, and achieve one worldwide ideology.
\n\nAccordingly, until we realize that will, we must endure and endure and then still go on enduring. Following your example of silently enduring the tedious six-thousand-year course of history, we should go forward enduring in silence.
\n\nFather! Now we must go forward once again. We must go forward embracing the lonely situation of this people, and we must once again go forward feeling our way through the devastation of this nation.
\n\nThis people has been in situations that made it impossible not to become a pitiful people. But we thank you sincerely that while no one else knew it, you let us know first that the will of your providence, which should be praised all over the world, dwells in the midst of the Unification Movement.
\n\nFather! Please let us come to understand how hard you have worked during that time. Moved by their longing for you and feeling your heart, the members of this Unification Movement are embracing this people and struggling.
\n\nIn the end, please don\'t let their earnest hope be for nothing. Please let this people overcome this age and become a liberated people who can rush out to the world. Furthermore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow this people to become the third Israel which can build the Kingdom of Heaven throughout the entire world.
\n\nWe earnestly have prayed all these things in the names of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMay 2, 1969
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_11t">
Father!
\nAmong the many nations we know Korea is the nation that will dwell in the midst of the hearts of mankind in the future.
\n\nToday we were born in this land which can become the original homeland of all the people of the world. In this place we have longed for you, Father; we have heard your words; we have been educated; and we have been trained here while shedding tears. Please let us realize how precious and awesome a fact that is.
\n\nNow the time has come when this fact will unfold before our very eyes not just in words but in reality. Now when many people come to this place with hearts filled with longing for their original homeland, they should have such devotion that the very marrow of their bones melts for the sake of their original homeland.
\n\nThey should not want to leave; they should not be able to pick up their feet. And they should be able to weep. We earnestly hope and desire that you will let your children here understand that they must make those things happen.
\n\nAfter they have come here and gone home, please let them be able to feel again a tangible longing for this place based on what they really saw and felt, rather than from a position of imagining or conceptually longing for this place.
\n\nAnd please let the Korean family members of this original homeland clearly know that they must become your children who know how to be of such help to those members that they will provide them with relationships and motivation that will let them decide again that they want to come back here.
\n\nEven though we can\'t understand each other\'s languages and our living environments are different, we earnestly hope and desire that you will make us realize once more that through our facial expressions and feelings we must make them long for the land of their original homeland, and want to see it again, and furthermore, feel an internal relationship such that they want to live here.
\n\nWhile living in the original homeland, we must become your sons and daughters who thousands and ten thousands of times praise its historical value which you can remember, and who can speak proudly of it and reveal it to all people.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will let us realize that if we do not do that, we will remain as your reciprocal objects of sadness, and the original homeland will lose its value as the original homeland.
\n\nWe must not work from the position of hoping to realize your Will centered only on the Korean people. Please let us reach out in our lives and in our hearts to form relationships that will allow us to have relationships with the people of the world and to embrace the people of the world going beyond our own people and national borders.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMay 11, 1969
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_12t">
Father!
\nThere are more people than we can count who do not know the location of the nation of the original homeland where they can rest eternally. There are so many people who praise their countries as the original homeland, but there is no nation that can pride itself as the foundation of eternal joy and rest for generation after generation.
\n\nThere is no nation on this earth that you can claim as the place where you can rest for eternity. Father! The original nation and the original world which you have anticipated and sought remain as the foundation that you have worked so hard for.
\n\nOn that foundation, you would like to establish one center as compensation for all the work you have done. But when we think of how many true sons and daughters there are who you can be proud of, together with all of history, together with all the ages, and together with the future, we know that there are far too few who remain.
\n\nIn order to establish one nation that you could be proud of, through the thousands of years of the course of history, you testified through the mouths of the prophets. But due to the Israelite nation causing Jesus to face that tragic day, the Israelites have been driven out and pursued by many nations and people without leaving a trace.
\n\nNow even though it is late, centering on the many people who follow the destiny of your blessing, tying them together as one offering, we have received liberation as the people who can offer Israel and Jerusalem to you once again. But we know that that people could not cope with its mission to attend you, by preparing an altar for you in front of the whole world.
\n\nWhen we look at the circumstances of the present era, and when we think about the kinds of places of your providential history, the kinds of countries, the kinds of people through whom it was started, was carried out, and will be brought to a conclusion, then we realistically understand through your history of heart that it is not one of the advanced nations leading the many peoples of the world that does your work.
\n\nRather, it is a people that have a heart of loyalty and fidelity, a sincere heart towards you, Father, even while going through a more miserable historical course than any other people of the world. It is a people who are unchangeable in living for you.
\n\nIt is the kind of people whose loyalty to you does not change even if the age and the environment change. We know well that unless it is that kind of country, it cannot become the ideal people and nation you and humankind are looking for.
\n\nThrough your words we have come to know the manifestation of the third Israel, and we know that the people of the third Israel will occupy a more precious position than any great person of history or any famous person of this age.
\n\nBut in order to stand before you understanding that kind of value, we must offer all kinds of devotion and sacrifice ourselves until its real meaning permeates our flesh and bones. At this time please let us reflect once again and think about how many people have come forth to offer their loyalty in order to establish that nation and that people.
\n\nFather! Today through us you are testifying to this new historical relationship centered on Korea, and you must have internal matters that you want to fulfill through us and reveal through us, so please let each of our individual selves know how very careful we must be in the position we are in, and please let us know clearly that we must become your children who know how to fulfill the duty of loyalty and filial piety to you, Father.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMay 25, 1969
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_13t">
No one has known how difficult it was to go over the peaks of restoration which are so filled with grief. How often have you gone back and forth on that path until now, Father? When you carne you had hope that you would find a son of hope, but as you returned you were infinitely disappointed. How can we describe that, and with what words can we comfort you?
\n\nFather! We have come to know that you feel pity for this pathetic Korean people. Until now no one knew this, but now through our tragic course of history we have come to know that you have been in the background of our people with our history of blood and tears.
\n\nNow while reflecting on our history, we have come to think that the tragic history of this people symbolizes your tragic history, and this people`s having been surrounded and attacked by the powerful nations of the world resembles your lonely situation, Father.
\n\nWe know that you lamented over that, Father, and that by finding one nation, you were seeking to bless one person related to that country. We thought that it was our misfortune that we were in a position to dash out centered on your heart which is connected to the history of Korea. But now because we have come to realize that it is an infinitely fortunate thing, we cannot help but offer our gratitude to you, Father.
\n\nAfter the liberation, this people was not able to go the path it should have gone. Christianity, which represented this people, did not fulfill its responsibility, and this people is a nation without a name which still cannot participate in the U.N. Therefore, Father, please let the suffering of this nation end.
\n\nWe are your children, Father, and at the same time for the sake of that day when all the nations of the world will be able to bow their heads to this nation, we should know that we are also your ambassadors who have received solemn orders from heaven.
\n\nFather! Through the fifty years of my life I have come to realize that I was born with a destiny that cannot cast aside this people even if I die. Therefore, even along the way of rejection and even from the position of sorrow, loneliness, and being falsely accused, I have clung to you, Father, and comforted you. I thank you that you could bless me and let me have times when I could do that.
\n\nI have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 4, 1969
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_14t">
Father!
\nIn the present situation there remains a task that can be inherited in the historical work of heaven which is filled with grief. Therefore, please allow these young people to become those who solemnly praise this work, who consider themselves a movement of sons and daughters who can carry on your work, and who are considered by you as sufficient to the task.
\n\nThey are your young children who have gathered from all eight provinces. What is the path that they are taking? The university world, which from now on should take responsibility for the destiny of Korea, is in a state of chaos. But now we should initiate an assault here because this is the age when we should plant the flag of victory.
\n\nTherefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow them to become heaven`s princes and princesses who can fulfill their responsibilities as those who have received orders from you, Father, and who have missions that they must accomplish in this age. When they came here they looked simply like young people strolling along, coming in with a meaningless stride, but now as they go back, in their breasts they must carry a load which no one can move for them.
\n\nWe have learned through history that it is difficult to form a unified relationship without passing through an offering of blood and tears as sacrifices that can tread upon and go beyond the grief of this people. And we have learned that today in this age we cannot help but do that.
\n\nFather, please let the young people gathered here today become the brave people of heaven who can raise up a beacon and adapt themselves to you in order to completely fulfill their responsibility to offer their flesh and blood to this people and settle as anchors in every corner of the country. Father, we earnestly hope for and desire this.
\n\nPlease let them clearly understand that this is the mission of the young people of this age, a mission that they must fulfill in this age, and please let them be able to give their entire strength for this responsibility. I earnestly request and desire that you will let them become the sons and daughters of heaven who will clench their fists tightly and go forth to establish the bright new morning.
\n\nWe know that the remaining days are calling to us, and this tragic people is calling to us. Therefore, please let them become your children who offer all kinds of devotion to fulfill that responsibility even in their academic environment. I earnestly hope that you will let these young people become your children who live not for today but rather live for tomorrow.
\n\nWe earnestly hope that you will not let us become small-minded people in relation to the hope of tomorrow; rather, allow us to become strong and courageous champions of heaven. We earnestly request that you will allow us to become your children who leave a victory for the world, and can bequeath the victory when we go.
\n\nPlease let all of us determine that our minds will be strong and of good courage. Please let us pledge that we will offer our entire lives to you, Father, with hearts that can break rocks if we collide with them, and break apart steel if we collide with it.
\n\nWe earnestly request that you will allow us to go back with strong conviction. We ask that you will let us become your children who can receive your praise and who can receive your guarantee in the Kingdom of Heaven of tomorrow.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of our True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 4, 1964
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_15t">
Father!
\nThank you that heaven has taken care of this people. Now we must realize the fact that the opportunity for a new revival of heaven is corning to this land. When we realize that your hidden works were for your relationship with this people, we come to understand that this people is not pitiful, but rather more precious than any other in the world.
\n\nThis people appears to be covered with wounds, and this land appears to be devastated, but when we realize that heaven is permeating the center of this people and land, we must love this people. We must become your sons and daughters who can embrace this land of Korea, and who can sanctify it by shedding blood and tears, offering it up entirely as your holy altar.
\n\nFather! We must go forward protecting this people and this nation. Becoming sentries, we must protect this nation and this people. Because we know that there is no one who can protect this nation and this people at present, we have determined to shed blood and tears and have been struggling to protect this nation.
\n\nAnd we have stood in the vanguard crying out that we would make this people into a world-level people. Therefore, this work must not be branded as false. When the holy work of heaven begins as good, but the result bears fruit as evil, how many times has Satan accused that that is how it always is on heaven\'s path? Because we know that, please let us realize clearly that the path that the unification children have been walking must not remain as merely a private event.
\n\nFather! Now we must love this people and we must defend this Korean peninsula. Please let us become your sons and daughters who can feel the responsibility to keep it and protect it with our bodies becoming cannon balls and earthen fortresses. We sincerely hope that you will allow the Unification Church to become like that.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 14, 1964
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_16t">
Father!
\nIn the environment of the world, people are forgetting heaven, and forsaking your name, they are unfortunately living lives that distance them from your will. When we realize objectively that in this world of fallen men the facts are like that, we worry that we might come to a point of turning our back on the mission of heaven.
\n\nWe must have hearts that can deal with the temptations of the environment which come to us like enemies, and we must turn our backs on honor, power and prestige.
\n\nFather! For whom have we wept, and for whom have we suffered? Is there by any chance any foolish person who has wept for himself? I know that if there is any person going this way as a means to advance his career, then in the near future he will certainly fail. We must not become foolish people like that.
\n\nEven at the point where one could be destroyed, thinking of the fatherland and carrying out the responsibility together with you, who are the subject of the fatherland, one should be able to say, "Because I have gone over this kind of boundary line, oh Father, please leave a trace of the victory here."
\n\nEven from this kind of pathetic position of not being able to connect to or to communicate with all hearts or peoples, please let us become sons and daughters who can overcome this and serve this people. We must realize the fact that when we stand in such a position, we can inherit totally your complete heart which no one else can receive.
\n\nWe know that it is only through that kind of internal relationship that we can stand in a position to receive blessing in front of you, to receive protection, and to receive love. Even if we stand in such a position, we must realize that it is because of the foundation of our ancestors\' historical merit that we stand there, and we must have a humble attitude. And if our ancestors were not able to carry out that mission, we earnestly hope that you will let us become your sons and daughters who know how to struggle and fulfill that mission millions of times over in their stead.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 16, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_17t">
Father!
\nBecause the point for deciding the final altar is a point that requires a sacrifice, we have come to understand that the standards for good and evil must be established centered on the will of the providence which must judge the good and the evil of the people who will live or die.
\n\nWe are in this kind of position centered on the destiny of the nation. For us there remains the wall of how to unify the already existing division of the North and South. Therefore, we have realized that we need a nationwide thought movement as a new movement of the people centered on the desire of our people to live for heaven which is deep in the hearts of our 30 million people. Therefore, we know that in order for this nation and this people to live, we must arm ourselves first with Unification Thought, and we must arm ourselves with strength.
\n\nThrough history we have learned that centered on confrontations of power, evil takes a position such that we cannot even communicate with it until we have comparable power. Throughout history, evil has always shown that kind of result.
\n\nTherefore, we have realized that unless we establish a level of power that exceeds them, they will never concede to relate in a reciprocal atmosphere. We know that this is the path that evil has walked historically.
\n\nOur idea, that for your sake we should become one in heart internally and establish a level of power externally, is now coming into reality. At this kind of time, because we are taking responsibility for the mission to unify centered on Asia, we must go beyond our own difficulties, and we must invest all the material things that we have. Father, we must become like fuses who can give even our lives for your will. We must become the motivated people who can do that.
\n\nWe must be able to return the nations of enemies to you, Father, and we must be able to like those nations. In order to do rewarding work for Japan, your sons and daughters are working on the unification frontline there. The spirit world is there; the Unification Church is there; the Federation for Victory over Communism is there. Since your sons and daughters are beginning activities centered on these organizations, Father, we earnestly hope that you will bless them.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 8, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_18t">
When we get a glimpse of our people`s destiny which is to come after this, an earnest desire returns to our minds. When we think that the destiny of Korea today is at the center of the destiny of Asia tomorrow, we realize we are at the point of having to resolve our final mission.
\n\nEven if our destiny is the most miserable of any people in the world, for us there is no despair. We should appear on this earth as fruits which, having the historical power of life, can live new lives, going beyond the dividing line of the historical autumn which has come, filled with hope for tomorrow and having the power of life to greet the new spring. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to remember that we are able to take the big step filled with hope which can greet the new morning of tomorrow.
\n\nWhen we see that the fallen world has continued historically until today, with joy and sorrow, and life and death intersecting, we see that the tragedy of the destiny this people has faced is not going to continue as tragedy. Rather, we must become the popular figures of tomorrow who can connect to a history of joy.
\n\nWe know that this movement, which has endured until now in the midst of being driven out and pursued, this movement, which remains on a course of struggle, consists of your children who have gathered in Korea, the brave unification soldiers. As for us, we have shed tears for the sake of the people and for the sake of the world, and we have shed tears out of concern for the world of the future.
\n\nBecause you have done that through us, Father, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us at this time to become aware of and to re-declare our conviction that we must become those who have the authority of substantial beings able to have confidence in ourselves and able to possess the value of reciprocal objects before you, the subject, Father.
\n\nWhen we reflect on the flow of history until now, we see that it was not a history of sorrow, but rather a history of your protection. The more we feel your sorrow which remains as our own sorrowful ideal, we are in a position where we must attend you and go forward in order to have self-confidence and to go forth towards the hope of tomorrow. We lament, and we are not able to greet you in glory because that position is one where we are pierced by enemy arrows and we are turned back by sorrowful struggles.
\n\nBut, Father, please be patient. We have started out on the path of destiny which we must go beyond, and we must overcome the winter season for the site of tomorrow\'s hope. Therefore, we will have to make ourselves up beautifully and calmly gather together, joining ourselves together without damaging the price of our lives.
\n\nPlease let us concentrate our power of life for the sake of the moment when we, who are like this, can go beyond the boundary of the spring season and please allow us to have external abilities. We earnestly request that you will allow us to become a movement that rises up to the level of a subjective foundation which heaven and earth can guarantee when we are united as one body and have gone beyond that boundary. And please let us be able to long for the beginning of the new spring.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMay 3, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_19t">
Father!
\nThis nation is divided into north and south. It is the confrontation point of democracy and communism. Therefore, please guide the path of destiny that Korea must absolutely go. We have started along the path of suffering which we must go carrying the cross of your blood.
\n\nWe are standing in the position to be struck first, and even though we are struggling and our hearts are filled with sorrow and loneliness, we are holding before us the victory of tomorrow. Oh, Father, because of that, please allow this people to be strong and of good courage.
\n\nWe know that this is a tense moment that does not permit anything like despair or hopelessness, even for a moment. Right before our eyes we see that it is that kind of point in time externally throughout the nation and also internally centered on the will of the church. Since we cannot go into the Kingdom of Heaven if we do not completely fulfill the mission of the Abel nation, oh Father, please protect us.
\n\nThe time has come that our people`s righteous spirits must cast off the fallen world and reveal themselves with hearts of loyalty to the nation and the people which have been buried in your breast. But when I ask how many sons there are who have inherited your heart and are loyal to the nation and the people, I feel that 1 must repent while weeping in front of you, Father. Oh, Father, please forgive us.
\n\nWhen I look at the group that has followed my footsteps along so many bloodcurdling paths as I took the lead to relieve the grief of this people, I see so many who would cause you worry, Father. And I realize that there are not many who can take responsibility for your worries. When I look at these kinds of people, I feel that in the future where I must go there are still more paths of the cross before me.
\n\nFather! Since there remain paths of the cross which must be gone, in the course after this we will have to clear the path of the battle in place of the people and we will have to clear the path of destiny which we must go with strong footsteps.
\n\nOur people is divided into north and south and with that division of the people there is the grief of the relationships of sorrowful hearts which we cannot avoid having. Please let us understand that we are responsible for relieving that grief and for calling together the north and the south. Please guide us to fulfill that responsibility.
\n\nWe pray all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMay 31, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_20t">
Father!
\nWe thank you for having raised up our unworthy selves in front of your holy Will. Please allow me, this being standing before your Will, to fulfill my responsibility at this historical point in time and to be a person who is able to remain to the end.
\n\nWe must not be people who come and go once and just flow past. Rather, by presenting content that can influence this present historical age, we must fulfill our mission which is in the subject position and which can call in and establish a new age.
\n\nYou called us and raised us up, but as we are not able to feel the matters of your earnest heart that you want to give us responsibility for, please urge us on. Please allow us, your beloved children, to feel deep in our hearts the situation you have been in until now.
\n\nFather! Isn`t this a people to be pitied? If from now there is only one way for this people to go, and they do not know that way, then this is truly a people to be pitied, and this people`s future will be dark. When we closely analyze the present reality and look at the future situation for Asia and the world, we cannot help but worry about the way that this people and Korea are going.
\n\nFather! If up until now history has traced your footsteps which have been seeking to end the course of indemnity which you are manifesting to Asia and the world through this people, then please live in the minds of this people.
\n\nAlso we earnestly hope and desire that you will make this people one with your Will by resurrecting your hope in their minds. Father! Please let this people have hearts that cannot help loving their nation even if they don`t want to; please let their minds rise up until they cannot help loving North Korea even if they don`t want to.
\n\nWe have come to know the fact that the person who lives for himself just fades away in history, but the person who tries to live for his descendents, for the future generations of his people, and for the world appears as a victorious individual and remains as a central figure controlling that history. Therefore, we must not become a group that seeks to avoid this course of tears, this course of bloodcurdling struggles in this historical age.
\n\nEven in the midst of any kind of difficulties, let us take subjective responsibility and think, "I\'m the only one who can do it." We know that our Unification Movement must become a new group that can take hold of this people and this nation and influence Asia. You have called us and raised us up as individuals who can do that, Father.
\n\nWe individuals who have come here ought to be those who have awakened to the fact that we are the ones who can do that. Please let us realize that we are too inadequate. In the past this pitiful people shed much blood.
\n\nWe know that this people has gone a path of sacrifice which no one wanted because it was your will to bequeath this people to Asia. Please let our hope become one with that kind of hope of yours, Father, and let us unite. Then please find in the midst of our Unification Movement those who can give their loyalty to the Will that you have been desiring as you dealt with this people.
\n\nFather, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who can feel anew that this must become a place where you can feel it is rewarding to come and look around personally, and where you can rest.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJune 21, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_21t">
Father!
\nPlease take pity on this people. We imagine that from the time that your providential Will appeared in this land until now, this people did not know where to go, and this has caused you great sorrow. Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will bear with this people once more.
\n\nYou have said that whatever is loosed on earth will definitely be loosed in heaven. In the same way we have a deep longing in relation to this people, and even though we have sorrow in relation to the people of the world, when we consider that you have hope for this nation, this people, and this world, we feel that we also must have new hope.
\n\nBecause until now there has had to be someone responsible to offer sacrifices of atonement for our wrongdoings and inadequacies, we must feel once again that we are those who must control our sorrow, put on the bloodstained garments of the chief priest and in the direction of the holy of holies bow down before you, Father.
\n\nFather! When we think about your deep heart of love for this people and the course of difficulties that you have gone through for this people, and how much we are able to attend you and to praise you in this day, we cannot help but realize that we must always feel how unworthy we are.
\n\nAs we go forward believing in you, Heavenly Father, we have forgotten this people and this world, but have you at any time ever forgotten this people or this world, or have you ever forgotten about humankind?
\n\nEach time you were moved by loneliness, you were denied by humankind to your face, but after that you sought to hold humankind again. That is exactly what your situation has been. You have sought a father-son relationship with the heart of a parent. Because we must experience this directly, not only through words, we earnestly hope that you will allow each one of us to awaken to this once again.
\n\nWe pray all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJune 28, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_22t">
Father!
\nThank you for having protected the destiny of this nation. North Korea attacked, the south, and devastated land during the Korean War. So many people of this nation were sacrificed, and even the young men of friendly nations who were concerned for Korea shed their blood here.
\n\nWe know that this was not a battle due to the political or environmental changes of the age. Rather, it was a decisive battle which came about because the Will you are directing had to anchor in this land. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to feel once again that the time has come when we must be ready and resolute in our deepest hearts.
\n\nWe know well that your direction in order to establish the starting point for your Will and desire were behind this kind of repeatedly difficult course of suffering which Korea has gone through from the time we attained our sovereignty until now. Therefore, Father, please watch over the future of Korea.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow the 30 million people of this nation to become a people who see you, Father, and who can go forward to Asia for you. We know that we are too far from being able to do that, so we must shorten that distance. When we consider that this responsibility is ours, all we can feel is embarrassment and sorrow before you, Father, as you watch our inadequate selves and yet have hope.
\n\nWe know well that our people are in the midst of a history of misfortune which we cannot solve by ourselves. In order to solve this our people must join hands with the powers of Asia and be in accord with them.
\n\nTherefore, please unite us all together by linking body to body and mind to mind. We know that we are still responsible to overcome a path of many difficulties which remain before us. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that everything will be accomplished according to the Will which you desire and are directing, Father.
\n\nFather! There are children here whom you can call your sons and daughters. Please allow them to adore you deep in their hearts. And please allow them to take all of your situations into their hearts as their own.
\n\nPlease let their hearts become one with your heart and let the blessings of adoration shower down on them like rain. And we earnestly hope and desire that you will lead them completely with your strength.
\n\nWe know that any group that does not prepare for tomorrow but rather seeks only safety and ease in the present day can only fall into ruin. Therefore, since those of us who have gathered here in this place have done so in order to prepare the foundation of victory for our descendents and for the world of tomorrow, we will have to be able to turn today\'s sorrow into tomorrow\'s hope and change today\'s difficulties into tomorrow\'s expectations.
\n\nIn that way, according to your wish we will prepare the foundation for the victory of your Will, and until we can offer it to you, we will endure and endure. We earnestly request that you will allow us to become the group that fights and fights again, and remains to the end.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of our True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nAugust 16, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_23t">
Father!
\nPlease protect the path that this 30 million people will walk. You know the wretched situation of this people whose anguished, bloody history has continued on and on, and whose nation has been divided into north and south. Their heart of love for this nation divided at the 38th parallel will have to be higher and deeper than that 38th parallel.
\n\nTheir attitude should be one of regarding North Korea as their own hands and feet. The people who are to take responsibility for this nation are the members of the Unification Movement who don`t know anything. When we think that the Unification Movement must do it, we must firmly grasp the grief of this grief-filled people and become a movement that pushes it aside.
\n\nOut of concern for the remaining destiny of these 30 million people we have determined a period for devotion, and we are offering devotion; therefore, please protect this people. This nation, this people must not believe some person, Father; they must believe you. They must stand close before you. And more than anyone else, our Unification Movement must struggle to become the people who can do that.
\n\nOh, Father! Please protect this pitiful people. Please take pity on this people that have left a history of grief in front of you, who sought hope. We know that the daily life of humankind always has temptations, so you will have to forgive what these people have done wrong.
\n\nNow we will have to become a movement that can prepare the way for you to come. Even if we are held in contempt by others please let us become a people who repent for the past with tears, and in this age please let us become a people who find you again with new hearts which can become one before you. Since we have not yet become that kind of people, we must come to feel deeply that the Unification Church\'s mission still remains to make this people into that kind of people.
\n\nCentering on this religious body, the Unification Church, what will we leave before you in that moment when we pass over the final path of death? When we gather together our sons and daughters, or gather together the disciples who are following us, and we tell them what we are leaving for our co-workers or our people, please allow us to be Unification Church members who can say I am a son or I am a daughter who leaves various kinds of things.
\n\nFather! We are not people who are blindly following the environment of this age. We are a movement that must create a new history and lead this age. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will remember us.
\n\nWe know that the footprints that we have left as we walked and our appearance as we have struggled up until now have been too weak. We know that we must once again control our tired, exhausted minds and bodies and turn once again and go before you.
\n\nBut even in spite of that, we are at a point where, on our own, none of us can find even vigor for our own bodies. So, Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will please take responsibility and once again allow us to have vigor.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nSeptember 27, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_24t">
We don`t know whether our church has been victorious on the individual level. And we don`t know which level of victory has been attained on the family level. And we don`t know whether a victorious foundation has been laid on the level of the church.
\n\nBut these kinds of things are not our goal. We must realize the fact that a sacrifice is being demanded so that we can save this nation and bring about north-south unification. And we must realize the fact that we must prepare an altar.
\n\nFather, we earnestly hope that you will protect and love this pitiful Korean people. Please love them. We must realize that historical sorrow is dwelling at the center of your direction which has divided North and South Korea.
\n\nWhen we think about the fact that this history of suffering was extended for scores of years because our ancestors and our elders were not able to fulfill completely the missions that they were responsible for, with hearts like that of Jonah who repented, we will have to fulfill our responsibilities for the future of this people.
\n\nFather, please take to your breast this entire people who are divided into north and south. We will have to go forward until we find the nation of victory that can spread your authority.
\n\nPlease let us have earnest hearts which are yours alone, Father. And please let us feel earnestly for the nation and for the world. Even if we pass on, and even if our descendents pass on, we will have to hand down only that nation and your love.
\n\nWhen we think that we have this kind of historical mission, even if we are destroyed and killed thousands and ten thousands of times we will have to make a nation of the ideal of creation which you are longing for.
\n\nJesus, who also desired this, urged us, "Therefore do not be anxious, saying, "What shall we eat?" or "What shall we drink?" or "What shall we wear?" For the Gentiles seek all these things; But seek first his kingdom and his righteousness"
\n\nWe sincerely hope that you will allow us to become filial sons and daughters who have loyalty and fidelity and who will take your place in this situation about which you warned the people, this situation of sorrow and who have a burning desire for the mission of handing down the nation which is deep in your heart.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of our True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 1, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_25t">
Father, you already know the destiny of this pitiful Korean peninsula where the north and south intersect. Going through 5,000 years of history, this nation still has not been able to leave the path of suffering and it is now facing the final wall of the dark last days.
\n\nOh, Father, please look on this nation with pity. The north and south are divided, and have been placed in a situation where even if they want to unite, they cannot. And even though they long for each other, they cannot meet, and even though they want to go to each other, they cannot because there is a wall blocking them. Father, please take pity on the destiny of this nation. We believe that only you can take dominion over the victory or defeat here.
\n\nWe feel that you have called and raised us worthless people from among so many people for the sake of the future of this people, and for the day of unification of this people. As we face such a historical destiny, we must bring our minds into oneness with your mind, Father, and we must bring our desire into oneness with your Will, and we must bring our ideal al into oneness with your ideal of creation.
\n\nGoing beyond the history where people could not become filial sons, we must become sincere filial sons before you. We know that our historical ancestors passed away unable to fulfill their duty as loyal subjects as they were not able to give you a nation over which you could take dominion.
\n\nFather, if there is a way for us to become loyal subjects in a nation over which you can have dominion, we realize that going that way would be a rewarding path which realizes the highest dream someone born as a human being could have.
\n\nTherefore, please open up for us that kind of way where we can fulfill our duty as loyal subjects who give our entire lives for the sake of that nation and that sovereignty and who find that nation for you.
\n\nFrom a position of loving heaven more than anyone else, we should love this nation, we should love this people, and we should love the sovereignty of this nation. We earnestly hope and desire that by personally taking dominion over this entire nation, you will allow Korea to become the nation that can attend you.
\n\nPlease let this people become a people that can offer itself to you as your people. And we sincerely ask that you will allow this land to be able to offer itself as the foothold for your eternal victory as your land.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 1, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_26t">
Father!
\nWith hearts lacking in filial piety, we are longing for you. With hearts lacking in loyalty, we want to form a relationship with your true life. Please receive us and gently embrace us. We who have become your sons must not be less than Jesus. We must become sons and daughters who can greet death with gratitude if we go to the point of death, centered on your will.
\n\nWe know that without making that kind of determination we will not be able to subjugate North Korea, which has appeared as the central model of the satanic world, or the factions of evil spread throughout that land. We who are gathered here know clearly that that can be realized only by uniting with Unification Thought.
\n\nWe know that this thought will have to be expanded to the people, to religions, and to Christianity. We know that this thought will have to fit with the people, with religions and with Christianity. Therefore, we ask you thrice over to allow us to fulfill this mission quickly during this time period.
\n\nPlease liberate North Korea and allow us to have a sovereign nation, the victorious Israel, a nation of hope which heaven has sought and you have blessed, Father. Then please allow us to be able to praise the glory of victory within the realm of fortune of national unification, and all nations will attain their original nature.
\n\nAnd please bless this age as the age that can realize a world heaven can embrace.
\n\nFather! Since we feel grateful that you cannot help but give us internal responsibility, please always shower upon us your heart of mercy and compassion. We sincerely hope that from now on you will allow our Unification Movement to develop in reality and that you will allow us to go our way together with you, Father, and to share the blessing of glory and the praise of victory together with the entire world and the spirit world.
\n\nWe humbly pray this in the name of the li-ue Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 3, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_27t">
Father!
\nAs individuals who have been born into a relationship with the historical course that Korea has been walking, we know that we must become substantial beings of hope who can shoulder the destiny of this nation.
\n\nThis nation has had such a miserable and pitiful history. Please look down on and take care of the miserable history of this people who could not look to anyone, who could not depend on anyone, who lost track of the direction you were leading things and had to struggle and fight on their own. We have come to realize that you placed your Will in the history of this nation and behind this people are traces of your warm love.
\n\nWe need to realize how much our ancestors intended and longed for the coming of the day when the hope of this nation would be able to shine forth like the bright light of the sun rising each morning.
\n\nFather, please remember the many patriots who were concerned for and worked for this nation. They hoped that your desire would shine forth, but the days that it could have shown forth, they spent in frustration, and they lived through a history of sorrow which saw the sun set, and they met the night together with tears and darkened hearts which could not be fathomed.
\n\nWe know that night will not continue as it is, but rather morning will come. And we know that these tiresome times no one wants will all pass away, and a historical new age of light will come to the heavens and the earth.
\n\nPlease protect this nation. When we consider that the time is coming when we must greet a new spring day, and determine a new mental reformation from the realistic point of view of determining an external standard, we earnestly hope and desire that you will take responsibility for the future of this people.
\n\nIn order for us to inherit as our central undertaking the things that you are taking responsibility for, please let us be able to pledge before you, Father, and please let us become sons and daughters who are believable and upright in your sight, and please let us stand before you in ranks that can go forward towards the new world and the new Kingdom of Heaven. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to inherit everything.
\n\nFather! The place where we gather now should not be a place of loneliness, nor should it be a place of sorrow. Please let us become an organization of destiny, a place where you always are, a place about which you cannot help but be concerned, where we live with you and go with you.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of our True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nApril 4, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_28t">
Father!
\nSince we know that we must give all the devotion we have for this pitiful people, oh Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will protect them. And we earnestly hope and desire that as you completely protect them, you will allow this people to live together with your Will.
\n\nWhen we ask who is responsible for having separated the North and South we know this people is. We know that the many religious bodies on which this people center are responsible. And when we think that we must take on the responsibility that these religious bodies have held, we must have confidence and pledge ourselves effectively to the mission of tomorrow`s pioneers.
\n\nToday it would not do for us to become discouraged while on our pilgrimage as heralds; so Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will encourage us. The day on which north and south unify, that day, which many peoples will praise and which will give you joy, must come quickly.
\n\nThe day must come when we can build the Kingdom of Heaven of victory which can resolve your grief on this Korean Peninsula. However strong evil may be, we know that evil cannot invade a place where there still are people of filial piety who live for you, or where there still are people with loyalty.
\n\nYour children who are gathered here should be able to lament the fact that we lack filial piety and we lack loyalty even though we are several people, we should become one body, and we should have one mind. We know that we will prosper on the day we become one centered on the Will, and we will be destroyed on the day we become divided.
\n\nThe name "Unification" has been a name of suffering until now, but from now on it will have to be remembered as a name of glory. When we think that the path on which we must go towards glory is already determined, today we must have a sense of the extreme importance of our mission, and we must secure absolutely the foundation for unification.
\n\nPlease let this church become one, and please let your children who are spread all throughout the north and south become one, please let your children who are spread throughout the world also become one. And as the final religious body, please let the Unification Church fulfill its responsibility completely without shame in front of this age, in front of the world, and in front of history.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nApril 11, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_29t">
Father!
\nPlease look with sorrow at the present situation of this nation and please remember it. From now on, Father, you will have to take responsibility for the destiny of Korea. There is no one who can lead this nation, and there is no one who can take responsibility for it; only you can bring this nation into oneness with the direction of heavenly fortune.
\n\nSo we earnestly hope and desire that you will act, Father, to connect our individual hearts and the hearts of this people so that in the midst of your care this people may find the direction that will allow them to become one with the Will you desire.
\n\nHowever great a person may be, there is no one who can block the way of heavenly fortune. Each time that we think that we should adapt ourselves to the wave of heavenly fortune and follow it, we ask you to fill to overflowing with your heart the hearts of the many people leading this nation, and in the face of these final, decisive circumstances please reveal the one point where we must absolutely come to a conclusion about your will of the providence.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nSeptember 5, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_30t">
Please, you take responsibility for Korea now. Oh Father, if you who have come to this pitiful people, cannot take their future into your hands and establish it by joining them together into one, then would you not be even more pitiful? When we center on individuals, we, who are unworthy, have divided minds and bodies.
\n\nThe men and the women are divided, and families are divided, and the tribes, the nations, and the world are divided. Heaven and earth are divided, and between God and people who are divided, who will lay a bridge? We know that we need a union that can make the yous and mes into one family, which is so strong that even if individuals wanted to fall away they could not, but who can carry out that mission? Fallen humankind cannot do it.
\n\nBecause of that we are hoping for the cooperation of the millions of spirits in spirit world. Until you take hold, Father, and tie us and tie us again making us into one, there is no way to be unified. We are standing facing our destiny like people who are already floating away in the flood.
\n\nAnd because it cannot possibly be done through our strength, we earnestly hope and desire that you will look on us with pity as we look to heaven and call out to you, Father, and as we look to heaven and call out to our ancestors.
\n\nWhen we ask where is the family to which you can come, we know that there is none. In order to find that kind of path, that kind of family, the Unification Church has formed families with a new meaning.
\n\nThis is because we know that before any people or nation on this earth goes, unless you have gone first neither the people nor nation can go. We will also know that the new families were formed because you called for the path of unification. Isn\'t it so that you could make oneness of something that was two and have something which is yours alone?
\n\nWe gathered together these kinds of families and made tribes. Among those tribes we know that there are Abel tribes and Cain tribes. It is a law of the Principle that unless the Abel tribes restore the Cain tribes, we cannot inherit the realm of the ideal of the parents, and we cannot inherit God\'s ideal world of love.
\n\nTherefore since we are giving our life\'s strength, straining and struggling and we are rushing towards the realm of the tribe that can restore Cain, please remember this Unification Movement. Please remember the blessed couples. Then after accomplishing the unified tribe, centered on that, we will form one people, and as the Abel people, we will have the responsibility to become one with the Cain people.
\n\nThen, Father, since you know that our desire is to realize this nation\'s independence, this nation\'s unification, and this nation\'s second liberation, please take responsibility for Korea in the future. Since there is no one who can become the lord, we earnestly hope that you will be together with us.
\n\nBecause you clearly exist, Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow the will that you are calling for to be realized, and that you will stand on the side of this pitiful group who are going forth believing and knowing that everything will be done according to the will which you are directing.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of our True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nAugust 20, 1972
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_31t">
Father!
\nWe know the course of sorrow and the course of history that must pioneer the path of restoration in order to find the original world which all the people of the world have lost.
\n\nBecause of the fall of our human ancestors, this world of so many lamentations came about. The spirit world and the physical world were divided. As for individuals, the spirit and the body were divided, and the whole world, centered on Satan, divided and divided, and was separated into many nations and many peoples.
\n\nIn that way we left the bosom of God, and having lost the grounds for love for establishing a relationship with God, and being tied into a blood relationship centered on Satan`s love, we formed historical blood relationships of grief and sorrow, multiplied, and made this divided world.
\n\nFather, you have been dealing with this kind of real situation and have gone through so many hardships to gather this world into one. How much grief must have filled your heart as you struggled, pitted against Satan, to find the one world of unification which you had hoped for. We earnestly hope and desire that you can bear with the fact that we humans have nothing to our credit before you.
\n\nBut, Father, you did not cast us away, and now everything that was divided shall be gathered together in one world. It will not do unless the whole world is embraced by you. The world which has been divided into the communist world and the democratic world, has taken on the form of Cain and Abel.
\n\nAnd the divisions of the world called left and right shall now be made into one centered on your Will. You have sent the True Parents to the earth to do that, and you have established your providential Will such that it will not do unless the left and the right become one centered on True Parents.
\n\nWe know that your Will was to connect all the nations and to establish one unified nation right after the Second World War. Centered on Christianity and centered on America, you have gone forward preparing the domain for the final victory which will allow you to embrace this world as a unified realm.
\n\nWe realize that your hope is at the center of humankind, Father. Forty years ago, Christianity and this land lost the historical mission which they should have fulfilled through a new idea of national salvation.
\n\nThat mission was to indemnify Cain and Abel, to found a new nation, the nation of the new parents, to begin the new homeland, and to advance to the world, but all was lost.. Accordingly, the democratic world came under satanic dominion again and fell into a divided situation, and even in circumstances like that you went the opposite way of the course of indemnity of the individual, the family, the tribe, the nation, and the world through the Unification Church.
\n\nIn these chaotic circumstances, Father, the division of the democratic world has occurred. Even using the democratic world itself, heaven`s Will cannot deal with the situation, and even using the entire communist world, humankind cannot be led.
\n\nNow we have reached the final point where it will not do unless all consolidate. Centering on this kind of foundation you established the Unification Church today, and in the future after having indemnified all the things that must be consolidated, and are already consolidated, once again as left and right, centered on Cain and Abel, you have established the parents. And your Will, through which you seek to deal with the world, has reached this kind of moment in which the final victory is now to be determined.
\n\nThis nation was not able to become one centered on Christianity, but centered on American Christianity, pursuing the fortune of indemnity which can become one, now for the first time in Korea we have met anew the same level of fortune as 40 years ago. Father, when we look at this centered on the Unification Church, we have now finally prepared the realm of victory of the people who must connect to the world going beyond their people.
\n\nTherefore, please become the center here, Father, and look down on and take care of all the real situations of this Korea which is divided into north and south. We know that uniting the people of the Unification Church centered on the parents will be the beginning of being able to determine the domain of victory in the world.
\n\nWe have set the mission of the new will, and we have begun an awesome new work called the Citizens Federation for the Unification of the Fatherland. Father, here you shall be the center, and True Parents shall be the center, and the blessed couples shall be the center, and now all the blessed couples have gathered together, and in front of them is this awesome mission which must be indemnified in front of you Father; therefore, tying all these things together, please unite all of our hearts and minds into one.
\n\nNow please make the families into one, and the parents into one and at the same time as making the people into one, please connect the standard of indemnity with the world-level realm of fortune, and by doing that, centered on the domain of victory of the new universe, we earnestly hope and desire that you will bless us, Father, with being able to establish the cornerstone of your nation.
\n\nFather! Please release all the toil and grief of your hard work over the last 40 years. Now we unification people earnestly hope and desire that you will give us the blessing of being able to raise both our hands in victory and glory and boast of and praise that to all nations.
\n\nWe will inherit all this fortune you have granted us, and as far as offering restoration to you, Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will give us the blessing of being able to fulfill completely our mission of true sacrifice.
\n\nFather! Please allow the grief of the north and south to be released. This is the hope of our people now. On account of attaining north-south unification centered on the parents who are your hope, all the gates of the world will begin to open. Father, please balance this whole land of Korea which you have blessed, and form relationships that can create unity until the opening of the gate of the victorious kingdom of Heaven.
\n\nPlease grant your eternal protection to all the movements that are bringing this into reality now. Please reveal the fact that you are alive everywhere we go, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will act, Father, to not let us be at all inadequate while moving to unite our people.
\n\nThen, we will attend you, Father, and we will attend our parents, and possessing the attitude of the people of the Kingdom of Heaven who can speak proudly, we will attend you, Father, on the earth. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will bless us to be able to bring to completion your final purpose and to bring about on this earth a sovereignty of all nations centered on you, Father.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow a realm of liberation for this people and all the people of the world due to the rapid progress of the entire Will centered on you, Father.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will give us the blessing of becoming your sons and daughters, of completing our mission without shame in the remaining days and time, and of becoming blessed children and families who lack nothing when giving and receiving love in your embrace.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow this to become a movement that pledges victory and pledges advancement, and possesses a shame-free attitude in front of the remaining mission.
\n\nWe pray all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMay 17, 1987
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_32t">
We have realized the fact that there cannot be a world of joy, ideals or peace without a beginning of an ideal that can move towards the garden of love. We have also realized that originally, in the unifying beginning centered on God, the ideal of love, which could unite into one, had to connect God, Adam and Eve, and all the things of creation.
\n\nAs for this age, it is of course centered on the individual and on the family, but in connecting this to the tribe, people, nation and world forms, we must go through a sacrificial stage. So, Father, please take pity on the struggles of our unification Movement which is seeking to cast off the world`s realm of suffering and the realm of the fall.
\n\nAnd from now on, please guide our active works, and please protect our worldwide activities. We earnestly hope and desire that you will give us the blessing of being able to become the people and the nation that takes the role of the necessary condition to realize your desired goal.
\n\nFather! We know that North and South Korea must not be divided. We have come to understand that unifying this nation is not just a mission of the people of Korea, it is a historical mission. In providential history Abel without fail absorbs the Cain realm centered on this kind of standard, and the Unification Movement, which knows that the one garden of unified love must be realized before heaven, is taking the leading position.
\n\nTherefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will give us the blessing of all of us being able to rouse ourselves to action so that we will have no inadequacies in our efforts to spread the new tradition.
\n\nNow as for living our individual lives, and our lives in our families, tribes, peoples, nations and the world, we will inherit the traditional thought following the history of the heavenly fortune, and we will become those who love in stead of others, representatives of love, and we will love our families, tribes, peoples, nations and world from such a position, and we will inherit the ideal of being an object partner for heaven\'s love, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will give us the blessing of being able to realize the realm of unification, the sovereign realm centered on love which can be God\'s at that same time that it is the world\'s, and can be the world\'s at the same time that it is mine.
\n\nWe earnestly ask that in the midst of your care you will give us the blessing of being able to become one with all the things we pledged in order to not be shamed in front of the remaining age and responsibility.
\n\nWe pray all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nSeptember 20, 1987
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_33t">
As we look at this world of death which does not know the fact that as it passes, time is calling true people, we, who possess a realm of liberation are proud of that, even though the north and south are missing each other on the road now, they will be liberated for sure.
\n\nThe east and west are divided, but whatever conflicts there may be between cultural backgrounds, on the foundation of the unified blood lineage which is centered on true love and true life, we know that all those walls will break down and collapse.
\n\nHowever great the gap may be between the wealth and the poverty of the south and the north, because we know we are brothers, we know that it is only proper that the people who have a lot share what they have with hearts of love.
\n\nWe have come to understand the amazing path that can assimilate through your love, Father, the destiny of the kind of people who have their root in a life of realizing the world of peace centered on love. We know well that it would not do for us not to thank you sincerely that all this has arisen due to the destiny of True Parents.
\n\nWe know that in this amazing age when we are now seeking to create the world of a new culture coming from God and from True Parents, it is true that we have entered an age when all the standards of victory are already seeing the light of morning.
\n\nWe can see who is right and who is false, and since the age has come in which we can know who is evil, we ask and hope that you will lead all the people of the world to be able to tread upon and go over the realm of life and death, and to be able to transcend and to go beyond the standard of liberation.
\n\nAnd we earnestly hope and desire that you will bless all humankind to be able to be together with you in your family, and as the people over whom you reign to be men of the heavenly kingdom.
\n\nWith that age and that time before us, and the responsibility that we must fulfill as liberated members who have taken responsibility for liberation ahead of us, we ask three times over that you will guide and encourage us to be able to become a movement that is not ashamed.
\n\nWe pray all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 4, 1987
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_34t">
Beloved Father!
\nWhen we consider the passing course of history and the fact that we exist as one aspect in this historical age which is flowing by, it is a sad and miserable thing, but when we think that we are in a position where centered on God, who exists centered on eternity, we can embody you, Father, and be assimilated by you, we realize the fact that we cannot help but be grateful.
\n\nWe have also considered the division of the north and the south while attending you. We came to understand that here too it will not do unless the north and south communicate with an ideological concept of having exchanges for the sake of the other rather than with an ideology of confrontation.
\n\nThey should each take responsibility for the suffering path of the other, like doing something for one`s younger brother from the position of the elder brother, like doing something for one`s wife from the position of the husband, like doing something for one`s child from the position of the parent, like doing something for us from the position of God who is the center of all heaven and earth.
\n\nWe have come to clearly know the logic that north-south unification will be possible only in the kind of world of the realm of heart of living for others. The eyes that we see with also consist of two types. There are eyes that are for oneself and there are eyes that are for the whole. And there are also words that are for oneself and there are words that are for the whole.
\n\nPlease let us lament that we have not been able to establish a realm of daily life that can absorb and include an environment that can live for the whole, distinguishing everything about the five senses. And please let us know how to live the life of the central figure that is able to live in the subject partner position, analyzing himself and raising himself. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to be able to follow that way.
\n\nThrough the ages of history we have seen and felt many times that it is always possible for the power of re-creation to appear along the path of an unchanging relationship which is for you. Father, when we open our hearts completely and stand on our own, centered on north, south, east, west, up and down, we discover that wherever we go the elements of our lives that can live for others are the life elements.
\n\nIn view of that, we ask you to lead us to become those who are not ashamed, who can go towards the center of the entire universe with pride that we can possess that special realm which can inherit the entire realm you bequeath to us, and at the same time in which we can participate in everything with you.
\n\nWe pray these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 21, 1988
    </string>

    <string name="pr_unification_35t">
We have come to know that you are looking for true fruit because you sowed true seeds, Father. Whatever the place may be like where we humans came into being on this land, we have come to know the fact that the people you are looking for are the citizens whom the nation needs and the emperors, princes or princesses living in the palaces governing the countries.
\n\nWe have come to understand that: the person who can attain such a position is not the kind of person who has extensive knowledge nor the person who has struggled and fought in order to gain power, nor are there many such people.
\n\nWe have come to understand that it begins only from a person who, centered on one heart of love, is able to be concerned when a disturbance occurs in a corner of a country, and to think it happened because I wasn`t able to do that, because I wasn`t able to cope with it.
\n\nAs for those of us who are watching this pathetic destiny of the divided north and south, we have the responsibility to deal with it and reclaim it, no matter what its historical origin was. And we know that there remains a destined course that the people of this nation must go.
\n\nBut it will not happen according to the directions or methods they present; it must be connected to the great fortune of the natural laws. When a seed puts down roots, and that root sends up a shoot which can grow into a stem, flowers bloom and fruit is borne. We have come to know the fact that the essence of love must be born which can concentrate and unify the all the elements of that plant.
\n\nWe ask you to allow us without fail to be citizens of the heavenly kingdom who deal with north-south unification and who can go to the world as respectable people. We know that it is your hope that we will desire to become a movement that can be praised as representatives of love who possess the authority of emperors and queens who belong in the royal family of the heavenly palace. And furthermore, today we have realized that behind this historical age you have been carrying out the providence, and your hope has been urging us on day and night in that direction.
\n\nTherefore, from now on, please allow us to definitely become your partners of the love of heaven, and let us focus the direction of our whole lives and our daily lives there. Then in this age of chaos worldwide, centered on the vertical line of heaven in order for the ideal world in heaven and the horizontal world on earth to be able to unify as one sphere, please let us realize that the Unification Movement is a movement that can take the initiative in the ideal realm of love. We earnestly ask and desire that you will please allow us to become your guideposts who absolutely keep the path of that direction, and to become your sentinels.
\n\nWe pray all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 13, 1988
    </string>
</resources>