<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="pr_champumo_1t">
Father, I know that all that remains before us is the will of Heaven. We know that Father and True Parents are the center of this meaning, and we also know that humans living on the earth must become true sons and daughters of True Parents. Not only this, but we know that what the Father wants us to do is for all to become one brother, and for all to become Father\'s true sons and daughters.
\n\nFather, we also know that the sin of blocking and ravaging those who wish to stand in the position of the sons and daughters you desire is greater than any other sin on this earth. It is an unacceptable sin to violate the true integrity of man, but I sincerely hope and pray that you will lead us to not forget this, knowing that losing true brotherly love is a greater sin in the face of heaven.
\n\nFather, how can you say that you are moving under the guidance of a shepherd when you say that some brother cannot wake you up from the heavenly circle that is trying to wake you up from a deep sleep? Please don\'t let us stand in such a place. Please allow even those brothers to become sons and daughters who can take responsibility and build a hidden altar on behalf of the heavenly world.
\n\nAnd help me establish the ideal of eternal sons and daughters that you desire, and let me know that you have the eyes of your Father who is always looking out for you. Allow me to feel your touch of love, allow me to listen to your voice, give me words of instruction, and empathize with your mourning, so that I resemble your Father’s heart and imitate your Father’s image. Even if I die ten million times before you, allow me to become the chief disciples of Jesus Christ who can worship and give thanks.
\n\nDuring this time, we heard a new feeling about the many enemies who are blocking the way to liberate the grudges of the heavenly world, and we are able to deal with the Father\'s will anew. Keeping this newly felt fact in mind, today\'s sermon does not end with my personal feelings, but it should connect the whole in front of the will of heaven instead of historicity and cosmic nature. Let me know that you have a mission to do.
\n\nDear Father! Allow me to fight with a heart of justice and resentment in place of the heavenly world against the countless enemies blocking this path, and allow me to go forward with patience and patience to return the day of victory before my Father, and to celebrate the day of victory. Yes, allow us to express our grudges that we have endured so far to Father, hold your precious hand, and lead us to a place where we can be comforted.
\n\nAllow all mankind on this earth to be awakened, and since all the worlds you created are in the sphere of mourning, mobilize us to restore them, and to fulfill our responsibilities to mankind so that all of us can become heavenly citizens. Grant me wisdom. I earnestly hope that the little children gathered here will be able to go on regardless of the course of any battle, and that they will become soldiers of heaven who can go out for the will even if they give up everything they have. In Your name I have spoken.
\nAju.
\n(1957.5.19)
    </string>

    <string name="pr_champumo_2t">
Dear Father, may the glory, honor, and praise of You, Lord of heaven and earth, go mad before you along with all that you have made. Father, we are well aware of how hard you went through the history of re-creation through suffering for the mistakes of the first human ancestors through the course of many history. For our individual individuals, how miserable it is to cross the path of species, cross the path of servants, cross the path of adoption, cross the path of children, cross the relationship of True Parents, and return to your original position. I am reminded of whether I have come to pay the indemnity that was filled with suffering.
\n\nAs a human being who deserves punishment because he has committed a sin, it is natural that he will have to walk the miserable path of suffering, but it has nothing to do with that. We sincerely thank you for your hard work that is aggravating.
\n\nFather! We have come to know that there is no one body that has not gone through your touch, and that there is no country that has not been drawn out of your wishes until now. Furthermore, we are well aware that Father is guiding all to the present day as he crosses borders to lead all into his strange world.
\n\nWhen you think that there are only you, your beloved sons and daughters, and the heavenly angels in the world that must be left in the end, you see that there are too many powers and groups of satan in this world. The group of unification knows that they are in a position where they cannot hope that this will be settled before the Father. Considering the fact that the Unification Church group has a great responsibility to complete the original form of the angelic world in the earth and in the spirit world to praise the family by having the names of True Parents and true children. When we do, we come to think that we are in a position to inherit the achievements of our sons and daughters and at the same time to inherit the achievements of becoming parents and to inherit the original ideal of creation in heaven.
\n\nTherefore, we must be children born of your own flesh and blood, and we must embrace you and be loved as sons and daughters. Now that we are in the position of embracing again, we think that we have to go to the heart of love that our Father built and love Adam and Eve, who came out of hope and did not lose. How can we come forward before the standard of our heart as a descendant of the Fall? However, for you who have overcome the path of suffering for ourselves, the more we stand in a position where we strive to draw our original attitude, the more you think about how great it is to appear as a precious figure in front of the heart of your hard work. . At this time, I can only guess a little bit of your heart\'s desire to put us in front of your true feelings.
\n\nYoung children who are hardened, I have to go through your touch as a material for re-creation in front of you. We already knew that you have to be like the clay that you can mold and adapt to it, just like it was made by mixing soil and water. We cannot have our own opinions. Knowing that we can only have absolute faith, a heart to adore Your absolute love, and a heart to be loyal to Your absolute will, we earnestly wish and desire that you take over, Father, in charge.
\n\nMake it the vessel you want. It is not our request to make earthenware, valuable vessels, or earthenware, so we earnestly hope and wish that you will make it so that you can become the things you need to your heart\'s content. The Bible says that unless you are like a child, you cannot enter the kingdom of heaven. We know that children are the lives of their parents. We know that young children depend on their parents for their lifeline. A child appears in front of you as an object representing the whole, but just as you are unaware of it, the humans living on this earth today are in a place where they do not know you. When I see this, I think that I am standing in a more sophisticated position than a child.
\n\nWhen you look at a group like this, you will see that all the requirements of nature that can be associated with you have been defiled, and it has become like an insulator, which is extremely difficult to communicate with the heart of heaven. When you realize that you have to melt them again by touching them with your love, if they are tangled, you have to release them, if they are hardened, you have a responsibility to lead them to the point where you can know the Father. We did not know that we had become a pit of resentment that could not be resolved even after going through so much suffering.
\n\nOur eyes were like that, our ears were like that, our speaking mouth was like that, and our limbs drew and acted in the opposite direction from what you were asking for. Allow me to look in your direction ten million times when I think of what they are, allow me to listen to you, and bless me to have a mouth that can whisper with you and speak with you. I\'m looking forward to it. Even though we have to wear our limbs and follow you behind you in shabby clothes, not only that, but even though we should follow you while working as a secret agent, on the contrary, we are sad and forgiven that we cannot go when Heaven leads us. I know that they have become disloyalty things that do not exist, Father, increase the heart of mercy and the heart of love.
\n\nSince there is an intrinsic bond that cannot be abandoned, we leave an eternal ideal behind and we know that as long as you wish for it, we cannot discard it. I wish and want. Please hold our weak hands and lead us to the world you desire. We didn\'t know that you were going through hardships while being whipped and humiliated. Now, even in your heart, allow me to know the pain you are going through, allow me to feel it, and let me know. Please.
\n\nPlease allow many people to know how hard Heaven has suffered because of one person, repent through history, take responsibility for the times, and struggle to walk the path of the cross for me. Knowing that such a group is the only group of unification gathered here, Father, please admonish them. Since you have already spread a group of unification not only in this group in Korea but all over the world, I earnestly hope and wish that you will extend your loving hand wherever they seek with all their intellect, loyalty and earnest desire.
\n\nThe 3rd 7-year course that we have set up, the 2nd 7-year course as the period you have allowed before your will, and the 3rd 7-year course has been declared and it has already been a month. On this morning on the first day of February, looking back on the past month, it was a busy month, but through that month, allow a shining victory to be in Korea, and a shining victory to spread in Asia, and resonate in front of all people. . In addition, I earnestly hope and wish that you will allow the work of joy that can liberate the many spirits in the heavenly world as soon as possible.
\n\nCentering on February 8, the best men and women around the world want to hold a wedding ceremony in front of their Father. A historic and world-historical day is coming before us, and a group of people who oppose with various words and actions are trying to block this road and destroy it. However, this little boy knows that everything will come to fruition according to your beliefs, and he is taking responsibility and guiding this path. Now, Father, take charge of the 8-day period, so that the day will be glorious. This child earnestly longs for and desires that the day will come when we can praise your glory and honor throughout all peoples and nations.
\n\nThank you for being with us during your 40 days in Korea. Don\'t let all of this obscure your glory, and become a song of welcome and a voice of joy on your own journey. I long for and long for you to come back.
\n\nFather, now that that incident has passed, the International Mobility Team, which is now in Japan, will come to visit Korea. In the meantime, there are still many things we need to prepare for. We must have international prestige, fulfill our mission as our country and our home country, think for ourselves what we will leave in front of them, and reflect on our own image. It should become the focal point of trust as the image of the heavenly family all over the world by showing an image that is not ashamed in front of the sky, but rather, your children in Korea who are afraid that they will become the focus of criticism. Knowing that there are many who do not know this, I earnestly hope and desire that the Father instructs and educates them.
\n\nHelp us to show that we have nothing and nothing, but we love the sky and do our best for the sky, that we are devoted to you even though we wear ragged clothes, and that Heaven is young in our deep hearts. I know that that is the only responsibility and mission of the children in their home countries today. When we think of that which we have nothing else to show, we earnestly pray that you will allow us to become a strong and tenacious flock, built with the endurance to overcome the deep path of suffering in our lives, while appreciating our inner worth. I wish and want.
\n\nPlease bless the children all over the world this morning, and your Father will lead the way for all the children centered in the East Garden and the young Americans representing the world are preparing to go to this place. We ask you to protect and guide us so that we can achieve the beauty of victory. Father, we want to spend a month with your name now. In Japan, we are preparing for the conference on February 13th, so please join us in person. I earnestly ask you to guide the world with a new banner of unification and to guide your mind and body so that your mind and body can acclimatize to the new echo of heaven, with the help of countless angels in the spiritual realm. I have spoken all the words in the name of True Parents.
\nAju.
\n(1975.2.1)
    </string>

    <string name="pr_champumo_3t">
Father, spring truly symbolizes liberation, so we must once again miss the joy of being embraced by your love. Since spring promises a new start, we must make a new start in the arms of Father\'s love. Just as all things harmonize in spring, please allow us to be embraced by your Father\'s love so that we can restore our identity that can harmonize with the universe.
\n\nJust as spring creates a bond between song and dance, we should also miss the times when we can do that in the arms of Father\'s love, centering on Father\'s love. Just as this spring is a place of rest centering on your will, please allow us to be able to miss this time of resting in the arms of your love.
\n\nFather, by inheriting all of your inner story, help me to miss the original human being who was able to start in hope in the Garden of Eden and to fall in love with you in hope. I earnestly hope and wish that you will be able to feel that kind of connection in this spring and give me infinite thanks to my Father, and allow me to become such a garden of hearts.
\n\nThis time today is a time to worship in front of Father, so you personally drive and accompany us wherever your name is praised. Please kindly stay there. It is not the liberation of only humans, it is not the beginning of only humans, and not only humans, but Father must receive liberation, Father must see the beginning, and Father must become the center of peace.
\n\nWe must honor you as a Father who forgets your prestige and can dance and sing with open arms. We must be the ones who can provide the eternal place for you to rest, so I hope and pray that this spring will allow us to learn such wisdom through this spring. Please allow all these moments of worshiping you in this short time to be a time for us to cultivate an unforgettable bond of heart, and establish a condition for us to be deeply embraced by your love.
\nAju.
\n(1968.4.21, p. 1476)
    </string>

    <string name="pr_champumo_4t">
Father of love, you created Eden beyond the ideal you had before the foundation of the world, but because of the fall of the first human ancestors, who should be your natural counterpart, all beings on this earth could not live there, and the world was connected with it. It makes me think that the world has become so sad that I can\'t even make it. This is sad for the Father, and sad for all of creation. We have come to know that the creators of such a sad result are none other than the created humankind, Adam and Eve, the ancestors of mankind.
\n\nSons and daughters born as direct children of their Fathers were supposed to be good, but when they look back, they left a lot of regret in the history of mankind because they failed to fulfill the responsibilities entrusted to them. We come to know how great the effort must have been. We earnestly hope and hope that as we count the hard work of that Father in our hearts, we will once again deeply realize how embarrassed we are in front of you.
\n\nFrom the day you lost Adam, how hard have you worked to find someone you can trust? Also, how many people have you been looking for who will take responsibility and fight for your Father, and how long have you been looking for someone who can inherit your Father\'s full authority? When we think of this, we cannot help but feel once again that it was Father\'s regret that there was no such person on this earth, and that it was a part of human history. In this way, Father has been walking through a long and winding road of sad history for 6,000 years.
\n\nHe endured sorrow when he was sad and came out without a single pause until today as he took responsibility for everything. Humans are struggling on a dark road at night, but please remind us once again that Father is struggling to provide for human history in the darkest of times. I earnestly hope and wish that you will realize that it has become a reality. Also, please help me realize how sad it was for you to come to me while wandering the back of history for 6,000 years.
\n\nWhen we find out that the steps of my Father\'s hard work, who wandered from country to country, city to city, while being driven in front of countless peoples and nations, came to a halt in this Korean river today, we realize that we are truly ignorant of the Father. feel it again. This nation did not know that Father\'s providential hand was centered on this three thousand-li peninsula and thirty million people. Even our good ancestors who came to this earth did not know it.
\n\nHowever, as the time came, I came to realize that my Father\'s providential hand was moving around this nation. Considering these things, from the past to the present, this nation has no choice but to tell the Father that it has no face. Moreover, since our Father has placed us in the gift of love, who are not even able to respond to the Father\'s compassion and love, you humbly worship the Father from the standpoint of representing this nation, this river, and all peoples with a sincere heart. I earnestly hope and desire that you will allow me to become the children of In the course of history, an era that the Father hoped for has passed and we are standing at a crossroads where we can usher in a new day of history, so please remember your sons and daughters who participated here today.
\n\nPlease take control of each person\'s heart, and if there is content in the heart that was lacking in the past, please let it end here. Therefore, I sincerely hope and pray that God will allow us to become sons and daughters of our Father who can welcome the new year toward the promised world while reflecting on the past when we failed to achieve the reality of victory in the face of a new will.
\n\nWe know that those who are lacking cannot stand before the Father. But because of the gift of your love, we have fallen before your knees, so please accept us at this hour. I long for it and long for it. If the Father does not recognize us, where else can we be more pitiful than we are? Even in the midst of being driven and driven out by the world, we endured. Even in the midst of persecution, we are the ones who came out only to look up to the Father and appeal to us, so please have mercy on us once again at this time. We set up a 7-year course that no one else knew about and fought hard on this road. Father, during that time, persecution was so severe that there must be people who walked away from this road with tears in their eyes. So, have mercy on their heartfelt remorse, who are unable to contain their embarrassment before the Father. Even if I cannot raise my face in front of the Father because of my disrespectful heart, I earnestly hope and wish that you will remember those who call on you with only one heart.
\n\nAlthough we are poor and lacking, we were able to get to where we are today thanks to the protection of our Father. Therefore, I sincerely hope and pray that you will lead me to endure until the day that you promised, and allow me to give thanks to your children who have worked hard for this cause until now. We earnestly hope and wish that the Father will be in control of everything we do today, and that you will allow this time to be a time of resolution and resolution to start again toward a new world of promise in the new year.
\n\nFather! Our 21-year career is a long one, but when I think of my Father\'s sad and long history of 6,000 years, I realize once again that there is no one more pitiful than your Father, and there is no one more lonelier than your Father. We apologize to our Father, regretting our past, when we promised loyalty to our Father, but failed to fulfill that loyalty and promised filial piety but failed to fulfill it. I long for and long for you.
\n\nFather, there are your sons and daughters all over the country who remember and celebrate this day and pray before you with all their heart and soul, so please embrace them deeply. I earnestly hope that you will embrace me with your heart of love. Your sons and daughters are gathered here at this hour, so please encourage them. I earnestly hope that you will personally give advice to the sons and daughters who have not been able to gather together with the words of the Father. Make the whole thing become one with your will so that there is not even one small thing that is inconsistent with your will.
\n\nTherefore, we earnestly prayed for the glory that the Father intended on this earth to be revealed so that the road would be with us.
\nAju.
\n(1967.12.31, p. 1479)
    </string>

    <string name="pr_champumo_5t">
Dear Father, I once again kneel and apologize for the shame of our ancestors in the face of Your holy will to block the flow of history and build a shield of victory. Father , we are truly ashamed in front of your hard work.
\n\nIt is worthy to throw away these descendants of the fall ten million times, but since you are a creative entity that cannot be abandoned, you come to think of the fact that you have followed the path of restoration by principle. In the process, many people came and went, and many people passed through this land amidst the twists and turns of battles and sorrows, but I came to think that they went to the spirit realm and stayed in the sorrow that they could not hide their shame in front of you.
\n\nThere was no one who could comfort your feelings of being unable to be happy whether you looked at the earth or the sky, and there was no son or daughter to whom you could share your story by becoming a companion of your heart. Furthermore, there was no bridegroom and no bridegroom as long as they could dwell in your loving home. Dear Father, furthermore, there were no parents who could boast of how much you loved them, and there were no children who loved them before them. Thus, there was no one on this earth who could comfort his Father, who could not solve the sorrowful history of not seeing the completion of the four-position foundation.
\n\nAmong the fallen descendants, no one knew that it was the human beings living on this earth who had to go back and correct all these atrocious circumstances. Dear Father, I came to know that, following your existence, many people passed with death, and there were many stories that were higher than trying to block the historical Han\'s high road through the blood of martyred ancestors. (p. 1480)
\n\nYour holy will who founded Judaism, Jacob built a base for victory by fighting an angel at the river Jabbok, and the foundation of hope to see the beginning of many history. I\'m sorry I didn\'t finish it. So, through the course of 2,000 years after Jacob, you sent the Messiah on the basis of the external form of the nation, centering on the standards of individual, family, tribe, nation, and nation in the will of the Father, but you had no choice but to look at the misfortune of Jesus Christ. (p. 1480)
\n\nNo one knew that the Father\'s will, who put the splendid and triumphant Roman dominion under His sovereignty and drew a world of unification for all ages, was left as a bleak history due to the unfortunate day of Jesus. Thousands of Christians today are praising his death on the cross as a ground of glory, paving the way for his own resurrection, and as a banner of liberation. No one knew how great your sorrow was to help you realize those sad facts and how deep the twists and turns of Jesus Christ\'s pathetic heart were. (p. 1481)
\n\nYou have personally witnessed the sorrow of history that left many twists and turns of sorrow and the fact that Christianity was driven by the force of the enemy from the Roman Empire and the chosen nation of Israel and suffered the injustice of being shot down by numerous cavalrymen. And while watching the scene personally, there were ten million times that I would retreat and fall into despair with a painful heart that I had to take the lead. No one knew the story of my Father who had to stand. (p. 1481)
\n\nFather, the passing historical era has split into the form of a sovereign state, and the rulers of the state have changed a lot, but the heart of your love cannot be changed and the principle of creation you have established cannot be changed. The more the changeable environment unfolds, the more you realize how great your loneliness was when you were in an unchangeable position. Today, at this time, there is a wish to forget the countless history of twists and turns left in front of you. I earnestly hope that you will be able to receive comfort from this time of proclaiming. (p. 1481)
\n\nHowever, I am well aware of all the stories left behind in the sorrow of the historical era, the numerous twists and turns, and the unfortunate stories in which you had to cover the ground for victory while defending this child. The sad facts that made Christianity the enemy, the free world the enemy, and the communist world the enemy and put them in a position to point their guns at the enemy, are because of the Korean people who failed to fulfill their responsibilities today, and they do not know all the indemnity course of the will of heaven. It was because of ignorant people. That is why we are well aware of the historical twists and turns. (p. 1481)
\n\nFather! Now is not the time to blame anyone, but in the midst of this crucifixion, the sad facts about the Adam family, the sad facts about the Jesus family, the sad facts about our family, the sad facts about the Israeli people, The sad truth, the sad facts about Korea, and the fact that the world that should be built anew by covering all that has spread the history of sorrow in this world has not become a base of happiness in front of Father\'s heart and will, but a base of sorrow. As children we know, we have to take the oath ten million times and work hard to wash away all the historical shame, so we have to become the unification family who can bear anything, even if we sacrifice the whole thing, and we have to become a member of the Unification Church. I earnestly hope and wish that you will realize this fact today. (p. 1482)
\n\nFather, bless this hour today. It has now been declared that the 1st 3rd 7-year course is over. As the 2nd 3rd 7-year course has begun in heaven and on earth, please help us establish a new son and daughter tradition, a new married couple tradition, and a new parental tradition. So, let us know that the historical tradition that should be established, centering on the tradition of the new parents, and of the new grandFather and grandmother, remains. (p. 1482)
\n\nWe have been fighting while envisioning that day, so in the Unification Family, we inherited all the traditional facts that others did not have and that others did not know. It should be a place where we can complete the four-position foundation as we look like our grandparents and grandparents. As this is not a national, but a world-historical, cosmic core altar, I am grateful for the gift of giving the Unification such an external and earthly foundation today. (p. 1482)
\n\nThrough this, all spirits in the spirit world will be resurrected at the Second Coming, Jesus’ sacrament of liberation will come through this family, and God’s will be fulfilled through the base of heaven on earth. We saw the start of the 1980s with the headline of \'Base\'. Father, centered on this ground, relieve all the emotions of the ten million stories, and through this, you raise the ground of offensive feelings that can restore through indemnity and expand the ground of victory from New York to the entire Americas and Father, I earnestly ask and want you to work so that we can achieve the right to liberation not only in the whole world but also in the spiritual realm. (p. 1482)
\n\nAll the spirits who believed in the Unification Church, including all the people praying for this day, all the unification groups congratulating us for this event, and all the people who remember the name of True Parents in their hearts and praise the victory of the day before the Father. In the 2nd 3rd 7-year course centering on the shared responsibility as a system by uniting all the spiritual people who believed in Christianity, and all the spirits who believed in Judaism, they directly lead the blessing on this earth Father, I am begging you to give me permission so that we can make a historic start from this time that we must move and lead the families of the Unification Family and Christianity. I prayed that the gift and love for longevity be with us forever, and I prayed for all the words in the name of True Parents.
\nAju.
\n(1980.4.15, p. 1483)
    </string>

    <string name="pr_champumo_6t">
Dear Father! When we say that there is a stranger heading to a distant country, we did not know that the stranger himself was God our Father, who is the main subject of eternal cosmos and the body of the ideal of love. The stories of ten million people are entangled in the heart of his Father, who has a relative relationship that he cannot forget for a single day toward the earth, but no one could understand the feeling of loneliness because there was no one he could tell.
\n\nThe fact that I have the so-called True Parents does not face my Father. Even though there were billions of times when I could comfort my Father who was troubled by such a story in the middle of the night, when I think about how many times I lost it because of my own tiredness, I passed that time and lost it, I think of the ineffectiveness once again.
\n\nThe more we know, the more we can\'t hide our face, and the more we go, the more we can\'t help but feel our own shame. We are the wretched ones who cannot take off the name of the heir who has carried the sins of our ancestors. I am well aware of how cursed and ridiculed it is to be able to take off the name of the heir who bore the sins of his foreFathers. Even though we are in this position, how can the ordinary people who live in a position that is closer to the Father\'s emotional position than others, but are living as strangers in the world, can understand your feelings? (p. 1483)
\n\nI was trying not to talk seriously about the Unification Church group gathered here. Please write it deeply in my heart so that I will not forget it. Today is the first Sunday since a cosmic event. October 14, 1982 is the day that this child was liberated from the day of sorrow 32 years ago. On that day, I am sorry that the heavens and the earth have found a moment that can be praised with joy. (p. 1483)
\n\nI knew that there must be a heavenly day that my Father wanted on this earth, and I knew the wish of mankind who gathered the hearts of mankind and waited for a hopeful explosion. If there is one scene in which we can rejoice and say that we have done well since history, if there is one scene in which we can rejoice and say that we have done well since history, there is one scene in which we can rejoice by bringing together the minds of heaven, the hearts of good ancestors in the heavenly world, and the hearts of mankind who live on earth and follow the path of the Way and follow the heavenly world. I understand that it is a scene where young people from several countries gathered and laid the groundwork for a historic victory to relieve the pain of Christ and relieve the sorrow of Adam in front of His famous will. (p. 1484)
\n\nAs an intangible entity in heaven, we have created an environment where we can escape from the sad environment in which humans cannot freely communicate and have the name of True Parents on the earth\'s floor plan to replace God. It is the environment in which the human race of the world has become that way through instruction in the same environment and range while eating the same meal in a flat land area. I have come to a position where I can. Thus, the fact that it has brought a historic start for us to establish a heartfelt bond with the heavens and travel to the world with more value than the environmental seat of the Lamb Feast centered on the bride and groom who have been wishing for 6,000 years I know it\'s amazing. (p. 1484)
\n\nFather, forget the sorrows of the Old Testament times. Forget the wretched cross of Jesus in the New Testament era, and forget all the horrors in Christian history where they vomited blood and were torn to pieces in an oil kiln. (p. 1484)
\n\nLeave behind such a background, and at this time of birth, let us not be ashamed of the course of our destiny that we must go ahead with the heavenly world in front of us. In order to be able to take responsibility for each individual, family, church, and nation, so that we can correct and maintain the lack of traditional ties in front of all the people of the world and connect them with a new tradition, if we do not give an order to I sincerely hope that you will accept us with a happy heart, since you have sworn to become a group of unification, who are willing to see the difficult situation and promise to move forward without rest, with hope. (p. 1484)
\n\nFor all ages, please grant me the grace to be with me so that I can keep my vows and promises to myself. Please watch over them until they become sons and daughters with a heart and become sons and daughters whom you can build up to be proud of and love. I have asked you in the name of True Parents.
\nAju.
\n(1982.10,17, p. 1484)
    </string>

    <string name="pr_champumo_7t">
In the world until now, true religion has not been found, and since we have not had a true couple, true parents, true nation, true nation, and true world, we have been unable to have the true heavenly kingdom. In order to restore through indemnity what all children on this earth were not responsible for, their parents came to this earth and personally fulfilled all their responsibilities to establish the victorious kingship and have the right to liberation on this Earth. (p. 1485)
\n\nUntil now, the good spirits of the heavenly world could not return to the earth because the devil had defended it, and everything that was connected only through the mainstream religious base proclaimed the name of True Parents so that all the people could flatly receive the privilege of becoming true children. could be granted. As a result, the ancestors of their own clan were connected to the mainstream religious circles, inherited the common ground established by all good people, and a victory plan was established in which they could cooperate with the Second Coming anywhere. (p. 1485)
\n\nWith the arrival of this time, the proclamation of this privileged True Parents has been made on this earth. This is not only to find my country, but to find my world and connect the eternal world as well as heaven on earth, because it was found as a price for the sacrifices made so far by heaven. We need to know that as we walk on the way of the cross, we have reached a moment of fulfillment of our wishes in front of heaven. (p. 1485)
\n\nDear Father, now is the time to be at the forefront of unifying my country, centering on this year\'s motto, \'Reunification of my country\', and proclaim before heaven and earth with the awareness that you are the leader not only of the unification of my country but also of unifying my world. To make it happen, I spoke with the title of \'Unification of my country and world peace\'. (p. 1485)
\n\nIt is only here that you know for sure that the world will be connected and the unified liberation of the country will be achieved. You have received all your resolutions. Today\'s words are the words of a sign proclaimed in heaven and earth. We earnestly ask you to mobilize the spirits of the world to achieve a unified standard of parental perfection, resolve all the encroachments on the angelic realm, and accept it as the victorious conditions that can achieve the world of liberation. Please fill the whole universe with True Parents\' duty and True Parents\' right to love, which can be the sign of victory for all ages. In the name of True Parents, we pray and proclaim.
\nAju.
\n(1990.7.8, p. 1485)
    </string>

</resources>