<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_1t">
We have come to know that as long as God`s eternal hope remains, eternal hope remains for us today as well, and as long as the Will of God`s eternal faith remains, the Will of eternal faith remains for us as well, and as long as the practice of God`s eternal love has not been realized, the responsibility that we must realize the embodiment of eternal love will also remain for us today.
\n\nIn order to inherit the history of indemnity on this day, we must inherit the hope of 4,000 years and manifest it as the hope of 6,000 years; we must inherit the faith of 4,000 years and manifest it as the faith of 6,000 years; and we must inherit the love of 4,000 years and manifest it as the love of 6,000 years.
\n\nSince there still remains before us the responsibility of standing before you and of having to establish the hope of 6,000 years as eternal hope, the faith of 6,000 years as eternal faith, and the love of 6,000 years as eternal love, please pardon our present insufficiencies and inadequacies. Please pardon our present disloyalty and lack of filial piety. Please pardon our having raised ourselves up high.
\n\nNow the time has come when we must bring to fruition the hope of all people, and the time has come when we must bring to fruition the faith of all people, and the time has come when the love of all people must be manifested as one embodiment, but in what place has that one embodiment been brought into fruition? We are unworthy, but please awaken us to realize that we must adorn ourselves anew as brides.
\n\nWe know that today the people who must take charge of the central role of heaven and earth are the believers who have the Second Advent of the Last Days ahead of them. You want to entrust your eternal hope to those kinds of people, but we are concerned whether they are the people to be entrusted with it, and you want to entrust your eternal faith to those kinds of people, but we are concerned whether they are the people to be entrusted with it, and you want to entrust your eternal love to those kinds of people, but we are concerned whether they are the people to be entrusted with it.
\n\nHaving been entrusted with all these things, we must now stand as people who have become the tribe of eternal hope due to having become people who belong to your love and as people who are eternally unchanging in relation to you.
\n\nWe must stand as people who have become the tribe of eternal faith, and we must stand as people who have become the tribe of eternal love. Please allow us to realize that this kind of responsibility has been allotted to us. Today each of us must accomplish as individuals the purpose of Jesus Christ who is the victorious central embodiment of the chosen people of Israel. That is to say, we must prepare ourselves as the embodiments of hope, prepare ourselves as the embodiments of faith, and prepare ourselves as the embodiments of love, which represent the whole.
\n\nNow after the arrival of the Second Advent we must become embodiments representing everything Jesus did after he came to the earth; that is to say, it will not do unless we stand as the embodiments of the hope of Jesus Christ; it will not do unless we become his successors of faith, and it will not do unless we become his successors of love. Therefore, please allow us to understand this clearly.
\n\nNow faced with the course of restoration which must overcome the crisis of the fall, we must be able to say. "We will take charge of your hope, Father. We will take charge of your faith, Father. We will take charge of your love, Father," and furthermore, we must be able to stand as centers of unchanging love in front of all people.
\n\nWe know that we will be qualified people who are able to represent the final glory of the Last Days only if we become victorious beings who are able to receive love in your presence. Therefore, please allow us to become people about whom you are able to say, "You are the being I have hoped for; you are a person I can trust and a person I can love."
\n\nFurthermore having received the grace of this judgment, proclaimed before everything of creation in heaven and on earth, we earnestly hope that you will lead us to become victorious children who are able to establish a condition of harmony.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 6, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_2t">
Oh beloved Father!
\nWe know that the purpose of creation was for you to see the garden of life, and that the ideal garden was a garden of truth singing your glories, and that the original garden was a place where we should have lived intoxicated, manifesting your inner internal nature and outer external form and harmonizing with everything in the presence of your majesty, centering on eternal, unchanging love.
\n\nOh beloved Father! Please allow us to sense the garden of hope that we are longing for today. Please allow our bodies to be able to move and bow down at the same time that we adore you with our minds while experiencing the original garden, and please allow us to be able to offer our bodies as offerings at the same time that we raise tip your Will with our minds.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will now entrust us with all the toil that you have gone through in order to find us, and that you will receive the glory.
\n\nFather! Please do not cast away a single one of our lives, and first of all, please allow each of our minds to be on fire with your eternal life. Then please allow us to become one with your mind of love.
\n\nPlease allow this to become a time when our minds and bodies become one with your life, and all of us become one and give ourselves as an offering. We earnestly hope and desire, oh, Father, that you will then allow us to become offerings who have no inadequacies, and whom you can be happy to receive.
\n\nFather! Please protect us. Please take responsibility for our acts of discernment. Please do not allow us to be invaded by Satan. Please allow us to be able to respond, centered on the Will you have bid us, by being enthralled with your Will, and please allow us to be completely obedient with our minds and bodies here. Then we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to be able to frankly confess and repent by revealing before you all of the inadequacies and all of the elements that are not proper that are within ourselves, at the same time that we are able to receive your love.
\n\nSince this people is enslaved in the midst of darkness, please directly reveal your works so that the people can be more than awakened to this. We earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow your works to be revealed through each church that you are moving and through your sons and daughters.
\n\nThe Last Days which you promised are near, and the time of grace which you will allow has come, but since we are still imperfect, inferior, and incomplete, please lead us. Please do not allow us to become people who cannot uphold your Will which we must uphold.
\n\nPlease let us become people who are able to prostrate ourselves before you while lamenting our deficient selves. Then please allow there to be many children of loyalty who uphold the Will of our true father in these religious bodies which are representing this people.
\n\nThen please allow them to be able to move into one all the religious bodies which are so divided. Please lead them to be able to represent the entirety of your grace. We earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will manifest to this people the Will of heaven which has been hidden, and that you will allow a day of blessing to come soon when you are able to boast about that Will and when you can rejoice in front of all humankind.
\n\nNow please allow there to be nothing in our minds and bodies other than the Will you desire, and please allow us to root out any traces of Satan, and please don't allow any root fibers of sin to remain. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to be able to prostrate ourselves as gentle people, as a humble group whose minds and bodies, ire centered on absolute goodness and have purified and purified themselves and do not boast about themselves before your original nature.
\n\nOh Father! If you have designated us for the sake of this people, and counseled us, and have been together with us, please allow us to be able to boast that we are the sons and daughters of our living father, and please allow us to testify that we are sons and daughters who are standing at the center of life.
\n\nOh Father! We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to be able to save this people from the evil hand of Satan by testifying to the fact that we are held in your grasp and by awakening this people. And we earnestly hope that you will establish us and allow us to lead this people into your presence so that this people will not be ashamed before the complete Will of our Father, who seeks to allow grace on the level of the people.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 11, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_3t">
Father!
\nAccording to the words you have commanded us we have come to know that there remains a peak which all people must go over. Today we are in the position of having to fight in order to get rid of our imperfect natures in the presence of your perfect nature, and there remains before us the fate of having to pass the basic standard of unchanging truth.
\n\nNow the time has come when we must show ourselves to the entire universe. When we think that a historical destiny remains, and it will not do unless we take dominion over the things of creation while resembling the holy majesty of our perfect father, we come to realize that the "I" who exists today must become a person who will represent the lamentations of our eternal father, and the "I" who exists today must become a person who will testify to the love of our eternal father, and the "I" who exists today must be able to fulfill the mission of restoration by conveying your words to the dark world.
\n\nBut our life of faith that we have lived until today has not been a life we can show to you; therefore, please allow us to come to our senses on our own and to be able to repent at the same time that we feel regret on our own.
\n\nNow we must place all the ideas, opinions, and ideologies we have, before the Will of our sacred father and do away completely with the being called "I" and we must resemble the character of our perfect father by restoring our original selves which are eternal beings, and since there still remains the course of the battle to restore our own selves which can be immersed in your glom please do not allow us to become people who backslide along the course of today`s battle.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become beautiful sons and daughters who are appropriate for you to choose and who can become your joy and your glory day by day in our daily lives and throughout our entire lives.
\n\nThis time is a time that reflects the ages of restoration, and it is an age when we have to pass the standard of historical judgment just as at the time of Jesus long ago. This is a time when the acts of John the Baptist who baptized people and the acts of the testimonies on the bank of the River Jordan when he presented the new Will to the Jewish religion, are happening throughout the world. When we think about this, we realize that the mission of John the Baptist remains as a mission for those of us who have come after him.
\n\nNow it will not do unless each of us builds the garden of rest where we are able to sing songs hand in hand with united hearts, in that one garden of goodness where Jesus Christ should have been able to return glory to you without Satan or sin being able to invade, while John the Baptist testified, and each of us has a foundation of the resting place of heavenly morality.
\n\nSince you have called us today for the sake of this kind of responsibility and you have chosen us today for the sake of this kind of work, please do not allow us to become sons and daughters who leave anguish and sorrow in front of the Will you have chosen.
\n\nSince we, who know that history is permeated with the indignation of thousands of years due to the failure of John the Baptist, have now been called by heaven and have been chosen by heaven, please allow us to be able to come before your throne and make a foundation for the providence that will fulfill the Will of the total providence of the entire universe. Then please allow us to be able to complete the mission which remains on that perfect foundation.
\n\nAnd while earnestly hoping that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to sing a song of the glory of rejoicing in the garden of joy, and who are able to sing a song of the glory of victory's hosannas to the entire universe, and who are able to return glory to the Lord who is coming.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 25, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_4t">
Oh Father who has toiled and carried out the providence passing through the ages and crossing the centuries to the Last Days, please allow us to be those who hope to realize the Will of your providence quickly on the earth and who are able to come forth and take responsibility on the earth for your struggles.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become dashing sons and daughters who are able to fight on the earth with Satan in Jesus` stead by inheriting the heavenly mission centered on your holy altar, Father. Please allow us to reveal our individual selves to you, Father. Please allow us to become people who work hard doing your mission at the end of the century in your stead by presenting ourselves before all people, and please allow us to become loyal servants who are obedient to the heavenly mission and to the words of the call which heaven is requesting from us in this age.
\n\nNow please allow us to build up an internal altar of heaven by opening the doors of our hearts, and please establish us as sons and daughters who are able to present our bodies with confidence before you as victorious sacrifices confronting Satan. Since we know that heaven is looking for people of courage who are confident and valiant, and does not want people who submit to the enemy in a senile, cowardly way, please allow your sons and daughters, who are gathered here, to be able to become courageous people of heaven who are able to even throw away their lives if it is for the sake of the Will.
\n\nWe know that the time has now come when those kinds of courageous people are needed. John the Baptist faced the Will of heavenly morality, and the people who followed him were on fire with the internal heart of heaven. Just as he proclaimed the new truth by confronting the corrupt Jewish religion, please reveal the light of the love of grace to this people through us today. Please do not take back from us your hand which is stretched out to us through your providence.
\n\nOh Father, who has called us from among many people! We couldn't help going even when we didn't want to, and as we followed we realized on our own that this is a difficult way. Since we know that it will not do unless we pioneer the one way of the battle with the fighting spirit of a pioneer and go forward as a champion of heaven, Father, if the way we are going is the way of your Will, please let us be able to not mind a path of thorns and not mind dangerous, high, steep peaks, and even if our bodies are ripped apart and wounded, please let us be able to pioneer everything centered on your Will alone. Please reveal only the grace of your counsel to us.
\n\nOh, Father! Please give us unchanging faith until we secure the day of victory by fighting and fighting and giving our lives for the sake of the Will. Please allow us to become your sons and daughters who have one unchanging center, who do not mind the environment, and who. like bombs thrown into the enemy camp, are able to explode for the sake of the victory of your Will.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 6, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_5t">
Father!
\nWhen will the four billion people who are living on this earth be able to be held in your embrace? When we think that our ancestor`s mistake of one day caused enormous historical complications to be bound together like this, we realize that your heart is filled with sorrowful tears and painful truths alone.
\n\nOh, Father, who has gone through the course of history through the long period of 6,000 years as though it were a day, with a heart that has been seeking your lost children in order to save this one being called "me," please have mercy on our pitiful and lonely selves who are standing before your majesty with hearts that are weeping and clinging to your heart which is calling out to us today.
\n\nWe do not have anything, not even a single thing to show to you, Father. Just we long for you, and we have come to this place with the earnest desire to go where you are, no matter what kinds of difficulties there may be. And because we have learned about your historical situation of having been falsely accused, we have come to this place and bowed down before you while longing to become true people who, on the foundation of such a situation, do not betray you and do not collapse. Therefore, Father of mercy, please love us, and please comfort our hearts.
\n\nPlease let this be a time when you counsel our weak selves, and when we discover that we have resented you in difficult situations of despair, that we cannot come to know our father of sorrow without tears and that we are unworthy people who cannot relate to you.
\n\nAnd furthermore, please let us discover that we are the people who must become offerings by representing the wretched state of this people. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to realize that it will not do unless we become the brave people of heaven who confront the enemy Satan by standing in the vanguard of the way where you come to us as we represent all the people.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that at this time you will not let any of us think of our minds and bodies as our own, that you will not let us think centered on our own selves, and that you will allow us to discover that we are people who must take responsibility for the remaining Will of restoration, and must think only of heaven and earth.
\n\nPlease let us be able to handle your entire mission and represent your Will by pursuing the public purpose, and by not standing in a position of pursuing our own goals. We earnestly hope that you will let us become holy people who represent the high priest who burns incense to atone for sins before your majesty.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 17, 1965
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_6t">
The more we think of how many twists and turns there must have been along the course of restoration, we cannot help but think that there remain many paths with crises of the heart that we must go.
\n\nWe know that there have been so many twists and turns along your course and that your situation has been so miserable because of the sin of our ancestors. The time has come when we must tread upon and go beyond all the grief of Golgotha which is due to the mistake of Adam and Eve. Having followed the path that you walked, we have found that it was the path of the cross. But, having followed that way which no one else knew about, while struggling with the heart of the pioneer, we have found that this way is not the way of destruction.
\n\nPeople ridiculed us, but you encouraged us. Many people opposed us, but your comforted us. We know that so many times you counseled us, saying, "I am with you, and the billions of saints in the spirit world are protecting the way you will go."
\n\nIn order to greet the dawn of tomorrow, it will not do unless we gropingly find our way along the path of darkness even in the midst of chaos. Because we know that we can greet the new dawn only if we pass through this path of darkness, until now the Unification workers have gone forth fighting, groping along this path of daybreak which others despise.
\n\nYou know that when we shed tears along this course, we wanted to be together with you who were shedding tears, and when we shed sweat and went hungry, we were struggling in order to establish the day when we could comfort you for the course of toil you have gone through.
\n\nPlease let us become people who weep out of concern for God, and who leave behind the grief-filled past as a memory. And we earnestly hope that you will please let us become your sons and daughters who are able to struggle and fulfill completely our duty as sons and daughters of filial piety, having forgotten our miserable and pitiable selves of today, while longing for our father of hope who smiles looking for the goodness of tomorrow, and who liquidates the grief-filled memories and the past days of grief that he went through.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 26, 1965
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_7t">
Please allow us to know how to attend our father who has toiled while going through the long course of history, and please allow us to know the situation of our father who has fought against Satan while worrying about us for such a long time. Please allow us to become people who know the heart of our father who has been concerned in order to guide us to the place of glory and to embrace his sons and daughters who were chosen as the hope of tomorrow.
\n\nPlease allow us to understand that we do not exist today due to our own will, and we do not have the glory of life which we are enjoying due to our own selves, and we are able to rejoice in the presence of our father today not due to our own efforts; rather, all of this is due to the grace of the mercy bestowed by our father, who has toiled throughout thousands of years of history.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to reveal the entire will of heavenly morality by representing the people of the world while at the same time representing the power of your grace.
\n\nIs there any group on this earth that knows that you hope to raise up humankind and receive glory, and is realizing that will for you? We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will guide us all to realize that such a group would be the foothold for you to be able to bless all of humankind and would be the foundation of glory for you to be able to bless the entire universe.
\n\nPlease do not allow us to look for the "me" of today in our own selves. Please allow us to become your sons and daughters who are not ashamed before the will of heavenly morality, and who represent history, who represent the entire universe, and who represent the world of the future. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us the glory of the joy of being able to be proud that we have become those kinds of sons and daughters.
\n\nFather! Have your sons and daughters who have gathered here today revealed themselves frankly to you? Have they bowed down of their own wills before the altar you have permitted? And have they become living offerings which are able to indemnify historical sin by sacrificing themselves? Have they become children who have become the new offerings that take responsibility for the sins of the present reality and who follow the example of the personality of Christ who carried his cross and went to Golgotha? Having fought with Satan in your stead for the sake of the glory of the future, do we have any actual results of a victorious glory?
\n\nFather, please allow us to be able to sing songs of your glory by having become these kinds of sons and daughters, and earnestly hoping that you will allow us to become faithful, upright children who are able to follow you for the sake of this one Will, we have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 23, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_8t">
Father!
\nIf we are sent as the representatives of this people which is asleep, even if we are facing a position of hardships and privations, we know that this must become your glory and your joy, and we know that if our sorrows, our despair, and our lamentations are not centered on ourselves and are for the sake of all humankind and the cosmos, there is nothing more glorious than that. Please act to fill us with hearts that are concerned about heaven and are concerned about the earth alone, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will make us into people who on our own cannot help but feel the mission given to us by heaven even if we do not want to feel it.
\n\nPlease let us clearly realize that we ourselves are now standing facing the Will of heaven, and please let us have hearts that are conscious of the fact that when we act, we act representing heaven. Please let us fight opposing Satan while representing the people, and please let us fulfill the responsibility you have given us. And we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will guide us to become sons and daughters who are able to receive and handle the blessings you have allowed us while representing the people.
\n\nAnd please allow us to awaken this people which is asleep, and please let us become sons and daughters who are able to appeal to you in order to save all the people of the world who are being swallowed by the darkness.
\n\nEven though we take responsibility, please help us not to stand in a position of taking responsibility for our individual selves alone. While placing our lives before you, we earnestly hope that you will lead us to become the people you hope for who are able to stand as responsible leaders, representing the people and humankind.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nAugust 4, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_9t">
We know how much you, who lost the original true people, have toiled in order to carry out the providence of restoration throughout the long ages. Please allow us to experience and feel keenly through our minds and through our bodies that you have gone through crisis after blood-curdling crisis in the course of history while longing for the original Adam and Eve.
\n\nWe know that having inherited this work, our ancestors, who accepted the Will of the providence, have also walked the lonely path of the cross in each place they went. We, who are facing the Last Days today, know that the providential responsibility and the historical responsibility still remain that we must go this way of the cross which we have been going but which still remains. Therefore, please urge us on once again with your power and your counsel. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become people of joy who are able to sing songs of your glory in the original garden you hoped for by having gone through all the crises of the cross which are left.
\n\nSince the time has come that it will not do unless we make a heroic determination and go forward as though we were going out to the battlefield carrying arms in order to accomplish this work, oh Father, please let us become those who make a heavenly determination and who are able to go forward and sweep aside all of the crises of the cross which are blocking the way of the history of the providence, and please permit us to have the power to go forward fighting the many satans who are blocking the way we are going. Father, we earnestly hope and desire this.
\n\nThe time of the providence is hastening the Last Days, and the waves of death have swept around us and without any exception seek to swallow us. We know that you know we are faced with a chaotic environment, and your heart which worries about us remains on this earth, as do the footprints of your hard work. We know that as you look at all this, your mind is inexpressibly anxious; therefore, Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will lead us and have compassion for us at this time.
\n\nIf we have lonely hearts, let us empty them out at this time and we must change them and take on your heart. If we are sorrowful and have inexpressibly frustrated hearts, we are in the pitiful situation of having to exchange them for your heart of joy and life. Oh Father who knows this, in spite of our being those who should take responsibility in your stead and relieve you of your difficult position, rather you are taking care of our difficult situation. And we earnestly hope and pray, Father, that you will bear with the fact that we are within the fallen realm and have to receive strength from you again.
\n\nPlease allow us to be able to live attending you personally in your garden of glory having appeared as people of victory on the field of battle, and please let us become your sons and daughters who are able to sing songs of your love having realized the entire Will you hoped for, and please let us become the sons and daughters you have sought for and about whom you can boast, standing us up before the world of Satan and all things. And we earnestly hope that you will allow us to become true children who are able to comfort our father with songs of by and glory as people who have accomplished your hope, your work, and your thought, and who are able to live with you forever as the sons and daughters who were found before you.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 22, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_10t">
Father!
\nEver since the day when the battle between Cain and Abel began, since the time when the foundation of death became established, the world of death has not disappeared and still exists. And while humankind could not cast off the yoke of this kind of environment, we of the present feel that your history of struggle has continued.
\n\nNow if conditions for lamentation remain, those conditions must be resolved, and if work remains that we must do, we must once again feel that it is the work of having to organize and settle the accounts of this foundation which has gone wrong.
\n\nHaving goodness as its basis, and having gone the way of crisis after crisis until now, the history of sorrow has continued as a history of getting up and running into sorrow again, and collapsing, and after collapsing, getting up again and running into sorrow again, and since this wall of sorrow has appeared before the eyes of this present generation, we have come to think that it remains as the world-level wall.
\n\nOh Father! In order to break down this wall, the individual will not be enough. And a few friends who have a common will shall not be enough. In order to do that you had us establish families by calling and gathering individuals together, and establish tribes by calling and gathering families together, and establish the people by calling and gathering the tribes together, and establish the nation by calling and gathering the people together. The hope that you held was that even if we established the nation, we would march onward toward one unified world.
\n\nBut we must think that it will not do if we do not have the individuals, families, tribes, and people who are able to atone for sin and take responsibility for your work according to the purpose of your Will.
\n\nIn spite of the fact that history became sorrowful externally because of humankind, how many sons and daughters do you have who are struggling for the sake of the world and who are taking responsibility for all those things here on earth?
\n\nPlease let this become a time when we each re-examine our hearts and have a new attitude in relation to you. Please let this become a time when we are able to consider once again whether we have become people whom you can remember as having the conditions of compassion and the attitude of compassion.
\n\nOh Father! We must come to understand that even while you are suffering, you respond to our requests and you are waiting for the time when you can give us blessings. We have come to think about how severe the suffering of your heart must have been, and how severe the wounds of your mind must have been as you faced the sorrowful history for six thousand years as days like that continued on.
\n\nWho is there who could remove this kind of distorted, blocked, heartistic grief? It will not do unless it is a true son of filial piety, and it will not do unless it is a true daughter of filial piety. But we know that it cannot be done by a filial son centered on the family, and it cannot be done by a filial son centered on the tribe, and it cannot be done by a filial son representing the people, either. Please act to let us know the truth that unless it is a true son of filial piety who, representing the world and representing heaven and earth, is able to appear and be proud before Satan, he will not be able to bring out the pierced and hidden heart in your mind.
\n\nWe earnestly hope that you will pardon the patriots of the past who were not able to realize that you were in such an awesome internal predicament, Father.
\n\nAnd we have earnestly and humbly prayed in the names of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJune 8, 1967
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_11t">
Please take pity on your children who have gathered here. Through your word we have come to know that we have inherited something called "our responsibility" together with an awesome history. We have come to know that the courses of indemnity of the individual, the family, the tribe, the people, the nation and the world still remain in it. But feeling that the remaining years of our individual beings are far too few to go this way, we must become your sons and daughters who of our own volition are able to reflect on and blame ourselves for not having completed that responsibility while in our prime.
\n\nWe have come to know the truth that we should not avoid the cross we are carrying; rather, we should say we will carry even the remaining crosses, and that even if we die as we carry them, if we collapse at the point where we are able to say we will go all the way and then die, the domain of the good world will have been broadened in accordance with the principle of heaven which is that through one such person you can harvest three people.
\n\nWe have come to know that you have gone forward with the strategy of first being struck and then taking away, and with the strategy of multiplying after dying, and with the strategy of losing oneself and finding the whole. Today it will not do if our Unification Church becomes the Unification Church for the Unification Church itself. It must become the Unification Church for the sake of saving the nation.
\n\nAnd the Republic of Korea must not become a nation for the sake of the Republic of Korea; rather, it must become the Republic of Korea for the sake of saving the world. And the world must not become a world for the sake of the world; it must become a world relating to the love of God who is the sublime source of life. We must realize the awesome truth that humankind can find happiness when they are connected with the path of life of the entire universe.
\n\nWe have come to know the fact that although we are low, base beings, behind the lofty, precious direction of our minds lies an awesome historical destined relationship. When we think of things like this, we realize we will have to go forward matching our footsteps to the direction of our minds by becoming friends with the loneliness of our minds.
\n\nWe have come to understand that even if we have to cut off all our external relationships, we must be on that side and that way is the way we must go. We have come to know that in going the path of moral principles today, we must find the destined relationship of the subject partners and the object partners of the mind and go forth.
\n\nPlease remember your children who have gathered together here, and please allow us to stand in the position of object partners centered on your love. Please let us become sons and daughters who are able to appeal to you shouting out loud staying up all night. Please allow us to be awakened to the fact that if there are sons and daughters who shed tears over and over again as they long for you, the tears of those sons and daughters will not be for naught.
\n\nWe know that the position in which we must stand is the position of God's sons and daughters. We earnestly hope that you will allow us to fulfill the responsibility of sons and to fulfill the responsibility of daughters in that position with minds that embrace the world and not just our personal beings and with minds that would save the world and then die. Please allow us to understand that it is the responsibility of sons and daughters to go beyond this world and fly because what you are hoping for is on the world level.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the lime Parents.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 14, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_12t">
We know that the course you have gone while pioneering a path of life was an extremely serious course, and it was an extremely sanctified course. We know that if the course of the remaining providence is a course of sorrow, we are responsible to block this sorrow, and we also know that a person who cannot feel the infinite sorrow of heaven will not be able to take responsibility for that sorrow. Since we know that it will not do unless we take responsibility for the remaining battle for the sake of heaven and for the remaining sorrow of heaven, please let us become people who are able to take responsibility for the sorrowful heart of heaven and the remaining battle.
\n\nWe know that it will not do unless we experience and feel keenly a greater sorrow than anyone else in order to cope with this situation, and we know that we must not become people who give up even if we are in the position of being falsely accused more than anyone else while on the field of battle.
\n\nFather! Since Jesus came to the earth and left, 2,000 years of history have passed, but the altar of true victory, which Jesus established on Mount Calvary and about which heaven wept together with him, has not yet appeared on the earth. We know that the time has come when the summit of Gethsemane must appear and the time has come when the summit of the world-level Golgotha must appear which connects heaven and earth, when heaven cannot help but move and humankind on the earth cannot help but move.
\n\nThere must be many believers who are equal to this kind of responsibility. But the more we realize that there are no groups to which heaven can come and be happy, the more we realize that this is a reality about which we cannot help but weep as we look at this earth because we are sons and daughters who are concerned about our Father`s heart.
\n\nPlease allow us to become people who are able to take on all the historical sorrows by becoming sons and daughters who are able to establish ourselves in your innermost heart, and hold on to your hand while offering you all our minds and bodies today.
\n\nWe know that it will not do unless this becomes a time when our minds and bodies are resurrected through the work of your personal actions. Please pardon that we could not fulfill completely the responsibility you gave us, and please forgive that we could not offer complete devotion in relation to you, and please pardon that we could not live lives overflowing with tears as we clung to your heart, and please pardon that we have forgotten the fact that you did not mind walking a path of toil in order to find our individual selves.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to control our minds and step forward centered on your heart, having realized everything that was inadequate about each of our pasts, and having made new determinations and new decisions. We earnestly hope and desire that through this time you will bring down the blessing which you will allow to this people.
\n\nPlease allow your sons and daughters who have responsibility for the day of victory to be able to handle that responsibility and that mission. We know that it is this people's responsibility to realize this will and reveal your glory. Since we know that there are unending trials along the course of completing that responsibility, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to go forth representing you, having taken responsibility even for this course of trials.
\n\nPlease also bless the many people who do not know this Will. At this time when people are being carried away by the tide of life and death, please allow many groups to appear among humankind who can become your sons and daughters who cling to you. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that from among the people on the earth you will allow many sons and daughters to appear who are able to stand before you and handle the entire responsibility, thereby allowing humanity to avoid the rod of judgment.
\n\nIf there are people who do not know about this kind of mission, this kind of age, and this kind of responsibility, please warn them through us, and we earnestly hope that you will allow them to become sons and daughters who can handle the responsibility and mission of the Last Days.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 15, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_13t">
Father!
\nDo you have any daughters who say that they are blessed with your earnest heart and your sorrowful heart and they will take responsibility? Please encourage them. Do you have any sons like that? Please hold on to them.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become true sons and daughters who are able to show you that we are people you can be proud of, people who praise your glory, who raise high a triumphal song before you, and who obtain the glory of victory on the final field of battle which you left behind.
\n\nFather! How much you must have hoped for the appearance of families and brothers and sisters you could be happy about, and how much you must have hoped for such a tribe, people and nation! We know that if we become like that, then all these peaks of Golgotha cannot help but become flat land, and Satan`s power cannot help but be swept away, and heaven cannot help but take the rod of this Will and urge us on. We earnestly hope that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who are able to be obedient for the remaining course.
\n\nSince we still are filled with grief that we have not been able to love you, Father, that grief must be resolved, and since we still are filled with grief that we could not fulfill our duty of filial piety to you, Father, that grief must be resolved, and since we still are filled with grief that we could not fulfill our duty of loyalty to you, Father, that grief must be resolved. In order to do that, we must fulfill the duty of filial piety and we must fulfill the duty of loyalty during this course of battles.
\n\nWe must quickly realize the Kingdom of Heaven of Peace where we can have faith in you, Father, having fulfilled the duty of loyalty and having fulfilled filial piety while attending you. For the sake of that day, we must be proud of today and prepare for tomorrow. Please do not let us become exhausted while going this way in happiness, and we earnestly request and desire that you will not let us become people who betray heaven. Please do not let us come to a point where we curse heaven.
\n\nPlease let the tears we shed become the source of life for all people, and please let them become an incentive for life for the many people who cannot help but go that path of tears. Please let our way become one which leaves behind destined relationships that are able to fulfill the duty of loyalty and be grateful. We earnestly hope and desire, Father that you will allow our sorrowful lives to become those kinds of lives and our path of adversity become that kind of path.
\n\nFather! Please bestow blessings upon this people and please bestow blessings upon all the people of the world. Please resolve the grief of the many spirit people who are waiting in heaven for the day of the Second Advent. Please let the world that you are able to govern be quickly realized, and the kingdom of peace be built on the earth and your grief and Jesus' grief be resolved. We earnestly hope for and desire this. Earnestly, earnestly requesting that the day will quickly come when we are able to return glory to you and be happy together with you when the earth is filled with glory and victory for eternity.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 26, 1965
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_14t">
Father!
\nWe know that you are hoping that we will become true sons and daughters of filial piety. Now please allow us to understand that we must make true families, true tribes, true peoples, true nations, and a true world.
\n\nFather! Until today, where in heaven and earth has there been a land where you could place your foot? Has there been such a clan? Has there been such a nation, or has there been such a world? You were always a foreigner. We know that if the wind blew from the East, you were driven to the West, and if the wind blew from the North, you were driven to the South, and you have continued to live this kind of phantom-like existence for 6,000 years.
\n\nWe know that due to the mistake of one day of our human ancestors, you have had to go through this complicated history. Father! Since we have the Unification Church which looks forward to the true concept that the fallen history must be recreated and reorganized, please remember us.
\n\nWe know well what kinds of results were brought about throughout the course of history by all the historical mistakes of our ancestors, and we also know well that a history of great grief and sorrow has come down to us. Father, we have experienced and felt keenly to the marrow of our bones that this kind of history must not be repeated again.
\n\nPlease let only the path of loyalty and filial piety which can be for your sake become the highest purpose of our lives. Please let us become your workers who are able to be grateful for this kind of position where we are determining our loyalty and filial piety to you.
\n\nPlease don't let Satan, who has been following us, follow any more, and please let us separate from him. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who are able to joyfully go over the high, steep mountains which we must go over in the future.
\n\nFather! We thank you that you have established this holy day and this nation on this earth. Since we know how much you have worked until this day came, and how much all the things of creation, which have been lamenting, longed for this day, please receive all these things in joy. And earnestly hoping that you will act so that we will be able to quickly realize the day when the world-level victory can be obtained on this earth.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJune 19, 1966
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_15t">
Father!
\nNo matter how active an interest we may take in it, the path we will go has already been decided. We must go towards that place today, and we must go tomorrow as well.
\n\nWhile going the course of restoration through indemnity, there have been many times when we were discouraged, but we are grateful for your grace which allowed us not to be discouraged and to endure and go forward.
\n\nWhile going through the long time of over six thousand years, how often did our ancestors entreat you, and how many times have we gathered before you of our own accord? But no matter how difficult it was you could not turn your back on it, so you endured over and over again, and we have come face to face with your situation where you had to bite your tongue and suppress your heart and endure even at the point when your children, who had believed and gone forth, poured out insults. Because of that, we must become children who struggle for your sake. When we do that, we believe that you will call us your beloved sons and you will call us your beloved daughters.
\n\nPlease allow us to understand that if those kinds of groups gathered together and made up a tribe, it would be a tribe that you could not help but love, and if those kinds of tribes gathered together and made a people, it would be a people that you could not help but love, and when that people took on the form of a nation and went out on the stage of the world, you could not help but bless that nation.
\n\nWe, who are walking the course of restoration through indemnity which others do not know about, wanted to be loyal to you in the past, but we did not know how to be loyal to you, and one day we had to stand in a position where we could relate to you, but we could not find that position. But now we have found a position where we can call out to you, and we are standing on the foundation of circumstances where we can be loyal to you.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become your children who are heroes of heaven, who are able to go forward being grateful and thinking of it as glorious to be able to work for your sake.
\n\nWe should not have a vague life of faith; rather, we must go forward step by step walking a determined course before your Will. We know that this is the way we children, who are going the course of restoration, must go until the day the Will is realized.
\n\nSince we have realized that it will not do for us to go on a smooth path, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become your children who are able to go forward while reproaching our inadequate selves and being loyal to you.
\n\nWe earnestly request that the world of the idea which you and we are longing for will be realized throughout all of heaven and earth quickly. For the sake of that, each of us must go through the sacrificial course of indemnity. Even if we are inadequate with our present strength, we earnestly request that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who realize your Will for you one day by giving our full devotion.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the holy names of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJune 8, 1967
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_16t">
Father!
\nThe day after tomorrow we will greet the beginning of a new month, and your beloved daughters will go out to various places in all parts of South Korea for your Will; therefore, Father, please protect this path they will go. Since a decisive day is approaching which you have prepared and commanded for their sakes far in advance, we earnestly hope and desire that you will take responsibility for this path they will go.
\n\nPlease allow a new heavenly fortune to come to this nation centered on this day. Please prepare an occasion which these lonely unification members can find. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow this time period to become a holy time through their being able to return thanks, glory, and praise to you sincerely even though they are cast out, pursued, and left alone as they carry out their activities.
\n\nFather! Please protect their footsteps which are going beyond the family and out towards the enemy troops while others sleep, Father. They are facing a lonely position in order to represent your loneliness, and feel lonely in your stead, and they are fighting in a desolate place in order to inherit your field of battle because they seek a place of rest where they can be close to you; therefore, when they are lonely, please be a friend to them, and when they are sorrowful, please go together with them. And we earnestly hope and desire that you will protect them every day inside and outside so that they may accomplish your Will.
\n\nAs women who seek to inherit a nation of peace, they are raising up a new banner, and since they are your lovable daughters who are able to be grateful to you even when shedding blood and tears for the sake of the liberation of the Kingdom of Heaven, we earnestly hope and desire that you will hold them and do mighty works.
\n\nPlease allow each place that they pass through, each place where there remain traces of the blood, sweat and tears they have shed, to become springs capable of resurrecting life. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow them to accomplish a foundation of victory through the goodness you do in secret, and that this will become a time period about which they can boast all over the world to those who have had things taken from them that there exists a day when they can receive love like this.
\n\nAs for us, if we say we are pitiful, we do stand in a pitiful position. We are pitiful people who do not have a nation. We are pitiful people who do not have a people. We know that we have the responsibility for the sacred mission of having to establish the Kingdom of Heaven on this earth and to break down the final wall of misery which many religious people have gone forward to do until now in order to select out a people.
\n\nSince this is a time when we can witness the reality of this earth where people sacrifice their lives for the things of this earth, we hope and desire that you will allow them to become holy women who are able to struggle in order to establish the Kingdom of Heaven even if they offer their lives or offer their families as sacrifices.
\n\nPlease allow a mind that seeks to end your sorrow to permeate each of their footsteps which are crisscrossing the country. And furthermore, since the standard they are hoping for is to hold the banner of victory and to sing a song of victory to heaven, we earnestly hope and desire, my Father, that you will allow them to take doing that as their creed, and that together with your name they will have minds that are moved and able to do that and they will live lives that are able to be filled with such minds.
\n\nNow these footsteps which have yearned for you will have to become footsteps that are able to weep endlessly for the sake of your Kingdom. We will have to put our lives on the line and go forth clinging to your knees and the edge of your garments. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to have a day of victory when, in your stead, we can cut off with a sword the wrong history which has continued down from the past. Since we have come to know that the day of realizing your desire for this nation is now close at hand, we earnestly hope that you will let us become unification workers who put on white clothes and kneel down, and work from the bottom of our hearts in order to guide the world to you, Father.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 29, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_17t">
Father!
\nFrom time immemorial when the saints and sages talked about the Kingdom of Heaven, they did not talk about it from a position of vying with their enemies, expressing all their wrath and anger from a position of being infuriated. Rather, we have come to realize that they forgot themselves even in front of their enemies` swords, and they, spoke from the position of quietly longing for and worshiping heaven, from the position of being embraced peacefully in the bosom of heaven, and from the position of transcending the environment of their enemies.
\n\nToday sin is seething up, and in this reality where the forces of Satan are closing in around us in this place were the historical enemy is stalking us, who is there who is going forth with a happy mind and a happy body not minding the enemy, praising your holiness, and intoxicated with your sublime and precious nature, living and dying for a thousand and ten thousand years? We must realize that only those who are able to stand firmly, asking, "Who can take away the authority we have as the chosen people?" are members of the Kingdom of Heaven.
\n\nIn order to follow the Will of Jesus who was sad and shed tears alone as a solitary person on the difficult path of the cross, we must know the historical fact that even in lives of continuous famine and starvation, and even when being driven into miserable pits, the patriots of old did not submit even to the afflictions of heaven and earth.
\n\nWe come to know the truth that Jesus endured everything in order to build the Kingdom of Heaven, and even when being whipped and killed, his determination was not broken. We must genuinely learn the truth that only the people who go forth carrying the banner of victory can form a relationship with the Kingdom of Heaven and can possess the Kingdom of Heaven.
\n\nNo matter how anxious we may be, or how lonely we may be, or how pitiful a situation we may be in, when we think that you, our Father, are even more pitiful than we are, we have come to realize that in view of that fact we must become sacrifices and comfort you, our Father, who is more pitiful than we are.
\n\nAs for attending that father and in pursuing the duty of filial piety, you are a being who has the heart of a parent and who is able to communicate to us your position, your situation and your circumstances. And when we think that when you ask us to become filial children you are asking us to go the way of death, and when you ask us to become loyal followers you are asking us to go a thorny path which rips and tears at us, we must feel how very lonely your footsteps have been as you, who are in the position of our parent, came to this earth.
\n\nKnowing that you are our father and, even though you came with that kind of Will in your heart, you were not able to ask us to realize that Will, we must feel a ripping pain which spreads deep into our hearts. Please let us become people who struggle to become children who are able to need you alone, Father, and who are true people no matter what direction of the 360 degrees we go, and who are able to comfort you by inheriting the single direction of your innermost heart.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nSeptember 28, 1969
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_18t">
Father!
\nWe know that it is your holy Will to establish its in this position and to resolve grief through us. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become children whom you cannot do without and who give our full devotion to that Will through which you seek to resolve grief.
\n\nWe know that our being here today is not because of ourselves. Since we know that the beginning is you, and the end is you, and we have entrusted everything to you, please take dominion.
\n\nThrough us, please restore victorious individuals, victorious families, victorious nations, and the victorious world, and furthermore, we earnestly hope and desire that by your realizing the victorious Kingdom of Heaven, you alone will receive the glory.
\n\nWe pledge that we will become children who are able to resolve your grief without fail and return glory and joy to you by taking responsibility for all the situations of unjust suffering of our Father who was sacrificed and offered up.
\n\nFather! We know that centered on us the destined relationships of three ages are connected. Our many ancestors, who have come and gone in the past, are earnestly hoping they can be relieved of their grief through us, and the people who are spread all throughout the world are longing for a day of liberation, and our future descendents are longing for the day of liberation. Therefore, please let us become people who are able to liberate them. And please allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to find and establish the way of humankind by respecting the Will of heaven and the Will of earth.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the Prue Parents.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 19, 1969
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_19t">
Oh Father!
\nThe way that you must go is the way of the wandering stranger who must pass through the individual, the family, the people, the nation, and the world. Since we must have true children here who are able to become sons and daughters of filial piety in relation to our Father who is going that way and who can guard that path of yours, oh Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will bend down and extend your concern to us.
\n\nWe must follow the path of the cross of the family which you are going, and we must follow the path of the cross of the tribe, and we must follow the path of the cross of the people. We must follow the course of the cross, this awesome task of the restoration of the nation up through the restoration of the world and furthermore, the cosmos.
\n\nIn going that way it will not do to have you lead us. Please allow us to become people who are loyal followers and filial sons of heaven who are able to stand before you and say, "I will carry the cross which lies before you." We know that it will not do unless we become like that. Since we have learned we must be like that, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to do that.
\n\nNow the thing most precious to us is going the way that you are going together with you, and living on the stage of life where you are living, and dying along the way that you are going. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become your children who know clearly that this is the purpose of our lives, and this is our greatest joy as a human being.
\n\nNow our minds must become completely empty. We must offer ourselves completely before you as empty vessels. Please let us cast aside our own dominion of ourselves and all of our ardent wishes for ourselves, and please let the center of our minds be filled only with your ideas and thoughts.
\n\nAnd earnestly hoping that you will allow us to begin once again in your presence as new beings whose minds arise from you alone and whose minds are able to take dominion over our bodies, we have prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 14, 1969
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_20t">
Father!
\nIn order for us to become your sons, if we do not want to leave behind an unfilial relationship in relation to you, we must find and go a path with more misfortune than you who have gone through misfortune. When standing in your position in your stead we become children who are able to be whipped in your stead, and we have memories which we can share with you, wouldn`t we then be filial children among filial children and loyal followers among loyal followers?
\n\nWe must head straight towards such a path. Please let us be people who are loyal and filial, who are able to struggle to carry the cross in your stead when you are carrying a cross, and please let us be connected to a position where we are grateful even if we lose our lives.
\n\nOffering our lives, we were in the position of saying we would offer filial piety to you, though up until now you have been struggling to find sons and daughters who would have that kind of filial piety in relation to you. Please let us realize that you will pioneer the path for us if we want to offer our lives and if we say we will fulfill our duty of loyalty in relation to you.
\n\nIf our wives block our way, we must go, even if we have to give tip our wives, and if our children block our way we must go, even if we have to give up our children. Furthermore, even if our relatives, our tribe, our people, or our nation oppose this path, we must become people who can give them up and go.
\n\nWe must realize that in order for you to lead us over the peak of death, Father, we also must be determined to die. You desire that of our own will we will take on the position of being sacrifices for you. We must realize that that position is a position of going forth, clinging to love in a father-son relationship. We know that it is the nature of love that the father would rather die first if his child is at the point of death.
\n\nWhen we remain in such positions, you will remember forever such a memorable day. Since we will establish a day where that can happen centered on the people of the Unification Church. Oh Father, please do not forget that day which remains.
\n\nThese people who are fighting to have a memorable day remain are hoping that this day will remain forever and ever. They are also your children who want to inherit the path that the son is going as their tradition. Please let us become sons and daughters who are able to inherit the relationship of that position.
\n\nWe know that in the course of restoration, without offering to you a memorable day when we can be together with you, we cannot go to your Kingdom with the destined relationship of loyal followers and we cannot be recognized as your sons and daughters. Therefore, please let us become your sons and daughters who are able to leave a memorable day before you and establish the duty of filial piety. We earnestly hope that you will let us realize that if we are able to leave a memorable destined relationship in that kind of position, then even if we face the position of death, that position is a position of joy and it is a position where we can be of help to you.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 15, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_21t">
Oh Father, who knows the situation of your beloved sons as we have been pioneering the way of the messenger until now on the path the unification foundation is going in Korea, we know that your mind has been simmering with so much anxiety throughout that time.
\n\nFather! There were many times when we could not help but think and put our lives on the line. While gazing at the exquisiteness of nature, you have walked the path of indemnity wondering whether we would listen to your words or not. When we think of things like this, we realize how hard you have worked in that kind of position and that you could establish your position in the historical ages even less than I.
\n\nWe have come to realize that this life which is less than 100 years cannot be compared to your sacrifices as you passed through the ages. Even if our entire lives started with the mission of the messenger and even if they end with the absolute sacrifice of ourselves, knowing that we are people who must naturally do that, we must become your sons who know how to be in suspense in our hearts and struggle while saying that we will fulfill our duty of loyalty and filial piety even more in relation to you.
\n\nAnd while thinking that we don`t know whether or not this might be the last time we eat, we eat while worrying that we might leave behind a condition for the enemy before heaven, and even if we cannot dress well or eat richly, if we think of your work and pray asking you not to worry, how very loveable we would be in your sight, Father! But we must realize that due to being sons who are in the realm of the course of the messenger, even if that love appears raised up in the heavenly world, it cannot help but be hidden in the world of humankind.
\n\nThe path that the Unification Church has walked until now has been like that. Father, if the time comes when you want to set forth your beloved son in Korea, due to the merit of your toil, we want to remove completely from our minds any conditions that could lead to grief having deeply considered the mind of our father who has been sorrowful because in the past the responsibilities were not fulfilled, and we want to attend you.
\n\nFather! The man who has lived in the shadows looked lonely and pitiful, but this must become a time when we can once again feel pangs of remorse because we were not able to completely fulfill our responsibility of loyalty and filial piety for your sake when you have suffered to such an extent.
\n\nWhen we think that you have pioneered the way until this historical time could exist, we come to realize that this place where we are standing today is a foundation of blessed grace which no one has had at all.
\n\nFather! Please let us pledge deeply one more time to you that having received the mission and responsibility of messengers, we will become sons who are able to fulfill that responsibility by heading out to the nation and the world. Through this opportunity, please let us go back home having made a new determination, and we earnestly hope that you will let us become sons who can receive your recognition.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the holy names of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 16, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_22t">
Father!
\nPlease come into the hearts of your children who are gathered here. Don`t we have the foundation of earnest hearts which are able to worship you? Now we must fear that even though we attend you in our hearts, when we go back we will have a sorrowful attitude.
\n\nDo you have sons and daughters who are giving all kinds of devotion and who attend you in the real meaning of the word? Please embrace them in the realm of the grace of the blessing with infinite love, grace, compassion and forgiveness. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will bless us to be able to feel endlessly your sublime, precious heart of love.
\n\nAt this time, do you have warriors who are seeking to have the necessary armor for battle by investing their entire beings totally, warriors who are rushing to the battlefield for the sake of the Will you left behind while longing for your Will? Father, please protect them, and we earnestly hope that you will bless them as representatives who can protect the nation and the world.
\n\nDo you have sons and daughters who are taking on the positions of high priests who offer sacrifices for the sake of many people at your holy altar? And do you have any sons or daughters who offer devotion during the times others are sleeping and who go a course of suffering during the times others are enjoying themselves, and who know that they must go that way even if it is a way of suffering, and who run into all kinds of suffering which others know nothing about in order to broaden the foundation of your altar behind the scenes of the people and humankind? Father, please bless them.
\n\nPlease let them realize on their own that they are the roots of the world, and the world is living through receiving the influence of those roots. Please give them hearts that are able to be grateful to you even if others do not recognize them, and that are embarrassed if others do recognize them. We earnestly hope that you will let us become sons and let us become daughters who are able to attend you, Father, with hearts that are grateful even when others don`t recognize us and who know that we cannot become one with you unless we go through this kind of destined relationship.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 8, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_23t">
Father!
\nUntil now every day has flowed by filled with sorrow. Therefore, we have shouldered the responsibility that the days coming in the future must not be filled with sorrow. We are the people of the Unification Church who have the mission of having to push aside the misfortune of this time when misfortune dwells in our land, and of having to plant expectation and hope.
\n\nAs for the current trend of thought with its despair, discouragement, pathos, and grief swirling around, we have come to understand the truth that we must become a main current of unification which can overcome this, and can leave behind expectation and hope. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who know we must find and live a more public value for the sake of going that way.
\n\nFather! Until now in the course of following the Will you are administrating, the Unification Church has gone through many sorrowful situations. There were not just one or two times that, having been driven into frustrating situations which cannot be explained to anyone, stomping our feet we wanted to curse, saying you didn`t exist.
\n\nEach time we think of those kinds of days which have passed, we feel once again how pitiful a being you are, having gone through moment after moment anxiously and impatiently without being able to speak. It was you whose face was wounded for our sakes, and whose hands and feet were wounded for our sakes. And not only that, we know that it was you who shed tears, sweat and blood for our sakes hundreds of thousands of times, taking on difficult public destined relationships.
\n\nWhen we think of the fact that you live with us in this way in our realm of life, an earnest desire to take your hand and never to let it go must well up in our hearts. Our hearts must well up with the desire to put our arms around your neck and to follow you on a mountain path or any path. Please let us become people who know that when our minds feel that with that kind of destined relationship we will have to live our lives carrying you on our backs even though our strength is inadequate, only then will we be in the position of having fulfilled our duty of filial piety and loyalty.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJune 4, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_24t">
We must understand that if a child has received benefits front his parents, it is his duty to repay those benefits, and if a person has received benefits from his nation, it is the duty of that subject to offer their his full loyalty to the king.
\n\nWhen we think that you have given us everything for our lives here on the earth, we must fulfill our duties of filial piety and loyalty in order to repay this grace we have received, and we must become high priests who with united hearts are able to represent the world you desire. We must realize that this is the way that the people of the Unification Church must go. We know that the life of people who have taken on that responsibility is such that we cannot sleep when others are sleeping, and we cannot rest and play when others are resting and playing.
\n\nToday the Unification Church is not just responsible for itself; rather, it is carrying a historical responsibility. We know that the way we Unification members must go must be gone with minds that limit our footsteps which cannot go quickly along this way we must run for the sake of the Will, and we must urge ourselves on even as we walk quickly.
\n\nBecause you have done that, Father, we who are your sons and daughters who hold up your Will must also do that. We have realized that if we want to leave this behind, we ourselves must become sacrifices. Because of that, even after we have gone away we feel sorrow there, and we come to feel that we must urge our footsteps back towards our work once again.
\n\nIf we have understood that our joy when we have found a family is greater than our joy when we have found an individual, then we also understand that for you as well, your joy when you have found a family will be greater than your joy when you have found an individual. And furthermore, we know that your joy will be greater when you have found a tribe than your joy when you have found a family, and greater for a people than a tribe, greater for a nation than a people, and greater when you have the world rather than a nation.
\n\nWhen we think about these things, we realize that we must understand how much you must have longed for the desire in your deepest heart which is to greet the day when you can give your blessings and embrace the entire universe with songs and dance as a sign to the entire cosmos of your joy over having found such a world.
\n\nAs for the many people living on this earth, no one was able to long for that and no one even imagined it, but you have given us this current position where we are able to experience and keenly feel this through our religion of unification which is advancing in the real course of our lives and not just in our minds. We know that all this is your love, is your compassion, is your mercy, is your overflowing grace, and we must offer our gratitude to you once again.
\n\nWhen we think that you have brought the blessing beyond the peak of the world level, we realize we must not become people who are fit to inherit the anguish of pitiful, shabby losers who did not understand properly the position they were facing and tried to just go beyond it as they were.
\n\nWe must be able to struggle in order to proudly bequeath the inexpressibly mighty favor you have bestowed upon us for thousands and tens of thousands of years through tens of thousands of generations of our descendents by giving our full devotion and giving our full loyalty in order to shine beautifully and bequeath it.
\n\nWe must understand that without doing that, we cannot establish our prestige on our own in front of you. We earnestly hope that you will let us become sons and become daughters who are able to praise your grandeur and infinite value and shed tears before your generosity and grace while reflecting on our pasts once again and critiquing our present situations once again.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the holy names of the True parents.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 11, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_25t">
Oh Father!
\nNow we must attend you, who are more precious than anyone, in the center of our hearts. If we attend our absolute father in that place in our hearts that cannot be invaded by anyone, and if we discuss together with you, and if we have lives where we can discover and live the three-dimensional nature of our own infinite value as an object partner together with you, our father, as the subject partner from a position of correspondence with you, then no matter how evil the world is we will be able to discover something different that can create a new foundation for the creation of history which can double infinite value even within that realm of evil.
\n\nWhen we think about things like that, we come to understand that the suffering that a person experiences is not suffering; rather, it can be understood as joy, and a person being on this earth where the waves of death are overflowing is not an unfortunate person, but rather a person who is living joyfully, and is a person who exists for the sake of joy.
\n\nBecause we Unificationists know that we must go this kind of path, the path we have walked until now was a path of suffering, it was a path of persecution, and it was a lonely path; but each time we stood at the crossroads where that persecution and loneliness crossed, it was clear to us which path we had to take.
\n\nThe Unification Church has been struggling in all directions in order to leave behind destined relationships of goodness which are able to flow and overflow to the way that intersects and spreads out in all directions rather than just establishes its own course, in order to plant the destined relationships of value which all humankind must have. When we think about that historical truth, even though we were miserable in the midst of that, we thank you that you have established us in a position where we are able to have hearts of gratitude which others do not know about.
\n\nFrom that kind of position we will put down our roots, and by training we will prepare worldwide footholds. And bursting with hope, we will have not only the hearts of national patriots, who are able to dream of one new world looking beyond Asia and the world; rather, we will go forth searching for a higher level value.
\n\nWe will seek to learn the duty of filial piety following the providence, and we will seek to learn the duty of loyalty following the providence, and we will live with patriot hearts for your kingdom and your family, centered on your love which no one among the people of the world has had.
\n\nPlease personally reach out with your blessings and be together with us eternally on the way we are going. May your mercy and love be even more present with our people who are going out knowing that this content, the value that is added in that kind of life, is of such a high level that it cannot be compared with any other value of the people who are living centered on the two-dimensional world of today.
\n\nWe know better than anyone else that we must not be weak, that it will not do if we are not stronger than the subjective force that leads this evil world no matter how evil the world may be. We know that even when we are lonely, representing your power, we should not be lonely. We earnestly hope that you will allow us to become people who influence the world in front of us.
\n\nThe people of the Unification Church of this age today are people who feel more strongly than anyone else that we must become families, become peoples, become nations, and become the people of the world who can be connected together centered on the world that cannot be divided by anyone.
\n\nThere is a movement occurring centered on the name "family member" where even the many races of different colors are living together with brotherly and sisterly affection such as has not been found and cannot be found within any race, and even when Japanese people, who were our enemies in the past, come to have the name of "family member," they become our brothers and sisters.
\n\nThat kind of movement is laving a foundation on the earth today and is rushing forward towards a stage of realization. Therefore, we earnestly hope that you will look on us with mercy, you will add your infinite power here, and you will allow us to become brave people of heaven who go straight forward bravely and courageously looking like victors and not like petty cowards, while going forth towards the position of the victory of our work.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 11, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_26t">
Father!
\nWe know that no one can stop the flow of this world which is rushing forward. Now we realize that the end of the world is approaching us. The end of the communist world has already been announced. The end of the democratic world has already been announced. In the midst of this end of the world, there must appear in heaven and earth a direct new movement where you are able to settle down comfortably. We have come to think that without doing that, heaven and earth will not be liberated for eternity; and will not be able to help but be covered with moaning, pain, and distress.
\n\nNow we must once again find our father whom we lost. Turning back once again from the way our steps were going, we must return to you, Father, and bring back all the realistic given conditions and all the systems of thought of humanism and materialism. In order to do that we must know our father, who is the subject of mighty power. We must clearly know our father who is the center of infinite value.
\n\nWe know that the issue is how close a relationship you and your children possess while living in the realm of daily life moment by moment centered on one content. Please allow us to be able to come to have on our own the power and value that are able to overcome and then overcome again in this realm of the historical environment which requires a second and a third liberation.
\n\nFather! The members of the Unification Church must now clearly know that you exist. They must know through their feelings in their daily lives and they must become aware through the actions of each of the cells of their bodies. Then we will all call on the name of our most high and precious Father, and attend you, and since we must become holy sons and daughters who are able to shed blood and sweat for your sake, please allow this, Father.
\n\nIf you are in motion, we must also be in motion, and if you are at peace, we must also be at peace. If you are happy, we must also be happy, and if you are sorrowful, we must become sons and daughters who are sorrowful together with you.
\n\nPlease let us go forth with bold and vibrant attitudes as sons and daughters of hope who must go towards the nation of peace and the Kingdom of H eaven of peace. And earnestly hoping that you will allow us to become the elite troops of heaven and the heroes of heaven.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the holy names of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nAugust 16, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_27t">
Oh Father!
\nHow hard have you worked in order to come to this earth? Since we have learned through the Principle how very hard you have worked to go this anguished course called restoration which no one knows about, please do not let us forget it.
\n\nPlease allow us to clearly understand that the mission remains that we must pioneer the one way of victory and fight and overcome the foundation of indignation which is in your breast by following in the footsteps you have personally gone.
\n\nEven though we, who are inadequate, say we will have faith and fulfill our duties of filial piety and loyalty for your sake, we know that we cannot go beyond a certain boundary because our bodies are limited. But you always came to us and held us, and you encouraged us in order to accomplish the goal we must reach. But we cannot express in words how many were the times that we fell down and caused you worry. We earnestly hope that you will forgive the fact that each time we did that we caused you sorrow and we caused you to carry more burdens on your back.
\n\nAnd today, too, if there is a family which has offered devotion for the sake of a day of victory while struggling for the sake of your Will, we earnestly hope and desire that you will shower thousands and ten of thousands of blessings on that family.
\n\nPlease let us be able to prepare the foundation of victory where heaven and earth are able to have give and take through the people who are offering devotion on the earth becoming one with the people of the spirit world. Since we know that due to that you will be made manifest and will act concretely in the entire horizontal world, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow that kind of destiny of unification to appear on the earth.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the holy names of the True Parents
\nAmen.
\nJune 29, 1969
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_28t">
Father!
\nWe must reflect on whether we who are in this place today have really become individuals whose tears come first while we long for you, and whether we have become a group that is living each day struggling and saying that we will become sacrifices of our own will for the expansion of the Unification Movement.
\n\nAs for the path we come and go on in life, as for the circumstances of our daily lives, where we eat and sleep, as for our emotional lives, where we think things are good or had, the things we think are good should be good because of you; the things we think are had should be bad because of you; and our coming and goings, and our eating and sleeping, too, the totality of our daily lives should be because of you.
\n\nWhen we think that our lives are such that we must live in a position where we cannot exist without you, we come to realize that the realm of possessions centered on ourselves is far too large Father, please personally appear now and let us realize that we must feel ashamed of ourselves; we must feel that we are children who must always be spurred on by you to redouble our efforts, and we must come to have an attitude of mind that is able to receive at least your sympathy.
\n\nJesus gathered together his beloved disciples, and to Peter, who could represent them, be asked over and over again, two and three times, "Simon, son of John, do you love me more than these?" And Peter answered, "Yes, Lord; you know that I love you." According to the number of times Jesus asked Peter that, we know that at that point he was not putting him in a strong position; rather, he was in a position of being admonished that he should feel guilty about his inadequacies and he should make a new determination.
\n\nNow if you ask any one of us that kind of question, we must be able to answer, "You know that I love you, Father, and I love your Will." If our Father asks us, and asks us, and asks us again, we must answer with confidence, "Yes, I love you." When faced with that question, we must weep and think about our inadequate selves of the past.
\n\nAnd if we have stood in a position where we can feel why he would ask such a question, we must answer, "I will become a person who fulfills the duty of a child just as I am." And when you call us and ask us to "Fulfill completely the responsibility of a child of heaven by representing the world," we must love you.
\n\nFrom the position of a child who is longing for your command we have been longing for that day to come, but while saying, "Now we will finally be able to accomplish what you want," we must go forward knowing that this is a path of destiny which we must absolutely go even if it crosses with death hundreds of thousands of times, and even if it is connected to a path where we are sacrificed as offerings.
\n\nWe are not hoping for the touch of your sympathy even when we are at the point of collapsing. Rather, we will determine to fulfill our duty of loyalty and filial piety in relation to you on our own in order not to be derided by Satan. And we will have to determine ourselves, saying, "Father, don't worry. Even without your cooperation, I am confident that I can overcome my relationship with Satan as an individual. No matter what sufferings there may be, I do not need your cooperation; and understanding that position as my own realm of responsibility, I shall follow that model."
\n\nWe are not hoping for your sympathy; rather, we know clearly that if we struggle to become sons who are able to comfort heaven even if we are destined to collapse and vomit blood, we will not be destroyed. Please let us understand clearly that if there is such a son, even if the place where he collapses is in the enemy camp, when you rush to comfort him without hesitation, it will remain as a realm of victory which Satan cannot falsely accuse.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 9, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_29t">
Father!
\nThe mission of the standard-bearers of the awesome new age, which the Unification Church members must accomplish from now on is spread out before us. We know that only a spirit of sacrifice which is able to offer everything to you and an attitude filled with devotion in which everyone is able to become one in relation to the Will you desire, can maintain this.
\n\nTherefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will please allow us to go following the way that you guide us with a pure mind which can do that, and to seriously inherit the Will that you are seeking to accomplish on earth, and to accomplish it by ourselves.
\n\nFather! Please allow us to understand how very important our attitude is now. We know that the more we appear before the people, it will not do unless we fulfill the responsibility of the subject partner. When we think of things like that, we must be careful of all of our actions, and we must show to all humankind the standard of character that has been established through the history of the Unification Church. And we earnestly ask and desire that you will accept us as your children who have no unworthy aspects and whom you can always praise and establish and be proud of, and who can clearly present the co-ordinates and the direction that humankind must go.
\n\nOh Father! Now the time has come to hold high the banner of the new destiny of the entire world and to head directly in the direction of the Kingdom of Heaven. We have established the awesome standard called the "establishment of the Kingdom of Heaven." This nation and this people in name as well as in reality are standing in the position of being able to follow with their minds the direction we are going.
\n\nFrom now on we must not forget that we have a great and heavy responsibility to gather together and offer to you, together with the people, an altar of victory by not killing this destiny and embracing it to our hearts while cooperating harmoniously.
\n\nTogether with the name of our Heavenly Father please let us wash away all the times that have come and gone, and please forgive that until now the Korean people could not fulfill their responsibility. We earnestly hope that you will love this people once more.
\n\nPlease embrace the pitiful established churches. We know well that it will not do for you to cast them aside. It is that Christianity for which you worked so hard for two thousand years, and which was established by the Christians shedding blood.
\n\nNow we know that together with us they must hold hands behind the scenes, and it will not do unless we bring all the people of the world into your embrace by casting out a net. Therefore, we earnestly ask and desire that you will accept us as people who are needed in establishing your Kingdom and who have the standard of the subject partner and the object partner. We earnestly hope that you will lead us in everything in the future.
\n\nAsking that, together with your name, grace and love will be together forever with everything, we have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJune 8, 1975
    </string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_30t">
Beloved Father!
\nAmong everything that happens in the flow of history; there is nothing that happens without a relationship to your providence. We did not know that in relation to the course for overcoming the fact that the history of sorrow was centered on Satan, there was a destined path of restoration which had to tear down the walls of the individuals and had to tear down the walls of the families, the tribes, the peoples, the nations, the world and the cosmos.
\n\nOur Unification Church members have come to know that in order to tear down these walls, we must find a realm of heart where the beginning of ideal love can pass through this world where the seeds of fallen love have been sown and have taken root, and that without doing that, restoration cannot occur.
\n\nCentered on this kind of heart, Jesus also taught us not only that we cannot become his disciples unless we love him more than anyone else, but also that a person who does not deny himself and carry his cross and follow Jesus is not one with him. That was an historical proclamation. He said that unless we love our neighbors as ourselves, we cannot be saved. If we are in a position of attending the True Parents and the True Heaven, we know that it is the hope of Heaven and it is the hope of the Parents that we love the world even more than the Parents.
\n\nWe know that heaven loves, and wants to establish as the representative of all the inheritors, that child who loves all his brothers and sisters with an even greater heart than his heart of filial piety for his parents, from the position of a filial son who is attending his parents. Therefore, all the children of the Unification Church who are here now will have to represent the position of filial sons and filial daughters who love humankind even more than the Parents.
\n\nIn that way we will tear down all at once all the walls that were connected to the realm of heart of Satan in the spiritual world or the earthly world. And we will claim the victory, and we proclaim at this time that we will become sons and daughters who are not ashamed to inherit the Kingdom of Heaven. Therefore, we earnestly request and desire that you will allow us to have no unworthiness in relation to receiving your blessing and not to be lazy in training ourselves for that kind of position.
\n\nWe have clearly understood that a person who does not love his parents and the world cannot enter the Kingdom of Heaven. Therefore, we will have to be in a position where we are able to love and absorb everything, even if there exists the Satanic world which opposes us here centered on this work. Since we know that it will not do unless we do that, we earnestly request that you will allow us to fulfill the duties of heart and of loyalty and filial piety with an unchanging heart in relation to testing and realizing whether we have become such people or not.
\n\nWe know clearly that only the person who has done that is the final victor, and is a person who can participate in the final glory, and is a person who has the right of inheritance centered on all love, and is a person who stands in a position that can be blessed. Please bless us to be able to sacrifice everything and to dash forward while going that path.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 11, 1986
    </string>
</resources>