<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_1t">
Oh Father of love!
\nPlease extend your hand and take the hands of your inadequate children and guide us. Since we have bowed down to you with united minds and bodies, Father, please take us and lead us and raise us up, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will change our minds into minds of heaven.
\n\nToday we have placed all the ideas we have about the present age before you, and since we have come before your majesty with the hearts of gentle, mild children, Father, please bring about your work of re-creation through the touch of your grace. Please reveal the fire of the Holy Spirit. Please reveal your love which has been held back and in the last days. Please open the door of the realm of death which has been blocked, and beloved Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow them to be able to bring to the fore your victory and glory. If there is an empty vessel, please fill it.
\n\nPlease establish us as living children who are able to return glory to you and to be grateful, intoxicated by your ample grace. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us the grace of your finding us to be your children whom you can love.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow our minds to be inclined to heaven\'s inclinations, and our bodies to move to the movements of heaven, and our minds and bodies to take the example of and to resemble your external form, Father.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 1, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_2t">
Oh Father who has promised the resurrection of life!
\nPlease find again the original external form which you created for us. Then looking at that beauty you will be able to feel joy, and you would be able to present us respectably before all the things of creation of heaven and earth, and we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will establish us as sons and daughters that you can be proud of.
\n\nOh Father! Please allow us to hold as precious in our minds your will of the blessing which you have promised since before eternity, and please raise us up in relation to heavenly morality. Please do not let us become pitiful sons and daughters who give an impetus to sorrow.
\n\nPlease allow us to become your sons and daughters who are moved to tears by your mind, and moved to tears by your nature, and who through our minds and bodies are able to realize the entire will you have established by realizing it before you have spoken it, and by doing things before you have asked for them, and by accomplishing things before you have even wished for it.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, oh Father, that you will allow all people to be awakened to your will, and that you will raise up a foundation of life for all people. On that foundation, peace will be able to appear.
\n\nNow please allow your sons and daughters who are bowing down here to become children who are able to receive your love and blessings with new hearts. Please allow our bodies to possess the beauty of glory you have blessed us with and to possess the beauty of love.
\n\nAre there any sons or daughters embracing the bitter roots of sin which can create anguish and are not acceptable to you? Father, please act at this time and appear to us. And through your personal touch please bring about the work of re-creation.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of our beloved Lord.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 25, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_3t">
We know that you are lamenting that on the earth there are no embodiments of your words of goodness which you spoke in the Garden of Eden, saying, "It is good; it is good." We also know that as long as the condition remains that we must find again the lost words of goodness, we won\'t be able to find embodiments of goodness.
\n\nFather! Please reveal the words of goodness. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that through the words of goodness which have been found, you will please command us again, and through our minds and bodies you will carry out your special work of re-creation.
\n\nFather! Please come to us and establish the center of your words and carry out your work of conditions to be able to win over the authority of Satan. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that if our minds and bodies are held in the satanic realm, you will separate and divide us through your word and you will let us receive your seal of sanctification.
\n\nFather! Since we know that our minds need power in order to be reborn, please act through your power and please act through your omnipotence. Earnestly hoping that you will cast out all concepts of evil, reveal the words of life which can give resurrection, and carry out the work of the resurrection of re-creation.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 2, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_4t">
My Father!
\nWe know that in the beginning you had a will of goodness and you created all the things of creation, and through the standard of your original nature you existed as an unchanging being. But because humankind could not become an object of goodness to their father who was like that, humankind could not realize your ideal for us, and we know that humankind came to face everything a long way away from the standard of a good conscience. And furthermore we know that this has been the lamentation of heaven and all the things of creation.
\n\nOh Father! For us there still remains the path of providential destiny which must be found even if we have to offer our eternal lives; and since the mission remains that we must go that path until the end, please urge us to be able to go that path through your mighty omnipotence. Since elements of evil invade through our bodies and block our minds which are heading towards goodness. Oh Father, please guide us so that in this battle our minds which are heading towards goodness will not be restrained by our bodies and defeated.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will please let our minds be led only by the power of goodness and the power of love, and please let us find you and harmonize as unchanging beings; please let us resemble your external form as eternal substantiations who cannot be separated, and please hold on to us so that we may attend you eternally, Father.
\n\nFighting with evil throughout the long course of history, we have been covered with wounds, and the roots of sin have penetrated into our bones and flesh. The responsibility to remove them is ours, but since we are so inadequate, oh Father who has the power of life, oh Father who has the power of omnipotence, oh Father who has the power of re-creation, please extend your omnipotent hand one more time to our inadequate minds and bodies, and remove all the elements of evil which are holding us in the shadow of death. And we earnestly hope and desire that you will please reveal heaven\'s direct works of life which can raise up minds of victory stimulated by that center.
\n\nThen please raise up the power of resurrection from within us, and we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who are able to bring about the work of resurrection by representing that center in the circumstances we face.
\n\nPlease lead us so that we will not become those who lament due to being in an unsatisfactory position, and please allow us to have the qualification of being your true children by being victorious in the battle with the enemy satans who are blocking our way as we rush along the course to the position of perfection.
\n\nAnd please guide us to become sons and daughters who can be proud in front of billions of satans. And then please allow us to be able to fight and have victory over billions of satans and to carry the weapons that the heavenly forces and angels carried in their stead.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 6, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_5t">
Father!
\nPlease allow us to come to understand all the content of those grief filled 6,000 years and your internal situation during that time. And if we come to understand something, we ask you to please allow us to be able to take responsibility for it to the end.
\n\nAt the same time that we feel the preciousness of the responsibility of the person who conveys your words, we have come to understand that the responsibility of the person receiving the words is just as precious. In fate, we have come to understand that the responsibility of the person receiving is more important than the one giving.
\n\nThe time of giving is one time, but since we know that the time of receiving must continue forever, please allow us to become people who are able to keep for eternity the truth that we received one time from heaven. And please allow us to be able to keep forever the life that we received one time from heaven. And please allow us to be able to keep forever the love we received one time from heaven. We earnestly hope and desire, and we request that you will allow us to be able to understand that only if we become like that will we be able to become your true children.
\n\nSince our minds are empty at this time, please fill our empty minds, and since we repent at this time for the scores of times we have betrayed heaven until now, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will bear with us.
\n\nIn that way we will find the key of truth, and we will find the key of life and love. And as we open the door of the remaining universal truth, life and love, please allow us to become children who are able to relieve the internal situation for you who are the center of the cosmos. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to be able to go forth to the position of true children whom you can believe. We earnestly ask you to please separate all the things that remain, to fill in all the inadequacies, and to please guide us until the eternal Kingdom of Heaven is eternally realized.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 17, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_6t">
Beloved Father!
\nWe know that the only thing remaining before us is the will of heavenly morality. And we know that the center of that will is you, Father, and the True Parents. And furthermore we know that the people living on the earth must become the true sons and daughters of the True Parents.
\n\nAnd not only that, we also know that what you want of us is to have all humankind become one brotherhood, and to have all humankind become your true sons and daughters.
\n\nFather! We also know that the sin of blocking the way of and violating the people who want to stand in the position of the sons and daughters you are hoping for is a greater sin than any on this earth. Violating the true sincerity of humankind is also a sin which can not be borne. But since we know that causing the true love of brothers to be lost is an even greater sin in relation heavenly morality, we earnestly hope and desire that you will guide us to become those who do not forget this.
\n\nFather! In the presence of heavenly morality which is seeking to awaken us from a deep sleep, when someone says he is not able to get up because of another brother, how can he say that he is being led by the shepherd? Please don\'t let us stand in that kind of position.
\n\nBy representing heavenly morality, let us take responsibility for that brother as well. Please allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to prepare hidden altars. And please establish the ideal of the eternal son which you desire, and please let us realize that your gaze is always upon us.
\n\nPlease allow us to feel the touch of your love, and please allow us to hear your voice appealing to us. and we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to experience your heart which is aching and exhorting us, to resemble your heart, and to follow the example of your internal character, and to become the head disciples of Jesus Christ, who can be grateful bowing down to you even if we die ten million times for the Will.
\n\nFather! Please let us fight with hearts of righteous indignation and hearts for the common good representing heavenly morality, facing the many enemies who are blocking the way. Please let us go forward enduring again and again in order to offer you the day of victory. On greeting the day of victory, please allow us to be able to report to you the sorrows that we endured during that time, and please lead us so that we will be able to go until the place where we can cling to your precious hand and receive comfort.
\n\nPlease allow us to awaken all humankind who are sleeping on this earth. Since the entire world which you created is in the realm of lamentation, please mobilize us and let us restore this, and please allow to all humankind the wisdom of heaven so that all may become people of the Kingdom of Heaven by each individual fulfilling his responsibility.
\n\nPlease let us become sons and daughters who are able to go forth without minding even if it is a course of struggle. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become heaven\'s elite troops who are able to go forth for the Will alone even if we have to give up everything we have.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMay 19, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_7t">
We have not been able to bring anything to give you, Father. Since we have come as objects of your concern, Father of compassion, Father of omnipotence, Father of love, please do not leave us as we are now. It will not do unless you take responsibility for us. Since millions of satans are surrounding us and are seeking to take our lives, Father, please protect us.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will please allow our individual beings to be submerged in the midst of your deep love and to be able to sing of your glory with our minds. And, Father, please allow this time to be one in which we can bow down to you here.
\n\nSince we know that in our lives there remain actions that you do not approve of, and many elements that cannot appear before your Will, oh Father of compassion, Father of omnipotence, we earnestly hope and desire that you will please appear with your power of victory, and grant us your touch of re-creation.
\n\nSince we entrust everything to you, Father, please receive us as living sacrifices, and please guide us so that not a single life will go outside your will.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become true sons and daughters who are able to say strongly that you are our father even if we are attracted by Satan.
\n\nSince there are lonely sons and daughters who are fighting difficult battles today, we earnestly hope that you will allow us to testify that we are your sons and daughters; and raise up your omnipotent power of re-creation.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nSeptember 15, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_8t">
Please bear with our not being able to feel love when we come before your majesty, and please bear with our not having been able to work hard for the world.
\n\nWhen we consider our father\'s toil and our father\'s sorrow and our father\'s course of hardships, please allow our minds to be able to feel sorrow, please allow our minds to be able to feel the hardships, and please allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to feel that pain.
\n\nSince we know that it will not do unless we become those kinds of sons and daughters, oh Father of love, please allow us to have the love of heaven. And since we are sons and daughters who have gathered to find heaven while we are living, even if we cannot stand before you in view of all our sins, please bear with us, for we have bowed down before you longing for the grace of resurrection which you have established through an altar of blood, having fought for 4,000 years.
\n\nDearly beloved Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will please allow our minds to be able to give you joy, and please allow our bodies to be able to give you joy, and please allow us to offer everything to you as yours.
\n\nNow please discern each individual\'s innermost thoughts, and please allow us to be able to search and see what the center of hope is and what the goals sought for are, which are penetrating the center of each one\'s heart. If there is something centered on ourselves, please allow us to realize that we have not been able to find and establish the center of heaven in front of the will of the providence, and please guide us to evaluate ourselves and not to be disobedient against heaven\'s will.
\n\nPlease allow us to admit sincerely that we are sinners, bowing down before you on our own to report everything truthfully to you. Please let only earnest adoring hearts which are able to repent with tears before you, Father, flow into and overflow in your sons and daughters\' minds and bodies. And we earnestly hope and desire, my Father, that you will bring about the work of rebirth centered on those hearts.
\n\nSince we have bowed down before your alter, oh Father, please allow all the doors of our hearts to open and be filled with the will of heaven. Then please allow us to experience your heart, and please allow us to appear as the people of glory that you are hoping for.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 19, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_9t">
Father!
\nPlease let as take a close look at our minds, and please let us consider our bodies, and please guide us to become sons and daughters whose minds and bodies are able to be moved to tears by your heart.
\n\nWe know that as all of the saints in heaven accepted and went the way of the will of the providence, they were ashamed and could not raise their heads before you, considering that they were descendents of the fall. We who are on the earth have bowed our heads before you, and since we must make an effort in order to possess the mind of our father, we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will please allow pride to be removed from within our minds, and please allow our bodies never to be disloyal to you.
\n\nAs we come closer and closer to you, Father, we cannot help but bow down our heads, and we feel that we can not help but report truthfully of our own accord about our sins. Please allow us to have earnest hearts which are able to admit on our own that we are sinners, and to wait for the touch of your compassionate love, and to long for your heart with our heads bowed. And if there remain in us any roots of the black darkness of sin, oh Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will remove them.
\n\nAnd then please act to let us go forth pioneering a new path, following the commands you have given us at this time. We earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to possess the original strength of heaven which is able to bring about new actions and receive new power.
\n\nFather, if we have some kind of theories, or if we have some kind of knowledge, ideology, assertions, or concepts, please allow us to be able to forget them all, and to be able to become like little children who long for you alone. And please allow us to be able to offer silently at the altar everything that our minds and bodies have. Then we earnestly hope that you will mold and remake us once again through your new words, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow, to appear, here your direct work of re-creation through which we are embraced in your love.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become your true sons and daughters who are able to return joy and glory to you and relieve your concern.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 2, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_10t">
Father!
\nPlease allow our hearts to endlessly soar up towards you. Please put the concept of creation which you had when you created everything, into the center of our hearts, which are like that, and please allow us to become people whose minds are able to be moved if you are moved, and whose hearts are able to be determined if you are determined.
\n\nPlease allow our minds and our hearts to move according to you, and to be able to be used only as yours. And we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow our minds and bodies to be able to transform themselves into belonging to you alone, and to be able to penetrate into the original world as belonging to you.
\n\nToday our minds are longing exceedingly for our original hearts, and they are demanding the original nature of the original creation. We know that in order to do that, your new words are needed. Even though humankind, whom you created in order to find joy, fell and is living in an evil world, the original nature is moving towards the original world. In order to have our original nature called and raised up, for 6,000 years we have longed for and sought the original words of re-creation. We have looked for and yearned for those kinds of words for 6,000 years. Now the city of death has the day of judgment ahead of it.
\n\nFather! Being faced with such a period, humankind, which is struggling with this world of fear, which is wandering around without knowing which way to go, has lost its center, and doesn\'t know what it will be faced with, and can\'t find a place to stay. Please have compassion for all humankind, and please guide humankind to be able to return into your embrace.
\n\nWe know that the children who have gathered here are temples you may come and visit, and at the same time are original foundations. If you do not act, Father, all the things of creation on this earth will face the Day of Judgment and go through endless suffering. Therefore, oh Father, please extend your touch of re-creation.
\n\nIsn\'t there the original principle of creation of you having created Adam and Eve in order to love? Depending on that principle, in order to find and raise humankind back up to you, I shall not care about fatigue; I shall not care about suffering unjustly or sorrow; I shall not care about going the way of anger and tears; and I shall not care about an altar of blood. Please allow me to be able to understand the heart of my father who is holding me. Please guide us to understand the historical situation of our father who cannot help but do that.
\n\nAt this time please let us consider our father\'s impatient heart, and quietly, beautifully please transform us into people who belong to you alone.
\n\nPlease expel everything that is not yours alone. Please allow us to be able to be happy if you are happy, and to move if you move. And we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will restore us to being those who are able to speak out with a new voice and to appear as the original beings who have the glory of beauty in the presence of all things.
\n\nNow I have understood that my mind is not mine; I have understood that my body is not mine; and I have understood that this land where I am living is not mine. I have understood the fact that this universe is not mine, and all the things you created are not mine.
\n\nI know that all these things originated from you, Father, and as things connected with your will, they were created for you. I know that the original nature of creation is for all people, who were created related to one center, to find the glory of happiness. Please restore the original state, the realization of the kind of harmony where our minds can move and the entire universe can move transformed into the glory of the one established center.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 21, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_11t">
Please establish us in relation to the Will and teach us our moral obligation. And we cannot help but thank you at this time for teaching us our original value.
\n\nNow please connect our minds with your mind, Father, and please allow our minds to become able to represent your mind. Please let everything that we feel in our minds represent your feelings, and we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow this time to become one when everything we experience is able to remove our human nature and we will become able to represent heavenly nature in our experiences.
\n\nFather! Since we who left you must meet you again, please allow our footsteps to become earnest struggling footsteps seeking to find our lost father. Since we know that it will not do unless our behavior flows out of earnest hearts and earnest faithfulness, oh Father, please let us go forth with new determination.
\n\nOn this day, we know that it will not do if our innermost thoughts do nor become one in relation to you. Since it will not do unless we are held by your embrace, oh Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will come personally and caress our minds and embrace our bodies.
\n\nSince we know now that it will not do unless we become living sacrifices for you, Father, from this time forth please allow us to become living sacrifices for you.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 11, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_12t">
We must open our eyes and look to heaven. Our eyes have become dark as though it were dark outside, but without resting day or night we must look up to see whether something is appearing. We must look at everything that has been left in pieces in the history after Adam.
\n\nSince these things have made us unable to find the center of life and the standard of ideology, please let us have minds which are able to overcome them, to look again to heaven, to go beyond human emotion and to be moved by heavenly emotion.
\n\nWe know that we are those who must find your lost idea and the original garden which was lost, and we must take dominion over and protect all the things of creation. We must form a relationship of love with all the things of creation and tie them together and offer them back to you. And we know we have the complete responsibility to let the flowers of your love blossom through your heart which created heaven and earth and to tie them together and offer them to you.
\n\nPlease awaken all the people of the world who are in a deep sleep and have not been able to move even one step. And we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow them to become people who can see again and can look to heaven greeting a new morning of brightness.
\n\nPlease allow us to become the second group of people who are able open our eyes anew and to look up to heaven and raise up a new sense of determination in front of world history. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become those who move a new tribe connected by a new heart and new ideology.
\n\nPlease open our eyes again towards heaven. Since we know that you first blocked the way of this people in order to let them become a group who could find a new place which humankind has never seen, please lead us to go forward steadily today and tomorrow, not being disappointed and forgetting our fatigue.
\n\nThis land can survive only if people appear who can open their eyes again and look towards heaven. And since we know that because of this movement the world will be able to survive, we earnestly ask you to please allow us to become the people who can take responsibility for this.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 15, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_13t">
Father!
\nPlease take dominion over our minds and bodies. We have minds, but we know that they are not ours, and we have bodies, but we know that they are not ours.
\n\nAlthough our minds head towards goodness, our bodies go in the direction of evil; so between them we find ourselves struggling. We know that you relate to us knowing that we are not able to escape the realm of heaven\'s lamentations. Father, please have compassion on us who are like this, and please give us the grace of the life of heaven. It will not do unless you give us the strong power of resurrection in our hearts.
\n\nOur bodies seek to subjugate our minds, but the will of heaven is to find and establish a standard of victory where the mind strikes the body and is able to eternally subjugate it. Today we know that it will not do unless that standard is realized through us, and that inevitable battle remains before us. Accordingly the battles which continuously appear before us are not battles we should fear. The many kinds of sorrow we run into in this situation of struggle are not great sorrows. Rather please allow us to feel today that a greater sorrow is the fact that in the battle between our minds and bodies our mind is dominated by our bodies.
\n\nOh Father! Please raise up strong minds, and please add powerful grace to them. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will help us to possess the ability to be able to have our minds subjugate our bodies.
\n\nThrough living centered on the mind we know that if this work is not accomplished by us, the complete resurrection of life will not be able to be accomplished. Therefore, oh Father, it will not do unless our minds are stirred up.
\n\nOur minds deal with life, and deal with grace, and are able to be transformed by the work of resurrection. Please allow the stimulation and inspiration which our minds receive be able to shield our bodies and to be able to shield our environments. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that such a work of heavenly re-creation will appear in the midst of our bodies.
\n\nAlthough our minds are endlessly soaring up towards the glory of our father, our bodies which are heading towards our father are endlessly exhausted and struggling. Therefore, Father, please alter this environment and please allow a garden of joy where our bodies can move as our minds desire to appear quickly before all people on this earth.
\n\nIf there are sons and daughters like that, please bless them to be able to move heaven to have dominion over this earth and to remain long in history.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nApril 26, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_14t">
Father!
\nWe are exhausted from sorrow and exhausted from difficulties, and we are struggling and don\'t even know which direction to go. Please look at us compassionately. Please take hold of us who are wandering and don\'t have any place to depend on.
\n\nWe have felt that the grace which you allowed us is amazing and great; but even having received that grace, our disloyal selves have not been able to return glory to you. Father, please bear with us.
\n\nFather, although you have already presented to us the way to avoid sorrow in this sorrowful world, please bear with the fact that we have been insufficient to support the Will you announced in advance. And please bear with our not having been grateful to you and not having gone that way, even though we knew you had established for us a path that could avoid our having to go the course of suffering.
\n\nNow for the rest of our lives we hope to live entrusting ourselves to your heart for the sake of your glory and your joy, but on this earth the power of death and the influence of sin are surrounding us so strongly. Since you also know that this is very difficult to overcome, please manifest yourself, oh Father of compassion.
\n\nFather, please bear with the fact that as yet we have not been able to return joy to you, Father, or praise your glory from a liberated position. Please reach out with new authority and dominate the powers of darkness.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will carry out the work of re-creation so that we will be able to sing of the glory of resurrection as people of victory.
\n\nBecause the power of death is sweeping us away, while going through this final decision of life and death and the sense of life, we need spontaneous ability and automatic strength to be able to push through this. Therefore, Father, if there are sons and daughters of yours who desire this, please personally supplement their power, and allow them the authority of resurrection. And we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow them to become elite soldiers of heaven who embrace the hope of tomorrow and go forth pioneering their lives day by day.
\n\nEven if the lives we have lived up until now have been inadequate, Father, please bear with us. If it is your will to stimulate us and tell us in advance about the new promise of tomorrow, we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to fulfill completely the responsibility of the pioneers today and tomorrow.
\n\nFather! Since our minds want to live for you, want to follow you and want to follow the example of your heart, please act upon that foundation.
\n\nFather, please move and show us the glory of resurrection. And we earnestly hope and desire that you will move us into the realm of the blessing of liberation.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 7, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_15t">
The thing that many people have longed for and aspired to is the garden of hope, the garden of your idea, but there has been no one who sang that this is the whole of hope while holding you. Father, if there is something that your sons and daughters who have gathered here today now feel, please let them feel passion for you.
\n\nPlease allow us to realize that you are the whole of ideology, you are the whole of life, and you are the whole of love. Because of the fact that we are unable to represent your entire will, please allow us to understand that today it causes you anguish that you are not able to relate to us in circumstances where you are able to establish your dignity.
\n\nPlease allow us to be able to establish your dignity now, and since you have allowed us to become those who can establish the dignity of Jesus, if there is sorrow on the earth, each of us must become those who are able to take responsibility for it ourselves. If there is suffering on the earth, please allow us to understand that each of us must take responsibility for it.
\n\nOn earth our real hearts must communicate with your mind and must communicate with Jesus mind. Please let each of us determine to take responsibility for your sorrow and difficulties and push everything aside. Since we know that we are facing a historical turning point where it will not do unless we feel the grace of your life, please allow us to have a new foundation in our minds at this time.
\n\nNow if we have not been able to have a new concept and a new heart or a standard that is able to have a relationship with you, we earnestly hope and desire that you will please allow us to realize at this time that we will not be able to avoid settling the accounts of our destiny together with the judgment of history. We know that Jesus also lived for the sake of this work, and we know that he did not live the 30 years of his life for his own sake; he lived for his people and for fallen humankind.
\n\nNow we know that the age of the Kingdom of Heaven is corning where Jesus will be able to live for himself. We know that there remains for us the final task in which it will not do unless we are allowed to receive the glory of resurrection as those who are substantiations of victory who have gone over all the peaks and valleys of the cross which Jesus went through while on the earth in order to stand as a chosen person of that age and a citizen of that nation.
\n\nIf we have come to understand this kind of content, we realize that we must bring ourselves into conformity with that reality and that will, and in order to realize the purpose of that will we must prepare a substantial sacrifice. Therefore please be with us, Father.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to possess the original temple and make an altar of victory which you can recognize.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 7, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_16t">
We know that the course of restoration is one that goes on and on without end, and we human beings must go in cycles over and over with grief remaining. But when we communicate with the world of heart of our father who has worked so hard, the history of sorrow which has been going in cycles comes to form a relationship with us today. The relationships of those struggles today will be able to become the foundation to constitute the destined relationships of the future. We must realize that these destined relationships of heart are those which must establish the garden of unlimited hope, unlimited joy, and unlimited longing.
\n\nWhere are the mountains and streams that you are able to be proud of as you go here and there leading Adam around? Where are the flowers that you wanted to be proud of together with Adam, and where are the growing trees, where are the green plains, and where are the flowing streams?
\n\nAdam, who could have stood in a position of going together with you in a state of being able to communicate with your heart which is like that, this Adam fell and left your side, Father. But I earnestly hope and desire, my Father, that you will allow us to become people of joy who attend our Father, whom we have longed for, and who keep you right next to us, and who know how to rejoice together with all things, together with all people, and together with the entire cosmos.
\n\nWe know that if we do not go through the loneliness and anguish of the cross which was left behind, we cannot form our destined relationship, and if we do not have minds that revere the garden of your ideal and are filled with longing, we cannot form that destined relationship. Therefore, please allow us to become sons and daughters of victory who have received your blessing and who have no relationship to the circumstances of the fall, and to become sons and daughters who are able to relate to all things in the original garden as original people who have hearts tilled with longing. And we earnestly hope and desire that you will lead us to become the true ancestors of humankind.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 28, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_17t">
We cannot help but feel that those of us who have bowed down before you have found the path of life after having wandered around here and there.
\n\nHow can we ever repay your grace of having established us in a position where we can call you, "Abba, Father," and your not having minded the endless suffering we did not even know about, and your having protected us, purified us and led us to this place?
\n\nWe don\'t have anything to repay you with. At this time we cannot help but feel that even if we give you our bodies, we cannot repay that grace; and even if we all offer you our hearts and minds, we are inadequate to raise our heads before what you have achieved through your suffering.
\n\nWe know that it is your desire and it is your situation that you who have led us to this point have the responsibility to save us and to see a day of glory through us. And when we think that you hope to find comfort through people like us, we cannot help but feel ashamed in the presence of our father who has endured the peaks and valleys of the course of history, placing your hope in our inadequate selves.
\n\nIf our flesh and blood were able to feel for your heart, and our bones were able to take on a form that could constitute a personality, then we would earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you would allow that being to be able to become a substantial form who is able to testify to your unchanging self.
\n\nHow much you must have longed for a holy, glorious being who could be part of you and return glory to you even with each and every cell. In the course of history our ancestors could not attend you in that way. We know that it is a fact of history that they followed heaven, and then at times felt resentment, and at times broke their promises, and were proud of being in the realm of the chosen people and then gave up.
\n\nFather! Since we have received this kind of grief-filled blood lineage, today we confidently say we believe heaven, but we are people who are in a position close to the evil world which is able to betray heaven tomorrow.
\n\nFather, please have compassion on us who are like this. Father, please hold on to us. We earnestly hope and desire that you will please graft your heart of life to our thirsting minds, and please carry out the work of resurrection which fills us with new life.
\n\nAlthough many people have come and gone, and even now many are coming and going, since until today there have been no people who grasped your situation and grasped your heart and wept, please allow us to become people who are able to grasp your situation and heart and weep. Please allow there to be many sons and daughters on the earth whose minds are filled with a desire to live for you and who think, "I want to attend my father," and who know how to be indignant with heaven and earth, and to be indignant with history and to be indignant with our fallen ancestors.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nSeptember 6, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_18t">
Please allow us to realize, Father, that you are not desiring any external form; you are longing for and looking for hearts and minds that adore you and that have been awakened to their original selves deep in their innermost hearts.
\n\nWhen we think about you, our father who has sought for and worked for the being of hope whom you desired while going through the course of complicated battles through the ages and through the course of history, we cannot help but feel that we did not become the "I" we are today by ourselves.
\n\nWhen we were born on the earth, we were born centered on the destined relationships of above and below, front and back, and right and left. Please allow us to understand that without our knowing it, these relationships are urging us to pursue the value of the total object or the value of a completely faultless purpose. Please allow us to realize that centered on this kind of aspect of ourselves, heaven is above us, and the history of goodness together with heavenly fortune is moving below us.
\n\nAnd please allow us to become sons and daughters who can feel that before us is the world of hope and to the right and left are our friends and people and brethren, and please allow us to seek to hold onto the original heart and be able to observe all these things and form the destined relationships of above and below, front and back, and right and left. If there are people who forget themselves completely and long for and struggle for this, even if they have walked a course of not being tolerated in their age and are opposed in their lives, we know that they will stand in front of the palace of heaven without fail in the last days.
\n\nFather, please command us now. Please speak. We are longing for and adoring your heart with our minds. Therefore, Father, if there is something that frustrates you, please let us experience it; and if something miserable and sad happens, please demonstrate it to us through our bodies. Please allow us to become sons and daughters of hope who are able to feel the reality of your existence from it being demonstrated through our bodies, and please allow us to bow down our heads and be grateful before you.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nSeptember 27, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_19t">
Today as we unworthy people come before the amazing will of our father, first we must clearly realize that we are inadequate and we must feel deep in our flesh and bones that we are fallen descendents who do not dare to stand before heaven. Whether we look here or look there, we have come to understand that we have nothing to present before heaven and be proud about.
\n\nThe blood lineage that has come from our ancestors is a lineage that has betrayed you; and even all the prophets who inherited the flesh and blood of our ancestors could not be embraced in your broad bosom of love through your heart of eternal and joyful love because they had the bitter root of sin. Therefore today we too know very well that we are people who are not proper to be approved by heaven.
\n\nWhen we come to understand the unjust fact that we beings whom you created as extremely holy are living on the earth with aspects and elements that you cannot help but dislike, we cannot help but lament bitterly. Now we vow that we must push aside, step upon, and mercilessly cut off this horrible fact that the nature of evil and the elements of evil lie latent in our flesh and blood and in every one of our cells. We cannot help but confess that we are grief-filled descendents who have not been able to form our destined relationship with your holy original nature and we could not inherit your original heart, your original lineage, or your original bones and flesh.
\n\nIn the midst of people like us, where would there be sons and daughters whom you can raise up and bless in the middle of that garden which you will leave as an eternal work? Nevertheless, please allow us to become sons and daughters who know how to bow down, lower our heads and shed tears in the presence of your mighty grace which raises our inadequate selves up to a position where we can be without sin by reducing it here and reducing it there by establishing conditions of forgiveness and conditions of approval.
\n\nThe more that we come to know heaven, we cannot help but realize that we are shameful beings in relation to you, and the further we go, we cannot help but feel fear at revealing ourselves before you with bowed heads, but we know that this is the path of following heaven. We know that your sons and daughters who have gathered here today are not appropriate to be called your sons and daughters, but even so, since we know it is your will to not cast them away, please bend down and care for us.
\n\nFather, please cover all the flaws of these people who have lived in sinister places and have been wounded. Even though they are children with whom your destined relationship of flesh and blood has been cut, still we know that through their original hearts they are in a position where you cannot say you don\'t know them, and therefore you seek to remember them as true children.
\n\nFather, we earnestly hope and desire that you will bless this day and remember it. Today we are establishing this day as a new historical day; and we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to offer our bodies and minds and hearts to you, and that we will be able to be close to the justification of children and the glory of children.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 27, 1960
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_20t">
Father!
\nWe know that today is a time like the 40-year period when the people of Israel wandered and couldn\'t find their way in the wilderness, and like the time the people of Israel were struck by the rod of heaven and were consumed due to their unfaithfulness. From every aspect we look at, we know that the present is that kind of time.
\n\nFather, you are hoping for works that can cope with this kind of age, and we are also hoping for that. But if on our own we are not able to control our minds and decide the direction, and determine which way we must go, and you show us the direction we must go, we know that even if you tell us to go to that place, we will not be able to go there.
\n\nWe know that the problem is not all the things of the earth being scattered; it is the center of my mind being scattered, and having lost the direction we must go and the position we must face. We are looking at the phenomenon of the last days like that, without knowing the direction we must go and without knowing the position we must face. If we have now realized that you are the center, we will have to kneel down and bow our heads and offer devotion of our own accord in order to match the standard and position that you are hoping for.
\n\nSince we know that in the Last Days we should pour oil on our hair and go into a secret chamber and pray, please allow us to become those who establish ourselves in a position of oneness between the standard of your heart and our hearts, and find the condition of victory in our lives, and become those who discuss the value of that. If we cannot do that, please allow us to understand that we will not be able to stand in your presence.
\n\nWe are facing this kind of position, and we are watching the present situation of this kind of world and this kind of society, and our minds and bodies are suffering in this kind of environment. Therefore, please remold us since we are like this, and please establish the standard of our hearts, and please show us works centered on you, and please sanctify the center of our hearts and minds. Please sanctify our bodies and our environment and allow us to be able to be close to you.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 11, 1960
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_21t">
The multitudes who should have praised your glory of the ages should have lived together with you, together with your glory, embraced by you. But when we think that mistake one day`s by our human ancestors created a history of sorrow like this and that they have gone over rugged, desolate paths shedding sweat, blood, and tears, we earnestly hope that you will bear with our not being able to have anything to offer in order to comfort you in your sorrow and great grief.
\n\nPlease have compassion on us. We cannot help but feel sorrow at having been born the descendents of the fall. Please allow us to become children who know how to be grateful in the presence of your heart which has searched for us through our destined relationship which could not be thrown aside.
\n\nWe thank you for having come to the Korean people among the many different peoples, and we thank you for having called our worthless selves first from among the many individuals.
\n\nWe know that this blessing is not for ourselves, and we are sincerely grateful for your having established us in a position where we have the responsibility of being an organization of blessings, sharing those blessings with many people of our nation and many people of humankind, and in a position where we can feel that kind of heavenly relationship.
\n\nWe thank you that we are those who have been called to this position as fruits of the relationship you formed without our knowing it. Please allow us to understand the fact that the responsibility we shoulder does not remain with one individual. Please let us take seriously that this mission which must go beyond our people and affect humankind and the world has been placed on the two shoulders of each and every one of us. And please allow us to become sons and daughters who receive your love and who know how to determine to fulfill this responsibility taking a step towards you.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 26, 1965
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_22t">
We know that it is the common course of humankind to come and go here and there on the earth while alive and then without fail to have to go. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will not allow us to become pitiful people who are born as human beings, but when seeking God are not able to have a standard which we are able to follow on our own.
\n\nWe know that in order to possess a treasure that others cannot have, we have to go through a course of trials which others do not go through. We have to recognize clearly through our relationships with the world of creation and our lives in society that it is a fact that one cannot raise one`s standard without going through trials and tears.
\n\nPlease allow us to attain the title of holy filial children who are famous in history for having fulfilled completely our duty of filial piety in relation to you. Please let us hold the treasured position of being able to remain as representatives of heavenly value, representing the whole of history centered on your heart.
\n\nIn the center of our breasts there are no trees or grass. The center of our breasts is a hollow place among hollow places. It is an empty place among empty places, and a dry place among dry places. But there is one thing that we have.
\n\nWe have hearts that want to call out, "Father!" and hearts that want to meet you, and hearts that want to attend you. We know that those hearts alone are something precious which could not be exchanged even if we were given the heavens and the earth. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to have hearts that will become the totality of that value until the very end.
\n\nSince we know that that has extremely precious value, please do not allow us to forget the fact that in order to do that we will have to have heroic hearts and make blood-curdling efforts.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the "True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 11, 1966
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_23t">
Father!
\nEach time we bow down and pray before the majesty of our sacred Father, the more that we consider the fact that you are not joyful, there is no way to keep ourselves from feeling ashamed and remorseful. Father, in the midst the vastness of heaven and earth there is no people worse than our Korean people, but you have chosen this people. Among the many persons of humankind there are none worse than we are, but you have come to us.
\n\nWhen we consider that you have protected and kept us a hundred, a thousand times even though we are behaving so foolishly, we come to feel once again that you love this people, and you love us unconditionally. You have come to us immature, ignorant people and granted us the concept of the blessings of heaven and earth which are so hard to be equal to. And we are grateful that you have allowed us to have this day in which we can call you, "Father," with hearts that overflow like never-ending springs on a foundation of holy grace which others cannot even imagine. We feel all this as the caress of your love.
\n\nWhen we consider how you have raised us up until now and what you have done to have us become standard-bearers who can carry out your commands, and when we consider how your path must have been as you went forth in order to prepare the way of restoration setting aside complaints and enduring the sorrows of the past, we cannot help but repent once again for the past when we have been unworthy children millions and millions of times. Please establish in front of this nation and this people a movement that, even as it is driven out, is able to go forward to the standard of final victory which you have gone over until today.
\n\nPlease let us become people who are able to bow to you of our own accord, feel ashamed and urge ourselves on. When we realize again that you have come filled with your mighty Will, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to feel on our own that there is no way for us other than offering gratitude and more gratitude, and hymns and more hymns thousands of times before our glorious Father.
\n\nFather! We were people without a country. We were refugees who had lost their nation. We were beggars who were starving in order to find the nation we had lost. Since we have come to understand that your will to find and establish a new hometown, a land of the original homeland, is the truth, we will have to find the land of the original homeland and the original family which we have lost, and take revenge against Satan.
\n\nAnd we will not stop there. We have realized that it will not do unless we retaliate and indemnify everything, no matter what kind of difficulties or what kind of suffering there is, combining every authority we have inherited as heavenly means of blessings which Satan cannot take advantage of, we will face Satan, who is our historical enemy, our enemy in the present age, and our enemy of the future. Therefore, Father, please give us strength. We earnestly hope and pray that you will give us the ability to offer all our loyalty and filial piety to you.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 18, 1966
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_24t">
Oh, Father!
\nWe know that the ideal world of the original creation which you desired is a place centered on your love where true children and true families can feel joy, and all of creation can be harmonized and joy overflows. But when we think about the fact that through the fall the original world, the land of the original homeland, came to remain before humankind as death, how could this not be something to lament about?
\n\nThrough the fall, we lost you, Father; we lost the land of the original homeland; and we lost the original Taste Parents, and the ideal original true family, the ideal tribe, the ideal nation, the ideal world, and the ideal cosmos. We lost them all. A world where authority is centered on you, Father, should have been realized in a natural environment, but due to having collided with the sorrowful fate called the fall, humankind came to have no relationship with you, Father, and the world became a world which has no relationship to the world of your ideal.
\n\nWhen we consider that the fact that you who are our Lord could not be our Lord, and we received the blood lineage of your enemy Satan and were dragged down into the realm of darkness which Satan dominates, we must reflect once again on how exasperating and regrettable a fact this is, and we must bear in mind at this time that it is your hope and is the hope of humankind to expel Satan who has been our enemy for millions of years from this earth up to the spirit world where multitudes of spirit people are staying.
\n\nFather! We are people who cannot feel in our lives how much is left of the foundation of Satan`s power and authority. We have come to realize, Father, that as we spend hour by hour and even as days pass day by day, up until now we have not been able to feel in our lives of faith how much Satan`s power and authority have invaded the realm of our lives and how much they have invaded this stage on which we live our lives.
\n\nThe more we think about the fact that we certainly cannot go into your presence without clearing up what has become dirty, standing in the middle of a path of tears crying out to our father, we come to think again that we are in a desolate and pitiful position where we cannot help but hope for your touch of salvation.
\n\nOh Father, you know we are in such a situation! Please extend your mind and heart of compassion and once again protect the path we must go. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will separate us from the satanic realm and make the area around us clear.
\n\nFather! Our minds and bodies are not able to form a direct relationship with you. We know that the root of sin which Satan can control still remains. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will please bear with ourselves which have not been able to do the good our minds desire, and have not been able to escape from the realm of such lives, and our own bodies which delight in acts of evil we do not want.
\n\nFather! We will have to be segregated from Satan in our courses of life, and we will have to be segregated from Satan in our courses of resurrection. We have come to clearly realize the fact that we will not be able to become citizens of heaven if we do not become one with you and if our daily lives and our entire lives are not the ones you planned for us. Therefore, please allow your sons and daughters who have gathered here to all offer their entire minds and bodies and be able to rush towards new lives and lifetimes.
\n\nWe earnestly ask that you will allow us to become people who are able to determine ourselves before you once again at this time.
\n\nWe have humbly and earnestly prayed all these things in the name of the "True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 17, 1968
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_25t">
Father!
\nPlease allow your love to dwell in the hearts of everyone, and please allow us to appear in heaven and earth as eternal true people through love. We know the fact that you are hoping for all of creation to move centered on such a being; and we know that you will become one with that true human being and build a world of glory, a world of a brilliant culture. But we know that your love not having been able to dwell in us is your grief, and furthermore, our not having been able to find and meet your love is grief.
\n\nWe are those who have gone through the course of history carrying the sorrow of not being able to find a relationship with your true love even though we looked for it, because we were born as descendents of the fall. Therefore, oh Father of compassion, we earnestly hope and desire that you will come to us with your original heart of love, and you will allow us to become children who are able to bow deeply in the presence of your heart.
\n\nFor thousands of years, humankind has been born as the descendents of those who betrayed you, and we have lived as people who betrayed your heart. Father, please bear with us. Since we have bowed down before your majesty as beings who are like that, please take hold of us through your compassion and love and comfort us with your caress of mercy. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow this time to become one where we tell you in detail about and repent for our inadequacies of the past, our disloyalty of the past, and our lack of filial piety of the past.
\n\nYou are our father whom we must attend for eternity. Please let us realize clearly that the relationship between you and us is an original relationship which cannot be broken. It is to our great anguish that we fell and lost our father, and our eternal destined relationship with you was cut off. Today we have bowed down before you in order to find again our father whom we lost and to reestablish with you that destined relationship which was cut off. But since we know that without your love this cannot happen, please allow us the grace of resurrection through your love. Please tie us together through the destined relationship of your direct love, and please allow us to be able to offer ourselves to you as one unified altar.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 31, 1968
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_26t">
Father!
\nPlease allow us to consider your heart in silence and to be able to discover ourselves. The more that we think about it, we cannot help but discover that we are very far away from your will. The first ancestors of humankind forsook you, and we lament that we have been born as descendents who must be ruined forever because of having gone the path of annihilation of the fall. And when we realize, while searching for you, the fact that there remains between us a great distance which is very difficult to close, we discover once again that there is nothing we can do about it.
\n\nWhen we realize that we have been born from the root of death which multiplied, we realize that this is why the past is as it was, and why in the present we are entangled in the world of death and are being swept away, and we cannot help but discover that we are too distant from you to be part of you, Father. Therefore we know that we need the touch of your love, and we need the touch of your omnipotence.
\n\nOh Father! Deep in our hearts and minds we possess the destined relationship of the original nature. This alone is what we have inherited from you. Because of this, we know that it remains for us to form the destined relationship which we must form with you. In order to establish that relationship, you have awakened us through the course of history, and since you are continuing to work for that today at this moment, please do not allow us to forget that fact.
\n\nPlease allow us to recognize the desire that our original nature is earnestly crying out for, and please allow us to come to know that our original nature really desires to form a relationship with you, Father. And please allow us to come to know the fact that the bitter root of sin which is an enemy opposing the original nature is surrounding us.
\n\nPlease let us come to know that it will not do unless the original nature appears to us representing your power. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will raise up a new beginning of life that is able to trample and go beyond all the tangled relationships of death through the touch of your omnipotence.
\n\nFather! Please bring about a new history that is able to cast out all the elements of sin through each one of us. In that way we will become one with your heart, and one with your situation in the midst of our lives. Please allow us to be able to offer ourselves to you as the true sons and daughters you wanted to find from a position where we can have hope and become one with the eternal future.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 1, 1968
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_27t">
Father!
\nWe hope that all the things of heaven and earth will eternally offer hymns of praise to you who are the Lord of the universe.
\n\nSince there is not even one created being which is separate from a relationship with you, because of you, all the things of heaven and earth which were molded through your heart raise up your glory and reveal your holiness and profundity, and we know that they reveal your infinite value. We know that in the midst of that, when you created humankind as the center of all things, you combined your entire internal nature and entire external nature and made them as the external form of a son and the external form of a daughter to represent all things.
\n\nOriginally, people are beings who should have been inside your mind and heart eternally, and they are beings who should not be able to separate from their destined relationship with you.
\n\nIn the midst of that kind of destined relationship, all the things of creation have a reciprocal object relationship with humankind, and together centered on God they should exist in the Kingdom of Heaven where freedom, peace and joy can dwell. They were to enjoy being in the place of eternal victory and attend you, Father.
\n\nHowever, we know the fact that because of the fall of the first human ancestors the origin of history was so miserable. We also know the awesome fact that through that result, it was not humankind alone who became miserable, but God, the Lord of creation, could not help but be placed in a miserable position as well.
\n\nOh Father! We have come to know that the portion of responsibility that humankind must fulfill still remains to be done, and it is the very thing which can completely release all humankind who began this kind of sorrowful history.
\n\nWe know that in order to go through the course of this portion of responsibility, many good spirits in the spirit world have hearts filled with hope as they look at this second foundation, just like the world of the good angels who cooperated at the time of the creation of Adam and Eve, and they have come fighting representing the earth.
\n\nUntil now you have been braving the current of history, and the reason for your working this hard is because of the mistake of our ancestors. But you did not let it finish as a mistake, and since you are working to restore it and to seek liberation from it, we know that it is your history of pain. Like this we, who have the traces of sorrow inherited from our ancestors who left behind this history of sorrow, have gathered together today once again before your majesty.
\n\nBut we are people who are not worthy to call you "Father." We know well that we are the descendents of an unworthy son.
\n\nWe are people who are not able to form the destined relationship of the life of heaven, and who are not able to receive the grace of resurrection; we are rebellious, wicked and shameless, and we definitely cannot stand in the presence of your will. But we know that you are in a position where it will not do unless even now you call us even though we are like that, because you have compassion, and you are the original being of merciful love.
\n\nSince we know that, with our unworthy minds and bodies which we cannot control we are bowing down to you with an attitude of shame. In your presence with tears of repentance, we have communicated with your heart deep in our minds; we have come forward with minds that want to call you "Father." Therefore, oh Father, please come, and through your heart of compassion, please raise us up; and we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us the special grace of being able to call you "Father" through a relationship of life with you.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who are able to realize the fact that we will become unworthy children who of our own accord will not able to raise our eyes in the face of your hard work, if, as we live our lives as one part of history, we do not prepare a foundation of victory resolving the sorrow of our own individual selves, no matter what our circumstances may be.
\n\nFather! We do not have anything. And we do not desire to have anything. Until now all we have had is flesh and blood which has been defiled due to the traces we have received of the blood lineage of Satan. Because everything that belongs to us is in your realm of lamentation as belonging to Satan, none of those things can be placed before you as sacrifices.
\n\nTherefore, we cast away all these things, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters with bodies and minds, as children whom you can embrace.
\n\nPlease eliminate completely the concepts we have had until now and everything we know. Please let our knowledge, purpose, and life become entirely for you. In that way, from that kind of position, please allow this place and this time to become one in which we are able to serve you as our parent with filial piety and bow down before you. We earnestly hope that you will allow this time to become one of our bowing down to you, with minds able to cut off and cast away everything we have when you personally give us directions.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 7, 1968
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_28t">
Father!
\nThe path that we are going is not a path we are going for some individual. Please let us understand that at the same time that it is a path for ourselves, it is a path for the world and the nation; and we are not living for some individual being, we are living for the world. Please let us come to understand that when we were born, this being called "I," if I am so and so Kim, was not born for so and so Kim alone.
\n\nI, so and so Kim, was born in order to go this way. Please allow us to be proud of this of our own accord, and to become those who say that this is the duty of our lives; and please allow us to understand its value. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will let us know that the purpose for having become Unification Church members is to find a central substantial being who can let us see this problem clearly and solve it and make its value even more precious.
\n\nFather! We have understood that going this path should be more urgent than anything else in the world. If we ask for whom we have gathered, we have not gathered for the Teacher of the Unification Church, and we have not gathered for anything of the Unification Church. Since we want to go forward for the nation, the Unification Church is needed, and since that is the nation and world which the Unification Church is hoping for, we are believing in and following it.
\n\nSince this is the nearest path to that goal, we are following this path. But Father, please do not allow our unchanging hearts which seek to go to the nation through the Unification Church, to the world through the Unification Church, to the cosmos through the Unification Church to become dejected. Please allow those hearts to quietly, calmly endure and go forth.
\n\nPlease let the sound of the heartbeat coining from our hearts and the sound of the heartbeat coming from the heart of heaven become one with our bodies, and please let our very beings be able to take on the role of arteries to let the feelings of our lives move and flow. And please allow us as the pulse of those arteries to be able to shine forever in the annals of history and to be able to become the friends of all people in our lives. Please let us realize that now at this time you are asking us whether that wouldn`t be our hope.
\n\nWhere are our minds flowing now? Where are our bodies staying? Please don\'t let us remain at the point of our selfish minds of the past. Please don\'t let us be those who hide our bodies in a self of the past which can be ruined or who remain in a position where we can be punished.
\n\nPlease allow us to be able to have minds and bodies in a position able to take on the burden of your mind and able to make the minds of humankind on the earth bloom. Please allow us to become your princes and princesses who kneel down before you, Father, and determine our loyalty and who imagine an "I" who is able to become the light of all.
\n\nPlease allow us to become those who are able to quietly, gently grow and to quietly, gently establish our individual positions which are able to blossom with the fervor of adoration, or positions which are able to shine with the fervor of longing.
\n\nWe will have to rouse ourselves to action having hope in a shining tomorrow. We will have to rouse ourselves to action having hope in the "I" of the shining tomorrow. We will have to rouse ourselves to action for the sake of the shining new Kingdom of Heaven. In order to do that, we will have to become appropriate vessels for it.
\n\nWe will have to become those who are able to shine internally and externally. And furthermore, we must become your sons and daughters who bow our heads before this relationship preordained by heaven, and we must become children who are able to call you "Father" sincerely. Then in the midst of that love we will sing of our daily lives, and we earnestly ask you, beloved Father, to allow us all to become your sons and daughters who in that situation are able to praise the work of each day in a holy way.
\n\nPlease let the remaining time, become glorious, and in relation to praising ourselves, please let this become a true position.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nAugust 31, 1969
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_29t">
Father!
\nBecause we are those who were born from evil, we must be born again to goodness. This destiny of having to be born twice is a very miserable one. Isn`t living as a stepchild very regrettable even in the world? We are not at the level of stepchildren; since we were born as the children of the enemy, we must find our original parents, but that path is never a smooth one. Therefore, we are receiving countless attacks from the spears, swords and arrows of Satan.
\n\nBut we will have to cut the ties that are binding our bodies and go forth. We will have to collide with those who are binding us, and cut them off with our mouths or cut them off with our strength. We know that in order to do that, we will have to go through a miserable course of history where we will not be able to help shedding blood.
\n\nHow great your sorrow must be over having sons and daughters like us when you cannot advise us even as you watch this. We must come to know that your heart is like that. We must become sons and daughters who know how to experience your situation, the heart of a parent whose pathetic breast is constricting at a point which cannot be expressed when his son who committed sin is dragged away by the court and stands on the gallows.
\n\nWe must know how to feel your pitiful heart as you watched your sons and daughters who were born with the central value of the universe and who could not be represented by anything else be dragged away by the touch of the enemy and your heart as you have gone forward silently hoping for a time of hope.
\n\nWe bow down before your anxious heart, before your mind which is hoping for sons of hope like that, and we are thinking about you, our wretched father who has been struggling in order to find his lost sons and daughters even if it will take billions and trillions of years. When we think that even when that wretchedness unfolded in reality in the course of history, and even while in such a position you have not been able to receive pity, we realize that we deserve to be cursed over and over again. But we know that you have endured all that and forgiven us because if you curse us, you would be in the position of cursing your own children. We must follow this example of forgiveness and patience which you have given us, Father.
\n\nWe know that the person who seeks heaven in circumstances more pitiful than anyone else on earth remains in history. And indeed the people who know this way and who are going this way are people to be pitied. They are lonely orphans of the world. They are people who are in a situation they cannot complain about to anyone.
\n\nEven if they had a nation, they could not believe that nation, and even if they had the world, they could not have hope in that world. In that way, everywhere they went they could find you only if they stood in the position of being struck by the spears, arrows and swords of the enemy. We know that our being able to form a deep, heartistic relationship with you in this way is a tragic reality that we alone are able to have.
\n\nFrom that kind of position as sons and daughters who inherit your indignant heart, we will have to be able to call you "Father" sincerely while in your presence. Therefore, we know that we cannot go your way without shedding blood.
\n\nTherefore, thinking of the history of the blood shed by Abel, we must become a fortress surrounded by walls of blood for the sake of our father, and we must prepare a foundation of eternal rest, a citadel that can receive your sympathy. And please allow us to become heaven\'s true children who are able to eternally defend you and comfort your misery, Father.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 7, 1969
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_30t">
Father!
\nUntil now in the course of history, the union of a man and a woman centered on you has not existed. We know that it is all because of your hidden good works and your meritorious hard work that things that have never happened until now could be accomplished in the Unification Church.
\n\nWhen we think that until now the course of history existed in order to find one man, we have come to understand that it was the blessing of heaven to have been able to open the door of a new history, to pave the way to be able to go to the new world, and to have for the first time the foundation of a new religion through families centered on the concept of unification.
\n\nWe sincerely appreciate the grace you have given by letting us be able to receive this awesome blessing due to your hard work. Now please allow each of these people to offer all that they have before you. When we think about this thing called marriage, we cannot help but be reminded that it is an issue directly linked with the fall of Adam and Eve.
\n\nAs for us who were borne having received the blood lineage of fallen parents, when we think about how awesome is this event called "the blessing centered on you, our Father", we sincerely offer our gratitude before your grace. We who are like this must know the fact that we must become men and women who can first be offered substantially before you as sacrifices centered on true goodness.
\n\nBut we have come to realize that we are people who are at a point where we cannot reach that position as individuals. We know that this kind of position is one where we absolutely cannot stand as fallen descendents. But now since they have moral justification through their relationship with the True Parents, please take the lead there, Father. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to clearly realize the fact that this kind of foundation of grace cannot help but be established from this position where the work began through a relationship with the True Parents.
\n\nNow, if one is a man, as a man, and if one is a woman, as a woman, each one has offered himself or herself before you, Father, so please keep them as yours forever. Please give them authority and please let them become good ancestors by becoming examples in relation to establishing the order of your love in the satanic world.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 23, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_31t">
Father!
\nIn your presence we are as naked children, so you will have to dress us, and you will have to feed us, and you will have to raise us while embracing us. But we have never been able to relate with you like that as sons and daughters. Please let our minds and bodies stand in that kind of position, and please bless us to be able to become your sons and to be able to become your daughters.
\n\nWe don`t own anything in this world; we are people who don`t have even one thing; we have nothing to show off that we can be proud of. But we do have our destined relationship of sons and daughters who can grow up in your embrace. We know that this kind of destined relationship is a special realm which is able to represent the authority of victory, and we must become people who know how to be grateful here.
\n\nWe don`t look like anything, but please allow us to become sons and daughters whom you feel are precious and of whom you can be proud.
\n\nEven if we go a difficult path, we go together with you, Father; and even if we have a sorrowful experience, we have it with you; and even if we stand in a difficult position, please lead us, Father, to be able to comfort you. Please let us embrace deeper and deeper in our hearts the day of hope and desire, and please allow us to become your true sons and to become your true daughters who are able to add to the progress of the advancement towards tomorrow
\n\nHowever rugged the path we are going may be, please allow us to have new determination to never become a burden on the path that you must go. We have come you know you, Father, and we know the direction that you are going. Even if we go the path of the heavy cross and are injured, we know that there is only one time when we can comfort you; therefore, please allow us to become your children who gather all our devotion together as we go.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of our True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nApril 19, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_32t">
We are binding together and offering before you our hearts and minds which long for and adore your precious and mighty internal character. Since we are reflecting on the past and critiquing the present and longing for our true selves of tomorrow, please grant us evidence that we are your sons and your daughters.
\n\nPlease let us become the kinds of sons you have been hoping and longing for, the kinds of sons you have been looking for. We represent the entire value of the universe, and are the people who represent the central value; who therefore, you are able to long for. Accordingly, please allow us to become true children who can be called your sons and your daughters through your very mouth and through all your emotions and sensations. We are hoping that through our inadequate selves, you can feel that we are such sons and daughters.
\n\nOh Father who loves us from a dim distance, and who has worked in order to develop a foundation for our lives, we are so grateful for your having endured and gone through the long ages with the hope of a day for when you can meet true sons and daughters. Because our minds have their origin in you alone, at this time also we are longing to be true sons and true daughters who are able to have value in relation to the world you are hoping for, and according to the place where your mind is going.
\n\nWe have come here wanting to become sons and daughters who are called into the presence of our holy, merciful and majestic Father. Please let us become your sons and become your daughters who are filled with strong determination about the hope of tomorrow and the mission of tomorrow.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 13, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_33t">
Father!
\nIt will not do unless we determine the position in which we are placed, and can go straight in the direction of the goal which you have determined, and be one with the will, and become one with your mind and establish ourselves as the true sons and daughters you long for; therefore, we have come to this place longing for those things.
\n\nWhen we think that this place is a place where not only humankind but also heaven is taking on an extraordinarily important mission, and where both are hoping to make a determination for a new historical origin, we realize that this place is a place heaven is watching carefully, and a place humankind is watching carefully, due to our going a path proper to human beings who attend heaven in between heaven`s side and humankind`s side.
\n\nAnd we realize it is a place carrying the responsibility of having to go directly towards your will and not lean towards anything. However, Father, we must have a definite view of the goal. Relating to that goal we must become people who clearly know the solemn fact that without an absolutely accurate sense of direction in our lives day by day, we will not be able to go the full course of a true life.
\n\nWhile watching many days pass, we must not let them pass just staying as we are. We must become a movement of holy people who become different and change, and who know how to long to be able to become unified with your nature, and know how to stand in that position, and who are able to represent the substantial beings of your ideal of creation. We already know that you seek to meet and find these kinds of people through your Will. When we call you "Father." that father must not become an ambiguous father.
\n\nWe must face you squarely, Father, and follow the direction that you go. Please allow us to become children who are able to feel that it is the duty of children to not want our path to be a smooth one, but rather to feel that it will not do unless we follow the path that heaven has gone because it is the path of our parent even if it is a path that adds suffering upon suffering.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 8, 1972
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_34t">
Beloved Father!
\nTogether with all the things of creation which you made, we hope to offer before you, who oversee heaven and earth, praise of your glory and majesty.
\n\nFather! We know well that while passing through the eventful course of history, you have come through a history of re-creation that was extremely full of suffering in order to restore the mistake of our human ancestors. We realize how much misery and suffering filled the historical indemnity you paid in order to have each of us individually return to your original point by going beyond the path of the servant of servants, going beyond the path of the servant, going beyond the path of the adopted son, going beyond the path of the child, and going beyond the relationship of true parents.
\n\nAs human beings whom it is proper to punish because we sinned, we have walked a miserable course of sorrow-filled suffering, but as though there were no relation to that, you took responsibility for everything. We offer our sincere gratitude in view of the mighty accomplishments you attained while carrying out the work of re- creation, taking the lead, and going through all sorts of difficulties.
\n\nFather! We have come to understand that there is not a single person who has not been touched by you, and we know that there is no country whatsoever that has not been led through your hope. And furthermore, we know well that going beyond national borders, you are leading all people to the present point in order to lead them into the original world which was your ideal.
\n\nWhen we think that in the world that must remain in the end, there will be only you and your beloved sons and daughters and the heavenly forces of angels, we see that in this world the power of Satan and the people of Satan are far too great. We know that we Unification people are in a position where we cannot hope to resolve this for you.
\n\nWe have the name of the True Parents and the name of the True Children, and we praise that family. We realize the fact that our Unification Movement has the extremely precious responsibility of having to achieve on earth and in the spirit world the original state of the angelic world which is able to attend that family. When we realize that, we are in the position of having to inherit the accomplishments of the position of having become parents and at the same time inheriting the accomplishments of the sons and daughters.
\n\nFather! Your young children must pass through your touch and become the material for re-creation in your presence. We have already understood that it will not do unless we become like clay and can be molded as you wish and adapt ourselves to that.
\n\nSince we have understood that the only kind of mind we can have is one that seeks to become a faithful servant of your absolute will and a mind that adores your absolute love, oh, Father, please accept us, take dominion over us, and make us into the vessels you want.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 1, 1975
    </string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_35t">
Beloved Father!
\nWe have understood what kind of world you desire. We have understood how the love that you want must go. We have come to understand what the present world we are facing these days is like. We have understood that we are human beings who cannot live for ourselves; we have understood that we are Unification Church members whose families cannot live for our families alone; and we have understood that we people of the Unification Church of the world cannot live for the Unification Church of each nation of the world.
\n\nWe have understood the awesome and amazing fact that it will not do unless we live entirely for one world, entirely for one Kingdom of Heaven. Therefore, we will have to be able to change the order of our consciousness to God`s consciousness by transcending the people, transcending the nation and transcending the world. We have understood that at the same time that the discovery that we are able to do that ourselves is a great discovery, it is also the foundation for being able to be endowed with the qualification of being a great son.
\n\nWe have understood that the God who oversees the entire heaven and earth is a father in relation to our very family, is a father in relation to the nation, is a father in relation to the world, and a father in relation to the heavens. We have understood that while going through the historical ages representing the position of that father, parents of the family were needed, a king of the nation was needed, and saints of the world were needed. We know that it is because of that people have sought the way, of the truth.
\n\nSince we have truly come to know that, we will have to form a parent-child relationship as though it were a formal standard now, and you and we will really have to live together in our families, Father. We will really have to live centered on the nation. We will really have to live centered on the world. We can have the authority of father and son only if we find the joy of really being able to live together with the whole spirit world, and we have come to know that we will not be able to resolve the fallen realm if we cannot have the authority of father and son.
\n\nBecause of that we know that we absolutely need a realm of victory which can expand the authority of the father and the son from the individual, to the family, the people, the nation, and throughout the world. Therefore, Father, please bless us. We have now understood that there is nothing more precious than having God as our father, and once again we pledge of our own accord today at this time before you, Father, that we will become your sons and daughters in every way. Therefore, we earnestly hope that you will please allow this.
\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
    </string>
</resources>