<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">True Parents</string>
    <string name="app_start_name">TF PRAYER</string>

    <string name="advert">Advertising</string>
    <string name="konkurs">Brothers and sisters, I want to make a page with triumphant experiences in prayer. Please send me your experience / history by email.</string>
    <string name="sorrow">If after the update you do not see the prayer list page, this can be fixed if you go to the settings of the phone - application - find the installed application "TF Prayer" and click "clear data". I apologize for this inconvenience.</string>
    <string name="info_text">Hello. I`m Vadym. \n\nThe application is designed only for the prayer list. On the main page there will always be True Parents. The "Prayer List" menu allows you to add, edit and delete items. In the circle counter, how many times do you call the name of the person you pray for. There is also a chronometer that counts the time. After 3, 7, 12, 21, 40 minutes, a signal will sound with a message that expired according to the time. \n\nThe "Father's Prayer" menu is a collection of prayers that are in translation to russian for the time being. \n\nYou can always unsubscribe to me according to the wishes of the application. If you want, you can express gratitude by transferring the money.</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy"><a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1kkNl-DxcwSJC_99Ux2qXFd_5fiUR6DCV/view?usp=sharing">Privacy policy</a></string>
    <string name="coffee_gift">Site (ru)</string>
    <string name="about">About app</string>
    <string name="share_by">Share:</string>
    <string name="share_body">I want to share "TF PRAYER" application.\n</string>
    <string name="empty_list">Empty list</string>
    <string name="author">Author: Vadym Gryganskiy</string>
    <string name="email">E-mail: vadym.adv@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="explanation">Value of prayer</string>
    <string name="loading_mp3">Wait a moment while loading the mp3</string>
    <string name="kido_counter">Prayer %s</string>

    // App rater
    <string name="rate">Rate "TF PRAYER"</string>
    <string name="later_rate">Remind me later</string>
    <string name="no_rate">No, thanks</string>
    <string name="to_rate">Take a moment to rate the TF PRAYER app. Thanks for the support!</string>

    // Dialog
    <string name="add_new_person">Add new person</string>
    <string name="add_person">Add person</string>
    <string name="edit_person">Edit person</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="task_cancelled">Task canceled</string>
    <string name="something_wrong">Not write. Check your enter data</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="add_new_condition">Add new condition</string>
    <string name="add_condition">Add condition</string>
    <string name="edit_condition">Edit condition</string>

    // Timer
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="reset">Restart</string>
    <string name="min_3">It`s been 3 minutes</string>
    <string name="min_7">It`s been 7 minutes</string>
    <string name="min_12">It`s been 12 minutes</string>
    <string name="min_21">It`s been 21 minutes</string>
    <string name="min_40">It`s been 40 minutes</string>

    // drawer navigation
    <string name="home_page">Main</string>
    <string name="tp_photo">True Parents</string>
    <string name="tp_kido">Prayers of Father</string>
    <string name="tp_mKido">Prayers of True Father</string>
    <string name="mense">Family Pledge</string>
    <string name="mense_k">가정 맹세</string>
    <string name="anthem">Anthem</string>
    <string name="menu_condition">Condition</string>
    <string name="anthem_chonilguk">Anthem of Cheon Il Guk</string>
    <string name="kido_list">Prayer list</string>
    <string name="communicate">Contact</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="send">Write to the author</string>
    <string name="donation">Read</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    // EU GDPR Consent texts
    <string name="eu_consent_text">Dear user!\n\nWe use Google AdMob to show ads. Ads support our work, and enable further development of this app. In line with the new European Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), we need your consent to serve ads.</string>
    <string name="eu_consent_question">Read the terms of use of your data and check the box to agree with them.</string>
    <string name="learn_more"><a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1kkNl-DxcwSJC_99Ux2qXFd_5fiUR6DCV/view?usp=sharing">Learn <b>Privacy Policy</b> how your <b>Data is Used</b></a></string>
    <string name="agree">I agree with privacy policy</string>
    <string name="error_accept">You can accept privacy to continue</string>
    <string name="let_continue">Continue</string>

    // Condition
    <string name="toolbar_title">Indemnity conditions</string>
    <string name="condition_title">Indemnity condition</string>
    <string name="lider">Central figure:</string>
    <string name="duration">Duration:</string>
    <string name="date_from">Date from</string>
    <string name="condition">Condition:</string>
    <string name="public_goal">Public goal:</string>
    <string name="personal_goal">Personal goal:</string>
    <string name="leftover">Leftover: </string>
    <string name="duration_value">%s, starting from %s</string>

    // Kajon mense
    <string name="one"><b>一(일)</b> 천일국 주인 우리 가정​은 참사랑을 중심하고, 본향​땅을 찾아, 본연의 창조이상인 지상천국과 천상천국을 창건할 것을 맹세하나이다.</string>
    <string name="two"><b>二(이)</b> 천일국 주인 우리 가정은 참사랑을 중심하고, 하늘부모님과 참부모님을 모시어, 천주의 대표적 가정이 되며 중심적 가정이 되어, 가정에서는 천주에서는 효자, 국가에서는 충신 세계에서는 성인, 성자의 가정의 도리를 완성할 것을 맹세하나이다.</string>
    <string name="three"><b>三(삼)</b> 천일국 주인 우리 가정은 참사랑을 중심하고, 사대심정권과 삼대왕권과 황족권을 완성할 것을 맹세하나이다.</string>
    <string name="four"><b>四(사)</b> 천일국 주인 우리 가정은 참사랑을 중심하고, 하늘부모님의 창조이상인 천주 대가족을 형성하여,자유와 평화와 통일과 행복의 세계를 완성할 것을 맹세하나이다.</string>
    <string name="five"><b>五(오)</b> 천일국 주인 우리 가정은 참사랑을 중심하고, 매일 주체적 천상세계와 대상적 지상세계의 통일을 향해 전진적 발전을 촉진화할 것을 맹세하나이다.</string>
    <string name="six"><b>六(육)</b> 천일국 주인 우리 가정은 참사랑을 중심하고, 하늘부모님과 참부모님의 대신가정으로서, 천운을 움직이는 가정이 되어, 하늘의 축복을 주변에 연결시키는 가정을 완성할 것을 맹세하나이다.</string>
    <string name="seven"><b>七(칠)</b> 천일국 주인 우리 가정은 참사랑을 중심하고, 본연의 혈통과 연결된 위하는 생활을 통하여 심정문화세계를 완성할 것을 맹세하나이다.</string>
    <string name="eight"><b>八(팔)</b> 천일국 주인 우리 가정은 참사랑을 중심하고, 천일국시대를 맞이하여 절대신앙, 절대사랑, 절대복종으로 신인애 일체 이상을 이루어 지상천국과 천상천국의 해방권​과 석방권을​ 완성할 것을 맹세하나이다.</string>

    // TP kido books
    <string name="pr_nadezdy">Prayers of Hope</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy">Prayers of Victory</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca">Prayers of Heart</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty">Prayers of Filial Piety</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya">Prayers of Resurrection</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya">Prayers of Entreaty</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty">Prayers of Determination</string>
    <string name="pr_faith">Prayers of Faith</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty">Prayers of Loyalty and Filial Piety</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration">Prayers of Restoration</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion">Prayers of Devotion</string>
    <string name="pr_unification">Prayers of Unification</string>
    <string name="b_hananim">제1장 하나님</string>
    <string name="b_champumo">제2장 참부모</string>
    <string name="b_chamsaran">제3장 참사랑</string>
    <string name="b_chamingan">제4장 참인간</string>
    <string name="b_chamkajon">제5장 참가정</string>
    <string name="b_chammanmul">제6장 참만물</string>
    <string name="b_yongye">제7장 지상생활과 영계</string>
    <string name="b_suren">제8장 신앙생활과 수련</string>
    <string name="b_mesia">제9장 가정교회와 종족적 메시아</string>
    <string name="b_penhwasasan">제10장 평화사상</string>
    <string name="b_menjol">제11장 예식과 명절</string>
    <string name="b_chonilguk">제12장 천일국</string>
    <string name="b_penhwamesigi">제13장 평화메시지</string>

    <string name="pr_nadezdy_1">1. Please reveal the beauty of Your original nature, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_2">2. Please let us return glory to You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_3">3. We bow down respectfully before You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_4">4. Please let us become children who find and return glory to You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_5">5. Please let us return glory to You while shouting out hosanna</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_6">6. Please establish us as our original selves in the original garden</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_7">7. Please let the day come when we have become completely one with You</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_8">8. Please let us become beings of love which go in all four directions</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_9">9. Please let us have the joy of resembling the original external form</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_10">10. Please let us become original people who atone for the sorrows of history</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_11">11. Please let us become beings who sing praises to You eternally Father</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_12">12. Please let us have hearts of hope heading towards You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_13">13. Please let us become fruits of joy who establish a day of rejoicing</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_14">14. Please let us seek and enter into Your world of heart</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_15">15. Please let us become children who open the age of Your glory</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_16">16. Please let us become children who build the original homeland</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_17">17. Please let us long for the original world</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_18">18. Please let us know heaven through our hearts</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_19">19. Please allow us the destined relationship of Father and son through our hearts</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_20">20. Please let us long for heavenly families</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_21">21. Please let us harmonize with You through our minds and bodies</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_22">22. Please let us harmonize and become one through our hearts</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_23">23. Please let our hope and Your hope correspond</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_24">24. Please let the ideal world of creation come quickly</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_25">25. Please let our new determination become the foundation of Your glory</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_26">26. Please let us realize that You created all things to receive joy</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_27">27. Please let us fulfill completely the mission of the victorious lord of dominion</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_28">28. Please let us become children who seek the original homeland</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_29">29. Please let us realize the precious value of families where the love of heaven is putting forth shoots</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_30">30. Father! Where are you dwelling?</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_31">31. We want to become lights of joy before You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_32">32. Please let us long to have the destined relationship of father and son with You</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_33">33. Please let us appear as symbols of You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_34">34. We thank You that we were born in this new historical age</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_35">35. Please let us make a nation of hope</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_36">36. Please let all of our emotions long for things of original nature</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_37">37. Please realize a family that can become the beginning of the kingdom of heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_38">38. Please establish us as Your eternal substantial object partners</string>
    <string name="pr_nadezdy_39">39. Please let us become the unification movement which realizes the ideal world of love</string>

    <string name="pr_pobedy_1">1. Please let us become the elite troops of heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_2">2. Please let us follow the example of Jacob`s course and return the glory of victory to You</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_3">3. Please let the glory of Zion come</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_4">4. Let us break down the walls of resentment and become courageous, victorious people who are moving forward</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_5">5. Please let us become harvest workers who have been grafted to the love of heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_6">6. Please let us become heaven`s elite troops who maintain unchanging fidelity</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_7">7. Please let us have victory in this final battle</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_8">8. Please let us become the elite troops of heaven which have victory over satan</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_9">9. Please let us attain the third Israel</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_10">10. Please let us realize the world of true freedom, liberation and unification</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_11">11. Please let us become those who remain with You to the very end, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_12">12. Please let us become brave men of heaven by overcoming all things</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_13">13. Please let us become the elite soldiers of heaven who are strong and of good courage</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_14">14. Please let us bear the final fruit by making an effort and enduring to the end</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_15">15. Please let us bear good fruit</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_16">16. Please let us become brave soldiers of heaven who rush towards Canaan</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_17">17. Please let us push forward bravely for the sake of victory over the world of satan</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_18">18. Please allow us to be those who remain the same on the final battlefield until the end</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_19">19. We have gone forth determined to die</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_20">20. Please allow us to become brave people who advance bravely towards the world</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_21">21. Please Let Us Go Forward With A Clear Sense Of Purpose</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_22">22. Please Let Us Become The Young People Who Are Establishing Your Nation, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_23">23. Please Allow Us To Become The Children Who Offer The Final Victory To You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_24">24. Please Let Us Be The Pioneers Who Establish Your Nation Of Victory</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_25">25. Please Allow Us To Overcome The Trials And To Be Victorious</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_26">26. Please Let Us Go Forward With Brave Courage Like David</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_27">27. Please Let Us Be Strong And Of Good Courage, And Please Let Us Win The Victory</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_28">28. Please Allow Us To Push Through Adversity And Be Victorious</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_29">29. Please Let Us Realize The Completion Of Your Will Through Home Church</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_30">30. Please Allow Us To Be The Young People In The Forefront When Following Your Will</string>
    <string name="pr_pobedy_31">31. Please Let Us Be Aware Of Being The Elite Troops For Building The Kingdom Of Heaven</string>

    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_1">1. Please allow us to become filial children who comfort You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_2">2. Please allow us to become children who completely fulfill our responsibility</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_3">3. Please allow us to become children who resolve Your heart of enmity, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_4">4. Please let us become heartistic sons and daughters who are strong and of good courage</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_5">5. Please let us fulfill our responsibility completely from a bride-like position</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_6">6. Please let us become true children who represent the cosmos</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_7">7. Please let us become children who are able to comfort You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_8">8. Please let us find the rest that comes from Your love, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_9">9. Please let us become children who respect Your counsel</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_10">10. Please let us move only as Yours</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_11">11. Please let us lead the way in the resolution of historical grief</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_12">12. Please command us through the original heart</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_13">13. Please let this become a path of faith where we attend our sorrowful Father</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_14">14. Please let us search for Your course of suffering</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_15">15. Please let us be able to sing of your liberation</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_16">16. Father! We are in deep awe</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_17">17. Please let us become children who do not leave behind grief</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_18">18. Please let us walk the path of loyalty and filial piety while attending You</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_19">19. Please let us become true sons and daughters who serve You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_20">20. Please let us become true filial children who attend you offering all our devotion</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_21">21. Please let us become true filial children and fulfill our responsibilities</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_22">22. Please let us have the qualification of true sons and daughters</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_23">23. Please let us welcome in the original spring together with You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_24">24. Please let us become children who comprehend through our hearts</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_25">25. Please let us become children who are able to be held in the embrace of Your Heart</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_26">26. Please let us inherit Your path of sacrifice</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_27">27. Please let us become children who are able to say we will go forward for Your sake alone</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_28">28. Please let us be children who do not forget our destined relationship as parent and children</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_29">29. Please let us possess the features of children who are able to represent You</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_30">30. Please let us become children who are able to take over Your great work</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_31">31. Please let us stand as fitting children before You</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_32">32. Please let us become able to testify that we are Your children</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_33">33. Please let us realize the precious value of True Parents and attend them</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_34">34. Please let us comfort the situation of heaven which has suffered unjustly</string>
    <string name="pr_pochtitelnosty_35">35. Please let us become children who are concerned about our parent`s heart first</string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_1">1. Please let us be aware of Your heart</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_2">2. Please allow us to experience Your heart</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_3">3. Please let us bow our heads before Your course of sorrow</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_4">4. Please allow us to become leading figures who inherit the sorrow and suffering of heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_5">5. We want to become true sons and daughters will comfort our Father\'s heart</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_6">6. Please enlighten us about Your heart though Jjesus</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_7">7. Please let us testify to the sorrowful heart of our Father</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_8">8. Please let us feel Your sorrow in place of You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_9">9. Please let Your situation and heart become ours, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_10">10. If the path leads to the heavenly palace, we would follow it even though it be a path of tears</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_11">11. Please let us comfort heaven for its hard work in the course of history</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_12">12. We long to become humble people who understand Your sorrow</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_13">13. Oh, sorrowful Father, please let us comfort you</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_14">14. Please let us be close to the wellspring of Your heart</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_15">15. Please let us communicate with Your lonely heart</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_16">16. Please let us communicate with Your heart</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_17">17. Please let us form our destined relationship of heart with You</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_18">18. Please let us become true sons and daughters who know how to hold on to You and weep</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_19">19. Please let us share Your heart</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_20">20. Please let us be moved by the heart of heaven and shed tears</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_21">21. Oh Father, who has walked through this course of history of lamentations</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_22">22. Please let us fully realize the intricacies of the sorrowful history</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_23">23. Please let us consider how much pain You feel as You sent out Your children</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_24">24. Please let us become Unification church members who comfort our sorrowful Father</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_25">25. Please find the destined relationship of heart and accomplish the completion of restoration</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_26">26. Oh Father, You have carried out the providence from a position of more suffering than I</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_27">27. Please forgive this pitiful group that has gone against You and betrayed Your confidence</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_28">28. Please let us become children who experience Your Heart of love</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_29">29. Everything was because of Your love</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_30">30. Now that it is over, we see thai everything was love</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_31">31. Please relieve the 6,000-year history so interspersed with grief</string>
    <string name="pr_serdca_32">32. Please bless this day as the day of the complete resolution of historical grief</string>

    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_1">1. Please make us resemble your external form</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_2">2. Please re-create us</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_3">3. Please allow us to become embodiments of goodness through the word</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_4">4. Please resurrect us as substantiation of Your goodness</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_5">5. Please allow us to become true children of truth, life and love</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_6">6. Please let us become true sons and daughters of the eternal True Parents</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_7">7. Please protect us through your touch of re-creation</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_8">8. Please let us have lives of heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_9">9. Please allow us to clear out the root of evil and go forth on a new path</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_10">10. Please restore us as original human beings</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_11">11. Thank You for letting us come to understand our original value</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_12">12. Please allow us to awaken from our sleep of ignorance, having forgotten our original appearance</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_13">13. Please take dominion over our minds and bodies</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_14">14. Please look at us with compassion and carry out Your work of re-creation</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_15">15. Please let us form relationships with You, trough our new hearts</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_16">16. Please lead us to become the true ancestors of humankind</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_17">17. Please graft us to Your heart of life</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_18">18. Please let us realize that we are beings who have formed relationships above and below, front and back, and right and left</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_19">19. Please allow us to possess the justification of children and the glory of children</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_20">20. Please establish us in a position united with Your standard of heart</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_21">21. We thank You for having chosen us and formed a relationship with us</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_22">22. Please allow us to realize the precious value of being Your children</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_23">23. We offer thanks and praise for Your having chosen us</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_24">24. Please allow us to leave the satanic realm and become one with You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_25">25. Please form a relationship with us through original love</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_26">26. Please cut off the root of sin through the power of the original nature</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_27">27. Please let us cast away the traces of sin caused by the fall</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_28">28. Please allow "me" to become someone who shines in history</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_29">29. Please let us cut off our relationship with the realm of satan and find our original Parents</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_30">30. Please establish a new order of love through the grace of the blessing</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_31">31. Please bless us to become sons and daughters You are able to embrace</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_32">32. Please allow us to become the children You hoped for</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_33">33. Please let us be reborn into a life thai is one with the will</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_34">34. Please take dominion through Your touch of re-creation</string>
    <string name="pr_voskresheniya_35">35. Please allow us the authority of sons</string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_1">1. Father! Please bear with our unworthiness</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_2">2. Please allow us to become living sacrifices of goodness alone</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_3">3. Since we will humbly take on everything, please go ahead and act</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_4">4. Please keep us and take dominion over us</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_5">5. Since we have repented for our unworthiness, please assert Your dominion over everything</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_6">6. Please enlighten us in this hour</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_7">7. Please grant us Your love and the grace of Your compassion</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_8">8. Please let us have an universal idea and truth</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_9">9. Father! Please become our center</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_10">10. Please allow Your work of sanctification</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_11">11. Please guide us to be children who fight with satan and are victorious</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_12">12. Please allow us to become one with Your mind</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_13">13. Please allow us to find the true path even in the midst of confusion</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_14">14. Please let us open our hearts and feel Your existence</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_15">15. Father! Please take pity on us</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_16">16. Please seek us reaching out with love</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_17">17. Please allow us to make a new beginning in the midst of this new shock</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_18">18. Father! Please have compassion</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_19">19. Please let us have meek and humble minds</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_20">20. Please allow us to realize that we are in a miserable situation</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_21">21. Please allow us to have a substantial feeling</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_22">22. Please allow us a foundation of security and Your outstretched hand of protection</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_23">23. Please bear with our mistakes of the past</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_24">24. Please allow us to feel deeply ashamed in front of You</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_25">25. Please allow us to become aware of the mistakes of the past</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_26">26. Please allow our minds to long for our original home</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_27">27. We long for You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_28">28. Please allow us to have minds that long for You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_29">29. Please allow us to become children longing for our real Father</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_30">30. Please allow us to go forth with childlike hearts</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_31">31. Please allow us to become those who can be together with goodness forever</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_32">32. Please allow us to consider on our own the situation with which we are faced</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_33">33. Please allow us to realize through experience the existence of our Father who is always near us</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_34">34. Please allow us to walk the path of life together with You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_35">35. Please allow us to live lives of gratitude</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_36">36. Please allow us to become children who cherish the pulse of Your life</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_37">37. Please set on fire our hearts of adoration for You, ether</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_38">38. Please allow us to become new shoots</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_39">39. Please allow us to pursue a true life with a gentle, humble attitude</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_40">40. Please allow us to be those who are able to be sorry even if we have given limitlessly</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_41">41. Please allow our meeting to be centered on heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_42">42. Please let us go the path of living for others</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_43">43. Please let us know the time of our life</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_44">44. Please establish us as children of whom You can be proud</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_45">45. Father! We did not know in time</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_46">46. Please allow us to become true</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_47">47. Please let us realize that on the path of faith our own selves are our enemies</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_48">48. Please allow us to become substantiations of Your hope</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_49">49. Please allow the fallen realm to be overcome by Your heart alone, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_50">50. Please remember your children who are working hard for the restoration of the world</string>

    <string name="pr_reshimosty_1">1. Please let us realize the will centered on heaven alone</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_2">2. We will run forward for the sake of God`s will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_3">3. We will go the way of the will gratefully</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_4">4. Please let us become children who can be entrusted with Your will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_5">5. Please let us become substantial beings who realize the will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_6">6. Please awaken us to our historical destiny of accomplishing Your will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_7">7. No matter what kind of suffering it is, please let us win over all of it</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_8">8. Since we have come to know Your will, please let us act on it</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_9">9. Please let us dash forward constantly towards the will today as well</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_10">10. Please let us go the way of the will of our Father sincerely</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_11">11. Please protect Your children who are fighting for the will in each place</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_12">12. Please let us go all the way on the path we must go</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_13">13. Please let us become a movement that remains by having endured and endured</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_14">14. We thank You that we have come to participate in the way of Your will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_15">15. Even if there is a path of the thorns of suffering, we will go for the sake of the will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_16">16. Please let us become unification church members who realize your will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_17">17. Please let us become children who are able to go directly toward the will alone</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_18">18. Please let us become people who can save the world</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_19">19. Please let us accomplish the realm of the will for the sake of the establishment of the ideal world</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_20">20. Please let us all walk the family-level course of responsibility for the will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_21">21. Please let us fulfill the missions of people who are going the way of the will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_22">22. Please do not let us be inattentive for even a moment while going the way of the will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_23">23. Please let us have humble minds while bowing our heads before You of our own accord</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_24">24. Please let us become victorious sons and daughters who are able to go straight towards the will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_25">25. Please let us live together with the will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_26">26. Please let us be able to cope with the way of Your will on our own</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_27">27. Please let us walk a course of life that corresponds with the will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_28">28. Please let us overcome the suffering way of the will by taking Your example</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_29">29. Please let us walk the way of public righteousness for the sake of humankind</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_30">30. Please let us become a movement that is able to advance altogether towards the way of the will</string>
    <string name="pr_reshimosty_31">31. Please let us straighten out and go the way of heaven by offering ourselves completely</string>

    <string name="pr_faith_1">1. Please let us experience the heart of Jesus christ</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_2">2. Please let us become people who represent Jesus</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_3">3. Please let us actualize the value of christ`s life</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_4">4. We will experience the heart of Jesus and go the way of Golgotha</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_5">5. Please let us hear the voice of the good shepherd</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_6">6. Please let us experience and feel keenly the heart of christ</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_7">7. Please let us experience and feel keenly the aching heart` of Heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_8">8. Please let this become a day resolving the sorrow of Jesus</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_9">9. Please let us fathom the heart of Jesus this day</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_10">10. Please let us fathom the sorrowful situation of Jesus who was rejected</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_11">11. Please let us sing of the glory of the resurrection beyond the cross</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_12">12. Please let us become people who can greet the Messiah</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_13">13. Please let us feel the sorrowful heart` of Jesus</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_14">14. Please let us feel the heart of deep historical regret through Jesus</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_15">15. Please let us go forth clinging to the sorrowful heart of Jesus</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_16">16. Please let us learn a lesson from Israel which turned its back on the will</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_17">17. Please let us become people who are fit to greet the Messiah</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_18">18. Please let us become people who console and comfort Jesus</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_19">19. Please let us cope with the heavenly responsibility like Jesus</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_20">20. Please let us reflect on the day of the historical anguish of Jesus</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_21">21. Please let us stand before You with hearts like Jesus` heart</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_22">22. Please let us comfort the heart of Jesus who died leaving behind grief</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_23">23. Please let us realize the mission that Israel could not accomplish</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_24">24. Please let us resolve the grief of the will which Jesus could not realize completely</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_25">25. Please let the Unification movement resolve the grief of Jesus</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_26">26. Please let us fulfill the mission of the final pioneer</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_27">27. Please let us take responsibility for the grief-filled heart of restoration</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_28">28. Please let us be victorious along the course of restoration</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_29">29. Please let us become children who fulfill completely the responsibility of the providence of restoration</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_30">30. Please let us lay a solid foundation which is in accord with the Principle</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_31">31. Please let us appear as those who will inherit the future world of hope</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_32">32. Please let us feel keenly and have deep experiences of heart</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_33">33. Please let us be able to form a destined relationship with Heaven`s circumstances and heart</string>
    <string name="pr_faith_34">34. Please let us have minds and bodies of oneness centered on the will</string>

    <string name="pr_loyalty_1">1. Please let us become the people who inherit the faith, hope and love of Heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_2">2. Please let us become loyal children who restore the original garden</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_3">3. Please let us be conscious of our destiny and bring the mission of the providence to a successful conclusion</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_4">4. Please allow us to become brave people of Heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_5">5. Please let us become brave people who are able to handle the heavenly mission</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_6">6. Now we go Your path with all its twists and turns, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_7">7. Please let us become children of loyalty and filial piety who are not ashamed before the will</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_8">8. Please guide us as those who represent the people and humankind</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_9">9. Please lead us through the crisis of the cross which is leading towards the ideal kingdom of Heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_10">10. Please let us become children who go beyond the worldwide wall of sorrow</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_11">11. Please let us fulfill our responsibility as sons and daughters who go beyond the world and fly</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_12">12. Please let us become sons and daughters who have taken responsibility for the battle for the sake of Heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_13">13. Please let us quickly realize the kingdom of heaven of peace where we can have faith in You</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_14">14. Please let us go the path of filial piety and loyalty for the sake of the foundation of rest for our Father</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_15">15. Please let us become children who fulfill loyalty and filial piety while on the course of restoration through indemnity</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_16">16. Please let them become holy women who establish Your kingdom</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_17">17. Please let us resemble the patriots of old who died for the sake of establishing the kingdom of Heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_18">18. Please realize Your will through us, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_19">19. We long to accompany You on the path You are going</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_20">20. Please let us become filial sons who carry the cross in Your stead</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_21">21. Please let us fulfill our mission as Your messengers</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_22">22. Please bless Your children of loyalty and filial piety</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_23">23. Please let us become children who bring an end to the history of being children without filial piety</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_24">24. Please let us become children who return loyalty and filial piety in response to the benefits You have given</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_25">25. Please let us become unificationists who create a new history</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_26">26. Please let us be victorious in the realm of the providentially historical environment</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_27">27. Please let us go forth pioneering the one way of victory</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_28">28. We love You and we are going the way of the will</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_29">29. Please let us fulfill the mission of the standard-bearers of the new age</string>
    <string name="pr_loyalty_30">30. Please let us love humankind as ourselves</string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_1">1. Please let us become offerings on the Abel-type altar</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_2">2. Please let us walk the way of the tradition of Abel</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_3">3. Please let us become offerings on an altar that heaven is able to be happy about</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_4">4. Please let us become offerings that tear down the walls of the indignation of heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_5">5. Please let us become offerings who offer gratitude for the grace of heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_6">6. Please let us become true brides who offer everything as pure things</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_7">7. Please let us give ourselves as offerings for the sake of the way of victory</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_8">8. Please use us as offerings for the will</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_9">9. Please let us dash forward embracing the mission heaven has commanded</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_10">10. Even though our minds and bodies are inadequate, we offer them to You completely</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_11">11. We want to become offerings for You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_12">12. I offer everything i have to You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_13">13. Oh my Father, Who has protected me even in the midst of difficulties!</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_14">14. Please let us be offerings in front of these people who are wandering</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_15">15. Please let us become offerings with humble minds</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_16">16. Please let us offer everything we have to You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_17">17. Please let us go the way of loyalty, filial piety and virtue</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_18">18. Please let us become sons and daughters that take responsibility for the sorrowful history</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_19">19. Please let us become living offerings that are able to represent this people, humankind, and everything under heaven</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_20">20. Please let us become sons and daughters of heaven who are substantial beings of joy before You</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_21">21. Please let us become a unification altar that struggles while moved by the will</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_22">22. Please let us become sons and daughters of heaven who are able to handle this mission of world history</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_23">23. Please let us fulfill the mission and responsibility that remain by offering our entire minds and bodies</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_24">24. Please let ourselves become true offerings</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_25">25. Please let us offer ourselves entirely as offerings of indemnity</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_26">26. Please let us be able to sacrifice for something bigger</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_27">27. Please let us go the way of victorious offerings for the whole</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_28">28. Please let us sing the song of victory by having offered ourselves completely</string>
    <string name="pr_devotion_29">29. Please lift us up as offerings on the world-level unification altar</string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_1">1. Please let us become a movement that settles the debts of the past</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_2">2. Please let us be able to tread upon and go beyond the grief left by our ancestors</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_3">3. Please let us become heavenly leaders who straighten out what was tangled</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_4">4. Please let us end the course of endurance of six thousand years</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_5">5. Please let us restore the Cosmic day of the Parents</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_6">6. We thank You for the day of all things which You have restored</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_7">7. Please let us become Your children who go over the world-level wall of sorrow</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_8">8. Please let us harvest the fruits of goodness at this historical crossroads</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_9">9. We thank You that we have this universal-level Children`s day</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_10">10. Please let a new age come, in which we are able to love even cain</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_11">11. Please let us become people who establish the world-level day of dedication</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_12">12. Please awaken us to the fact that we are people who represent history, the present age and the future</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_13">13. Please bless all humankind and the many spirit people from Children`s day on</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_14">14. Please let the Unification movement resolve the grief of the history of troubles</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_15">15. Please let us bear the fruit of the six-thousand-year history of restoration</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_16">16. Please let us become Abels who are able to make cain submit voluntarily</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_17">17. Please let us walk the public course of indemnity</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_18">18. Please let us reflect on the shameful past as we welcome the day of all things</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_19">19. Please let us live for You and for the future world</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_20">20. Please let us become people who know the age of the providence</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_21">21. Please let us go beyond the family level course of indemnity</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_22">22. Please let us prepare the firm foundation of true families</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_23">23. Please let this become the day of liberation for all the things of creation which are lamenting</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_24">24. Please let us horizontally indemnify completely the vertical grief of history</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_25">25. Please waken us to the fact that we are faced with a historically precious position</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_26">26. Please let the hard work of the good spirits bear fruit, Father!</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_27">27. Please let us become people who will be remembered as good ancestors by the future generations</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_28">28. Please let us go out to the world while embracing the Abel-type mission</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_29">29. We thank You that You have called us to the way of restoration</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_30">30. Please let us become people who bring the history of the evil dominion to a full stop</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_31">31. Please let us fulfill the responsibility from a position that represents the three ages</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_32">32. Please let this become a day in which the spirit world and the physical world rejoice</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_33">33. Please let us welcome a new age by going beyond the accusations of satan</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_34">34. I proclaim the foundation day for the nation of the unified world</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_35">35. I proclaim that the Kingdom of Heaven of victory and liberation will come to the earth</string>
    <string name="pr_restoration_36">36. We dedicate the foundation on which You are able to settle down comfortably throughout the entire cosmos</string>

    <string name="pr_unification_1">1. Father! Who will become the central person of this people?</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_2">2. Let us carry the cross of our people first</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_3">3. Please let us become aware of the course of tears you have gone to choose this people</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_4">4. Please allow us to become the people who resolve historical grief</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_5">5. Please bless us as the third Israel of hope</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_6">6. Please let us know Your will for leading this people through this history of sorrow</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_7">7. Please let us become a people that attends You, Father</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_8">8. We thank You that we are the children of Your chosen people</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_9">9. Please enlighten us as to Your Heart which has sought this people in suffering</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_10">10. Please let us become a Unification movement that is concerned about the korean people</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_11">11. Please let us give our up most for our original home land, Korea</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_12">12. Please let us be able to establish Korea as the third Israel</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_13">13. Oh Father! Please let the suffering of this nation end</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_14">14. Please let us become strong young people taking responsibility for the destiny of our people</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_15">15. Please let the Unification church participate in the destiny of the nation</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_16">16. Please let us become sons and daughters who serve the people</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_17">17. Please let us fulfill our mission completely at this point of the decisive baffle of national destiny</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_18">18. Please allow our movement to bring about the beginning of a new spring</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_19">19. Please relieve the grief of this divided people</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_20">20. Please let us become subjective, responsible people, pioneering the future of our people</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_21">21. Please let us experience what You felt in Your Heart as You dealt with this people and humankind</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_22">22. Father! Please watch over the future of Korea</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_23">23. Please allow our unification group to build a new history</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_24">24. Please make the nation on the foundation of this people</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_25">25. Please achieve the unification of the people</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_26">26. Please realize a victorious israel by liberating North Korea</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_27">27. Please allow this nation to greet a bright new morning</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_28">28. Please let the victorious Kingdom of Heaven come and Your grief be resolved</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_29">29. Please allow us to become a people that adapts itself to the laws of heavenly fortune</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_30">30. Father! Please become the lord of this nation</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_31">31. Please allow us to become brave unification people who unite the divided world</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_32">32. Please allow us to establish a unification realm centered on love</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_33">33. Father, please allow us to realize the world of peace with Your love as the center</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_34">34. Please allow us to establish the world of the realm of heart of living for others</string>
    <string name="pr_unification_35">35. Please allow us to become partners of the love of Heaven</string>

    <string name="b_hananim_1">1. 승리의 깃발을 들고 아버지를 모시고 살 수 있게 하시옵소서 (57.3.6, p. 1455)</string>
    <string name="b_hananim_2">2. 아버지의 뜻을 성취하게 하시옵소서 (56.10.7, p. 1457)</string>
    <string name="b_hananim_3">3. 하늘의 심정을 책임질 줄 알게 하시옵소서 (59.3.15, p. 1459)</string>
    <string name="b_hananim_4">4. 최후의 운명길에서 승리하게 하시옵소서 (69.7.27, p. 1461)</string>
    <string name="b_hananim_5">5. 새롭게 결심하고 나아갈 수 있게 하시옵소서 (67.12.24, p. 1463)</string>
    <string name="b_hananim_6">6. 정성을 다하는 무리가 되게 하시옵소서 (81.11.22, p. 1465)</string>
    <string name="b_hananim_7">7. 승리의 해가 되게 하시옵소서 (84.1.1, p. 1467)</string>

    <string name="b_champumo_1">1. 잠들어 있는 인류를 깨우치게 하시옵소서 (57.5.19, p. 1470)</string>
    <string name="b_champumo_2">2. 당신이 원하는 그릇으로 만드시옵소서 (75.2.1, p. 1471)</string>
    <string name="b_champumo_3">3. 주체성을 복귀할 수 있게 하시옵소서 (68.4.21, p. 1475)</string>
    <string name="b_champumo_4">4. 다짐한 대로 실천하게 하시옵소서 (67.12.31, p. 1476)</string>
    <string name="b_champumo_5">5. 새로운 부모의 전통을 세우게 하시옵소서 (80.4.15, p. 1479)</string>
    <string name="b_champumo_6">6. 사랑하는 아들딸이 될 때까지 지켜 주시옵소서 (82.10.17, p. 1483)</string>
    <string name="b_champumo_7">7. 참부모의 사랑권이 충만하게 하시옵소서 (90.7.8, p. 1485)</string>

    <string name="b_chamsaran_1">1. 당신의 심정을 선포하게 하시옵소서 (60.11.27, p. 1486)</string>
    <string name="b_chamsaran_2">2. 통일의 세계를 이루도록 그 길을 재촉하시옵소서 (66.12.18, p. 1489)</string>
    <string name="b_chamsaran_3">3. 새로운 마음과 몸으로 각오할 수 있게 하시옵소서 (59.3.29, p. 1492)</string>
    <string name="b_chamsaran_4">4. 사랑의 세계에 들어갈 수 있게 해주시옵소서 (86.2.1, p. 1495)</string>
    <string name="b_chamsaran_5">5. 충절을 지키는 아들딸이 되게 하시옵소서 (56.12.30, p. 1496)</string>
    <string name="b_chamsaran_6">6. 사랑의 심정으로 달려가게 하시옵소서 (82.10.27, p. 1498)</string>
    <string name="b_chamsaran_7">7. 아버지의 사랑과 인연을 찬양할 자녀가 되게 하시옵소서 (69.5.2, p. 1500)</string>

    <string name="b_chamingan_1">1. 아버님의 형상을 닮아나게 하시옵소서 (56.7.1, p. 1503)</string>
    <string name="b_chamingan_2">2. 부활의 역사를 일으켜 주시옵소서 (59.9.6, p. 1504)</string>
    <string name="b_chamingan_3">3. 재창조의 부름을 그리워하게 해주시옵소서 (66.12.11, p. 1506)</string>
    <string name="b_chamingan_4">4. 충직한 자녀가 되게 하시옵소서 (57.6.23, p. 1509)</string>
    <string name="b_chamingan_5">5. 새로운 방향을 취하게 하시옵소서 (59.6.28, p. 1511)</string>
    <string name="b_chamingan_6">6. 끝까지 싸워 나갈 수 있게 하시옵소서 (80.11.10, p. 1513)</string>
    <string name="b_chamingan_7">7. 당신이 사정을 알게 하시옵소서 (69.5.25, p. 1516)</string>

    <string name="b_chamkajon_1">1. 사랑의 질서를 세우는 선한 조상이 되게 하시옵소서 (70.3.23, p. 1519)</string>
    <string name="b_chamkajon_2">2. 당신의 자녀들을 기억해 주시옵소서 (70.4.19, p. 1521)</string>
    <string name="b_chamkajon_3">3. 참다운 효자와 효녀들이 되게 하시옵소서 (58.3.23, p. 1525)</string>
    <string name="b_chamkajon_4">4. 아버지의 사랑을 잊지 않게 하시옵소서 (68.11.17, p. 1525)</string>
    <string name="b_chamkajon_5">5. 부끄럽지 않은 부모의 인연을 갖게 하여 주시옵소서 (71.2.1, p. 1529)</string>
    <string name="b_chamkajon_6">6. 참부모의 사상을 지니게 하시옵소서 (71.4.29, p. 1531)</string>
    <string name="b_chamkajon_7">7. 축복받은 후손들이 되게 해주시옵소서 (2007.3.8, p. 1533)</string>

    <string name="b_chammanmul_1">1. 만물을 주관할 수 있는 아들딸로 세워 주시옵소서 (56.6.10, p. 1535)</string>
    <string name="b_chammanmul_2">2. 만물복귀의 날을 기념하기 위하여 (63.7.26, p. 1536)</string>
    <string name="b_chammanmul_3">3. 모든 것을 뜻대로 이루어 주시옵소서 (63.5.15, p. 1538)</string>
    <string name="b_chammanmul_4">4. 만물이 해방을 받을 수 있게 해주시옵소서 (69.6.15, p. 1539)</string>
    <string name="b_chammanmul_5">5. 만물의 날을 문자대로만 알지 않게 해주시옵소서 (70.6.4, p. 1541)</string>
    <string name="b_chammanmul_6">6. 대제사장의 책임을 다하는 자녀들이 되게 하시옵소서 (66.6.19, p. 1545)</string>
    <string name="b_chammanmul_7">7. 봉헌전환식을 선포하오니 받아주시옵소서 (98.5.26, p. 1547)</string>

    <string name="b_yongye_1">1. 골고다의 한을 밟고 넘어가게 해주시옵소서 (65.12.26, p. 1549)</string>
    <string name="b_yongye_2">2. 뜻적인 승리에 동참할 수 있게 하시옵소서 (82.9.26, p. 1552)</string>
    <string name="b_yongye_3">3. 길이길이 바라는 뜻대로 이루어 주시옵소서 (86.1.3, p. 1553)</string>
    <string name="b_yongye_4">4. 모든 것이 평준화될 수 있게 축복해 주시옵소서 (89.1.2, p. 1554)</string>
    <string name="b_yongye_5">5. 가정들이 정착할 수 있는 본향 땅을 축복하시옵소서 (2000.2.6, p. 1557)</string>
    <string name="b_yongye_6">6. 승리적인 터전을 마련할 수 있게 축복해 주시옵소서 (2000.9.3, p. 1558)</string>
    <string name="b_yongye_7">7. 자녀의 면모를 갖추게 해주시옵소서 (96.3.17, p. 1560)</string>

    <string name="b_suren_1">1. 사명을 알게 해주시옵소서 (56.11.25, p. 1562)</string>
    <string name="b_suren_2">2. 당신의 영광을 세워 드릴 수 있게 해주시옵소서 (57.9.15, p. 1563)</string>
    <string name="b_suren_3">3. 모든 것을 깨달을 수 있게 해주시옵소서 (57.3.17, p. 1564)</string>
    <string name="b_suren_4">4. 새로운 생애를 향하여 달음질할 수 있게 하시옵소서 (68.1.7, p. 1564)</string>
    <string name="b_suren_5">5. 참효자 참효녀가 되게 하시옵소서 (66.1.2, p. 1568)</string>
    <string name="b_suren_6">6. 아버님 홀로 영광 받으시옵기를 원합니다 (69.10.19, p. 1571)</string>
    <string name="b_suren_7">7. 지상천국이 되게 해주시옵기를 바라옵니다 (6.3.1, p. 1572)</string>

    <string name="b_mesia_1">1. 가정교회의 승리적인 날이 이루어지게 하시옵소서 (80.10.19, p. 1574)</string>
    <string name="b_mesia_2">2. 가정교회를 중심삼고 전부가 하나되게 하시옵소서 (82.1.1, p. 1575)</string>
    <string name="b_mesia_3">3. 여명의 때가 목전에 다가왔음을 깨닫게 하시옵소서 (80.11.1, p. 1577)</string>
    <string name="b_mesia_4">4. 통일교회의 사명을 망각하지 않게 해주시옵소서 (80.10.16, p. 1578)</string>
    <string name="b_mesia_5">5. 가정교회의 시대를 맞게 된 것을 감사드립니다 (81.1.1, p. 1582)</string>
    <string name="b_mesia_6">6. 한국을 불쌍히 보시옵소서 (85.12.29, p. 1583)</string>
    <string name="b_mesia_7">7. 사랑·믿음·소망의 계승자가 되게 하시옵소서 (56.6.6, p. 1586)</string>

    <string name="b_penhwasasan_1">1. 당신을 저희들 마음 가운데 모시게 하시옵소서 (71.2.11, p. 1588)</string>
    <string name="b_penhwasasan_2">2. 무한하신 자비와 사랑으로 같이해 주시옵소서 (1970.11.1, p. 1590)</string>
    <string name="b_penhwasasan_3">3. 만민이 하늘나라에 속할 수 있게 하시옵소서 (87.10.4, p. 1591)</string>
    <string name="b_penhwasasan_4">4. 전진적인 발걸음을 재촉하게 해주시옵소서 (90.11.18, p. 1592)</string>
    <string name="b_penhwasasan_5">5. 전체가 하늘 뜻 가운데 일취월장하게 해주시옵소서 (2000.6.12, p. 1594)</string>
    <string name="b_penhwasasan_6">6. 화합 통일의 안착시대로 전진할 수 있게 하시옵소서 (2005.7.1, p. 1596)</string>
    <string name="b_penhwasasan_7">7. 사랑의 왕권시대를 전수받는 시대가 되게 하시옵소서 (2006.5.3, p. 1597)</string>

    <string name="b_menjol_1">1. 모든 것을 저희 가운데서 성취하시옵소서 (61.1.1, p. 1599)</string>
    <string name="b_menjol_2">2. 지옥에까지 사랑 빛을 비춰주소서 (1977.2.23, p. 1602)</string>
    <string name="b_menjol_3">3. 통일의 나라를 이룰 수 있게 해주시옵소서 (69.11.10, p. 1603)</string>
    <string name="b_menjol_4">4. 인류의 해방을 선언할 수 있는 때를 맞았습니다 (98.5.26, p. 1604)</string>
    <string name="b_menjol_5">5. 부끄럽지 않은 아들딸의 모습을 갖추게 하시옵소서 (80.11.8, p. 1605)</string>
    <string name="b_menjol_6">6. 천주의 통일과 해방을 선포할 수 있는 시대를 감사합니다 (2001.8.25, p. 1608)</string>
    <string name="b_menjol_7">7. 지상천국해방태평시대를 맞이하게 되기를 바라옵니다 (2006.1.3, p. 1610)</string>

    <string name="b_chonilguk_1">1. 이상적인 아담 문화를 완결하게 하시옵소서 (1.12.9, p. 1612)</string>
    <string name="b_chonilguk_2">2. 앞날의 갈 길에 동고동락해 주시옵기를 원합니다 (2001.12.30, p. 1613)</string>
    <string name="b_chonilguk_3">3. 하나님 조국의 정착과 천일국을 선포했사옵니다 (2002.1.26, p. 1616)</string>
    <string name="b_chonilguk_4">4. 만세에 승리의 태평성대국이 되게 하시옵소서 (2003.1.1, p. 1618)</string>
    <string name="b_chonilguk_5">5. 정착의 시대를 선포할 수 있게 되었습니다 (2004.12.1, p. 1620)</string>
    <string name="b_chonilguk_6">6. 일화통일 정착해방의 세계로 향하게 하시옵소서 (2005.4.9, p. 1621)</string>
    <string name="b_chonilguk_7">7. 사랑의 주권이 확장되게 하시옵소서 (2005.2.25, p. 1622)</string>

    <string name="b_penhwamesigi_1">1. 하나님왕권즉위식 기도 (1.1.13, p. 1624)</string>
    <string name="b_penhwamesigi_2">2. 쌍합십승일 선포 기도 (2004.5.5, p. 1625)</string>
    <string name="b_penhwamesigi_3">3. 천주평화의 왕 참부모님 천정궁 입궁·대관식 기도 (2006.6.13, p. 1628)</string>
    <string name="b_penhwamesigi_4">4. 2001년 원단 기도 (2001.1.1, p. 1629)</string>
    <string name="b_penhwamesigi_5">5. 청심평화월드센터 봉헌식 기도 (2012.3.22, p. 1633)</string>
    <string name="b_penhwamesigi_6">6. 2005년 원단 기도 (2005.1.1, p. 1636)</string>
    <string name="b_penhwamesigi_7">7. 2007년 원단 축도 (2007.1.1, p. 1641)</string>
    <string name="b_penhwamesigi_8">8. 참아버님 최후의 기도 다 이루었다! (12.8.13, p. 1646)</string>

</resources>