<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="pr_hananim_1t">
My Father, in the beginning, you created all creation with the will of goodness and existed in an unchanging form as the standard of nature. We know that we are thus far from the standard of a good conscience, and we know that it was the sigh of heaven and of creation.
\n\nFather, we have a path of providential destiny in which we must find the eternal standard of good even at the cost of our lives, and we have a mission to follow this path to the end. Please.
\n\nThe element of evil that invades through the body is blocking the path of the mind that aims for good. Father, please guide us so that our mind that aims for good will not be defeated by the body\'s sanctions in this battle.
\n\nI pray that I will be led only by the power of good and the power of love that leads my heart, so that I can find my Father and live with you forever, resembling your image as an immutable, inseparable, and eternal existence, Father. , longing for and longing for.
\n\nAs we fight sin through a long history, we have become full of scars, and the roots of sin are ingrained in our bones. It is our responsibility to get rid of them, but we are so lacking. Father who has the authority to live, Father who has power, Father who has the authority to create, Once again, reach out your hand of power to remove all the elements of evil that are held in the shadow of death, and reveal at this time the direct work of life in heaven that can stimulate the heart of it and create a victorious heart. I long for and long for you to come. So, raise up the power of resurrection from ourselves, and allow us to become your sons and daughters who can create the work of resurrection on behalf of the center of our environment, dear Father, we earnestly pray and desire.
\n\nLead us from groaning because we are in an incomplete position, and allow us to qualify as Father\'s true children by winning the battle against the enemy satan who is blocking this path on the road to perfection. Lord, guide me to become sons and daughters who can boast in front of billions of satan. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to take on the weapons possessed by the heavenly angels in our stead and win the battle against billions of satan.
\n\nFather, at this time, a small number of people are on their knees to confess their shortcomings before you. Lord, grant me the eyes and heart to discern between good and evil. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that your direct work will be with us at this time so that we can see and understand correctly.
\n\nNow, this is the time to make a sacrifice in front of Father, so even if I have nothing to offer in front of you, allow me to give my heart to you. Remove the elements of evil from your sin-stained body, and honestly expose yourself to your Father so that you can act according to your commands and become a body and mind worthy of your will.
\n\nEven this evening, please give the gifts you promised uniformly to the countless sons and daughters who are scattered everywhere and are building lonely altars. Allow the moving work, the work of inspiration, and the work of power to be able to fulfill your will that you foretold at the end of the day to appear wherever your children stay. I know that there will be many sons and daughters, so hurry and command them to come together in one place, so that they may meet your will. Lead me to the end, dear Father, I earnestly hope and desire you.
\n\nAt this time, the work of your Holy Spirit will be with you wherever you gather to worship on the altar in heaven, and by showing the moving work and the work of repentance, it will lead the nation to become altars capable of fulfilling the mission entrusted to this nation in the last days. Please watch. I prayed in the name of the Lord, praying that the remaining time would be governed by your will.
\nAju.
\n(1957.3.6)
    </string>

    <string name="pr_hananim_2t">
Loving Father, I know that it is your lament that there is no one who can put an end to the history of the battle that remains the resentment of heaven. Humans will have to uproot the fundamental root of the fall that has been planted by humans, but despite the passage of a long history, humans have not yet uprooted the fundamental root of that sin. Father, please allow us to uproot it.
\n\nI earnestly hope and wish that all the audience gathered at this time will be deeply touched by the Father\'s heart and allow them to become one. Please allow us to emulate your sorrowful heart, and allow us to have the hope that you desire anew. Please allow me to become the brave men who can take responsibility for the history of resentment and fight the billions of millions of enemies, satan, who appear to represent heaven, and allow me to become brave men who can stand on behalf of the earth.
\n\nPlease allow each of us to take responsibility for your will until a garden of joy where we can share your eternal Father\'s love with each other is realized in the remaining battlefield. I earnestly hope and desire, dear Father, that each one of you will become your valiant sons and daughters who can fight satan on behalf of your overall will.
\n\nAllow us to realize at this hour what sign our hearts are facing in heaven and what sign our bodies are facing in the whole universe, and allow us to become children of joy who can avenge your Father. Come, Father, I long for you and I long for you. Our bodies and minds have not yet been embraced in your bosom, so please advise and work with your power to correct the direction of our hearts. Orient our hearts toward Heaven, and allow us to go on the path of hope that you desire.
\n\nPlease allow our bodies and minds to sympathize with the grace of your joy, and start the work of re-creation centering on us. So, by holding on to the root of sin and fighting and overcoming it, allow me to become children who can empathize with the love of the Father and give glory to the Father. Dear Father, I earnestly pray that the children gathered at this time will not fall into the accusations of billions of satan and allow them to be offered as a sacrifice of glory on your altar.
\n\nNow, allow us, who have fallen before you, to be aware of our shortcomings and to stand up for ourselves while facing your majestic image. As meek and humble sacrifices, I earnestly beg and desire that you will allow me to become children who yield to the gift of the Father\'s atonement, and to appear as the prodigal son who has found his father. Please do not let this crowd shed tears of mourning, and let satan not walk in ridicule. Please share with me just for this one hour so that my mind and body are taken captive before the Father, and allow this time to be offered as an ideal sacrifice that can be rejoiced in contact with the gift of eternal life, the gift of resurrection, and the gift of love. Please do it, Father, I earnestly hope and desire you.
\n\nFather, this is a holy day. It is a day of promise to bless all people, so please allow the gift of joy to be shared in every temple that gathers on behalf of mankind. Now that the end has come, pour out the fire of the Holy Spirit like water, so that your chosen children can unite and fight against this dark world. Allow them to be your sons and daughters, Father, I earnestly hope and desire you.
\n\nFirst of all, bless the altar on behalf of the nation, and on behalf of the altar, allow your sons and daughters who live with all of your devotion, heart, and integrity to become sacrifices to your eternal Father. come Now allow me not to become debtors to you in the battlefield that remains, and grant me the gift of eternal victory. Please allow me to build up your will with the heart of an indomitable warrior until the ideal garden is built that can express the feeling of your blessing on earth. Father of love, I earnestly wish and wish .
\n\nFather of love, there are so many children who are not able to attend this evening this evening. No matter where you are, you will work uniformly, and you will be able to proclaim your will that you want to be accomplished in the last days to all nations so that heaven and earth can be in harmony. Allow me to build an altar of joy. I earnestly ask you to allow me to be your children who only accomplish your will with all your might, heart, and energy, and I prayed in your name with all your words.
\nAju.
\n(1956.10.7)
    </string>

    <string name="pr_hananim_3t">
Today, on the day you have granted, we kneel down and gather in your presence, worrying about ourselves, who are lacking, so now allow us to see where our hearts are. We know that the course that the Father pioneered the path of life was a very solemn and sanctified course.
\n\nFather, have mercy on your sons and daughters gathered here. I earnestly desire and desire that you reveal the image of your majestic Father here, establish the standard of victory that you have allowed, and acknowledge that you are a consecrated group. If the course of providence left behind is a path of sorrow, we know that we are responsible for stopping this sorrow, and we also know that those who do not feel the infinite sorrow of Heaven cannot bear the responsibility for that sorrow.
\n\nPlease allow me to become the ones who can take responsibility for the sorrow and battle left behind. I know that in order to be able to bear this task, I have to feel the greatest sorrow than anyone else, and I know that I must not become a loser in the battlefield of an unfair position more than anyone else. Father, I earnestly hope and wish that you will allow us to become a crowd at this time with a heart for whether our bodies can become victorious sacrifices before heaven.
\n\nTwo thousand years have passed since Jesus came and went, but the altar that Jesus built on Calvary and the altar of true victory that the heavens wept together have not appeared on this earth. I know that the time has come for the world-wide Mount Golgotha where heaven and earth meet, and the time has come for the summit of Gethsemane to appear.
\n\nThere must be many saints who bear the responsibility, but the more we know that there are no crowds who can rejoice when heaven comes, the more we know that sons and daughters who are concerned about their Father\'s feelings are forced to look at this earth and weep. . Father, please allow me to know that the greater the earnestness of your longing for the day of your wish, the greater your anticipation for your faithful image to appear on the earth.
\n\nWith all of our hearts and our bodies today, please allow us to become sons and daughters who can be held in your hands and built up in your heart, so that we can take on all the sorrows of history. We know that this must be a time when our hearts and bodies are resurrected anew through the work of Father Himself. Please forgive us for failing to fulfill the responsibilities entrusted to us over the past week, forgive us for not being faithful to your Father, forgive us for not being able to hold onto your heart and lead a tearful life. Forgive me for forgetting that you did not mind the steps of your labors to come.
\n\nAt this time today, Father, I earnestly hope and wish that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who can make new resolutions and resolve, realize all the shortcomings of the past, and hold onto their own hearts centered on Father\'s heart. Father, since this is a holy day, have mercy on the 30 million people who are in pitiful situation. Be their friend, be their leader, and be the master of resurrecting their lives, Father, I earnestly hope and desire you. May the Father be the center of their hope. Let these become a group that cannot move apart from you, make them a nation, make them a denomination, Father, I hope and desire.
\n\nI earnestly hope and wish that the blessings that will be granted to this nation will come down through this time. Please allow your sons and daughters who were responsible for the one day of victory to fulfill their mission and responsibilities. I know that this nation has a responsibility to fulfill this will and reveal the glory of the Father. I know that there are infinite trials in the process of fulfilling that responsibility, so I earnestly hope and pray that you will allow me to become sons and daughters who can fulfill their responsibilities in the course of such trials and act on behalf of Father.
\n\nPlease bless the countless people who do not know this meaning. At a time when the waves of life and death are being swept away, hold on to you and allow a multitude of people who can be your sons and daughters to appear among this human race. Father, I earnestly hope and desire that you will allow many sons and daughters to appear among the human race of this earth, who can stand before the Father with the full responsibility of saving mankind from the scourge of judgment.
\n\nIf you say that there are people who are unaware of such a mission, a time like this, and a responsibility like this, please warn them through them and make them sons and daughters who can bear the responsibilities and missions of the last days. come I pray that you will spread your hand of a uniform gift over the crowds who have a lonely heart and appeal to the Father in the countryside, and hold them so that they do not fall out of the way of the battle to find and establish the one day of victory that you have granted, Father. I wish and want.
\n\nFrom the first hour to the last hour of this hour, I earnestly ask and wish that the Father Himself will take care of it, and that the authority of darkness will not become a moving time. I give everything before my Father, so please take charge of it. I pray in your name.
\nAju.
\n(1959.3.15)
    </string>

    <string name="pr_hananim_4t">
Father, your children who fought in the countryside have come to Seoul, the heart of Korea. Father, allow them to see how desperate they must be. For whom did we ourselves come to this place? Although we have grown into a single life through the basis of victory in our individual battles, first, we must be a person who has chosen the solemn task of building a heaven and calmly reflects on whether or not we have become ourselves who can take responsibility for it. I understand that the problem is not the surrounding environment, but the attitude of the person in charge. Therefore, Jesus also met the fateful moment in the Garden of Gethsemane at the end of the three-year journey in harmony with his Father along with the third prayer.
\n\nFather, now we have the responsibility to bring this Seoul City Wall back to you. Please help us feel how pitiful you are to look at and lead us, who do not even think about your feelings in ten million times in such a serious time. You have to criticize yourself mercilessly and analyze your own individual consciousness to feel what your position is in relation to the whole. So, you have to realize that you are lacking, and you should hope that the brothers around you are better than you. Also, with the hope of building hidden achievements, I earnestly hope and wish that you will once again feel the need to move by finding a connection point that can be helpful in front of the will of the whole.
\n\nFather, the time has come to bring Seoul back. In the meantime, we tried to return to Seoul centered on one will, but there was a period of time when people in the world did not understand and were not able to work freely, but the wall was too high for us. Thus, we have been focusing on consumption only to sustain the life of a ephemera in a desolate place afflicted by a storm of severe trials.
\n\nHowever, the time of the offensive is coming, which we did not expect. Now is the time to take the offensive because of the course that Father has been toiling. In spite of the fact that the final battle should be resolved and we should be prepared to praise the glory of our Father, even if it results in victory, we must not become a group that does not have the content to tell. Even in the field of battle, and after winning, we have to become a hundred times more energetic, and we must become people who can boast that there is nothing lacking in what Father sees and asks us to do.
\n\nFather, please protect your children all over South Korea. I hope that all of the system of activities that focus on us, focusing on the final victory, can match your feelings and your actions, so that we can become a victorious group in the final battlefield. come and want Father, I earnestly hope and wish that you will remember the children scattered all over South Korea or around the world at this time, mainly in Seoul. Father, help us to know that you are always pouring out your compassion and compassion on our poor image as we are hastening ourselves on the final fateful path we have to go. Also, let us know that you have a lonely Father with us when we are lonely, and let us know that you have a Father who is concerned with our difficulties when we are in trouble.
\n\nHelp us to be those who understand the fact that our own misery does not end in our own misery, but also makes you miserable. Today, we often forget that we were responsible for the solemn task of liberating the Third Age. However, our historical ancestors are looking down on us from the spiritual realm, the humans of this age are looking at us, and our descendants in the future are looking forward to us. Make them feel like marathon runners on the pitch. We will have to overcome all the trials and pains we face there.
\n\nPlease let me know that there is a final pass to overcome and overcome even though I cannot sleep, and even if the trials and pains are aggravated in the step towards the finish line of that pass, I will have to overcome all the aggravated difficulties and move on. I hope and hope that you will let them know that only then will victory shine globally. Father, help me to realize once again that in order to cross the mountain in the future, it depends on how united and united the people responsible for pulling it over. So, in your sight, let us become a group that does not hesitate to give orders and are not anxious to lead, so that we can cross over high and high peaks without hesitation, defeat the enemy\'s last cross and break through the last mountain, become a united group. Come, Father, I long for and long for you.
\n\nDear Father, we earnestly ask you to help us become your sons and daughters who can fight even a thousand times by devoting all our energy to the one day we meet once a day by constantly equipping ourselves with equipment while worrying about the remaining days. want you I asked Father to be with me on this day as well, and I spoke all the words to True Parents for a while.
\nAju.
\n(1969.7.27)
    </string>

    <string name="pr_hananim_5t">
Father, there are many people on this earth who praise your name and who claim to be your beloved sons and daughters, but how many of them are true sons and daughters with whom you can truly open your heart and share your affairs? come back? The more I think about it, the more I realize that this is a miserable fact.
\n\nFather, in memory of this poor people who were driven out from among many peoples and lands, I firstly thank you in front of your holy will to select this lonely mountain of three thousand li and set the focus of the providence. The more I think about how precious a group of people who can be loyal to this will is, the more I can\'t help but feel a sense of shame. However , I hope that you will forgive this nation, which has a historical background, that makes you worry when you consider that the heart of a Father\'s love resides more in a child who is crippled than in a perfect child .
\n\nFather, the children of unification have walked the history of bloody and tears of struggle without the knowledge of others, with the limit of 7 years standing up to the present day. Sometimes he was driven, sometimes he cried while beating his chest, and sometimes he hugged his hungry intestines and discussed his Father\'s circumstances, and wept endlessly. In this way, all the past started with tears, but I cannot help but be more grateful when I think that it was all because of my Father\'s help and protection that it was not reaped with tears, but with laughter, and I was able to have a day in which I can thank my father. I buy it.
\n\nWe pray with all our heart that the heavens and the earth of freedom where we can bring our Father and express our proud feelings soon come to pass. come Father, today is a holy day. Please deal with the earnest feelings of your lonely children, who are scattered all over South Korea, looking at this place with their knees open. We earnestly hope that you will comfort them with the same love you were to be friends and protect them when we came to our Father for sad circumstances.
\n\nNo matter what anyone says, we are lonely people who have nothing. We should be the ones who know that you are on our side, only you are ours, and that you are living for you is a precious thing that cannot be changed even with billions of dollars in the world. longing for and longing for
\n\nSeoul has the headquarters of unification, which is connected to the world. Remember your children who remain here. We know that this is a scary place if you are afraid, a sad place if you are sad, and a difficult place if you are difficult. But if we say that they are in the Father, can communicate with the Father, and live because of the Father, do you know that the Father sits forever in the place where they stand and directs and governs our lives? I am even more grateful for the gift of my Father who made me stand here.
\n\nFather, please help me to be truly grateful for being built in this position today because of the foundation of justice that our ancestors have built up throughout their lives and the benefits of the times. Please allow me to give thanks from a historical standpoint through the past, present and future, rather than from my own standpoint. I earnestly wish and wish that you would put me in such a position, knowing that my Father would recognize that such victory is more valuable than any great person in history.
\n\nDear Father! Now that we are entering a new year, all the programs of heavenly enemies planned for understanding will be completed, and we will achieve the heaven that the Father wants on this earth, raise the number of victory and return honor, glory and praise to the Father. I earnestly hope and wish that it will be a year of joy. Father, help all children who are connected by heart to become brothers who can bring out your heart. I sincerely hope that you will become sons and daughters of the Father who can achieve the race of hope through the relationship between the parents of faith and their children.
\n\nPlease remember the children all over the world. Even today, there are many people who are fighting in a lonely place centered on the relationship of Father\'s heart, so I sincerely hope that you will remember them. I sincerely hope and wish that you will protect me until we meet again, and that you will be the ones who are determined to leave behind the incisions of the heavenly enemies that your Father desires by doing your duty of loyalty and filial piety for the rest of your life.
\n\nWe, who have to go on the 2nd 7-year course in the new year, help us to make new resolutions and move forward dignifiedly through the words we have heard. Heaven has triumphed even in the place where the fierce wind blows. We know that once we firmly decide to follow him, the road will be shortened and flat. I earnestly ask and wish that you will allow me to become all children who know how. I earnestly beseech you to grant your gifts and the glory of victory in all things, and I have spoken all your words in the name of True Parents.
\nAju.
\n(1967.12.24)
    </string>

    <string name="pr_hananim_6t">
Loving Father, even if the road is rough, when the heart of integrity that loves you drags me, even if my legs bleed profusely, I count it as the blood of gratitude, and it is amazing that there is a way to go to heaven with my collar closed. found out that it was by
\n\nNow that I am over 60 years old, when I heard that some people are talking about a successor, I still have a way to go and I feel sorry for not being able to fulfill the principle of loyalty in front of you. When I think of such a thing, please do all my strength to go on the rest of the road. I started on the path of Passion, so even if I end my life on the path of Passion, please guide me, dear Father, so that I can finish everything beautifully.
\n\nI don\'t need power, I don\'t need money, I don\'t need knowledge. However, we need a way for the nation to come to you with tears centered on your love. There is only the need for the world to forget everything and follow the path of your love with tears. While this tradition is alive, we should leave it as a material for the tradition in the short course of life, and lay the foundation for the explosion of living water in the hearts of young people of the Unification family not only in this era but also in future generations. Father, who is well aware that this is the path we must take as our duty at this time, please remember the group of unification scattered around the world right now.
\n\nThose who offer congratulations with tears as they think of this place where I am here in lonely Korean land, and their slender appeals, wishing that the teacher will be blessed along the way, is not because they want to be saved from me, but to cooperate with you. There is no doubt that it is only for the victory of your will. I am also a poor person, and they are also poor people. Please, remember, give your blessing and drink the bitter cup of defeat in the crowd, and do not become a group that betrays the heavens with lamentation. Drink the cup of victory, not defeat. We ask that Father help us to make it sound like a song of praise and a glorious song.
\n\nFather, please join us on the battlefield that is now taking place in America. It is a battle that can show you what your glory and love are like, that you can show the dignified appearance of the Unification Church, and that you can show the true nature of the sons and daughters of heaven. Knowing that, you go ahead without worrying about everything. I do not want to hear the prayers of the poor, the tears of the poor, and the voices of their prayers with sorrow. You know that too. Please have pity on them, forgive the American people so that their wishes can come true, and again, I ask you to bless the American courts and guide them in obscuring the path of goodness.
\n\nDear Father, I am coming to Korea and staying for 20 days. During that time, there were many changes and many stories, but please do not allow me to take a step that fails to leave behind the love of heaven or leave the ground of victory where the nation can reside. Even if I am reviled and disrespected, if there is a way that Heaven can come and bless the future of this nation, I will go that way.
\n\nBecause we know that the way for the human race to enter the world is blocked because of this, please accept the story of having to hold on to this and pray. If there is a fault of the nation, please forgive it, and if there is a fault in the rulers, please forgive it. I know that I am going down that path because of my ignorance, so please let Heaven teach me and put it into practice. If you don\'t do it, if it\'s the law of heaven to rebuke, if you don\'t listen to what you teach them to do after you know whether it\'s true or not Know and forgive me, Father, I earnestly beg you and I beg you.
\n\nI earnestly wish and wish that those who have been looking forward to the day of victory after hearing the news of the teacher will pray for a thousand times and ten thousand fold blessings. Now, Father, protect this altar. This group that I am leaving behind has vowed to fight to leave a history of fierce battles. I earnestly beg you, Father, to allow me to become a group of people who hold on to one life, writhe, cry and cry, but do everything they can to open the head of Han on their own. Please watch over them until we meet again. I ask you to remember the group of unification in Korea and around the world, to remember the future of this country and this people, and to protect the democratic world and pave the way to victory over the communist world. So, on a glorious day in heaven, I thank you for this time you have given me, asking that the foundation for your more than love be realized on this earth. I have spoken all the words in the name of True Parents.
\nAju.
\n(1981.11.22)
    </string>

    <string name="pr_hananim_7t">
Dear Father, Happy New Year. May the blessings of heaven be upon this earth on this fabric. In this time of succession to the new year, let the historical and celestial relationship flow from heaven to earth. And, centering on all the Unification Church groups, please allow the blessings of heaven to be connected to all religions and mankind. So, with one heart as the center of your heart, I pray that it will spread out into one family, one race, one nation, one nation, and one world.
\n\nFather, at this time, the democratic world and the communist world have reached the final summit and are in a state of confusion with each other, unable to take their place. Such is the case with the United States, representing the democratic world, and the Soviet Union, representing the communist world. In the democratic world, focusing on the Adam nation, the Eve nation, the Abel nation, and the Cain nation that you were trying to establish, all these nations today are the United States representing the democratic world at the top of the world and the Soviet Union representing the communist world. It is at the same point as the position.
\n\nIn this era, by linking the will of the United States with the will of Japan, and the will of Korea, centering on all the scholars in the world, the new anti-communist system was strengthened, and Korea was prepared as a new global starting point and a ground for leaping into a new world. Thank you for the gift of heaven that made it possible. Now that you know that the fate of the world depends on the movement of the Unification Church, please bless the way you go. I earnestly pray that God will grant you permission to set the conditions so that you can enjoy the victorious today while reversing history and relieving the pain you have harbored for 6,000 years.
\n\nHow long have you been walking the path of suffering as you stretched out your hands for the work of providence after the Fall to the Unification Church through Judaism and Christianity? You have come to pay a lot of indemnity. Thousands of people who follow the will of heaven and do not even know them well have given their lives, leaving a blooming history. Today, the year of 1984, when all the merits of blood have come to fruition and we can provide world-historical liberation centering on the Unification Church, we have reached a turning point.
\n\nWe know that the day will come when those who have been trampled on will set up their own posture and look up to the sky, and those who were pursued will set an example for themselves and praise the sky. Until now, the group of unification has been a group that is being pursued both in the historical era and in this era. Until now, we have been chased by countless nations, peoples, families, and individuals, but now the sunset road has passed and the bright sunlight of the morning has risen centered on the Unification Church. I earnestly hope and wish that you will allow this year to be a year of sunshine.
\n\nI earnestly pray that the chased ones will come in, fasten their collars, give thanks for the time, and allow the time to come when they can give thanks to the Father. At such a point in time, there is a son who is in the position of a sacrifice, so I earnestly hope and wish that you will use him as an opportunity to achieve victory in the kingdom of heaven as a sacrifice of livestock.
\n\nSo I earnestly hope and desire that the Father\'s work through the omnipotent power will come down from heaven to the earth so that all religions can become one and all nations can become one and unite in the realm of heart centered on one God. Now is the time to be strong and courageous on behalf of the country centering on the Unification Church, and now is the last time to make a decision and draw a line of justice. I earnestly hope and wish that you will allow us to become a group of unification that can move forward on a direct path toward welfare.
\n\nFather, bless all of this year anew so that understanding may be a year of victory. Please allow 1984 to be a year of celebration before the Father, with a whole new beginning from the fight against satan centered on legal matters. And this year marks the 30th anniversary of the founding of the association. As the victorious nations start with the number 30 as the center, I pray that you will bless me so that the same period as the three-year public life course in the age of Jesus can be accomplished.
\n\nPlease allow me to make a uniform resolution of my heart over all the children who bow their heads as they gather here to welcome the New Year. For the establishment of a new world, I earnestly ask and ask that you allow this time to be a time when each of us who can now pledge to go on a campaign as a soldier in the kingdom of heaven can strengthen their inner and outer resolve. Please allow this year to be a year in which all the sad facts and incomplete facts of the past year can now be brought before you as a result of victory. I earnestly ask and hope that this year will draw a decisive and epoch-making line and lead understanding into the year of victory so that it may become a turning point in heaven and a turning point in the world and the universe. I prayed all the words in the name of True Parents.
\nAju.
\n(1984.1.1, p. 1469)
    </string>

</resources>