<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="pr_zelaniya_1t">
Father!
\nSince many members are thirsting for life and have gathered here before this altar, please allow them to represent your glory; and representing the altar of joy please let them know your deliberations and dilemmas; and please allow them to be able to experience your heart. We know that you are in a position where you cannot help but believe in these insignificant beings as you relate to them, and we know that you are in a position where you cannot help but carry out your works through them.
\n\nEven though we know that up until today heaven has been in a position where it must believe us, believe in and establish us, we ask you, Father, to please bear with our faults of the past which made you unable to believe in us.
\n\nWe humans beings have not been able to fulfill our responsibility to become people you can trust, so Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will bear with us at this time. Please allow us to become those who believe you and trust you, and can give up our lives for you, and can honestly offer our daily lives to you. My beloved father, we earnestly hope and desire that you can take us as sacrifices proper for you to accept. Oh, Father! Since you have called us who are so unworthy from among so many people, please accept us and embrace us with your compassionate love.
\n\nWe offer our minds and bodies to you, so please allow us to experience your anxious mind, and our beloved Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become children who are able to accept and carry out your desire. Your heartbreaking situation formed throughout six thousand years has continued until today, and when we consider your history of lamentation which has continued until today, and consider that today, we ourselves are the very source of your lamentations, we ask you to please bear with us.
\n\nPlease make us into the realizations of the life and the idea you desired, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will make us into roots of life which can give you joy. We have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMay 23, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_2t">
Oh, Father of love!
\nOh, Father of compassion! By ourselves alone, with just our strength, we cannot possibly separate goodness and evil and raise goodness up to be goodness. Therefore, please reveal the power of goodness which heaven has sheltered and the power of love which heaven has hidden, and please work through the power of resurrection.
\n\nPlease allow us to be able to reveal a power capable of being good even in our unworthy position. And our beloved Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to be able to have the glory of resurrection, and to be able to bow before you, having given our minds and bodies fully for you and to be able to reveal glory having spent our minds and bodies completely.
\n\nFather! Please purify our minds, and please work with your purifying touch in the soul of each one here. Please reveal what is in the mind and body of each one, Father, and purify each thing. Since it will not do unless all the improper elements are divided out and cast away, oh, Father, please personally become the master of separation and the master of our hearts.
\n\nI earnestly hope and desire, my Father, that you will allow us to be able to separate good and evil and then do away with evil, and to be able offer ourselves through one center before the majesty of our father as living sacrifices of goodness alone.
\n\nOh, Father! Please allow us to recognize the unworthiness of ourselves in front of your manifested external form, and to discover that we ourselves are in the realm of death, having received the power of the sins of the past. In front of you, Father, in front of the altar of the glory of goodness, please let us be able to reveal ourselves and please eliminate any improper habits from the past and any concepts that keep us from believing you.
\n\nPlease allow us to receive a new stimulation of goodness and to feel anew the value of your internal nature and to feel an impact in our minds and bodies. We earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will carry out a work of repentance and inspiration. Father! Please accept us and take dominion over us. Please don\'t allow even one person among us to be dominated by Satan.
\n\nAfter going through your almighty works and your works of efforts for recreation, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to cast away the force of today\'s habits. Please eliminate at this time, Father, all the unacceptable, improper elements of sin, and by personally intervening, please act to fill all of us with only the elements of glory that you can take dominion over, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will completely take dominion over us.
\n\nWe humbly pray this in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 11, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_3t">
Father!
\nPlease, you alone protect everything, and you alone take over and take dominion.
\n\nPlease let this become a time of knowing that not even our lives are our own, and not even our knowledge is our own, nor are all our concepts our own. Please allow us to be on the move only if heaven is on the move and to decide something only if heaven decides, as people who have entrusted ourselves only to you.
\n\nPlease let us understand that even if a concept is considered outstanding in the world, it cannot avoid the destiny of heaven. Please let us realize that the ignorance of the world has penetrated this land, and please allow us to understand that the shadow of sin has formed a relationship with the entire world. Beloved Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to be awakened to our unworthiness and to be inspired by the movement of destiny and to feel awe-stricken as we deal with the whole.
\n\nFather! Please command us. Please advise us and tell us what you want. Please reveal the power of resurrection, and allow the power that can push aside the wall of darkness which is blocking us to explode. We earnestly hope for and desire this. Since the spirit is willing but the flesh is weak, please reveal a power that can go beyond this weak body, and please move according to the authority of your touch, and please allow us to be able to truly accept being molded by your touch, by the blessing of recreation which you shower upon us. We earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to become gentle, humble people who can be molded into an external form of glory.
\n\nSince today you have called us though we are worthless people, please allow us to be able to fulfill your desire. Please allow a living altar to appear for the sake of finding a way for this pitiful people to live, this people who are in the midst of distress, who are dying. Please place our individual beings in front of you today Father, and allow us to stand in a position of being able to receive answers to our questions, and please allow us to be capable of receiving and carrying out the mission heavenly destiny asks of us.
\n\nPlease allow us to be able to fight with all evil and separate it out, and please allow us to separate good and evil and to stand in the position of goodness.
\n\nPlease allow us to believe that Satan\'s evil will be liquidated, and things of goodness will remain, and please allow us to become those people who enter on the straight way and live in the midst of your glow.
\n\nWe pray in the name of the lord.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 19, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_4t">
We are praying earnestly to you, Father. First, we know that our minds and bodies must become sacrifices like the gold, frankincense and myrrh given by the wise men from the east.
\n\nWe know that it will not do unless we become sacrifices. Please allow us to offer our minds and bodies. Beloved Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will not allow us to become abominations before the altar.
\n\nThe more that we understand what you have chosen as your purpose of goodness and righteousness, and the more we think about your having once again sought out our unworthy selves, we cannot help but be contrite about our insufficiency in relation to you. We have let go of all our rituals, concepts and insistence on ideology, and since we have bowed down before you, Father, please help us.
\n\nFather! Please take responsibility for everything. Please receive our minds and bodies completely and take dominion over them, and please allow us to become people who are able to embrace the history of six thousand years and comfort your anguished heart. Beloved Father, we earnestly hope and desire that we will be able to unite, and as a unified sacrifice be able to bow before you in joy together with the many saints, and that you, the living God, will take dominion over the entirety of our minds and bodies.
\n\nFather! Please take pity on this people. We know that you have toiled through the long course of history in order to be able to love this people. We know that when you chose us, in order to reveal your will you had toiled in ways known to none.
\n\nWe know that the enmity of this people has penetrated into heaven, and we know that the enmity of all humankind on the earth has also penetrated heaven. Since we know that heaven is lamenting because there is no one to become a sacrifice representing the anguish of heaven and earth, please allow us to become sons and daughters who entreat you to resolve in your stead the enmity penetrating the entire universe today. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who will come forward and fight Satan in your stead.
\n\nPlease allow us to be able to sing your blessings unified around your one will by bringing our minds and bodies into harmony. And we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to be able to bow before you in gratitude for your blessing of liberation.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 12, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_5t">
Beloved Father!
\nOn this lonely course of restoration which cannot help but be trod whether one wants to or not, who is there who will shoulder again the burden of the destiny caused by the fall?
\n\nThrough the fall of our human ancestors, you came to embrace grief early, Father. And enmity remained in the minds and bodies of humankind. And we know that through the sinful history of the unfaithfulness of the Jewish people, this enmity came to affect the entire world. At this time when heaven and earth are permeated with complaints over this enmity, we earnestly hope and desire that you will open before us the path for us to go.
\n\nIn order to go on the path you will lead us, first we must find a place where our lives can be at rest. After that, our minds and bodies must become your place to find peace, and then we know that your love for which we long must dwell in our minds and bodies.
\n\nOh, Father of compassion, Father of love, benevolent Father, oh my Father who has worked so hard to reveal your will, please reside in the midst of us! Since we have come before your knees, ashamed, Father, with our defiled minds and bodies just as they are, please bear with us.
\n\nIf you do not bear with us, if you do not become our standard for going forth, then there is no one more pitiful than us. Oh, Father! Because you have been our eternal ideal, our eternal hope, and our eternal life, and you know the situation we are facing today and the entire will we are hoping for, it will not do unless you appear to us and take dominion personally.
\n\nFirst, please allow us to become people with elements of the original nature and essence which can receive your dominion, and please allow our minds and bodies to be able to be captured by your words of bidding and your work of construction. And then, in front of your glory, please allow to be revealed your direct works of power which will make us unable not to surrender even if we don\'t want to.
\n\nAnd we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will take dominion over all our minds and bodies and that you will remove from us the roots of sin which you cannot endure. Since the waves of death are trying to sweep us away, please block all those things. And if personal enmities have permeated us, please remove them.
\n\nAre there any minds, or wills, or thoughts, or insistence on ideologies left that are centered on ourselves? Oh Father, please appear as the reality of power and please only you take dominion and assert yourself, and mold all our minds so that we may be able to resemble your external form.
\n\nWe earnestly ask you to allow this, and we have prayed these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 3, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_6t">
Father!
\nWe know that at this time it will not do unless our minds and bodies resemble you completely. So please embrace us to your eternal bosom and in order to realize your will, please let us inherit your heart which has loved billions of people. And please allow us to realize that this is the time when we must appear with hearts like yours.
\n\nThis land is the land where you toiled and shed blood, and because we know that this land is the land where humankind went the difficult path of the cross, the land where the people of the world went the course of Golgotha, Father, please lead us to come to realize by ourselves what kind of situation we are facing today.
\n\nIf we are going to acknowledge that we are following the footsteps of Jesus thirty-year life of suffering, then please lead us to clearly understand what kind of environment we are living in and what we must hope for and desire.
\n\nAt this time when the remaining battle of the cross has come right before our eyes, as individuals we know that we must have hearts that are aware that they can push aside all these sufferings and enmities, so, Heaven, please have pity on us at this time.
\n\nPlease lead us to feel our unworthiness, and guide us to feel our inadequacy by ourselves, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow this time to become a time when we can shed tears of anguish in front of you, Father, lamenting our own incompleteness.
\n\nAsking you to take dominion over all things, we have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 10, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_7t">
Oh Father of compassion! We earnestly hope and desire that you will bear with our situation of not being able to think of the authority, honor or situation of our Father who has such an aching heart, but rather we are living by receiving the power of your compassion.
\n\nSince we, who are here on this dark earth of death, know that without grace and the power of life, we would never be able to offer the glory of victory to you, oh Father, please allow us your promised grace. We earnestly hope and desire that as you turn out the providence, you will reveal your entire will and that you will reveal it to us.
\n\nInadequate as we are, how dare we show ourselves before you? How could we raise our heads before heaven? Even if we died a hundred million times, we are beings who deserve it. We are held prisoner by the chains of sin, and we are people who deserve to go through the suffering of the judgment.
\n\nTherefore, we hope for your merciful love and hope for your grace, and since we have prostrated ourselves before you with minds that report truthfully on their own, we have laid out before you everything that we have. Please allow us to do away with anything that is not proper, and to maintain the mentality you grant us, and we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will guide us to be able to appeal to heaven for your mighty grace.
\n\nFather! Please take pity on us. In order to find and go this way which others deny, we remember times that filled our minds with sorrow, and we know that there were times filled with worries and trials; accordingly, Father, even if this is a position that others deny, may the grace of your recognition alone pour down on us.
\n\nBeloved Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you alone will embrace us, that you alone will comfort us, and that you alone will counsel us. Among ignorant humankind if there is a person who can understand the anguish of heaven, oh Father, even if he were struck with the distress of anguish a hundred million times, we know that he would be victorious without fail.
\n\nPlease let us be sons and daughters who experience your anguish through our minds and bodies, and please let us experience the concern your heart felt when dealing with the earth, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will establish us as sons and daughters who can fulfill our duties.
\n\nFather! Please do not let us remain, in our ignorance, in a position that can lead to ruin. Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will give us the grace of being able to wait impatiently for your love and compassion alone and being able to eliminate the stronghold of evil by exploding it ourselves. We earnestly ask that you will allow our minds and bodies to be captured by the grace of your love and the will you have bid us.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in die name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nApril 14, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_8t">
Oh Father!
\nPlease don\'t leave us only to ourselves. We know that this world is an environment of failure where humankind has walked a historical course. We know that faith alone is not enough, nor are we alone enough. We hope that you will let us have a universal ideology and truth which will allow us to find the origin of our lives and to transcend ourselves.
\n\nAnd at the same time that we have truth, we know that we must establish a standard where heaven can be present with us. Please guide us to be able to go forth from the position of being able to call you "Father," Father, from a position of knowing that completely through a course of absolute faith.
\n\nJesus told us to seek him through the relationship of the bride and bridegroom. Internally, it is the heart that can understand circumstances, and if it is the word that allows circumstances to be understood internally, then please let us understand the word; and through that word, please let us know truth and heart. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to form a relationship, Father, which through a heartistic ideology allows us to know even your heart.
\n\nFather! Today please do not allow us to remain in our terribly narrow circumstances. Please don\'t allow us to become foolish and lose the totality of our value by leaning towards small works. Please allow us to see your greater heavenly nature while we adore your greater grace.
\n\nThat nature has not yet appeared in any form on this earth. And if heaven is hoping to reveal that nature through us, please allow us to move and go forth before you with a bit greater standard of faith and a proper mentality and feeling. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will guide us to be able to fulfill that responsibility.
\n\nFather! Please pour out the final grace that you wish to allow at this time. Through sacrificial lives, as the sons and daughters of our father of glory, please let us receive our eternal father\'s entire ideology of faith as the ideology for our daily lives today. We earnestly ask you to guide us to become victorious people who are able to be proud in front of all people of having accomplished that.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nSeptember 8, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_9t">
Please, may your deep internal nature of love be present in our minds and bodies. Since we have been embraced in your bosom, Father of love, please pour out upon your sons and daughters the joy of love which is hidden in the fullness of your life.
\n\nIf it seems we are not able to experience your preciousness and your heart, Father, we know that we will not be able to erase all our relationships of sin which are not proper. Oh Father of compassion, now in this one moment please allow us to be submerged in your love alone, Father, and please allow us to give our full devotion to your providence.
\n\nMy Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become loving sons and daughters who adapt ourselves to your having dominion, and whose minds can experience the original will and can feel the original heart, and who can more than fulfill our entire responsibility which has been established on the earth.
\n\nWhen we walked along rugged paths until today, when our hearts were sorrowful, we know that you were sorrowful before we were, and even when we were lamenting on our own in the pits of despair, we know that in our stead you were reflecting on all our sins and you were fighting in our stead in the instances of Satan\'s accusations.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire beloved Father, that you will allow us to feel in our minds and bodies that even if we offer our entire mind and body as a sacrifice to you at this time, Father, there is no way we can repay the grace of our Father who has worked so hard until now.
\n\nOh Father! From among many people, you have called and raised up our unworthy selves. How dare we present ourselves in front of you who have called and raised up this people, from among the many peoples. We have nothing to be proud of. Now what we want is to become people who are able to feel anguish together with you when you feel anguish, and who can feel joy when you feel joy, and whose minds and bodies explode for the will when you desire it.
\n\nFather, please protect us. May you alone be our center, May you alone be our Lord. Even though we have nothing to be proud of on the earth, and the place we are standing is a lonely place, since we know that the path we are on is rough, Father, please accept as and take dominion.
\n\nEven if we collapse in the battle of the Last Days, please be comforted through the sound of our voice calling, "Father."
\n\nSince we are your sons and daughters who have received the counsel of your love, and have determined and pledged to go out and fight again,
\n\nFather, please do not turn our minds and bodies over to Satan.
\n\nPlease embrace us in your realm of love, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will hold and lead us to the end, Father, so that through us you will be able to realize the garden you desire and bring into being the day when all people can rejoice. We are earnestly hoping that you will allow us to remain as centers who can be proud in relation to your will, and who can become like light in relation to your will when we offer everything we have now.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nSeptember 22, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_10t">
If it were not for you, Father, we could not be comforted. And we know that you cannot allow us your glory. By any chance are our minds moved by sin and sometimes asserting ourselves? We know the historical truth that acting centered on oneself became an act that betrayed the moral laws of heaven.
\n\nAccordingly, we lay everything out before you and earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to receive the grace of sanctification. And then please allow our mind to manifest itself as your mind and our body to manifest itself as your body. And please let the desire you have take the place of our desire, and today please allow our fighting minds to be together with your mind which is fighting for the will you desire. And we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will give us the blessing of being able to serve your one will alone with an indomitable spirit.
\n\nUntil now the lives we have lived have been worldly, and we know we have not been able to come out front the midst of the falseness of sin. Now please allow us to find absolute value which transcends time and space, and through one center please allow us to offer everything we have to the will through which you seek to reveal that value.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to establish a reciprocal standard where our minds can be harmonized in front of that will and that we will be able to have the joy of being able to sing in the midst of heaven\'s glory.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 20, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_11t">
We know that because humankind is living buried in sin, it is easy for us to consider everything centered on ourselves, and it is easy for us to establish wills which are not the Will and to follow them as if they were the Will. Oh, Father, please make us completely realize that we are like that.
\n\nThen please allow us to establish complete centers for ourselves and to go forward on the path of your eternal life. And we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who can fight with Satan and go forward rejecting everything for the sake of the Will you alone desire.
\n\nWe still do not know where the standard is that can guide ignorant humankind. We know that there have been many times we have worried about ourselves and prayed. Oh, Father, please make us realize how unworthy we are.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will guide us to be able to go forward to the final point of victory following the laws of the principle. We know that at this time, too, Satan is confusing us through intrigues and slander in order to block the blessings you want to give us.
\n\nOh, Father, please lead us to be those who can push aside all those things and fight with Satan and go forward. And furthermore, we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who are able to form an intimate relationship with you within the realm of the providence and go forward.
\n\nFurthermore, since we have to face the last days, please allow us to have a new sense of discrimination which can distinguish all things. Please allow us to realize that everything in the environment centered around ourselves is something to test us. And please do not allow those things to become satanic elements. We earnestly request and desire, Father, that you will guide us and protect us so that we will not be unworthy to reveal your glory by ourselves treading upon and going over those things.
\n\nIn order to find and establish the day of victory that can reveal your glory, Father, at this time please allow us to be able to have in our minds and bodies the power and strength that can face Satan and fight with new resolution and determination. We earnestly hope and desire that your infinite love and care will be revealed to all the people of the earth and to this country and this people. We have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 11, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_12t">
We know that if your mind and Adam\'s mind had become one, and your will and Adam\'s will had become one, today\'s anguished history with the two worlds fighting would not have happened.
\n\nToday your anguished and sorrowful mind is in our minds. Our original minds recognize this, and only the fallen nature, which is centered on itself, is denying that this is true. Since we know that we are always facing this kind of battle between our original minds and evil minds, please allow us to control our own minds ourselves and become one with your mind, Father. Since the time is coming near for the struggle of having to control our own wills and become one with your will, oh Father, please bear with us if we have a mind that cannot become one with you. Please allow us to make effort to forget everything and to become one with your will and mind alone.
\n\nWe know that a mind that is one with your mind could not be exchanged for hundreds of millions of dollars. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will lead us to be able to fight and go forth, and hold on and go forth to attain that one thing, even if we have to sacrifice everything.
\n\nFather! This time now is a very difficult time, and Satan is blocking our minds which want to become one. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to establish a new condition of sacrificing ourselves for others for the sake of establishing your will.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to be equal to the providential history which can broaden the glory of your will and that we will be able to fight while looking up towards your will. We earnestly hope and desire that you will please allow us to realize our desire for our minds and wills to appear as one before your altar as another condition for a relationship with you and as a condition to subjugate Satan.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nNovember, 10, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_13t">
This time now is like the time when the Israelite people were in confusion 2,000 years ago, the time when the Messiah had to come. We are now facing such a time, and we know that we are facing a time when it will be difficult to discriminate between what is true and what is false.
\n\nUntil now there have been many teachers who worked hard in the course of past history, and we have followed many leaders, but today we have lost the center of our minds on which we should depend. We know that you know that today humankind is facing confused living circumstances. Therefore, Father, please control our lives, please control our minds, and please control our ideas so that we may have a joyful time when we can live depending on our natural disposition.
\n\nToday as we live in such a confusing world, please allow our minds and bodies to spread this idea. Please let our bodies witness to it through our daily lives, and please allow us to be grateful in our minds. And we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to be able to receive the blessing of being your sons and daughters who have fulfilled the mission of restoration, and be complimented as the sons and daughters you desired. Father! Please supervise our minds.
\n\nMore than anyone else, our minds know better the way we must go. Since our minds desire to go along the original true path, Father, please grant to us the truth and the religion that are able to realize our mind\'s desire, and please guide us to be able to accomplish the will of the providence of salvation. Since the entire religious world is divided into many denominations, and is in confusion, Father, please take pity on it.
\n\nWe know that the problem here is not which religious body, or which group, or which denomination. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to understand that the main point of truth and the entirety of truth is having an internal heart that you are able to recognize and going forth with an earnest heart that can experience your mind. Now even if we run into adversity, the time is near when your will must be realized. Therefore, please allow us to go through the adversity and to have minds and bodies that can see your glory. And we earnestly hope and desire that you will guide us to become your sons and daughters who even alone win over adversity and while worrying about your heart, unknown to others, raise up an altar, and offer everything in order to resemble your mind and in order to experience your heart.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMay 18, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_14t">
Father!
\nWe know well that without even knowing the direction they must go, many people have struggled along the terribly anguished course of history in order to find you.
\n\nYou appear to exist, and then seem not to exist. You seem to be living together with history, and yet, Father, we have not been able to have a clear understanding that you really exist. You seem to be together with our minds, but with deeply sorrowful minds, we are looking at you as our father who cannot establish regulations like a real being. We know well that you created the entire universe through an idea of goodness, and you gave humankind a true conscience, and you gave us the amazing blessing of being able to experience that idea of goodness through the faculties of intellect, emotion and will.
\n\nAnd we also know well that the fact cannot be denied that the nature of your existence comes to be felt within the time limits of a certain age. Each time we long for your internal nature which comes to our minds, we cannot help but be captured by an anguish we ourselves don\'t understand. We can only lament over our wretched appearance. We know that you have led us into this situation, as a historical, heartistic action to lead us to eternal life.
\n\nWe want to know you, Father, who behind die scenes in history sought us through your heart and mind in order to arrange history into one realistic ideology. We are eagerly looking forward to establishing your mind as the ideology for our lives and our daily lives. But because we do not clearly know the value of your existence, we do not know the value of our daily lives, and without knowing the value of our lives we are faced with the wretched situation of having to struggle today and tomorrow. Therefore, please take pity on each of us who are wandering on the brink of death.
\n\nNow, Father, we know that the time has come that it will not do unless you stretch out your hand of love. That wave of love will have to reach the situation around us and even into our hearts. We know that this is the time when we must restore the authority of your heart, the leading authority you alone have. We know that we will reach the time when we must fight centered on mind, so please allow us to become people who have tolerance and can open our closed minds.
\n\nThe time has come when we must become sons and daughters who are ready to bend our bodies and bow before you. Therefore, we earnestly hope that you will allow us to become people who see your outstretched hand manifest before us and that you will allow us to be able to hear the voice of our father who is knocking at the door of our minds.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 18, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_15t">
Oh Father!
\nPlease take pity on us. Without your grace we are pitiful people who can do nothing but die. Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will not cast us aside and leave us, but will embrace us in your bosom of mighty love.
\n\nUntil now your sons and daughters who have been following have not thought this path of struggle was difficult; but if it were not for your love, we could only have wandered, so please take pity on us. And please embrace us in your mighty love and please let us be able to experience the grace of glory which you permit to us.
\n\nWe know that everything centered on humankind has an end, but every act centered on you continues forever, Father. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will remove everything centered on humankind and allow only things centered on you alone to appear out of the gardens of our hearts.
\n\nThe more our earnest minds search for you, Father, and the more we long for your internal nature and as we desire more to go closer to your mind, there are many times when we forget the fact that your great love is here among us without our knowing it.
\n\nPlease do not allow us to forget the fact that you are always together with us, to say nothing of when we are busy or in a hurry.
\n\nAnd we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will not allow us to forget the fact that you are always living together with us.
\n\nFather! Please look upon us with compassion. Please take responsibility for our lives and take responsibility for our hope. If you would grant your hope to us, please grant us the strength to be able to fight together with you until we make that garden of hope our own. And we hope and desire, beloved Father, that you would protect us so that we do not become exhausted in the battle with the enemy.
\n\nSince our hands and feet have been wounded while we made our way through the world of death, at this time we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will join hands with us and embrace us. Because we know that if you say you do not know us there would be no one more wretched than we are, Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will please hold and comfort us.
\n\nIf it were not your command, we would not have been able to give up even our lives; but we have followed the command you have given and gone forth because it is called a true path. "Therefore, Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will not cast us away but rather embrace us at this time. Father!
\n\nPlease look upon us with compassion. Please allow us to feel to our very bones that if it is not you, nothing will be accomplished, and if it is not your will, it will not be accomplished, and if it is not your work, it will not be accomplished.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to keep in our lives the work that you left, the will that you left, and the hope that you left, and that you will allow us to fight to the end, and to appear as your high-spirited sons and daughters.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 22, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_16t">
Greeting this holy day we come before your being, Father, with bowed heads. Oh father of love, father of compassion, father of magnanimity, please bear with us.
\n\nOur minds want to resemble your mind, and our bodies want to resemble your external form. We are not able to accomplish that because we don\'t know how. Therefore, please inform us through our minds and give us experience through our bodies. We earnestly hope to be able to bow before you, Father, as those who have taken the example of your internal nature.
\n\nIf it seems there are sons and daughters who are not proper before your will, please seek them out personally and instruct them. Our ears are dim, and our eyes are dim. We do not know how to hear your words, and we do not know how to look upon you. Please let us sense in our minds and bodies that having to make us hear and having to make us see is more sorrowful for you than for us, more heartbreaking for you than for us, and more frustrating for you than for us.
\n\nYou have beckoned to us hundreds of millions of times, but we did not know how to respond, and you called out to us tens of thousands of times, but we did not know how to hear you. Then how could we not be ashamed to stand before you? Even so, we hear your voice calling us to come, and even so we know that you are beckoning and calling to us, and we fall down on our knees. We are the pitiful people among the pitiful. We believe that you know that we are those who more than anyone else have no place to depend on. "Therefore, even though we appear crude, you will have to seek us out and hold us, reaching out with love.
\n\nOur eyes are dim and our bodies wounded, and even though we are in a position of not being able to know the essence of life, Father, please embrace us personally with love. We earnestly hope and desire that you will stop our tired footsteps, turn our minds from dejection to joy, and comfort us.
\n\nEven as sorrow is handed down, we know it is because this is a fallen world that you are caused to feel sorrow. Satan is blocking our path, and because you know that he is sweeping away the world through the power of death, you did not leave the responsibility up to us, but have taken on the responsibility alone and have gone forward facing and fighting the enemy, Father.
\n\nThe more our minds revere you as that kind of father, the more your mind will want to forgive us and forgive our faults. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that through that heart, you will once again seek us out.
\n\nWe regret having become sinners, and we weep. Our hearts are indignant hearts and our tears are flowing, and when with earnest hearts our minds repent, we realize that you have borne with us for 6,000 years, Father, and today at this time also you seek to relate to us with a heart of compassion.
\n\nPlease knock on the doors of our hearts as we weep. Please remove the thoughts and assertions of all the ideologies that have been stained by sin until now. And please let us sense your life in our minds and bodies. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow this to be a time when we can experience heaven\'s heart of painstaking circumstances, heaven\'s heart of love, and heaven\'s grace of love which we have not been able to feel, and we can form the kind of relationship where you can call us your sons and daughters.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nApril 19, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_17t">
Father!
\nWe have realized that when we are trying to think of a new work, we are not able to even think about it in the places where we have been doing things until now. We have realized that until we stop the flow of history and take a moment when we can think, we cannot awaken ourselves even though we want to.
\n\nWe know that we cannot be aroused from this sleeping appearance without receiving new stimulation. Therefore, Father, please continuously shock us anew so that we may be able to put aside the historical relationships we have. We know that we will not be able to be awakened if we do not have stimulated minds; therefore, please allow us to become beings who find such minds and know how to respect them.
\n\nIn each age you sent a responsible person who could awaken us, Father. You looked upon fallen humankind, and since you held on with your sorrowful heart and let them live and go, Noah lived and went that way, and Moses, too, and Jesus also did that.
\n\nOh Father! Please give us the shock of a new feeling at the bottom of our hearts. Please let us go beyond ourselves and experience your sorrow, and please give us minds that can be concerned for the people who are being swept into the world of death. If there is a person with this kind of mind, he is a person who can obtain the liberation of the people.
\n\nAnd furthermore, if there is a person who has a mind that is clinging to the world and worrying about it, he is a person who will obtain the grace of worldwide liberation. And furthermore, if there is a person who knows how to be worried about cosmic liberation, he will not be ruined together with history. We know that he is a person who will leave a new history to the world.
\n\nTherefore, today please do not let us become people who reveal our feelings and cling to ourselves and cry. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become people who represent your earnest heart as you look at us, Father, and please let us go towards the good for which the whole is hoping.
\n\nPlease let us feel in your stead the mind that was anxious that we might not follow and that humankind might fall. Please let us follow your example and let us know how to look at the people and look at the world, worried that those who are following might fall, and worried that those who have fallen might collapse and die.
\n\nIf there were sons and daughters who could look at you and say, "Father: I am here, and I have taken responsibility for your heart, so please rest," we know that kind of scene would mean that history is going in a new direction. Please let us become those people who know how to go forward having made all sorts of preparations to be able to begin in a new direction, and please let those of us who should begin in that direction, who must awaken make a new decision and determination and pledge in our minds according to the appearance of the historical screams of misfortune. We earnestly ask you to let us become those who know how to be awake as heaven is awake, and sorrowful or joyful together with the moral laws of heaven and with history.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nApril 19, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_18t">
Father of compassion! Father of love!
\nIf you just leave these pitiful people as they are, they will never be able to get out from under the shadow of death. What is there for those of us in this situation to be proud about and how can we come before you saying we are right? What do we possess that we could come before you defending ourselves?
\n\nWe have nothing. The only thing we have is our inadequacy, and the only thing we feel is our awe-stricken mind. Therefore, please have compassion, Father, for these people of death who are hoping for your compassion, your benevolence and your mercy. All of us are looking towards heaven, eagerly waiting for your hand to reach out to us. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will have compassion for us.
\n\nThe time of the providence is hastening the Last Days, and the waves of death have swept around us and without any exception seek to swallow us. We know that you know we are faced with a chaotic environment, and your heart which worries about us remains on this earth, as do the footprints of your hard work. We know that as you look at all this, your mind is inexpressibly anxious; therefore, Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will lead us and have compassion for us at this time.
\n\nIf we have lonely hearts, let us empty them out at this time and we must change them and take on your heart. If we are sorrowful and have inexpressibly frustrated hearts, we are in the pitiful situation of having to exchange them for your heart of joy and life.
\n\nOh Father who knows this, in spite of our being those who should take responsibility in your stead and relieve you of your difficult position, you are taking care of our difficult situation. And we earnestly hope and pray, Father, that you will bear with the fact that we are within the fallen realm and have to receive strength from you again.
\n\nFather! Please allow our hearts to be able to communicate with each other. We, who have been languishing in the realm of death and who had no destined relationship and were not acquainted, have gathered together referring to each other as the members of one family. Since we have gathered together adoring the idea of your heavenly providence, Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will have compassion and come to us.
\n\nCould anyone have confidence in front of you, Father? Since you have said that you have confidence, we have hoped to have confidence, too, and since you have said that you feel this wav, we too hope to feel that. If this is false, Father, please bear with us, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will personally take dominion.
\n\nEven when coping with a sad situation relating with humankind, your sons and daughters could not have a situation where they could speak out their minds, and even when faced with a difficult situation, they had no family members with whom they could open their hearts. We earnestly hope and desire that you will take pity on them.
\n\nWe know that in the world connected to your heart, we move transcending the distances of time and space. Therefore, at this time also, connected to that same heart, if the mind of heaven moves please let our minds be moved as well. Please inspire us by reaching out with your grace for all, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will connect us to your heart again.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 7, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_19t">
Before we report anything to you, Father, you already know our hearts. Please allow us to feel that this is a time when heaven is observing everything about us.
\n\nOh Father! You have gone through a historical course of such toil. Today please appear right in front of us and groom us through new words. Please relate to us with a new heart. We intend to sweep away every unfaithful aspect, and with childlike minds offer everything we have before you, our Father, whom we respect.
\n\nWe lay down before you, Father, all the rituals, ideologies and concepts of the world, and we ask that you will allow us to have meek, humble minds like those of children. May we have humble minds which are able to be molded as you would mold us, and since we seek to offer ourselves before you, please accept us. May the triune God act.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and pray that you will allow this place where we are bowing to you with rejoicing hearts, guarded by heavenly forces and angels, to become an altar of wondrous blessing which can lead our whole lives to victory.
\n\nWe have left everything up to you. Please let us open our hearts and all the ideologies we have before you. We hope that in that way you will allow us to be able to change everything we have into your things.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 5, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_20t">
Father!
\nWe see that although the many people living on the earth are at the point of death, the present state of affairs is that they are pushing themselves forward and they are busy bragging before the universe.
\n\nIn this kind of world, can one dare to be proud of oneself? Can one assess one\'s own value highly? When we recall our hearts and weigh them in silence, we will not be able to deny that we are faced with a false situation.
\n\nFather! Today what are our minds imagining, and what are we seeking to rise up to? The time has come that we must realize that now our minds are not able to be ours and our bodies are not able to be ours either. The time has come that we must recognize that we are in a miserable situation where we cannot put ourselves forward and be proud of ourselves.
\n\nWe cannot make the final decision about the value of our minds and bodies. Please allow us to feel how miserable we are who cannot lead even our own selves to the goal through the course of the situation that has occurred. If we have life, it is not because of us, and if there is an ideology that leads our minds in the direction of goodness, please allow us to feel the fact that it also originates not in ourselves but in something else.
\n\nFather! Today please allow us to realize that you are searching for a victorious person who knows how to take mastery over his ego and how to rid himself of the conceit which made him want to put himself forward and raise himself up and which made him intent on establishing and justifying himself. We have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 19, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_21t">
We do not want to believe in the Father of words; rather we want to believe in the Father who has created historical relationships. We are requesting a direct relationship with you today, a father with whom we can form a direct relationship, a father who can speak to us directly.
\n\nToday humankind believes in God as an objective being, but today we are not requesting that God be the kind of object of faith that they are seeking. We desire the God who is the substantial subject of our daily lives. We are longing for the father who can relate to all the realities of our lives and circumstances, and from whom we cannot be separated even if we tried, and who dwells with us in every moment. The hour realizing this kind of relationship on the earth is the hour humankind is desiring and at the same time it is the hour God desires.
\n\nToday we are conceptually thinking about what kind of ideal garden, the garden of hope, which you desire would be, but that is not our actual circumstances. We know the fact that the time has come when we must have the kind of concept of the Kingdom of Heaven that penetrates us beginning with our minds, and which through realization we can feel, and which through emotion we can sing.
\n\nWe know that forming that kind of destined relationship was the purpose of the providence of salvation, the purpose of the history of restoration and the purpose of the salvation of the cross. Therefore, please allow us to be able to call you our real father, and even if we determine ourselves and recognize ourselves as your real sons and daughters, please allow us to be able to sing from a position of not being ashamed, and to rejoice, and to be able to hear you speak. We have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nAugust 30, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_22t">
Father!
\nPlease particularly remember this time. Please give your blessing to many human beings. And among them, please give your blessing to the many religious organizations calling your name. Please especially bless those who are being cast out as they cling to your heart. And please bless those who have gone out casting aside everything in order to be a living sacrifice for heaven, not troubling themselves over blood, sweat and tears. We believe that you will be together with them. We believe that you will fight together with them.
\n\nFather! More than anyone else, more than any other people, more than any other believers, our minds want to live for you, and we want to attend you, and in your care, we want to fight every battle together with you. Among the many peoples, it was this people you called, and among the many believers, we are the sons and daughters you called; therefore, please consider our minds trustworthy, and we dare to ask you to come to us.
\n\nWe have understood your command calling us to come, and we have understood your will to send us out several times, telling us to pioneer this path. We know that you have counseled us when we were discouraged, have told us, "I am here," when we were in sorrow, and you have comforted us.
\n\nWe know that you did so in the past, are doing so in this moment, and will do so tomorrow.
\n\nWe know that we cannot form a relationship with you in a comfortable place, and we cannot meet you on a smooth path. We know that this is because you still are not in a comfortable place, and cannot walk a smooth path.
\n\nOnly if one seeks to take on your sorrow, Father, as ones own sorrow, and seeks to walk your path of suffering in your stead can one relate to you personally. We have learned, realized, and experienced that you can open your heart and speak your mind on the foundation of a natural heart.
\n\nThose who follow your footsteps on the lonely path you are going are lonely people. We know that you do not distinguish day or night to gather those who are in that kind of position because you are that way. Therefore, please personally reach out and protect your sons and daughters who have gathered together for the one will and at this time have the same situation, same heart and same hope, and we earnestly hope that you will move them onto a secure foundation through the same grace.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 6, 1960
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_23t">
Father!
\nBecause we know that you did not cast away fallen humankind, and we know the results of your hard work for 6,000 years in order to reach and reestablish us and we know your heart of compassion, we have come before you with a mind to bow down before you. We know that you have an eager heart which could not help but wander and search for us, a mind that could not just throw us away, and we have come before you today like this calling you "Father." Please bear with us.
\n\nWe are inadequate in view of your heart of longing for eternal sons and daughters with whom your heart can communicate. Please remember that our minds are longing for you alone. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will see and consider compassionately that in our minds our earnest, original hearts want to relate to your internal nature.
\n\nOh, Father! This position where we have to long for the world of your holy original creation has become a position of sorrow. And furthermore, we cannot help but think it is extremely deplorable that we are in a position where we cannot help but report truthfully that we are so inadequate that we cannot appear before you.
\n\nNow, when we consider all the traces in the background of history, we understand that we were substantial beings of sorrow, and pitiful beings who did whatever we pleased in front of you, Father. We cannot help but feel pain in our hearts that we were not able to appear at some point as object partners of glory before your heart, or to become the descendents of our ancestors who could praise your glory, Father, representing the entire universe.
\n\nPlease bear with the sins of our ancestors, and please bear with the pitiful situation of humankind today, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will bear with the fact that people do not know they have the mission to prepare the foundation for the eternal welfare of their descendents.
\n\nYou have worked hard until now, Father. Now through the Principle we have come to know that our father is a sorrowful father, our will is a sorrowful will, our history is a history of suffering unjustly, and our lives are lives invaded by Satan. Thus, we cannot raise our heads before you, Father, when we think that we are still struggling in the midst of an environment filled with grief.
\n\nSatan still has power on this earth; an unrighteous environment remains on the earth, and the dominion of evil is dominating the cosmos. At this time when we are watching this reality which is demanding the sorrow of heaven, please especially have compassion for us who are in the position where we who are seeking heaven, we who are praising your desire and calling your name, have experienced our inadequacy and cannot help but appeal to you, Father.
\n\nIf it were not for your power and your protection, Father, we would not be able to remain here substantially on this evil earth today. We are the inadequate people who would not be able to have anything remain in front of the will of the providence. In view of the fact that we who are like this have come before you, and we are those who know our reality as it is, please augment your heart of compassion one more time and remember us. Please call us to task for our lack of faith, and counsel us to be able to relate to the path of loyalty and filial piety. Please supplement our inadequacies, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will increase our power to be able to come close to completeness.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMay 22, 1963
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_24t">
Oh merciful Father!
\nPlease accomplish that which you desire and will in heaven and on earth. So many people have left your embrace and still continue in their filial impiety. Every day we see them moaning in the valley of death, unable to remove themselves from that environment even today. And when we think about facing this situation which causes us sorrow; please allow us to become aware that in front of you we are ashamed and there is nothing we can say.
\n\nFather! You have carried out the providence until now with the goal of a day of joy when you can embrace all humankind and call each one your child. But today on this earth there are so terribly few children who can relate to your love, and there is no one to inherit your entire providence of restoration and offer loyalty to you. When we think about these kinds of things, we realize that even today your sorrowful course remains before us. Therefore, at this time please allow us to take ourselves to task again and to discover that we are those who must go forth.
\n\nIn this evil, wretched world on this devastated earth, the will of your providence is taking a new direction, and we know that at the same time that it is your hope, Father, to lead us without fail to the world of your will, it is also the hope of all humankind living on this earth.
\n\nWe also know that without finding the way towards a standard where you and all humankind on the earth can become one, we will not be able to bring this entire will and mission to completion. Today, you have raised us up to have us pioneer the path of a new religion in front of this people, and to present a new page of history in the course of the world. We earnestly hope that you will please allow us to become people who know how to feel sorry and bow down in front of your effort and hard work to establish all the world-level indemnity conditions on a horizontal level in order to connect the past, present and future of life.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 17, 1965
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_25t">
Oh Father who created the universe!
\nPlease allow us to realize deeply at this time how earnestly you hoped for the day when you would be able to share your glory with all of creation. You created Adam and Eve, raised them in your embrace, and by having them begin a life of eternal love you sought to establish the welfare of humankind. And we realize once again that you are a father who hoped to find joy through Adam and Eve as they grew. Please let us realize once again at this time that you, who had such an earnest hope, lost Adam and Eve and had to face a day of sorrow.
\n\nFather! On this earth there are many nations and many peoples. They each have had different histories, and their living conditions and the things they hope for are different. When we consider again that this is contrary to your originally determined will, we come to understand that the difference in histories is your grief, and the difference in conditions is your grief, and the difference in hopes is also your grief. When we think of these things, Father, we know that they are the retribution of the fall.
\n\nIt will not do unless history comes from you, and it will not do unless the present comes from you, and it will not do unless the future forms a relationship with your idea, but today humankind is facing the tragic reality of not having one relationship, or one set of conditions for life or one ideological foundation.
\n\nPlease allow us to hear once again in our minds the ghastly screams and moans of all humanity who are living in a chaotic place like this, in this place which has been turned upside down, where each person\'s position contradicts the other\'s. Please allow us to think together with your heart, Father, to feel your heart, and to become aware of the mistakes of the past.
\n\nFather! You need to have sons and daughters weeping tears of sincere repentance and pleading for you to allow humankind to have blessed hope. But the more we feel that we have not done that, the more unable we are to raise our heads before you.
\n\nToday, there are many religions and religious organizations going forward towards one goal, but we know that there are not many bowing down before you humbly and weeping about the sorrowful path that you must go and about the sorrow of the ghastly judgment humankind must receive. The pitiful people who have gathered here today have continuously gone a path of anguish; embracing the command you gave, they have continued fighting until today. Please personally guide their footsteps, and since they are your sons and daughters who have remained in this place today, please remember them.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 2, 1966
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_26t">
We did not know that a historical end was calling to us from afar, and we did not know that you had set us up high and were urging us along the path we have to go. Father! Each time we went in ignorance onto a side path, you guided us back to the path ahead. We feel once again how very much you have toiled, guiding us until this point at the end of history today.
\n\nOh Father! Where do our minds want to dwell? And where do our bodies want to dwell? Since we have come to understand that the place where our minds and bodies should dwell is at the center of your original, deep love, Father, please encourage your children who have not been able to arrive at that point.
\n\nWithout your love, Father, we cannot rest, and without your love, we cannot feel your heart. Therefore, please let the waves of your love flow down into our lacking minds, and bring about in us the blessing of rebirth.
\n\nWe must long for that position until our eyes grow cold, and we must yearn for that position until our minds ache with the yearning. And furthermore, in order to find that position, we will have to go through miserable struggles, and even if we are destroyed and collapse a thousand, ten thousand times, and experience the anguish of the vanquished, we know that it is our duty that we must rise up again and go forward fighting. Therefore, our Father, please personally direct our minds and bodies, and please do not allow us to become the vanquished in this battle.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMay 28, 1967
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_27t">
However difficult the path you have told us to go may be, we pledge that we will not stop our footsteps which are following you. Even if on this path the persecution we receive crosses the path of death, since we have already offered ourselves as living sacrifices, please allow us to just disappear obediently as sacrifices.
\n\nWe know that in the midst of this world of death, you desire to establish a foundation of life which can form a relationship in your embrace. We will absolutely establish that foundation of life. Father! We long for you with an inexhaustible longing. We want to live with you forever and ever. We want to consult with you, and live according to your directions. This is our hope. Since the day humankind fell, we have lived without ever being embraced by your love for a single day.
\n\nWe know that until now humankind has continuously gone though a miserable history of tears, day by day going over peak after peak of sorrow. Please allow us to become true sons and daughters who cling to you, Father, who have sought us with a heart seeking to restore the standard of hope by seeking once again this kind of history, and we earnestly hope for and desire that you allow us to be able to share your joys and sorrows.
\n\nOh Father! Please look at this place with eyes of fire and do not allow any bitter roots of sin or death to remain deep in our hearts. Please look at us with eyes of fire and please allow us at this time today to pull out all the roots of sin and be unified before you. Since we have bowed down humbly before you, please act upon us.
\n\nWe earnestly desire this. Representing the multitudes of peoples, this people must receive love, and for the many tribes we will have to completely fulfill the mission you have given. We must become a movement that can stand in the place of the final glory singing a victory song to you, our Father, and we must become brave people who can remain through the final battle while carrying out the responsibility you have given us. Therefore, please work with us, Father, take dominion over us. give us directions, and lead us.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 31, 1968
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_28t">
Father!
\nWe must become children. We must become children who insist to you that we are hungry when we are hungry. Children thirst to adore their mothers. Children are simple and innocent. The more they are raised, the more they are brought up and gently embraced, the more they grow to follow their parents standard.
\n\nFather! Please repeatedly remember your children who are gathered here. If they who have come from so many diverse situations open their hearts about those situations, we know that you will not be able to help being moved. Therefore, please allow us to open our hearts, and to have hearts that longing for you like hungry babes longing for their mothers milk.
\n\nWho will be the teacher here? These people do not want the words of man. Until now they have heard many words spoken, and they have attended many churches, and they have met many people, but the nectar of life was not among them.
\n\nBecause the milk of life was not there, their minds have run dry. With nothing to depend on in their exhausted state, they are in a miserable position like a wasteland. Therefore, Father, please gather them together. Each one must put aside his own situation, and there must arise a work of intertwined lives wriggling for re-creation centered on relationships of life and words of life that are centered on your situation, Father.
\n\nI have not been able to prepare myself to bring myself before you, Father. But I offer everything I have and am before you, and I must find my "self" which begins with you. I must have the attitude of mind that seeks to begin from you. Since I must possess the true appearance that begins with you, I earnestly hope and desire that you will be with me personally.
\n\nSince they have come with minds that have been grieving for a week, Father, please comfort them. I earnestly ask that you will please apply medicine on their wounds, spreading salve over them and embrace them with love. And then for these lonely, miserable, shabby people, please allow a place in your home where they can change clothes and rest.
\n\nHow much you must look forward to people seeking you on their own with the nourishment of overflowing love. These people are also looking forward to such a position, so we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow it.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 31, 1968
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_29t">
At this time an inadequate group of small numbers has gathered before you. Our minds and bodies have good conditions for harmonizing with the world, but we have bowed down before you as those who cannot help but stand far away from you in our relationship. Therefore, Father, please separate us. We earnestly hope and desire that if our wounds are severe, you will please let your compassion reach those wounds, and when you see that we cannot appear before you as we should, please comfort us.
\n\nPlease allow us to have minds able to feel sorry and lament over the fact that we are imperfect beings who are ashamed before you and have nothing to offer you. Deep in our hearts, please allow minds that adore you to blossom. Please allow us to hear your voice as it called out in the original Garden of Eden, and to feel your holiness which our ancestors could not feel.
\n\nPlease allow us to become your simple and pure children who can penetrate to your heart of longing and love which desires to embrace us in the midst of your mind. We earnestly hope that you will feel the unbreakable blood relationship we have with you and will desire so much to see us that you will not be able to help embracing us and will not be able to help corning to us.
\n\nFather! When we called you "Father," we were not able to do so with a voice that flowed out of a sincere mind which penetrated even our flesh and bones. We have not been able to have a time when we could rush to you and cling to you from a position of oneness with that kind of emotion.
\n\nSince we have not been able to know you clearly in that was please allow us to be able to perceive you clearly. Please allow us to become those who struggle with deeply moved minds to grasp your outstretched hand and the train of your garment and never let go. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to call you "Father" in that kind of position and to become able to cling to you and confide in you there.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJune 9, 1968
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_30t">
Father of Mercy!
\nPlease let this place become a sanctuary where we become one with your mind. Please allow it to become a holy place where only you can take dominion and we can be close to your heart, be moved to tears by your situation, and be in harmony with your hope.
\n\nPlease remove all the humanistic private things. Born as descendants of the fall, we have used masks as we saw fit and have had ideologies on which we insisted. Please eliminate all these conditions which appear before you.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to have humble hearts like children, and that in our minds we will have hearts that endlessly long for and continually adore you like hungry babies long for their mother`s milk, and that our hearts can harmonize like that and be absorbed and penetrate deep into your heart.
\n\nWe know clearly that the appearance we give is miserable and pitiful, like children who have lost their parents. Please let a moving, howling scream explode out of our minds towards our mother and father. In order to kick away this environment and to forget that our bodies have been wounded, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to appear as those able to testify ourselves that we are your sons who have hearts that are able to be moved by our pathetic situation of struggling and longing for our parents.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become your children who long for the kind of relationship where you see us looking like that, and you rush to embrace us calling us, "My son, my daughter," and you can hold our cheek next to yours and embrace us tightly while weeping. We have come to this place not to find some thing of this world; we have conic longing for a relationship preordained by heaven which will allow us to remain together forever with you who are so precious and exalted.
\n\nWe have not come here to put down the roots of some personal feelings and remain here; we have come here to pursue a relationship of eternal roots which cannot be pulled out even if one tries, and a relationship where we cannot be separated from you even if we try.
\n\nSince we have come in order to move when you move, and to become what is decided when you decide, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will please, please, become the roots, and that you will allow us to become the trunks, branches, and leaves. Please allow us to become your children who will revive the world and represent your power, dynamic force and pulse.
\n\nNo matter what anyone says, we know that children who are being embraced by their father and mother are fortunate people. However savage the surrounding environment may be, no matter whether their daily lives are spent on dangerous, high peaks, we know that children who go to sleep in their parents embrace have hearts filled with peace.
\n\nLiving in this evil world, this chaotic world, this world where the waves of death are splashing up against us, we are people who cannot go to you even if we want to, but we have come before you with ardor, longing for, yearning for, adoring you at least for the moment when we can be embraced by you. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will give us directions.
\n\nWe have humbly offered this prayer in the name of our True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 17, 1968
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_31t">
Father!
\nPlease allow us to dearly realize that in our minds and bodies there remains the original root of sin, which we cannot deal with by our own strength alone.
\n\nPlease allow us to realize what kinds of things we have been through from the past until now, and that we have been people like that, and please allow us to ardently feel the need for a stimulating, dynamic force that will let us revolutionize ourselves once again today.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to clearly know that without putting aside the me of today and being able to establish a self who can make a new me for tomorrow, we will not be able to become beings who remain even in the lower levels of this good will and good historical course.
\n\nPlease do not allow us to become pitiful people whose lives just flow along with the flowing waves. And please allow us to understand clearly that we have remaining with us the purpose of goodness which must swim upstream against the current. When we look through the course of history, we know well that the will of heaven is not something that goes forward separate from history; it deals with history and raises history up quickly. From that kind of course alone we know well the fact that you have been working with us in history.
\n\nToday at this time we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to once again think about what kind of position we are in and to stand in a position where we can communicate with you about matters.
\n\nPlease allow us to understand completely that you remain with things of goodness forever and you will absolutely not allow evil to participate. You become partners with goodness, and go out together with goodness, and since you go forth looking towards the one will which can be accomplished together with goodness, even if our bodies are eliminated, please allow us to feel once again at this time before you, Father, that we must become people whose minds at least remain with goodness forever.
\n\nThen we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to have minds that can become one with your will, our eternal Father, and subjugate and take dominion over our bodies according to the directions and commands of our minds, and that our bodies will be able to communicate with our minds. We earnestly hope that you will allow this time to become one we are attending in order to desire once again to be people who are able to do that, and to control ourselves again to be able to do that, and to determine ourselves again to be able to do that.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJune 22, 1969
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_32t">
Father!
\nThis morning a lonely group has gathered before you. We must consider on our own the kind of situation we are in. We need to realize clearly through whom we have come here at this time and in order to form what kind of relationship we have come to this place.
\n\nHowever evil the world may be, and however filthy the world may be, we must examine completely on our own the position we are in, and we must determine our relationship with you, Father, and in the course of our lives establish a relationship with you which cannot be forgotten. We must know that if there is such a person, the relationship that person forms is greater and more precious than anything else in the world.
\n\nOur longing for our Father is soaring up out of our hearts adoring hearts longing for heaven of their own accord; these are the driving forces that can go against the flow of history. Please allow us to know that these shields of victory can trample the waves of death and stand over them. We must become those people of true love who know how to feel how precious the people are who can live as substantial testimonies praising you with their minds and bodies.
\n\nNow we must analyze ourselves in detail, and think about for whom our faces exist.
\n\nWe must think about what our eyes are seeing what our ears are hearing, for which tastes and smells our mouths and noses exist, and for which acts of service our hands and feet exist. Please allow us to completely realize that even though we should have been those whose entire being could become truly one with heaven and long for you, Father, and attend you, Father, and be those who were loyal to you, we are those who must grieve from a position of anguish that we have not had even one moment of our minds communicating with you and love.
\n\nWe, who say we live on this earth, live in a realm of life limited to seventy, eighty years or at most a hundred years, and then we are buried in the earth. No matter how good we might look while on the earth, we must realize that we cannot bring about any results by ourselves, and we must realize how meaningless is preparing a living environment only with accomplishments on the earth.
\n\nWe must clearly know that our birth and life and our four limbs and hundreds of body parts all exist due to you, Father. We must understand how very precious we are when we depend only on heaven, and take responsibility ourselves even when there are difficulties, and with a desperate attitude follow your will, pushing our way through a great diversity of difficulties and seek to relieve your grief.
\n\nWe must become those who know how to think of our relationship with you when we are in sorrow in such a position, and we must become those who are able to be grateful to you when we are happy.
\n\nWe must become true people who desperately weep and proclaim so that all of heaven and earth can be moved that you exist, our living Father, who has been taking on all the difficulties and going forth being driven out again and again in our stead throughout history. And at this moment as well you are not resting, but in order to save us you are searching for the standard of goodness.
\n\nBut each time we feel that no one has been able to experience that position, we want to receive your grace, Father, and we long to be able to live a life of grace within you and win your confidence. Father, we who are like that need a relationship with you, and need to be governed by you. Therefore, please allow only the glory of your life to rise up from the depths of our hearts. We pray in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 2, 1969
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_33t">
We must not think of you as a concept, Father. Please let us understand clearly that we must attend you as a real being, as the absolute subject of all aspects of our life.
\n\nYou have not been living in some distant relative world. You have been in the middle of our hearts and you have surrounded our bodies. Although there is air all around us, just as we don`t know whether it is there or not, we must realize that we didn`t realize that you were embracing our entire lives. When we receive that power which is surrounding us, an infinite power is being mobilized there. And we know that when we absorb that power as an eternal power, it gives us a new impact and a new stimulation.
\n\nWe must become sons and daughters who are able to realize through experience the existence of our father, who always stays near us like that and gives us life and is always filling us. We must come to realize how precious is the person who knows how to discuss his life course with you from such a position and from such a position can grow as your child.
\n\nMany people on the earth hope for heavenly fortune and hope about the rest of their lives, but we know that they are hoping for these things keeping a relative distance from them. But different from them, please allow us to clearly understand that all the authority of life begins from the closest point, from you who are the center of life. In order to do that, please remain close, deep in our hearts, Father, and by taking dominion over our bodies, please become the motive power of our lives. And we must realize the fact that you must become the origin of all our feelings.
\n\nPlease allow us to realize how great and how precious is the value of a child who can attend our father, who is the subject of wide, deep, sublime, precious, infinite value. When we go out to witness to that standard tens of millions, billions of times, please allow us to realize the fact that the inherent authority to be able to absorb all the content of heaven and to take dominion over the cosmos comes into being then.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 23, 1969
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_34t">
Father!
\nThrough looking at the course of history and through our own lives of faith, we have come to clearly understand that heaven is an eternal place. But what determines whether one can go into that heaven is what a person has made an effort to do on his own on earth and the state of his heart.
\n\nAs people who have come to know the will, we worry about ourselves that we might not be able to walk the way we must for the will. We are those who cannot help but live day by day together with heaven and yet cannot help but live together with the earth.
\n\nBut we know well that through our hearts which are like this, you are seeking to appear in our daily lives. In order to do that, we must realize the fact that you are judging the good and evil within us.
\n\nFollowing a lonely path of life like this, those of us who are looking at that and going forward cannot help but admit that we are descendents of the fall who are not able to find any hope without you, Father. For those of us who are like that, only heaven is good, and we know the truth that it must be heaven that becomes our everything.
\n\nPlease allow this time to become a time of reflection and evaluation of how rewarding and how truly human are living together with heaven and having the courage to die together with heaven. In the course of history, those who left behind the name "great person" as a person of goodness, and those who left behind the name "saint" as one individual in the world of men, their names have remained in a holy way because their purpose of life was to live together with all humankind and to live together with you, Father. They did not become exhausted along the path of life. And in order to live together with you and together with all the people of the world, we know that they walked a path of limitless struggles in order to tic the end together with the beginning.
\n\nThe many people who have come and gone throughout the course of history did that, but we, who have the name of being sons and daughters of heaven, who are shouldering the responsibility of the providence of restoration which must be completely resolved in the history of today, we ask you to allow us to know the fact that what we must do is already determined.
\n\nYour having called us in this way is not because we ourselves are fit for the calling, but you have called us as beings of hope through the course of the 6,000 years of pioneering, filled with so much grief since the fall, in order to establish the concept of creation which you were hoping for from before the beginning of history. When we realize that we are such beings, we cannot help but feel again the loneliness and misery of our father with his heart of grief-filled restoration.
\n\nPlease prod us because we have not been able to become our real selves who can straighten ourselves up and call you our father, and let us admit that we have not been able to lay the foundation of holy devotion which allows us to attend our heavenly parents. In spite of the fact that more than offering anything of the world, we ourselves must become complete offerings who are able to offer ourselves as sacrifices to whatever you desire, we cannot express how many times we have forgotten this.
\n\nFather! The external conditions such as physical appearance or any kind of worldly conditions are not the problem. Please allow us to be able to walk the course of our lives with earnest hearts which want to struggle for heaven, and want to witness to heaven and want to live for heaven from deep in our hearts.
\n\nFather! Even if while living for you it may sometimes seem like we are in a dreary, lonesome, lonely, and deserted place, we must realize that when we are assessed by you, we are considered as belonging to you.
\n\nWe earnestly desire that you will allow us to once again determine ourselves to stand by our own volition in the position of knowing that this is the original path we must go, and it is the original desire which humankind should pursue.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 8, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_35t">
Father!
\nIf we are sons who know your devotion, Father, even if we wake up in the middle of the night, we would not be able to help bowing down to you with embarrassed minds which are not able to cover up our shamefulness as sinners.
\n\nAt the morning breakfast table, please let us become people who ask ourselves what we`re going to do after we eat this rice, and at the lunch table please allow us to become those who, in an ashamed manner, feel remorse over the question of what we have left unfinished until now, and at the dinner table, please let us become those who ask ourselves whether we have spent the day well and concluded it without lack.
\n\nPlease allow us to become children who start the day as yours, Father, and who question whether up to this time we have remained as yours, and when we think about how much concern you have for us, Father, with an empty body which cannot leave anything behind of this day which we must spend in a valuable way, please let us think about whether we have not spent the day with a mind of the world, and please let us become your children who know how to go to bed after repenting to you with tears and with regretful hearts.
\n\nWe must live grateful lives. Even at the point of being beaten, even at the point of vomiting blood, we must live grateful lives. Because many ancestors betrayed you at that kind of point, Father, we know that we must fulfill completely the duty of filial piety among filial piety and the duty of loyalty among loyalty to you, Father, who have come with a heart filled with that kind of anguished, historical grief.
\n\nPlease let us understand here that we cannot stand in such a position with resentment and complaints. Please allow us to become those who fear that we might find ourselves to be like that. Please let us understand that although we are pitiful and weak people in the world, there is no one more fearful than such people.
\n\nEven if we are at a point where our bodies are exhausted to the extent that we cannot hold on anymore, we must think that you have longed for us, overcoming and going a path of suffering more severe than this. And when we discover the fact that only by going beyond this suffering will we become sons who can comfort your sorrowful past, we must purify ourselves as those who must go and become sons who offer ourselves completely as sacrifices before you.
\n\nWe have nothing more than living in gratitude. Even if the wife given to one husband is inadequate, because of being able to serve throughout our lives, we must be grateful for having been given that wife. And if our children give me a life of the cross, we will have to be grateful for your having provided us that kind of position. And even if the environment drives us into pits of despair where we cannot control our lives, no matter what condition that sets up, we will become your sons who can leave behind a relationship of gratitude and collapse. We earnestly hope that you will allow us to become your people.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 14, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_36t">
Since humankind are the beings who were born for the sake of your love, we cannot live apart from love. We were born for love, and we should attend you through love, and in front of our father who is the subject, as reciprocal objects we should love each other.
\n\nWhen we think that we should be able to receive love, we earnestly hope and desire that your will allow us to understand that we who have gathered here are your sons and daughters because of that infinite value. A meeting that has no relationship to you is useless. Please let us know that attending every day out of habit cannot be of any help to you.
\n\nIs there any weak person among those who are bowing to our noble Father, to the subject of eternal love, to you who are the source of eternal life? If there is, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow him to have a mind that longs for you as much as he forgets his own self importance, while falling down in front of everyone at the point when he recognizes that you are expressing yourself there.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to understand that we are a group that has come here in order to become children who can cherish the pulse of your life, Father, which is penetrating our minds. And we are screaming out for you to give us a moment of being embraced by you while we sob with earnest hearts, clinging to the edge of your garments and embracing your neck.
\n\nYour love can flow, reverberating deep in our hearts and link together our hearts. Please let that pulse of blood which is flowing at the base of your heart raise up our hearts. Please let all our blood be permeated by the pulse of the original nature of love. Then let us fight with your indignation and together with your courage, please reach out to us with the pulse of your enmity, and please let it become the source of our strength which allows us to go beyond each moment of life, Father. In the midst of the reverberations, let us recover ourselves and form a relationship with you.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nApril 5, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_37t">
Father!
\nThis place must become one that you can recognize as holy and that you can come to without hesitation. We earnestly hope that you will allow this place where your sons and daughters are to become a place where you can surely come freely.
\n\nWe must not become people who are exhausted from crying out without receiving any response, staring into space. We must step on the boundary of sin and go over it. Please let us greet the day of joy where we can call you "Father" and feel the sensation of you reaching out in concern to those of us who are like this. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us the state of being intoxicated by ourselves embracing all of heaven and earth in love with your heart.
\n\nFather! Please allow us a natural situation where we can call you "Father" together with earnest minds which are on fire with hearts of adoration according to our own wills. Together with all things of creation, we would like to be proud before you, Father, with an authority that can praise our value.
\n\nWe know that you created everything for us. We earnestly hope and desire that you will connect your sons and daughters in a place where we can call you "Father" in secret as valuable people. Today we must not just gaze remotely at the patriots of the past who cried out for you.
\n\nPlease let all the content of the past appear as material of the present reality. Then all the circumstances of today will connect the present reality and the future, and please let the actual past testify to today. And we earnestly request and desire that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who can attend you, Father. We earnestly ask you to please take responsibility for everything and protect it in a holy way.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nAugust 9, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_38t">
Father!
\nWe must become your true seeds and grow into true trees and put forth flowers and bear fruit and appear as hundreds of fruits which can be embraced in your bosom. Therefore, please sow us as true seeds greeting a spring day, and let as grow as true trees and allow us to become comforts to you. And furthermore, there in the fragrance of the flowers please realize your desire of having a banquet of joy in the last days, bearing fruit and filling all nations.
\n\nFather! Please let us love you sincerely. We know that our lack of filial piety towards you until now is because we have grown up in an evil environment.
\n\nFather! We know the law of putting down roots in true fertile soil as one seed, and centered on the roots the sprout will come up and grow into a tree in the midst of an environment filled with hope centered on your public love. We also will have to consider as important this environment needed by the new sprouts.
\n\nFather! Please arrange their youth in proper beauty. And please protect their path of relationship with you, and let them be able to grow centered on the foundation of that environment.
\n\nPlease let them become true shoots, and in relation to this people, this nation, this world, please let them become a new tree of life which all humankind can look up to and which can embrace all of humankind. And we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who can blossom as new flowers and bear fruit which can be spread to all nations with more to spare.
\n\nIn order to do that we will have to be strong. Oh Father, please allow this nation, centered on your open love, to be able to be so eternally united that no kind of strength can break it apart. Please allow it to burn with conviction which cannot be changed by any kind of adverse circumstances. In order to endure these kinds of trials, we will have to absorb sufficient nutrition. Please guide us to become sons and daughters who have the life power that can remove all the essential conditions of evil which are left in this people.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nAugust 23, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_39t">
The person who lives for the world and is raised up by the world is not the kind of person who insists that he is great. We must truly understand that it is the land of person who should be raised up by you, who do not reveal yourself and who walk the path of hard work in a lonely place. Please let us realize that sons and daughters who work hard quietly thinking of you in order to return that joy to you as yours are more needed than people who make effort to obtain whatever kind of happiness there may be as the pride of this people.
\n\nOur hardworking Father! Our lonely Father! If we are sons and daughters who truly know the dramatic situation of sorrow of our father who has endured closing his eyes, biting his lips and biting his tongue, we must truly feel that you, who have carried the grief of a thousand years in your heart, cannot receive comfort through people who seek for satisfaction in the life of one day.
\n\nIn spite of being people who are passing through a historical age in which we must live lives of reform, lives of inspiration which cannot hold back the tears even if we have the grief of it taking our entire lives, before you we should, of course, live true lives with gentle, humble attitudes. But on the contrary we must realize that we are making your work harder, and we are giving you heavier crosses to carry, and we have pushed you out on a lonely path.
\n\nAnd not only that; we must realize that we have been in the vanguard position striking the people of heaven\'s side as descendents who received the evil blood lineage. We must discover that we are those who cannot even request forgiveness from you through anything in heaven and earth.
\n\nThen, please make us realize that we can truly find you and relate to you only if in lamentation and anguish we have minds that seek to offer to you our lives which have caused grief in relation to your will. We earnestly hope that your will allow us to feel that this is the most important event, greater than anything else in our lives.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nSeptember 27, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_40t">
We must understand that until now our father has not been ruled by anyone, but our father`s mind has been sorry, even as he gave. It was our father`s mind to want to give pure, original love completely.
\n\nBut we must think about the fact that due to humankind`s fall, in the heart of our father who carried out the providence step by step, there are tears of loneliness from that period of thousands of years. Father! We must know that your situation has been that you could not help but go through the stages of the rugged peaks of the age of formation, the age of growth and the age of perfection in the course of the providence of restoration.
\n\nEven while receiving your love, until today, humankind has not known how to be grateful to you, and has not known how to reciprocate. We have considered the inner heart of our father who has led this sorrowful history bravely and with good courage, determined to give everything at some point, the more people are like that.
\n\nToday, please express your sorrowful heart. Your sons and daughters have gathered here feeling fear that we might not be able to become the sons and daughters who can receive everything from you and give everything to you representing the world, representing history, representing the cosmos at this time of your expressing completely the heart you wanted to give.
\n\nFather, we have come to understand that when a person who is filled with a mind that wants to give the things of creation meets a person who wants to receive those things, if that person bows his head and feels ashamed even as he is giving, that person is your person.
\n\nEven having given everything, feeling restricted by not being able to give more, wanting to give more, even if there is the grief of burning up one\'s mind and body and disappearing, if there is a person who has a mind that denies even the fact that he has disappeared, that person belongs to God. And when we think that all heaven is connected to him, we earnestly hope that you will allow us to appear at this time as sons and daughters who can connect with you, Father, at this central point which we cannot avoid even if we wanted to.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the\'Ime Parents.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 25, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_41t">
Beloved Father!
\nThe flow of past history was sorrowful at times and happy at times. Each time we think that heaven`s sorrow is dwelling in the center of a mind that others don`t know, we realize how continuously inadequate we have been as we relate to you.
\n\nFather! This relationship of your having met us has not been formed through our efforts; it is due to the merit of millions of generations of ancestors which laid a bridge and broadened and broadened its foundation. Please allow us to be able to feel grateful for all the grace you have given to let us have a day when we could meet you like this today.
\n\nIn a place where people gather together and part again, people are subjected to criticism, and we can see that divisions occur; but we must understand that in a place where people meet centered on heaven, only awe, gratitude and tears remain.
\n\nPlease let your children who are gathered here clearly realize that it will not do unless they feel more compassion for God deep in the center of their minds, and they love God who is our father. Please allow us to become sons and to become daughters who offer our minds and bodies in order to love you as though we were crazy and who are able to be grateful even if we sacrifice everything, and about whom you can feel joy when you look at us.
\n\nAs you searched for him, how much did you long for that one and only son to whom you could give all your love and about whom you could be proud before all people?
\n\nNow our impatient selves are advancing step by step towards your internal character; therefore, it will not do unless we become those who are waiting for the time when you call us to hurry and come to you. Please absolutely don\'t let us ever become sons and daughters who avoid suffering and worry that suffering may come.
\n\nWe know well that if there was a history of suffering, there was without fail a mistake between the people there. Please allow us to realize clearly that when you were doing well behind the scenes but humankind made a mistake, heaven was sorrowful every time, and stood in a position where it could not help but be in anguish.
\n\nHumankind must never overturn the blessings of the whole which heaven seeks to give, due to making a mistake or having cooperated together and determined together. Knowing this kind of truth, we earnestly hope that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to determine ourselves.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of our True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 9, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_42t">
Since we know that living for ourselves, for myself is always being an enemy in relation to the course of the providence of salvation, and living for others is the course that levels that path of all the difficulties and struggles which are always in front of us, please let us go the path of living for others.
\n\nIf our spirit becomes exhausted, that is not something we can resolve on our own. On the contrary, please let us realize that if we live for others or sacrifice more because of being in a position to suffer more and to live for others, there is another path that can be pioneered as a course of reaction. And please let us realize that there is another path that can lead to you by increasing the level of precious loyalty and offering more devotion to you.
\n\nWe earnestly hope that you will allow us to understand that the problem is not in other people; it is in ourselves, in myself. We know well that it is the principle of the real world that no matter how strongly a cold wind blows, if I prepare clothes for myself and wear them, that cold wind just blows by without affecting me.
\n\nBut if I don`t have the ability to be able to prepare myself for the cold, then I become ill, and I can be bent over. Accordingly, in our lives today as well we will have to take on this principle and reform our lives and be able to determine the value that heaven is hoping for, which can give light to the course of our lives.
\n\nPlease let us realize that only then will we be able to become the sons and daughters who can make you happy. We must understand the fact that having been excited sons and daughters who were happy in the past does not mean we will be happy sons and daughters today. We can be happier today than in the past.
\n\nIn order to become sons and daughters who can feel valuable stimulation, it will not do unless we stand in a position where we can believe heaven, and look up to heaven, and consult directly with heaven from a position of being able to take on a more difficult, a loftier, a more valuable, a more responsible position. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who know that taking on a more important responsibility is an honor, that going a more difficult path of the cross than others is our pride, and that living a more serving life than others is a valuable life.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 24, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_43t">
Until now for Unification Church members the time has come near; but it worries me greatly, and I cannot help but be skeptical about how many people know that the time is coming. The time passes as the time, but we know that nothing will work today if people are the same as they were in the past.
\n\nWe know that when spring comes as the time to plant seeds, if the seeds are planted, the shoots will sprout, and when summer comes, the shoots will grow, and when fall comes, they will bear fruit, and just before winter comes there is a time to harvest. When we see one living being going through the course of its life according to the laws of natural phenomena like this, if there is a person who in his lifetime is greeting the spring season of his life of faith, please allow him to also greet the summer season.
\n\nIn the summer season it is not the luxuriantly growing leaf that is good; please allow us to understand how precious the stem is which allowed it to grow. We know that this stem, as a stem I alone can possess, brings flowers into bloom and bears fruit, and if it is a yearly plant, that fruit brings the combined results of the value of the whole year. We must understand that a life of faith has times like that as well.
\n\nPlease let us know that throughout our lives in relation to our course of knowing the will, one time is die spring season, one time is the summer season. one time is the fall season, and one time is the harvest season.
\n\nWhen we reach the harvest season centered on the will, we must offer everything and give our full devotion and bring in the harvest. And if we do not claim the things we harvest as our own, but give them to you and then receive them back as ours, we form a relationship with you, and all things can belong to us.
\n\nBecause we know that being able to have a relationship has value, we who are going the course of restoration should not first have all things as our own; rather, everything must be yours, Father. We who are in the position of having received your call and are following must clearly understand that preparing our own personality and life does not come first; we must prepare for your personality and your life first.
\n\nMore than any thing else, please do not let us lose the battle through lives of a day; and we earnestly hope and desire that you will bless us, Father, not to lose in relation to the battle through our lives of a month. May all things be together with the standard of your victory, and we earnestly ask you to guide us to become sons and daughters whose minds will always rush valiantly and boldly in that direction and be there at the place of your final victory.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of our True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 24, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_44t">
Father!
\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become children who reveal our terribly petty, base selves in front of your broad, noble, internal character and eagerly long for the touch of your compassion and mercy.
\n\nFather, you are the subject of all capabilities! You are the prime mover of all life! You are the origin of heart and love! As real beings in front of you, we entrust our whole selves to you from the position of being like branches or leaves. If you are sorrowful, then we will also have to be sorrowful, and if you are happy, then we will also have to be happy, and if you work quickly, then we will also have to work quickly. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who deal with our entire living environment together with you in this way.
\n\nWhen we reveal ourselves before your internal character, we wonder whether we are the kinds of sons and daughters for whom you hoped, whether you can relate happily to us, and personally come and whisper directions to us about the path we should go. In order to become those kinds of sons and daughters, more than anyone else we must fulfill the duty of filial piety and the duty of loyalty in relation to you, and we must be able to offer even our lives to you.
\n\nSince we know that we cannot remain connected to the will on the stage of life if we are not able to have a relationship as your sons, please melt our minds which are like sticks and stones and let them resemble your mind. We earnestly hope and pray that you will allow us to establish a relationship where your situation and our situations meet, and we can be absorbed into you.
\n\nIt will not do to remain not being able to help lamenting our fleeting lives together with the flow of time. With hope, determining a hope-filled tomorrow, taking authority as your sons, we will have to greet a day of joy, a day of rejoicing and a day of pride.
\n\nWe who know the will know your capacity and know through experience how amazing you are, and we know that we must stand in a position with dignity and authority as the victors of tomorrow, as the builders of today, as the victors of history. To do that, we must not be pitiful people who always lament over themselves and cannot put themselves forward. Please allow us to become your sons and daughters who know how to determine ourselves.
\n\nNow please allow our minds to be able to give you joy. And please allow our bodies to be the way you want them.
\n\nPlease allow us to be able to offer eternally before you our bodies to become living altars of victory and our minds to become living sacrifices of victory. Then, please allow us to become the sons and daughters you are not ashamed to put forth before all things of creation and about whom you can say proudly that this is the sacrifice you have been looking for, and these are the beings of hope you have wanted to meet.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 21, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_45t">
Father!
\nYou are the only one we can believe; there is no one to depend on but you. We know that there is no one but you with whom to clear up matters and form a relationship. If we form a relationship with people, we see that it will become nothing more than an object of despair. As we walk the path of persons of faith, we have seen many times, experienced many times, and felt many times the incessant fact of human history that in the end our hearts are pierced with arrows.
\n\nOur sorrow was not being hungry; it was not standing in a position of being persecuted unjustly by the environment. We did not know in advance that what is more sorrowful than that is losing our beloved father. No matter how lacking a place may be, if you are there it has everything. Even if a place is in the center of hell, if you are there it can be transformed into heaven.
\n\nWe know that there is no other place for us to live or die than where you are, Father. It is under you that we have happiness; it is under you that we have hope; and when we think that it is under you that our existence has value, in this way you are the prerequisite of all our victories, the prerequisite of happiness, and we really, really did not know in advance the fact that it is you, Father, who can be the decisive standard of value.
\n\nAs for pursuing superior value, we did not know in time that before pursuing something external, already deep in our minds there is a standard that can determine the content of value. We thought that the source of happiness was in some relative world on the other side; therefore, we did not know in advance that deep in our minds a root is already connected there.
\n\nNow, Father, if through the Unification Church you are longing for us to become sons and daughters whom you can embrace as favored children of new resurrected life, we have realized that it will not do unless we make efforts in order for us to be able to stand in such a position. Therefore, we earnestly hope and pray that we may become your precious sons and daughters who can obtain your compassion by becoming gentle incarnations who relate to your will humbly.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of our True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nApril 25, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_46t">
Beloved Father!
\nYoung boys and girls have gathered in this place. Their longing for this place was not in order to stay here like this today, but in order to find their true selves find tomorrow. They have come here in order to go on the holy path where they can fulfill their duties of filial piety and loyalty to you in their three ages: the age of true youth, the age of true maturity and the age of true elderliness.
\n\nWe know the truth that there was sorrow in heaven; heaven was filled with tears for the long period of 6,000 years in order to restore one person. In order to connect to the beginning point of the victory of the greatest goodness, we quietly offer our entire lives to you, Father, and we will have to be able to sacrifice ourselves, fighting today and tomorrow. We earnestly hope and pray that you will allow the young people gathered here to become those who are able to volunteer and go forward on this kind of path.
\n\nIn the world, the older generation and the younger generation are arguing, but we know that in the younger generation there are true young people and false young people. We know that today the false young people are recklessly violating the most precious thing, but the true young people are saving to the utmost and protecting to the utmost this most precious thing in the world.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow them to realize at this time that that thing is chastity centered on obedience.
\n\nThrough hearts which are rising up in young minds, overturning together with you, Father, each one will have to be able to determine deep in his mind to become a person who will fight and remain until that point where we can have a relationship of victory. Therefore, we earnestly hope that you will cause each one to make that kind of determination.
\n\nWhen we think that all the things yearned for in the evil world are not things that lead us to the gates of happiness but rather they drive us into the snares of death and the traps of death, it will not do unless the young individuals gathered here become true young people who determine to be true individuals who will not change, and who, no matter where they go in society, will not be stained or influenced.
\n\nWhen we realize that if they do not become true young people, they will not be able to become true youth or true middle-aged people, we earnestly hope and desire that you will not allow us to be inadequate in offering and returning ourselves nicely to you, receiving gratefully the blessed gift of this age and this season.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nAugust 19, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_47t">
When we think about how very much you have sacrificed in the course of history and how very much you have toiled in the ages of history in order to find our individual selves, today we cannot help but report honestly that we are inadequate people who have nothing at all that can repay that great blessing, and we are disloyal and unfilial.
\n\nWe clearly realize the fact that the source of evil is not something else; it is ourselves. And we must realize the fact that, using ourselves as a base, it is doing worldwide activities, and it is appearing through our minds and our bodies. Because of that you have told us, Father, that on the path of the life of faith, winning the world is not the problem; winning over yourself is the problem.
\n\nThe enemy is not in another place; the people right in my own home have been enemies. And not only those family members; going one step more inward, we have realized that we cannot help but say that our bodies are our enemies. And not only our bodies, but at this time we must realize once again the fact that our minds themselves have stood in the position of enemies before you.
\n\nBut, due to the merit of your hard work for the sake of our inadequate selves, and not only that, but due to the rare favor of your establishing and sacrificing your many servants and many descendants, we are able to bow here today.
\n\nTherefore, before your grace overflows, please allow the merit of our many ancestors who shed blood in the course of history to remain with us, and please let the foundation of their good accomplishments remain with us and please let that form a bridge. And we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow this time to become one where you can come to us.
\n\nPlease allow us to be able to bow down to you with hearts of adoration and hearts of yearning, and minds that long only for you, Father. Since we have minds that hope to shine again as sons and daughters who can be embraced in your presence, we must not become those who reveal ourselves as one complete entity. We earnestly ask that you will allow us to become a leaven which you can kneed after you have completely broken us up.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of our True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 17, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_48t">
Father!
\nWe know well that from the time that Jesus Christ came to the earth, shed his blood and established the path of the cross until now, in this historical period of nearly 2,000 years, humankind has gone along the path of historical indemnity, paying the price of so much blood.
\n\nWe who know how very frustrated your heart must have been since you could not just cast them away, oh, Father, we must realize ourselves that we must become extremely humble, and that on this path that our unification movement is going, we will face the new spring day which can embrace and overcome the grief of Cain and Abel. From now on we must embrace humankind and return to heaven with them, centered on the people and centered on the world.
\n\nWhatever our attitude may be, we must reflect on ourselves internally and externally. We earnestly hope and desire that you will bless us to be able to become true children who can add to the stimulation of hope in your heart, and who can be dashing and bold and have no flaws as heroes building your kingdom; and that at the same time that we receive your blessing, we can receive your love, and we will not be found lacking so that you can put us forward proudly before all people.
\n\nFather! We earnestly hope that you will keep all of our lives. We earnestly ask that your compassion and love will always penetrate deep in our hearts.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of our True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 19, 1975
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_49t">
Beloved Father!
\nOnce again we long for the day that will realize the will you expressed after creating all the things of the universe. When we think about the existence of our sublime, precious Father, we, who know how low and inadequate humankind is. We cannot help but pursue all value and content that can become one with that lofty will. And furthermore, when we think that the people on this earth are those who have fallen from the ideal world of God, we think that the responsibility to take hold of oneself and to be brought to the world of goodness does not lie with heaven; rather it lies with humankind itself.
\n\nFather! We have realized on our own that the position with which we are faced is far too separated from the sublime majestic position where you stay at the center of the universe, and from you who are the lord of the ideal centered on love. Therefore, we know that in order to fill in this great distance, a path of submission to the reasonable course of restoration, which is so filled with grief, lies before us.
\n\nOur parents cannot help us with going forward on this path, nor can we receive help from anyone else. Today, as we realize that we can arrive there only if we have earnest hearts centered on God alone and toiling hearts of the original nature which are not concerned about life or death, we Unification Church family members are sensing our awesome mission of having to expand that purpose from our own individual selves to the family, tribe, people, nation and world.
\n\nWhen we think about the fact that from a position of being incomplete ourselves, we cannot pursue the completion of the family, and from the position of an incomplete family, we cannot pursue the completion of the nation or the world, we realize well that the situation humankind is in today is very pitiful.
\n\nWe know the fact that the realm of the fall covers the whole and dominates all the realms of life. We also know that we need our own efforts and our own insights that can overcome and go beyond this. We need a new truth that is able to discover this, and we need the strength to overcome it. But we know that such strength does not arise from loving for the sake of oneself, but rather only by loving for the sake of God.
\n\nFather! We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become children who can rush towards you from this place on our own with minds of love and with a life force that is strong and of good courage. Please remain with us forever through love and ages of blessings.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 9, 1980
    </string>

    <string name="pr_zelaniya_50t">
Please fill the entire world with your compassion and love and grace and power. As we bow down and consider again your history of suffering in order to realize the hope of tomorrow, we repent once again for our inadequacies of the past, and we have come to a point where we must determine ourselves again about this great mission that you have given to us. Therefore, Father, we earnestly hope and desire that you will please urge us on, increase our power, and allow us to become true children who are able to receive and attend your joyful will.
\n\nFather: Please bless all the members of the Unification Movement spread throughout the world. This morning, too, they are offering devotion to you and longing for this land of Korea as the homeland of their faith. Please be together with them through your grace and through a relationship of abundant life in those places where they are bowing down in the direction of the place where their teacher dwells, in those places where they are bending their knees and bowing down deeply to you.
\n\nPlease allow them to be unification workers who lack nothing as tomorrow\'s kindred spirits, as tomorrow\'s brothers and as tomorrow\'s family members. Please bless your children who are spread out in 127 nations around the world. We know that all the tears shed and all the prayers cried out to you, as well as all the foundations for which your children have risked their lives in order to tread upon and move those nations, will not be for naught.
\n\nTherefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will unite all the ancestors who are in spirit world with all the descendents on the earth, and that you will gather them together from all nations centered on one nation in order to realize the one nation and one world of your will. We earnestly hope that you will fill with your grace every place where people are gathered together centered on your name at this time.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nApril 26, 1981
    </string>
</resources>