<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="pr_serdca_1t">
Father!
\nWe do not know the original heart of our Father who created humankind, and we know that we have not been able to feel our Father\'s love which can cast out sorrow.
\n\nNow even if we have to sacrifice everything we have, we must find your love, and we must recover the original destined relationship between you and us. Father! Please allow us to be able to open our minds now and to find out on our own what your heart is and what your love is. And please open our ears and let us be able to hear your voice. Please allow our eyes to see and be able to look up to our Father who is seeking sons and daughters who can receive the grace which heaven is allowing.
\n\nThen, as those who can see and as those who can hear, please allow us to sense the touch of our Father who has worked so hard for us, and please allow us to experience that heart of endurance. Since we know a little of the heart of our Father who has gone forth enduring and struggling, please take complete dominion over our minds and bodies as your own, Father.
\n\nIf there are sons and daughters who are ignorant and caught in the realm of death, Father, please directly extend your touch of grace and act to create everything. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow this to become a time when we are able to be in harmony with your mind, and can respond to the original appeal of your heart.
\n\nWe have realized that you have a will, Father, for which you have given your entire heart and mind, and we have realized that the course of history is the course determined by heaven which you have walked. And we know that it has been realized only through the people who have sought a value system that can relate to heaven and who are able to communicate with heaven.
\n\nIf we have the mission of rooting out the source of all the sins of the past, and all the sins of the present, and all the sins of the future, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will not allow us to be attracted by sin and feel the qualms of conscience, and that you will allow direct acts of your love to appear which are able to inspire our minds to want to thank you in the midst of your love.
\n\nWe know that the time has come when we must be familiar with the truth of heavenly morality, and the time has come when we must be familiar with the character of heavenly morality, and the time has come when we must be familiar with your love, Father.
\n\nFather! We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow the revealing of the truth which is able to introduce your love to all humankind, and that today in these last days you will allow a person of character who is able to testify to your love to appear before all people.
\n\nPlease allow us the preparation and foundation to enable our minds to follow that truth, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will act to bring about quickly in history the day when everything can be revealed in front of your Will.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 16, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_2t">
We know the fact that the concept of creation is not to seek only a specially determined individual; it is to seek all humankind. Oh Father who has toiled seeking all the people on earth! When we think that the providential will to seek and establish an entire universe within the concept of goodness still remains to be done, we earnestly hope that you will allow us to be able to be of at least a little help to you and even if we were to die millions of times, that we would become fertilizer contributing towards realizing your Will.
\n\nPlease allow us to realize the fact that your sorrow did not occur because of all the things you created on this earth; rather it occurred because there has been no human individual who has been able to accomplish your concept of creation in place of you. Please allow us to be able to fight for the Will, offering our minds and our entire devotion, and please allow us to be able to understand that the creator who created all things is you, and the one who has worked endlessly for us is also you.
\n\nPlease allow us to understand that a person who does not know your heart is a person who does not know your life, and a person who has not experienced your heart is a person who does not know your situation. We earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to realize that at this moment, too, as you watch us you are filled with anguish since we are not able to attend your heart.
\n\nBy allowing our minds to become completely one with your Will, please lead us to live as your friends, and please guide us to be able to become people who can be directed by you and, who can live that way. We have come to understand that Jesus himself embraced your will like that and he was the person who appeared for the sake of the Jewish people.
\n\nPlease allow us to realize that it is heartbreaking for you not to be able to find substantial human beings in whom you are able to dwell even though human beings remain just as you created them and all things remain just as you created them. Beloved Father' Now please dwell within us, and please sanctify our minds and bodies so that we may become such people. And earnestly hoping and desiring that: you will lead us to become the heralds of the new age, accomplishing your concept of creation together with you and rejoicing together with you.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 16, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_3t">
Father!
\nWe know that a person who does not desire to bow humbly while attending you will not be able to form a relationship with you in the eternal kingdom.
\n\nNow as we open our hearts and go out seeking, we are seeking the day we have longed for when our bodies are able to follow the subjective commands of our minds and we feel your heart at the center of our minds. Therefore, please allow us to become people who are able to bow our heads of our own accord, feeling that behind the scenes you have gone through a historical course of misfortune and toil for the sake of finding each one of us, and today please let us hear your voice flowing out of our minds and be able to find our bodies which had been lost.
\n\nAnd please allow us to become people who are able on our own to feel through our minds and bodies, minds that are in awe of you. We thought that you always came to us only as the father of glory, but you came to us as the lord of sorrow, and as the lord of suffering, and you came to us as an expression of misfortune. Because we did not know that you were like this, we have wanted to give you responsibility for our sorrow, and have wanted to give you responsibility for our difficulties, and have wanted to give you responsibility for our misfortunes. Please bear with us.
\n\nYou have walked this kind of course of history, and have come to us lamenting and keeping your sorrow under control. Please let us realize that we are a fallen tribe who cannot even call you "Father." Please do not allow there to be any sons or daughters who do not know your course of sorrow as we seek to relieve you of your toil of millions of years.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nSeptember 14, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_4t">
Oh Father!
\nOur grief-filled history has wound itself around us and is moving us along. We know that we who are facing this living environment filled with grief have the awesome mission of dealing with the grief-filled history and of relieving the heart of heaven which is filled with grief.
\n\nWe who are shouldering this kind of mission must embrace the heart of heaven and earth, and even if we die ten million times feeling your suffering and experiencing your sorrow, we must become sons and daughters who seek to die in a position that is able to console our Father.
\n\nAt the time Jesus came to the earth, many religious bodies and believers were longing for the messiah, but they thought the messiah would come with the ideal appearance that they were hoping for. But the messiah who came was not a messiah of joy; he was a messiah of the encapsulated sorrow of humankind and was a messiah of suffering corresponding to the suffering of human history. We know that at that time there was not a single person who thought that the messiah who came as the representative of the Kingdom of Heaven would appear in that way.
\n\nWe know that history occurs as it has been shown. We are learning the principle that things are restored by indemnity, that realities which appeared in history are repeated exactly in the last days. We know that it is the responsibility of the saints of the last days to return joy of a horizontal nature to you, Father, having dealt with horizontally and developed horizontally centered on our own selves the sorrowful emotions of the Garden of Eden, the sorrowful emotions of the course of history, and the sorrowful emotions of the vertical flow of history.
\n\nOh Father! Now we want to offer our loyalty for the sake of the world. We want to establish the welfare of heaven for the sake of all humankind. Please let us realize that in order to do that, we must become leading figures who inherit the suffering and sorrow which permeate heaven.
\n\nPlease let us understand that only those who absorb all suffering and sorrow can appear as heirs of heavenly joy, and please let us endure whether there is sorrow or suffering, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become historical sacrifices who go forth saying, "I will die for the sake of the life of the whole."
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMay 24, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_5t">
Please allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to seek and experience through our minds and bodies your external form, your situation, and your heart, Father, as you made your way through the lonely course of restoration in order to find the true children you lost.
\n\nYou were not able to love Adam and Eve with a mind of love which penetrated your heart. Please let us become your sons and daughters who are able to experience your heart, oh Father, as you went forth starving for love for the long period of six thousand years. And please allow us to become earnest children who embrace and comfort your lonely heart.
\n\nNow please allow us to be able to offer our minds and bodies as yours, Father. We earnestly hope that you will lead us to become sacrifices of victory who are able to be proud of belonging to our eternal father and who do not think of our minds and bodies as our own. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become your descendents who are able to relieve you heart which has not been able to embrace and love with a true heart of love for six thousand years.
\n\nThere are many people living on the earth, but we know that there are no sons or daughters whom you can embrace and love, saying, "These are my sons and daughters," and explaining to Satan that they are your sons and daughters.
\n\nEven when 2,000 years ago Jesus walked the course of the battle to save all the people on the earth, we know that you were not able to directly embrace and love him.
\n\nWe know the fact that no one can take away your beloved child. We know that Jesus moved your heart deeply, but he was not able to receive your love. We also know your situation of not having been able to love. Therefore, please establish the day of glory and establish sons and daughters of heaven and release your full heart, and while embracing and loving please express all of your heart. Please allow us to realize that it is your hope for those kinds of sons and daughters of heaven to appear on this earth.
\n\nToday we have nothing, and even if we lost everything, we want to become sons and daughters who are embraced in the bosom of your love and are able to receive your eternal love.
\n\nBeloved Father! Please bless us. Please stretch out your mighty hand and sanctify us. Please cast out all elements of evil, and we earnestly hope that you will allow our minds and bodies to become completely yours, Father.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 14, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_6t">
When deep in our hearts we try to reflect once again on this thing called the will of the providence which we did not know, we realize only too well the fact that humankind has not been able to communicate with your innermost thoughts even though a long history of six thousand years has passed since our ancestors fell. Furthermore, we have realized that your situation is difficult and miserable, and we have realized that today your hope is remaining in front of the earth, humankind and heaven.
\n\nToday as we consider whether we possess the fidelity of sons and daughters who can receive praise in front of our sacred Father, and while standing in the garden of your heart, and standing in your realm of hope can say, "Father! Please be comforted for I am here." We cannot help but admit that we are far distant from that standard.
\n\nWhen Jesus Christ, who came as the incarnation of your hope and who could represent your heart, appears on the earth again, a person who is groping for and searching for the heart of heavenly morality will have to communicate with that heart of Jesus. And as for the chosen nation of Israel, which wandered in order to communicate with the heart of heavenly morality, we know that their situation and Jesus situation should have become one.
\n\nThe people of Israel should have known that the hope of our Father who sent Jesus was a hope for all people. But due to not recognizing Jesus who was the incarnation of hope, this anguish has continued down until us today, and we furthermore feel the historical sorrow of its having been passed down.
\n\nWhere has the Jewish religion gone which you sought and established over a four thousand year period, and where have the people of Israel gone? The temple you raised up in Jerusalem was prepared for the sake of Jesus, but it was not able to form a relationship with Jesus, and the Jewish religion was not able to form a relationship with Jesus either.
\n\nEven the prepared people, from their position of not forming any relation whatsoever with Jesus, stood in a position of driving him out. But we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will let us become people who know the situation of Jesus, who had no choice but to stand alone in a solitary position like that and pray for the sake of the people who cast him out.
\n\nNow facing you, Father, what do we want to shout out? And what do we want to find in relation to you, and what do we want to ask for? Please let us have hearts that represent your heart just as Jesus did, and which our ancestors were not able to do.
\n\nWe know that it will not do unless we become beings who, with Jesus' situation and hope, have hearts that are the same as yours in the last days and who have the responsibility to indemnify all the historical debts in relation to you up until now.
\n\nNow we know that the path of the cross remains ahead of our footsteps. The time has come when we cannot help but fight with the evil world with eyes brimming with tears, and we know that you have called us because the time has come for us to communicate with your heart, in order to do that, please allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to offer ourselves as sacrifices of victory, who are able to realize your hope for you, by making your heart and mind our heart and mind, your situation our situation, your hope our hope, your enemy our enemy and your battle our battle.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 1, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_7t">
Father!
\nYou lost the original garden. At this time please allow us to come to understand about your heart which was so sorrowful. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow our minds and bodies to feel that you have remained in endless sorrow and endless suffering and that you have shed tears without our knowing it.
\n\nPlease allow us to experience through our minds and bodies the entirety of your sorrowful heart, and please let: us realize at this time that your sorrow due to the fall of Adam and Eve was great. Please let us realize that it also caused unspeakable suffering, loneliness and sorrow for you that Jesus Christ, who came to the earth and took responsibility for the will of the providence of restoration, was not able to complete his entire mission and died on the cross.
\n\nAs we think about your having gone through the sorrowful course of history about which you could not help but feel greatly indignant because our ancestors betrayed you, we ask you to please not allow us to stand in a pitiful position which would add more to your sorrow through our lives today. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become people who are able to cope with the sorrow of Adam and Eve and to cope with the sorrow of Jesus Christ.
\n\nNow please do not let our minds and bodies remain as our own simple minds and bodies alone. Please allow our minds to represent your mind, Father, and our bodies to represent your external form.
\n\nPlease allow us to be able to testify to our Father who has a sorrowful heart.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 8, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_8t">
Father!
\nEach time something sorrowful happened on the earth, heaven was sorrowful, too, our ancestors were sorrowful, too, all the things of creation were sorrowful, too, and today we are sorrowful, too. Even though humankind looked forward to the day of liberation, which would eliminate this sorrow, humankind did not know the way to go, and even while looking for that something, humankind could not realize what it was and wandered around and groped along. But we, who have realized the fact that you have gone through this long period of time of six thousand years, have hearts that want to embrace you and weep endlessly if you appear now.
\n\nNow we who know all these things and have gone forth searching for our original parents, hope that through our minds and bodies the day will come quickly when instead of tears of sorrow we shed tears of joy, and we will eliminate sorrow and only joy will remain.
\n\nNow we have realized where we should go; we have also realized where we belong, and we have realized the value of the original children.
\n\nFather! Now we are running up the slope of restoration dragging our wounded legs, and we are heading towards the summit which Adam and Eve hoped for. Now we earnestly hope and desire that you will let your inspiration appear in our minds and bodies, adding to our final power to let us be able to go over this line.
\n\nIf there is anything that you want to say to us, we know the fact that you are not happy but rather endlessly sorrowful, that you have had endless difficulties, and that you have had endless suffering. Please let us realize and experience this through our minds, and please let us feel your original heart in place of you, Father.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 15, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_9t">
Father!
\nLike orphans going back and forth, we do not know our purpose or our direction, and without even knowing what kind of environment we are facing, we are being knocked over according to the flow of history; and without being able to establish the center of our lives, we have been pushed and pushed along. We realize that we have gone forth in such a pitiful manner until today.
\n\nOn the other hand, we did not know the fact that you held us even though we were like this; and when we were sad, you were sad together with as. And we did not know the fact that you were the Lord who did not distinguish between night and day and worked so hard in order to seek us out when we were caught and groaning in the realm of death. Please allow us to realize that a heart of joy which is able to know and feel this kind of fact is more precious than communicating with heaven and earth.
\n\nHeaven does not doze off at the time we doze off, and does not sleep at the time we are sleeping. Please awaken this movement, and please guide these individuals. Since we have come like unworthy children in the presence of our Father who has worked so hard, please bear with us.
\n\nWe did not know that you know each of our individual situations, and that you are the Lord of those situations, and that you even bear with all the unbearable, difficult situations. Now we earnestly hope and desire, father, that you will allow this time to become one in which we place before you all the difficulties, sorrows, and worries that permeate our innermost thoughts, and we are able to change them and adopt yours.
\n\nWe know the fact that our Heavenly Father exists who exerts himself for us and that an even greater heaven exists which is concerned about our lives. Please allow us to feel awe as we relate to you, our father, through our minds and bodies. Please reveal to us the heart of our father who has taken the position of being injured first before we were injured, and who when our bodies were exhausted and collapsing who has held us, embraced us comforted us and once again urged us on the way we were to go.
\n\nPlease let us admit that until today we have lived by words alone. From now on please allow us to be able to know you and to be able to become one in heart with you as sons and daughters who are able to understand your situation. And from a position so firm that even if we wanted to fall away we would not be able to, and even if we wanted to be divided we could not, and there could be no being whatsoever who could separate us from you, please let us feel heaven's sorrow as our sorrow, heaven's joy as our joy, heaven's work as our work, and heaven's responsibility as our responsibility.
\n\nToday we know that, standing in an eternally unchanging position, we have taken a position as people responsible for having to fight with myriads of satans. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to experience the sternness of the fact that it will not do unless we stand in the position of sacrifices in order to save the whole.
\n\nFather! Please eliminate all the elements of our minds that are not proper, and we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to be able to make the firm determinations and decisions that will allow us to become one with you and to harmonize with your internal character and your mentality.
\n\nPlease do not let there be any sons and daughters who seek to fathom your nature through the concepts of their own egos. Please allow us to become your sons and daughters who are able to appear completely adapted and harmonized, shaped as you have molded us, according to the desire of your will. If we have elements you cannot bear with, please eliminate them totally, and we earnestly hope that you will be seated and command us.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 8, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_10t">
We know that Jesus and God had no respite from sorrow as they related to humankind. When we reflect on Jesus life 2,000 years ago, we know that he shed tears which others knew nothing about; he lived an outstanding life which others knew nothing about; and he wept bitterly while going a course of persecution others knew nothing about.
\n\nJesus trod this kind of path, and the many saints who followed behind him were not concerned about walking a path of blood; we know the fact that they struggled forward, not being concerned even about the path of death.
\n\nThe path to the palace of heaven is the path of the cross. Therefore, please allow us to understand that each one must go to the top of Golgotha carrying his cross on his back, and each must experience persecution, even going to the point of shedding blood on the cross. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to understand that heaven is looking for people who forget about themselves, who forget about their own sorrows, who forget about their own pain, and who are giving their all today and tomorrow to go the path of Golgotha.
\n\nOh Father! Please allow us to understand the sorrow of Jesus who has laid bare his sorrowful heart today in this age. There is no need to know Jesus just as the historical Jesus; the time has come when we must know the modern Jesus within our own circumstances. Therefore, please let us become a movement crying out only to heaven, filled only with hearts that will offer our minds and bodies in front of that noble, majestic heart and in front of that love, whether we live or die.
\n\nWe know that this group is made up of people who have been chased on this earth, people who have been rejected by the religious bodies. We hope and desire that you will allow your sons and daughters who have gathered here to become a movement that is able defend that kind of position to the death.
\n\nThe mind of heaven appeared through the mind of one person and it had prepared a foundation of heart to unite 4,000 years of history, but because humankind destroyed and betrayed that, today humankind is in a wretched state. Father, please change the minds of the many people on this earth who do not know that their sorrow is your sorrow.
\n\nPlease allow us to become a solitary movement that knows how to weep and build an altar for their sake. We know that Jacob also built an altar in the wilderness, as did Moses and Elijah as well.
\n\nWe know the fact that among our ancestors who took responsibility for the will of heaven, there was no one who did not tread that kind of course.
\n\nSince we desire to become those who inherit their tradition, please allow us to become sons and daughters who know how to build the remaining altar and raise up again the fallen city wall and attend you preparing a sanctuary for you.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 15, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_11t">
Father!
\nHaving been swept into the death realm of sorrow and lamentation, we are unfilial children who cannot form our destined relationship with heaven. Therefore please allow us to become people who are able to cope with our original natures and who are in awe over the grace you have given. We earnestly hope and desire that we will be able to attend you, Father.
\n\nFrom the time that we knew about the path that you were calling us to go, we knew that you were together with us along this way of tears, and we knew that you were together with us on the way of the cross, the way of suffering, the way of sorrow, and even on the way when we were bound in chains. And we know about the path of thorns you will tread in the course of history as you work behind your beloved sons and daughters.
\n\nNow that we know about the history of struggle that you have gone through repeatedly for our sakes without our knowing it, as we imagine the countenance of our father who has worked so hard, even though we are now bowing down to you, we hardly know what to do or say. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will capture our very beings through your heart of inspiration.
\n\nWe have been called because the will of heaven exists, and the desire of heaven exists. Therefore, please allow us to understand that the way of the cross that is approaching us today is not because of us.
\n\nPlease allow even 10 million years of our descendants to know of the path of the historical destined relationship our ancestors worked for. If we have minds that are able to embrace unlimited joy, unlimited happiness, and unlimited hope, that reality did not begin because of our own selves, nor is it due to any human being. Rather, we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who know how to cherish deep in our minds and bodies the fact that everything began in heaven, and everything moves out from heaven, and who know how to long for the foundation that heaven has moved and cling to it and weep.
\n\nFather! You know the direction that we will go, and you also know the path we will choose to walk. Our minds do not begin from within ourselves, and our being placed in advisory positions is not for our own selves. Then, if it is for others and for you, Father, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will take dominion over our hearts and not let them change to the very end.
\n\nFather! Please do not allow us to become people who are unfilial to you and leave during the time of suffering which remains. Even if we feel the sorrow of our father who has carried out the providence, please do not allow us to become sons and daughters who cannot make it through this difficult period. We earnestly hope and desire that you will let us become sons and daughters who cast aside our selves, and are concerned for you, and who know how to comfort your heart and understand your situation.
\n\nAt this time in our minds, we are not asking for anything that is not of you. Now we must walk beyond today's suffering and look towards the garden of promise, and we must long for the Kingdom of Heaven of eternal blessings. We know that the blessings of God which will appear are a position of inexpressibly great glory. Therefore, today please allow us to become a movement of people whose hearts do not change in relation to you and who endure and remain to the end. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to fight to the end and stand before you, Father.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 29, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_12t">
Father!
\nAs you look at humankind, if there are sons and daughters who see the internal nature of their father whose heart has been broken seeking humankind, we know that they cannot ask you for blessings, and in the presence of that grief they cannot insist on their own ways. Please bear with these disloyal, unfilial children who have forgotten a thousand, ten thousand times that this kind of historical anguish remains.
\n\nNow is the one moment when we are able to call you "Father" naturally from our hearts, and when we become one with you, in this moment in which heaven and earth can rejoice, we know that a new history will begin and hope will be realized. However, when we consider today that in the depths of our minds we are not yet able to be filled with that kind of heart, we cannot help but despair and lament.
\n\nIf there is sorrow on the earth, where could there be a greater sorrow than the sorrow of our father who is comforting those sorrowful people, and if there is suffering, where is there a greater suffering than the suffering of our father who is holding and comforting people who are suffering because they betrayed him?
\n\nYou could not establish your own prestige, dignity and authority, and we have heard the historical message that while you went through the course of history leaving your hope unfulfilled, you clung to many of our good ancestors and cried out to and appealed to them to understand your heart, and to understand your situation.
\n\nBut we of today cannot be spokesmen for history, and as people who do not have anything we can be proud of as inherently good or can witness to as historical realities, we are on our knees bowing down before you, Father. Therefore, please let us reveal and report truthfully at this time, and we earnestly hope and desire that this time will become one in which we realize that we have been violated by Satan.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that at this time you will allow us to be able to understand your situation as a father who is not able to counsel us, speaking frankly about his heart and the will of the providence, and who worries about today, and worries about tomorrow because there are many who are disloyal, but none who are loyal to the will of the providence which remains.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nApril 12, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_13t">
We know the fact that because of the fall of the original Adam and Eve, who were to attend you, that until now history has been a course of sorrow. Humankind, who are the descendents of Adam and have who sinned, have been pursued and driven out and have gone through trials as people carrying the burden of sin which remains. Please let us be able to feel indignant when considering this human history which has continued until today.
\n\nWe know that you have gone through a historical course of toil; you have not distinguished between times or ages in order to find humankind again, because you have the responsibility of the creator who cannot forget humankind who have fallen to such a point, even if you want to.
\n\nToday please let those of us who are in this kind of position become people who, at the same time we lament over ourselves, know how to feel pain about the truth that your have walked a path of endless suffering and toil. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to have minds that are able to feel indignant over humanity\'s having inherited the historical blood lineage of sin, and able to feel that we cannot raise our eyes when in your presence.
\n\nIn our minds, the nature of sin still remains, and we feel the fact that our bodies are still bound by the chains of sin. We are longing for you, our father of mercy, to appear in your might and power, and we are longing to be able to become true sons and daughters. We know that you must be even more sorrowful when looking at your sons and daughters who have failed and who have not been able to cut off the wire net of sin or cut off the relationship of sin which comes into and permeates us and fight back.
\n\nNow please allow us to open the doors of our minds and escape the shackles of our bodies and possess new minds and new bodies, and please allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to appear before you, our father who is longing for us, as people who are able to call the original father our Father, saying, \"Father! Since we are here to represent your will, please receive us!\"
\n\nWe know that it is your hope that those kinds of historical victors will appear - sons and daughters who will be able to comfort your sorrowful mind, and fight with the enemy and be victorious.
\n\nNow we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to call you our father from that kind of position, and who are able to comfort you.
\n\nSince we know that this is our hope, and it is your hope as well, please encourage us and lead us to that position. We will cling to your hand as you lead us, and we earnestly hope that you will let us become sons and daughters who have earnest minds which are willing to go on any kind of path of adversity.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nApril 19, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_14t">
We long for the day when we can live together with you. Please let us become sons and daughters who long for you, and run towards you, and who can bring all the things of creation into harmony by offering greetings of joy and gratitude to you, having arrived at the day of glory when we can live together with you.
\n\nSince our minds and bodies were created resembling the external form of our father, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who resemble you completely.
\n\nOh Father! Humankind does not know that your sorrowful mind has permeated the earth, and does not know that the footprints of human history are soaked with the lonely tears of heaven. We have not known that the endless lamentations of heaven are encircling our minds and bodies. Now we cannot help but admit that we are the descendents of rebellious humankind and that we cannot establish our dignity before heaven or be trusted by heaven.
\n\nFather! There is no one on earth who can stop your tears, and there is no one to hold and comfort you in your sorrow, and there is no one to guard the path you are going.
\n\nTherefore, if there is grief on this earth, that grief is heaven\'s grief which has permeated the earth; if there is sorrow, that sorrow is heaven\'s sorrow which has permeated the earth, and if there is enmity, that enmity is heaven\'s enmity which has permeated the earth.
\n\nTherefore, humankind who are living on this earth are facing a destiny of not being able to help but be sacrifices of sorrow whether they want to be or not, and are facing a destiny of not being able to help but overcome their grief-filled selves whether they want to do it or not.
\n\nIn the midst of despair, the time has come to cry out to heaven with all that remains of our voices, saying, "Father! Please help us!" And the Last Days are arriving when we must call out, "Oh Father! Please find humankind with your heart of love." But in this kind of age, is there anyone who is clinging to and anguishing over your heart, and is there anyone who is clinging to and weeping over your mind? If there is such a person, that person could be called your true son or daughter, and could be called your substantial reciprocal object partner.
\n\nOh Father, who has empowered our minds! We long for the stimulation of our minds which will let us feel your sad and indignant heart, and since we want to be close to the wellspring of your heart, please grant us the grace of being able to do that. Then if we are transformed by that heart, we know that at that point we will not be able to help but reveal our unworthiness, and we will not be able to help but repent taking on ourselves the sinful guilt of humankind.
\n\nFather! We, who are unworthy and inadequate, we, who have not been able to become solid rocks, are ashamed before you, our father who has established us and worried about us. It will not do unless we become saints who have a foundation where you can manifest yourself in glory through our having comforted your heart of sorrow and enmity. Therefore, please take dominion over us through your strength and power. If there are people who appear to have been twisted by sin, please touch them with your love, and take dominion over them again, and mold them into another form.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMay 24, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_15t">
Father!
\nEven if we say that in the course of history humankind has struggled to find you, until now there have been no people on earth who have lived attending you.
\n\nIs there any corner on earth that is yours? Is there a single family that is yours? Is there a single people, a single nation that is yours? We are daring to ponder the heart of our father who has not been able to find or establish a single thing on the earth as his own. If you have sorrow, we know it would be that you who are the lord of the earth are not able to stand in the position of the lord, and you who must take responsibility for this earth have not been able to take that responsibility.
\n\nYou are in the position of having to take responsibility for all the people on the earth, but you have carried out a providence which could not take that responsibility. In spite of it being your position to command us directly, and take dominion directly through our hearts, you have not been able to be in such a position.
\n\nAnd in spite of the fact that you should have dominion over everything we have through our daily lives, you are not able to take dominion over our internal lives and circumstances. And in spite of the fact that you should be able to praise us as fruits of goodness, you have not been able to have that kind of day, or age or even one person. We did not know that you were in such a lonely position.
\n\nNow even if we would suffer the grief of losing everything that is on the earth, please allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to communicate with your lonely heart. And please let us feel your situation and its complications from the position of real children, and please let us shed tears when you shed tears. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who know how to go through difficulties together with you as you go through them.
\n\nFather! We have realized that our minds are unworthy; we have realized that our bodies are base; and we have realized that our ambitions are moving together with Satan.
\n\nWe, who have these kinds of internal elements, are miserable people who cannot wait for the lord who is coming, representing heaven, in a period, in an age, at a time that you permit. Therefore, please let us know how to lament over our pitiful selves, and please let us know how to lament over our pitiful families, our pitiful society, pitiful humankind, and pitiful heaven and earth.
\n\nSince the time has come when we must be redeemed before heaven and earth through our sorrowful hearts, oh Father, please open the doors of our minds.
\n\nFather, our hearts are in a position of not knowing how to and not being able to relate to your heart. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will remold our minds and bodies which are like this into beings that are able to be transformed by your heart and your external form.
\n\nPlease cast out any of the earthly concepts or ideologies we have insisted on until now which heaven cannot approve of. Please raise up the level of our original senses so that all those things can be transformed as yours alone, and please raise up the level of our consciences.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will please connect our hearts, let us be able to communicate with your heart, and let us communicate with heavenly circumstances.
\n\nPlease send billions and trillions of the saints in heaven, and sanctify the area around us, and awakening each of our hearts, please remold us through your powerful touch.
\n\nThen, together with the words of re-creation, please allow us to be able to receive characters of re-creation and we, who are beings of death, will be transformed into beings of life.
\n\nPlease let us greet the time of joy when we call you "Father" in glory, rejoicing and joy.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 14, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_16t">
We know that the greatest sorrows of humankind are: not having been able to form a relationship with your love, having lost our original consciences which could communicate with your heart, and not being able to harmonize our minds and bodies which would enable us to harmonize our consciences and your heart.
\n\nBecause of the Fall, our sense of being able to communicate with your heart left us, and our mind which could love all things through experiencing your heart was no longer with us. Therefore, Father, please guide us to be able to recover that heart. Please let our mind and body become one, and everything that is ours become yours. We earnestly hope and desire that you will work, Father, so that we will be able to place everything we have before you and, as people you can be proud of, we can open wide our arms of love with broad generous hearts which are able to embrace all of creation.
\n\nMy father: We know that we urgently need the word that will enable us to communicate with that kind of heart. What we have lost is the word, and next the substantiation of that word, and next the heart. Therefore, Father, through the word please raise up in us the original heart which was lost.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become people whose minds bow our heads to the original word, and whose bodies are able to lend their ears to the original word and who receive the grace of being able to be embraced in your bosom of glom.
\n\nBecause you are the one who started this work, we know that you are also the one who will accomplish it. And since it began through goodness, we know that it will be concluded through goodness. You have said that you are the Alpha and the Omega, the first and the last, and the beginning and the end. But because humankind lost the original heart in the beginning, when arriving at the end also, we cannot communicate with the heavenly heart. Now in the Last Days we should be clinging to the original heart and connecting to that heart. We earnestly hope and desire that you will bear with us who are languishing in the pits of the enmity of the fall.
\n\nPlease let us realize that our minds are not ours; they are yours, and please let us realize that our bodies are not ours; they are yours. We earnestly hope that you will allow us to be able to experience really and substantially the fact that our hearts and senses, none of these things belong to us; they belong to you and move through you.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 14, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_17t">
Father!
\nPlease allow us to experience heaven through our hearts. Please allow us to be able to experience the heart of our father which we cannot help but feel even if we don\'t want to. Father, please give us hearts that cannot help but repent before you even if we don\'t want to.
\n\nWe know that in places where people gather together with other people, things are solved and then become complicated again, but in places where people gather centered on heaven, the things that have formed knots in people\'s minds are solved. Now please raise up minds that are touched and that are able to long for the new day and reflect on ourselves and repent for the past through acts of inspiration, acts of repentance, and acts of indemnity which can solve fundamentally everything that has become tangled due to the tribes of evil. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow acts of re-creation to arise which will let us be able to repent for our selves having clung to that mind.
\n\nToday we are not longing for happiness of the body alone, and we do not want to live intoxicated by our minds alone. We desire only the garden where we can give our hearts the greatest value and live forever. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will please allow us to be able to form destined relationships which can exist deep in our hearts and that in our daily lives as well, the conditions for a heartistic destined relationship can explode out from each one\'s heart.
\n\nFather! On this holy day please pour down the grace of your blessings on all people. Representing the will and embracing your heart, appealing to heaven and raising up hidden altars, your sons and daughters who are praying know many things. Therefore, please bless them as well.
\n\nThis movement, which is embracing the lonely heart of heaven, and suffering with it, and even the many spirits of spirit world, who are awaiting the day of indemnified liberation, have a relationship with us. Therefore, Father, please allow their work also to have a good result through us. Please guide our inadequate selves who have not able to fulfill the level of heart that the Triune God who surrounds us is watching and longing for. Please establish us as beings of joy who are worthy of calling you "Father." If we have not yet received that kind of grace, we earnestly hope and desire that you will lead us at this time to become sons and daughters who, like gentle, humble children, attract your heart of mercy and compassion.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 5, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_18t">
Father!
\nWe went forth thinking that the path you were calling us on was not difficult, but we have realized that it is difficult, and we thought it was a path of joy, but now as we go along it, we realize that it has peak after peak of tears.
\n\nFather! If we are sorrowful, we want to be sorrowful holding on to you. We have realized that it is easy to be disappointed after holding on to people and feeling sorrowful, and we have realized that to go ahead and believe people is to be hurt. It is you who have not changed, Father. How joyful a time it must have been for Jesus to go to the mountain in order to hold you and weep!
\n\nWe want to become true son and daughters who know how to weep for our father, people who know how to hold on to you and weep, and who know the heart of our father who has first pioneered this path and raised up Jesus in front of humankind because the road of life is lonesome and lonely.
\n\nIf we have realized that before we felt any anguish, heaven has suffered everything unjustly, and been persecuted cruelly, and been beaten cruelly, then how can we excuse ourselves before heaven? Since we have realized that before heaven we have no condition to be sad centered on our own selves, please have mercy on your sons and daughters here who have been placed in that situation.
\n\nFather! We know that before we wept you wept first, and before we were struck, you were struck first. And we know that before anything happened to us, it happened to you first. And we know that before we were in pain you were in pain first, and we know that before we fell down, you fell down first.
\n\nKnowing that, though we silently head towards heaven again and again, discovering how inadequate we are, we bow our heads before heaven, and we wonder how much you must have longed for sons and daughters who can call you "Father." Please allow those kinds of feelings to move in our hearts, and when relating to this nation, when relating to the world, when relating to heaven, please let those kinds of feelings move us.
\n\nOnly when we are moved by those kinds of feelings can we say we have confident faith from the individual up to the world-level ideological realm. And in order to establish our own ideology, we know that we must be in the position of heaven with the greatest heart. Therefore, we earnestly ask you to please raise up our minds to be able to go forth and pioneer a path for this kind of environment.
\n\nWe earnestly ask and desire that you will allow us to become children who are able to critique our forlorn selves as we go along the road humankind must go, and live intoxicated by you, and bow our heads and raise up your glory, Father, assessing highly our having formed a relationship between ourselves and heaven.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 5, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_19t">
Father!
\nToday please allow all of our thoughts to move, our minds to move, and our bodies to move in the garden of your heart. We have realized that your heart is a heart of infinite love. And we have realized that your heart is an infinitely sorrowful heart and a heart that has been infinitely wounded.
\n\nOh Father, you have been exceedingly sorrowful; you have worked exceedingly hard, and even now your mind still feels exceedingly anxious! Please let us realize that you are the Creator, and you are the Lord of all things. Please let the extreme sorrow that you experience penetrate into our breasts, and please let your extraordinary anger and indignation flow into our breasts.
\n\nPlease let us become people who have experienced this, who are so submerged in sorrow that we cannot control our bodies and don\'t know where to go. And please let us become sons and daughters who weep, not knowing whether this is heaven or earth, unable to control our minds. We know that the altars of sorrow which continued for 6,000 years or more are due to the mistakes of our ancestors, but we are afraid that we might leave that sorrow to our descendents by once again not fulfilling our responsibility today.
\n\nToday, we have realized that we are responsible for blocking the history of misfortune in our present generation, and for saving the situation of the heart of heaven and changing it to a new heart of joy. Therefore, please allow us to share your heart.
\n\nThere are many people who look like people. But if we ask what is lacking on this earth and thereby makes heaven so sorrowful, we know that it is your having no sons or daughters who can communicate with your heart or who long for your love. Since we have realized that heaven is looking for such sons and daughters, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who offer our full devotion, and, giving our entire minds and bodies, are able to be recognized and to have no inadequacies in front of your heart.
\n\nWe do not want heaven to give us anything material, and we do not want heaven to understand our situation, and we do not want heaven to give us grace. More than that, please allow us to know the inner heart of our father who sought to celebrate after giving that grace. And we hope to become sons and daughters who are able to call our father who has been so sorrowful, "Father," and who are able to comfort our suffering father.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to make that our goal and not mind even a difficult path; who, even if the arrows of persecution and ridicule circle around our bodies, keep sincere hearts of devotion for our father; who are able to forget all these things and go closer towards heaven, and who are able to absorb that as internal advice.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 7, 1960
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_20t">
Until now we thought that you were a being of joy surrounded by glory. We thought that you were someone who would accomplish the goal and joy of liberation for us, and that you would give us blessings and wealth and prosperity in free supply.
\n\nBut now that we see behind the situation of heaven, we have realized that there are internal complications, so that even if you want to give blessings you cannot, and we know the solemn truth that the grief filled history of sorrow of 6,000 years must be restored through indemnity. Now that we have understood that kind of situation, please allow us to become people who lament the foolishness of humankind who have not been able to do that.
\n\nPlease let us know that you are a father who is coming to this people; that you are a father who is coming to the people of the world. We have understood that those footsteps are still soaked with tears of sorrow and there still remain walls of suffering for them. Today we will become the ramparts of our father\'s suffering, and become fortresses of his sorrow.
\n\nWe will embrace our father\'s unjust suffering and grief. We must become those who know how to fight shedding blood and tears along the road of the decisive battle with the enemy in order to fulfill completely that responsibility and that mission.
\n\nFather! Please let us be moved by the heart of heaven, and please let us become people who know how to struggle and hold on to hearts of love for humankind.
\n\nWe must become people who are able to embrace your heart, and look at things with tears even when we look and mountains and streams or when looking at the people of the world.
\n\nWe must become the individuals that you want, and establish the families that you want, and centered on those families, we will have to build the world of the idea that you want. We have understood that the larger the scope of the building is, the more tears and blood will have to be shed.
\n\nWe have understood that tears have to be shed in order to find individuals, in order to find families, and in order to find the people. When we look at this path through a human perspective, it is a depressing path, it is a path of anger, it is a path of suffering. But because it is a path you have walked, we know that is a complicated course that we must go and change to a path of joy, a path of gratitude, and a path of glory.
\n\nPlease let us consider it our pride to exhaust everything we have while attending you until the last day of our lives. We earnestly hope and desire that we will become those who can run this path to the end together with you. We earnestly hope that you will let us determine once again to become those who know how to sing your praises with tears in that kind of place.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 12, 1961
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_21t">
Oh Father of great love and exceeding goodness!
\nWe don`t dare think about how miserable the circumstances you have been in were or how mistreated you were or how great the wounds were to your heart and mind in order for you, our father who should be exceedingly glorious, to come to this sorrowful earth.
\n\nOh Father who established children of goodness, and imagined in your mind a heavenly kingdom of goodness, an ideal world of goodness, and longed for the day of hope! The more earnest that your mind was hoping to establish the day of hope through the human ancestors Adam and Eve, the more your mind would have wanted to love them, and the more responsibility you would have felt for that purpose, and the more your mind would have wanted to protect Adam and Eve.
\n\nWhen we look back on and think about the grief-filled history in which our human ancestors betrayed and turned away from your bosom of love and your protection, we are extremely regretful, extremely angry, and extremely resentful that we were born as the descendents of fallen ancestors.
\n\nOur minds and bodies have not been able to take off the yoke of sin, and swept away by the waves of death we have become those who should be destroyed in the pits of death without any room for argument.
\n\nThrough the dense course of history you have gone through so much suffering, worrying every day about us who are like that. Because your concern was great for the historical future of humankind, you have had a sorrowful mind, and you have followed the footsteps of us unworthy human beings. But we have come to know that you were not able to open your heart to anyone at any time, and we have come to know that you were not able to have any children who could comfort your heart at any time.
\n\nYou have gone a difficult course of restoration like this for 6,000 years! Now having reached the Last Days, you have gathered together on the Korean peninsula our pitiful and unworthy selves, to represent this people. Accordingly, we know that this relationship absolutely did not come about by chance. We have learned through the word and have received evidence through reality, but we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will let us realize the frightening truth that if we are not able to absorb the word and the evidence as our own, the word and the evidence will come to judge us.
\n\nOh Father who has gathered together this Unification Movement! We know that the misery of your toil along the road of history cannot be expressed. Please do not let us forget even in our dreams your earnest heart and your situation as you gather this unworthy, weak group together and, promising us a day of victory, push us out on the path of suffering.
\n\nPlease let us keep that deep in our minds even in difficult situations; and in sad situations, please let us become sons and daughters who are able to think first of our father who is shedding sorrowful tears. Even if we fall into bleak and miserable situations, we earnestly hope and pray; Father, that you will not let us become sons and daughters who forget the miserable heart of our father who has gone the path of the cross.
\n\nWe know that two thousand years ago the Prince of Heaven, the Savior of all humankind, the Messiah whom you sent to this earth lived in sorrow and died. When he was born, you were concerned as he was born, and while he was growing up, you were concerned as he grew up, too. And we know that along the course of his public ministry representing you, he confronted enemies along the road of persecution and took responsibility and went the course of suffering.
\n\nWe know that things were that way because our ancestors could not fulfill their responsibilities. Since we have found out the nature of all the historical crimes, please do not let us forget that we have the entire responsibility to establish reality on the earth and to relieve the grief of history.
\n\nPlease do not let us forget that the lamentations of the past are urging us forward, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will not let us forget that you want to give through us whom you established first in order to let people know the mission of the age.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMay 3, 1964
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_22t">
Who has understood your heart, and who has understood your situation, and who has understood your hope when you could not help but go forth enduring days of sorrow as you groped your way through the long history filled with grief? Please allow us to feel once again at this time how much sympathy we should have for you, Father. You have been relating to people who haven`t known about the heart and will you alone carried in your breast, the situation you faced alone, or your mind which you alone knew, and you have worked so hard in order to find one child who could be taught that hope, situation, and heart.
\n\nPlease let us understand that you, our father, are not someone unrelated to us; rather, you are the father we shall live together with for eternity. And you are not someone who should have to work hard; you are the Lord who created the entire universe. Oh Father, we must become children who know how to feel deeply indignant over the fact that the one who should be embracing and loving the entire universe left behind those kinds of historical complications.
\n\nWhen we consider the fact that the one mistake of our ancestors became a sin which cannot be permitted even after billions of generations, we ask you to let the people here realize that there is no way to repay this even by shedding all their blood and tears, and there is no way to repay this even by sacrificing their lives ten million times.
\n\nFather! Where is the person who says he knows you, where is the person who says he will accomplish your Will, and where is the person who will dedicate his life and go forth for you? When we realize that there is no one, we who have gathered here, even though we are a pitiful and unworthy group, have determined to be loyal to you. And since we are a group which has pledged to offer our lives for you, we earnestly hope and desire that if there are any who are exhausted, you will increase their strength, and if there are any who are disappointed, you will hold on to them.
\n\nWe have been ravaged by the enticements of the enemy, and we have inexpressibly pathetic situations in the sorrowful history of the past. Please do not let us become people who forget all those hearts filled with grief. Please do not allow us to become people who forget your grief and your sorrow. We earnestly hope that you will let us become your children who can appear as victors who without fail will return glory to our Father when you judge this world of sin.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 26, 1965
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_23t">
Even the hearts of parents of the fallen world feel more love in their minds after spurring on their children than they felt before spurring them on, and want to comfort them. But please let us understand how greatly your heart desired to comfort us when we were beaten and driven away from the place where you commanded us to take responsibility along the course of restoration.
\n\nAnd please do not let us forget that it is your mind to want to let us praise you eternally in the world of heart. You want to establish us as filial children who are able to comfort our father and call you "Father" in such a place.
\n\nUntil now the course of the Unification Church has been a sorrowful course. I know very well how solitary were the footsteps of those following your commands in the midst of other people who were unable to understand.
\n\nHow hard you must have worked until this religious body could be mobilized and this unification movement gathered! We know that you urged and encouraged the people who were playing, and awakened the people who were dozing, and commanded them to go. Please let us determine ourselves even now in the midst of such adverse circumstances. We understand that you are still in a situation of having to send us out.
\n\nWe know that this kind of anguish will remain as the universal history of the course of indemnity. Please let us understand that you must command the individual who sets the family in good order, the family that sets the tribe in good order, the tribe that sets the people in good order, the people that sets the nation in good order, and the nation that sets the world in good order, to go out in their stead.
\n\nAnd please let us know how miserable your position is as you look upon the course of restoration that remains and the course of bitter indemnity which cannot help but be gone through along that path.
\n\nWe understand your heartbroken mind which is not able to command anyone even if you wish to because there is no filial child who is able to understand your position. Please let us become your true children who now follow your bidding and go towards the goal, who prepare ourselves before your command, and who are able to call you "Father."
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 3, 1966
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_24t">
My Father!
\nI know that you, Father - I am calling out to you - have been so wretched.
\n\nFather! The great majority of humankind understand that you are clothed in glory, you are ruling for ten thousand years, and are held in glory as you proclaim that you love all people, and all humankind want to be held to the breast of such a father, and want to cling to such a father.
\n\nUntil now that has been the ambition of humankind. But the father that the Unification Church members are clinging to has been a father who has endured going forth gritting his teeth, looking towards a future of hope day and night in the very center of the point of death. The hope that Unification believers are longing for is to shed the tears of your painful heart, holding your hand which has been wounded along the path of thorns and the path of so much suffering and so many false charges.
\n\nNo matter what anyone of the world says, our image and prestige are not the problem. We must become a group who know for sure how to go to that point gratefully even if our bodies are ripped apart and our dignity trampled upon, even when your laws of the family, become crumpled, and clouds cover everything before your Will.
\n\nWe earnestly hope that you will not allow us to become a group that forgets how much you have struggled to find and establish this kind of group inside the Unification Movement.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 6, 1966
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_25t">
We cannot help but report to you once again at this time that we are ashamed before our father who has worked so hard in order to realize the Will. The providence that you manage should have been a providence of glory, and you should have watched your sons and daughters enjoying themselves in the garden of goodness, and you should have lived a life of rejoicing and joy. But because of the totally unexpected fall, your providence could not become a providence of joy; it became a providence of sorrow, suffering, and lamentation. Oh Father, who could not help but carry out this kind of providence!
\n\nAt this time before you, our unworthy selves which became the motive and source of such a providence cannot help but repent for our historical guilt, and we cannot help but repent for the guilt of the present age. And we know that there still remains the will of the providence for which, on the foundation of having repented with our heads bowed, we must ask for blessings for the sake of the world of the future so hoped for by our father, who is imagining and carrying out the providence for the world of eternal peace.
\n\nWhen looking at things from the viewpoint of the relationship between you and us, between us and the creation, and between you and the creation, we know that there is not a single thing that was created separate from your heart of love. We know that the kind of relationship where we could communicate with your heart through our destined relationship of eternal father and son with you was broken from the day we fell, and heaven as heaven, humankind as humankind, and the things of creation as the things of creation all lost the goal they were to head for, and until now have remained in the realm of lamentations.
\n\nOh Father of love! You have not been able to cast off the grief of the fall or the troubles of the fall, and you know well the situation of we who are groping along the path of our miserable fate. In order to permit the blessings of today, you prepared for thousands of years of history. But when we look at our state, we know that at the same time that we must receive your permission, we also have a great responsibility to have to establish the level of the blessing.
\n\nThe time has come that now we must find again all the heartistic relationships that have divided heaven and humankind, and we know that the time has come that it will not do unless all people relate to each other and the broken, destined relationships of heart which are able to sing praises to heaven are formed once again.
\n\nAnd not only that, we should have realized the harmony of all things, taking the things of creation as materials for a life of faith, as conditional objects of victory, and as conditional objects of harmony in the eternal realm of relationships, but we cannot help but lament over the loss of all the things of creation.
\n\nFather of mercy! There are many groups wandering around looking for relationships of heart, but there are very few groups that know what your heart is like. We earnestly hope and desire that you will once again embrace humankind who are going the way of restoration without knowing your heart, tormented in the world of darkness.
\n\nFather! This day is a holy day. At this time please bless your sons and daughters who have gathered here having decided and determined to follow the footprints you have left and not to avoid this path of grief-filled destiny. We are people who have pledged to offer everything we have as sacrifices before you, looking forward to the time of victory promised in your Will. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will let us become sons and daughters who head towards the goal of that Will, who step onto the field of battle, and sing the victory song, and who are not able to yield or be defeated until your glory is raised up.
\n\nOn this holy day, please give your blessing to all the people, and we earnestly hope and desire that today you will connect the many groups, many peoples, and many multitudes in each place to this relationship heaven has sought.
\n\nSince we know that it is the heart of the Triune God to want to resolve the grief of restoration in order to reconnect the destined relationships which were broken, please complete restoration on that foundation of heart. And beginning from our own selves our families, people, nation, world, up to everything in heaven and on earth, we anticipate that heartistic relationships will be formed, and even though we are disloyal and unworthy, we have bowed our heads before you, Father. And since we cannot help but offer prayers of tears before you, Father, please bear with us.
\n\nFather, we earnestly ask you to create relationships between everything according to the criteria of the providence.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nApril 10, 1960
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_26t">
I have gone forward experiencing the position of sorrow and feeling the heart with which you have faced this world of enemies. I know the sorrow of my father who could not come out and live in the sunshine, and the situation of my father who has worked in the shadows. Until today I have gone forward in that kind of life worried that I might become a child who resents his father or who contradicts his father at some point.
\n\nAnd I know that when you found me, you too were worried that I might be like that. You are more anguished than I am, Father, and I know that you are preparing the path you will go feeling your responsibility from a more difficult position than I am in. I have determined not to despair or to disappoint you, even if I go through being pursued and driven out, or imprisoned with both my hands in handcuffs, or experience the lot of a slave or the lot of a servant. I thank you for your grace of letting me not die and remain in your presence from the time that I determined to do that until now.
\n\nHow much have you worked, Father, in order to establish someone like this? How much have you sacrificed for the sake of the path I must go, for the sake of the family I must go to? How much have you worked for the sake of the tribe I must lead, and how much have you worked for the sake of the people and the nation I must teach and lead?
\n\nAnd how much have you worked for the sake of the world that this people and this nation must teach?
\n\nEver since I realized that you work far more than the blood in our veins and arteries which moves without stopping 24 hours a day, each time I awakened from sleep I could not help but beg you to forgive me as though I were a sinner. While eating, I could not help but put down my spoon and with tears ask for forgiveness for my wrongs of the past, and each time I lay down, not being able to control my tired body, I could not help but scold myself for not being able to have a mind that was concerned abut you. Please look compassionately on my past life which has been like that.
\n\nHow much humiliation you must have suffered up until now in order to eliminate so many enemies! How many times you must have suffered unjustly! How hard you must have worked in order to raise up in this way struggling groups, miserable groups which are driven out and pursued in the midst of sighs and screams on the path of death! How much you must have worked to lead us into an age when we could raise our heads and look up while relating to the people, the nation and the world! We must not become people who, even if we go through the grief of dying thousands or ten thousands of times, forget the fact that until we became as we are now, your internal sorrow has been great.
\n\nWhen we consider everything centered on the internal sorrow, of the heavenly side, we see that you are a being to be pitied. However much we might say that fellow named Moon of the Unification Church is to be pitied, it is nothing. I have realized how much you are to be pitied. However much we might say the children following the Unification Church today are to be pitied, we know that their sorrow cannot be compared to your sorrow, Father.
\n\nWhen we think of such things, we cannot accept your excessive grace, and we come to realize that we are people who must request forgiveness for our sins through minds to be pitied, who must straighten ourselves up a thousand, ten thousand times, and bow to you a thousand, ten thousand times.
\n\nWhen we become people like that, I know that we will not be ruined. Please let us realize that a path centered on ourselves is a path that will ruin us, and a path where we sacrifice ourselves for the world and the nations, and for our tribe and the people of the free world is a path that will resurrect us.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who know that you are preparing a realm of resurrection that is greater than what we have sacrificed, and who are able to have minds that are brave and of good courage and go directly towards the enemy.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 29, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_27t">
Oh Father!
\nPlease break all the arrows of evil that have flown our way until now. Since we do not consider the people sending them enemies, we earnestly hope that you will please forgive them.
\n\nWhen we consider that results of goodness should appear because the way you are going is good, we know that for that to happen, forgiveness and magnanimity must be substantially manifested. Because you are the fountainhead of love, we earnestly desire that you will please forgive through your infinite love and magnanimity the many religious people of this nation for their past acts of persecution against the children of the Unification Movement.
\n\nAlthough we were knocking on the door of unification, while on the way pioneering this difficult path of tears, this path of persecution, there are people who became exhausted and fell away because they could not meet even one person who could comfort them. And I know that many of the people going this way are exhausted.
\n\nI know that the fact that we are at a point where members are leaving and are exhausted is due more to not possessing the environment than to our own wrongdoing. Therefore, when we think of them asking for forgiveness with their heads bowed towards you on the streets here and there and in the situations they are facing today; our hearts which want to relieve your grief-filled heart are angry and can hardly endure, but if we think about the merciful path of restoration through which you have been seeking the children of the enemy, we know you cannot help but bless them again, holding back your tears. Therefore, we earnestly ask you to please forgive them.
\n\nPlease allow our true selves which are able to harmonize with goodness itself to be revealed through our minds and bodies, and as original children who were good, please allow only goodness to be reflected in our minds which long for the glory of your amazing original nature, the beautiful original nature. We earnestly ask that you will please allow this time to become one in which we long to become sons and daughters who are able to call you "Father," who have true attitudes through those kinds of hearts, who believe all things, and who become substantial beings who pursue goodness alone.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 28, 1969
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_28t">
Father!
\nWe have come to realize that the path you are going is a path of suffering we cannot even imagine; it is a path of humiliation; it is a path of grief-filled restoration.
\n\nEven though we often think centered on ourselves, each time we discover that we have hesitated to think centered on you, Father, we come to determine that we will have to have sympathy for your lonely situation of having to save not only individuals, but individuals connected to families, societies, nations and the world.
\n\nWhen we think that what you are longing for in relation to our world is the country you have hoped for, the people you have hoped for, the family you have hoped for, and the many people you have hoped for, we feel that you have a mind to embrace all of humankind and to love them like the people of one nation.
\n\nWe are individuals, but going beyond the individual we will have to long for the family which you are seeking, and going beyond the family, the tribe, going beyond the tribe, the people, going beyond the people, the nation, and going beyond the nation we will have to long for even the world. We must determine once again to become people who know how to follow the example of your holy mind and self which are seeking everyone from the individual up to the world, and we must always know how to look up to that standard of longing.
\n\nWe must not become people who are like lifeless sticks and stones, and who do not even know how to lament over how pitiful we are when we are like that. If we have feelings and emotions in our minds, we must become sons and daughters who know how to experience and squarely face the fact that you have come to us like this with an amazing content.
\n\nEven when we go through difficulties we must realize that we are not alone in the midst of them; rather, you are there together feeling lonely. And even when we experience sorrow, we must feel that we are not alone in our sorrow; rather, you are together with us in sorrow. And even if we end up alone in a position of anger and unjust suffering, we must feel that you are in that kind of position, too.
\n\nWe must realize that this is the mind felt by people going the path of filial piety, and the mind that can be possessed by sons seeking the position of filial sons. That is why you have stressed a faith based on experience. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to experience once again at this time that we need daily lives in which day by day we experience and learn through the course of our emotions that you are alive.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 5, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_29t">
Beloved Father!
\nWe know that the Unification Church has remained up to this point due to your love. We have wrestled with the problem of how to apply the principle of love to the circumstances of our daily lives and how to apply it to the course of indemnity. In that there was sorrow, there was suffering, there was mistreatment, and there was misery, but when love appeared and love was realized all those things turned into praise.
\n\nWe know that the Unification Church has remained until now because those incidents became stimulating things to be remembered, and because we have lived a history in which we could absorb those things as things to be grateful for. From the day that this child standing here came to know about the inner realities of history no one else knew about, I have believed in this way, and while going this way, and while achieving things, I have fought and offered everything because of your love, and for the sake of your love.
\n\nAnd I come to feel that it is all due to your love that we have this kind of substantial foundation today and that we are able to stand today having a mind that, while standing in the anguished position of the vanquished, relates to the world and the cosmos not with lamentation and disappointment, but rather with a mind that on the contrary relates to the world and the cosmos as objects of hope and wants to love them more.
\n\nWe know that everything exists because of the purpose of love, and everything moves because of love. But in order to increase love, we must become people who know how to prepare an original attitude in which we see, feel, move and go forward on our own. We do not know whether something starting because of us and occurring because of us will become the Kingdom of Heaven for the nation or ourselves, but when we consider that it could not be the Kingdom of Heaven for God and humankind, please allow us to understand that that kind of place could not help but be a place that is separated from heaven and close to hell.
\n\nTherefore, in the world of faith, arrogance has been considered an enemy; stubbornness has been considered an enemy; insisting on an independent position has been considered an enemy. We earnestly hope that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to apply all these works and traditions of the heartistic principle in our lives and clearly realize that this alone is the reason for having taught that God is love, and God's sons and daughters are love.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJune 1, 1973
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_30t">
In this historical age of great grief while not knowing what you were like, this unworthy son discovered you, and from the day that I came to know you, the days have continued into days where I have not been able to stop the tears from flowing from my eyes. I rushed forward grateful for having become like that, and now I have reached my old age and am nearly 70.
\n\nIn the prime of my life I burned up all the vitality I had, and attended heaven, and the time to return glory to heaven passed. Since the day I was driven out as one rejected by the people, as a rebel against humanity, I thank you that you have let the Unification Church endure and go forward until now through the heavenly principle of being struck without saying anything and then taking things back.
\n\nI, too, had not known this, and as a man with a character which doesn`t like to lose to anyone, when I reflect again on the historical age in which I could have struck at and punished my persecutors, I came to know you who are so expansive and great and who have endured in the midst of situations of anger and indignation.
\n\nHaving followed that relationship and aspect of yours I have come forward to this point today. But each time I think of pitiful heaven, because I know how many tearful, incredible situations there have been, I thank you today for having come over peak after peak of that difficult path.
\n\nFather! You were love. You, who put me behind steel bars, prepared for me the standard of a situation filled with joy, and when I think that it was in order to give me a position of inheritance in order to give me blessings, now that it is over, I see that everything was love, and was the touch of your expansive generosity. 1 offer gratitude when I think of that.
\n\nWe have offered up everything in this prayer in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nApril 17, 1987
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_31t">
Father!
\nCommitting historical sin, humankind has driven such nails into your heart, and has wounded your pride and your personality in ways that are unforgivable. But in spite of that, you have gone forward alone with your lonely heart, unable to express your views about your situation to anyone at all. And in spite of the fact that you should have walked in heaven and earth as your lands of joy, it has been your situation to have walked on lands of sorrow and grief throughout the days of history. Now, however, a small, unworthy group on this earth has come to know your situation.
\n\nIn order to straighten out the false history, you went forth to find the people of Israel, and no one has known the sorrowful grief that heaven carried in its heart during the 2,000 year period from Noah to Jacob. No one has known your heart as you watched the point of the hidden providence in the midst of the adverse situation of the struggle which came about centered on Jacob and Esau, and your heart which had to grope for the way to live for 20 years as you braced your heart against the cutting pain.
\n\nJacob followed your resolute heart and offered his mind to you. We underwent all kinds of hardships and privations, and after 21 years, on his course back to his homeland, he left behind signs of the providence. This became one of the bases for being able to bring the fortune of restoration into history. And we think that in the midst of that, our father who had set forth to find the people of Israel was able to have a day of hope.
\n\nThen we know that centered on the 12 tribes of Israel, having gone through 2,000 years of history in order to save humankind who were in the world of Satan once again at a blood-curdling price, you raised and put the chosen people of Israel in the position of sacrifices.
\n\nBut you silently raised the people of Israel, and it was the mission of Judaism to dedicate itself to you, and even though they did not know how immense their mission was in relation to history, looking to them you sent the messiah. When we think about your mind which anticipated the time of restoration, no one has realized how regrettable that 4,000-year history was.
\n\nFather! Jesus could not help but be born in circumstances that could not communicate with the human situation from a position of not knowing his father, from a position of not being able to appear to anyone. In the midst of miserable circumstances, the life of Jesus, who had to keep himself under control, was lonely in a way only you knew. We know that it was a very lonely path.
\n\nJesus birth should have been greeted with glory by the people, and in the midst of all history, should have consisted of days of glory such as no prince of the evil world had ever had. Until now we had no idea how very difficult it must have been for you to endure the pain in your heart about the unforgivable, rash behavior of Israel which changed that hope of glory to lamentation and despair.
\n\nAs for the course he walked carrying the cross towards the top of Golgotha, stumbling was not the sorrowful thing; rather it was the wounding of your Will. No one has known that the greater burden of Jesus was dying without fulfilling his duty and having become a child who could not help but pound nails in your heart.
\n\nThe grief-filled path of Jesus who left behind this kind of historical mission became a path trod by the footsteps of humankind together with blood. And when we think of the historical ages, Christian history paid that price, shedding blood desolately in the midst. of persecution for 400 years. We have come to realize the fact that the mistake of one day of that people not welcoming the Messiah has remained in this world like this, and it will not do unless it is indemnified.
\n\nWe know that it would not do unless the people of Israel became fertilizer for this land together with Jesus, and it would not do unless many people were ridiculed and condemned, and it would not do unless they became people who died alone without other people knowing.
\n\nNo one has known your heart as you sought the day of promise about which Jesus said, "I will come again," and which was the day you hoped for while going through 2,000 years of history. And no one has known your heart as you sought to choose that day which must be realized centered on the many Christian nations spread throughout the world.
\n\nWhen we think that you who are like that came to the Korean peninsula, this pitiful Korea, we realize that no one knew the fact that you worked so hard in order to raise up this nation, or that while as a pitiful people, the Korean people were going through a lonely course of history the likes of which has never existed, you left here a destined relationship with your heart.
\n\nIn regard to the short historical period during which they received the Christian culture, this Korean people, who had to fulfill a world level mission in Asia, walked a path of anguish. And as for the course of repeated trials these days, we know that the Korean people are struggling and groping their way along the path of suffering and the way of death, and have shouldered the destiny of the pitiful history because they have shouldered your inner reality which must indemnify horizontally all the vertical things of the historical ages.
\n\nWe have come to realize that while others didn't know, you have groped for the destined relationship of a lineage of life, and you worked so very, very hard in order to establish today's relationship of unification, and you looked forward to and searched for that relationship very, very much.
\n\nFather, now we will straighten ourselves up, and for the sake of your will we earnestly hope that you will let us once again steady our minds, which must decide and determine to become faithful servants in relation to the Will you have desired for millions of years.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 1, 1973
    </string>

    <string name="pr_serdca_32t">
Beloved Father!
\nWe know the regrettable fact that you were not able to able to accomplish your great work of creation on the earth. We know that the mistake of Adam and Eve has brought you sorrowful and indignant grief. You have been in the forefront working to greet the day when that indignant grief can be resolved.
\n\nAnd thinking again that you have gone forth leading and sacrificing many of our good ancestors, we thank you for the grace of your having accomplished that will of establishing a relationship with True Parents centered on the Unification Church, here in this land of Korea, after having gone through a long history for the sake of the earth.
\n\nThe son and daughter who are here, these two people were called by you; they were equal to the responsibility, and stand in this position. When we retrace in our memories the heart of our Father who went through so much suffering during the grief-filled course of restoration, we know well about your grievous truth about the time Adam and Eve, who are the ancestors of humankind, made a mistake.
\n\nThirty years have passed since I connected to that heart and looked back on the path where heaven was betrayed, and since the time I began to follow the will of heaven. Only you know the painful position of the internal circumstances of heart which began in your heart and have come as far as my heart today and which during that time I could not express to anyone and could not tell anyone.
\n\nWe thank you when we think of the amazing fact that this day, May 1, 1975, is the very day of hope which somehow goes beyond the limit of the people and releases your grief, and resolves the grief of the day of misfortune when Jesus, who had come to the earth, died on the cross.
\n\nWe have reached a dividing point in time marking the 21st year since founding Headquarters, and completing the second 7-year course of the course of indemnity for world Christianity. When considered centered on this son of yours, it is a time period completing 30 years of history. We are awe-stricken when we think about the fact that all of these have been obtained through your mathematical course of restoration.
\n\nFather! We know that your sorrow was great on that day when you faced the fallen ancestors of humankind; as was your sorrow when you had sent Jesus intending to realize your hope, but had to deliver him to the cross; and your sorrow when the many Christians who followed your son were slaughtered; and beyond that your sorrow seeing all the people sacrificed along the way even though it wasn`t clear while they worshipped heaven as the many collateral religions struggled along the path of sacrifice.
\n\nAll of the angels in the angelic world, who should have cooperated at the level of perfection of Adam and Eve, and standing in a midway position representing your righteousness and your name in back of these religions, have been in the pathetic position of not having been able to do so. They have been acting in concert together with your mind and together with your will.
\n\nNow, oh Father: we realize on our own that we are the beings of the True Parents and the family of the True Parents which you sought, we offer this day and this one son and this one daughter to you. And since the children centered on this son and daughter are here in this place and at East Garden, Father, please receive them. We thank you that you have allowed us to have a day we can offer to you on the foundation of this people and nation, centered on the family before you at this time, and to complete the resolution of the grief over the foundation which was lost centered on the family.
\n\nOh, Father, You also know that the complications of the angelic world became greater due to the fall of the family. Therefore, please allow this day to become one in which through resolving the grief of your mind, you resolve the grief of the mind of the True Parents, and are able to resolve the grief of the angels as well.
\n\nThrough the grief of God, True Parents, and the angelic world being resolved, please connect Christianity centered on Jesus which is connected behind True Parents, Confucianism and Confucius, Buddhists and Buddha, Muslims and Mohammed, and beyond them please connect the religions which have internally controlled the backgrounds of the many peoples spread throughout the entire world.
\n\nThis ceremony is the resolution of your grief; it is the resolution of True Parents grief; it is the resolution of the grief of the angelic world. We thank you that you have allowed today`s ceremony to become a ceremony in which all the religious people on the earth are able to have this kind of destined relationship and to resolve their grief.
\n\nDue to having a realm of the resolution of the grief of religions, now people who are able to praise you and establish the sovereign authority of your nation have appeared. And beyond that, conscientious men of society and men of philosophy, and the good kings, civil officials, and military officers of the nations, while those nations were on the course heading to the good kingdom of heaven, became good kings and loyal patriots to their nations, although their situations and environments were different.
\n\nCentered on their peoples they became saints and sages, and became people of conscience. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow this day to become the day of the resolution of their grief which they awaited impatiently but didn`t know how to reach until now.
\n\nNow, heaven has found the parents it was looking for; has brought about the liberation of the angelic world; has brought about the liberation of the world of religion; and has brought about the liberation of the good kings and good emperors and loyal patriots of the world of the conscience. But we know that beyond that there remains the pitiful Cain world which opposed the conscience, opposed religion, and opposed heaven until now.
\n\nIf we recollect history, we see that centered on the messiah from Judas Iscariot and the Emperor Nero down through the communist party today, people have betrayed heaven. Today at this time we have possessed a victorious destined relationship in the cosmos, and at this time of the complete resolution of grief, when we realize the fact that at the place of the judgment of heaven we cannot just sweep them up and throw them away, please let us form our destined relationships even with them through your name with the sacred, universal, victorious authority you established in the name of the True Parents.
\n\nAnd since it will not do unless you let us feel our way to a path that is able to contribute to the many conscientious people and many religions and to True Parents, oh Father, please allow us to do that eternally.
\n\nPlease allow us to reach the point of loving our enemies, even though they were the enemies of enmity who pierced your heart with nails, who killed your son Jesus, and who killed many of your beloved people. Please open the doors of heaven and earth, and please reach out with your heart and mind of magnanimous love. We know that because of liberating them, the doors of hell will be opened, and the way to abolish hell will gradually be paved.
\n\nPlease let this become a time when all the people of the Cain realm who are standing in the realm of such benefits, and the good spirits, and God's sons and daughters pledge their loyalty. And just as though they had shed blood and followed along the path of death, please let them turn back and raise the standard of revolt against the evil world and pledge loyalty to heaven. Please let them control all the spirits of the evil world, and control the evil people, and please let this become a time for them to pledge to go to the world that God wants, the world that you want.
\n\nThrough this we seek to grant a special benefit from you. Therefore, we hope that this will become a time when with joyful hearts the entire realm of evil which is spread throughout the entire world under the control of' evil spirits will now bow its head before the realm of God's dominion, before the True Parents, before the world of good angels, before the good religious people, and before the good kings and people of conscience. We hope that they will determine to do the work they should do in their place, and in pioneering the good domain of heaven that they will pledge to fulfill their responsibility before heaven and you, Father.
\n\nOh Father of love! We earnestly hope that you will accomplish at this time today the prayer that Jesus prayed while offering his life on the way of the cross. The True Parents who are standing here have also gone through a history of having received opposition nationwide for 30 years from this people, world Christianity, and the many people of the satanic world.
\n\nBut I do not consider them enemies. Even a shadow that is for the sake of unfolding completely the duties of your heavenly morality, when I think about the fact that that shadow cannot exist separate from a real being, we have going forth fighting until now as True Parents, from a position of being like shadows which follow real beings with generous love; therefore, please release all the unjust suffering we went through during that time. Oh Father, please bear with us, and we earnestly hope that you will release the knots in your heart and realize at this time, Father, what Jesus wanted.
\n\nWe know that as Jesus passed away on the path of death, he too had enmity in his heart which he alone knew internally. Please release that heart, too, and we know that unless what Jesus prayed for his enemies is accomplished on the earth, you, too, will not be able to be liberated. Therefore, please let Jesus be liberated at this time, and just as you let Christianity be liberated at this time, please let all beings that exist be liberated centered on you, Father.
\n\nSince we offer at this time in the name of the True Parents all the things of creation and, of course, humankind, the world of the angels, and even the many evil spirits under the command of Lucifer in the world of Satan, as yours, Father, we earnestly hope that you will receive them. At this time may all the billions of saints attending you in the spirit world there, and all the many good religious people who belong as your assistants centered on the 24 elders, resolution of grief in your name.
\n\nTherefore, together with the words of this proclamation, all the beings of the entire universe can adapt to the laws of heaven, and will have to adapt to the wishes of heaven. Since all nations will have to do that, all people will have to do that, all the spirit world will have to do that, the good spirits will also have to do that, and the good people will also have to do that; and since at this time we are seeking to open the way for even the people who had been evil to adapt to service at their own level within the realm of benefit of being able to do that, and through the results attained to be able to return to your embrace, please give your hearty approval.
\n\nBecause of that from now we will have a ceremony to achieve those kinds of conditions, so lather, please pour out you love with a happy mind and heart, and now send out your power and hold up goodness and press down evil. And now due to evil submitting itself to goodness, please allow in relation to the original Eden the restoration through indemnity centered on Cain and Abel to be accomplished through this people and the world.
\n\nBecause of that, now the communist world is bowing its head before the road heaven is going, and we earnestly hope that you will soon have the day when they can accept your banner of victory.
\n\nNow since I proclaim this work mobilizing all the good spirit people in the name of God and the angelic world, and in the name of the True Parents, to support and establish this centered on God, the many spirit worlds will be mobilized and all people of conscience will be mobilized!
\n\nToday at this time the entire spirit world is watching; the entire angelic world is watching; God is watching; the True Parents are watching; many Christian Churches on earth and many other religions are watching; many good nations and virtuous, loyal patriots are watching; many sons are watching; and even the communist world is watching here. Since we hope to offer this day to be completely embraced by you, Father, please accept it. We earnestly ask you to please accept these ceremonies in order as the foundation for your spirit and your victory.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMay 1, 1975
    </string>
</resources>