<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="pr_restoration_1t">
Father!
\nWe did not know that we are living lives that are creating debts to the world of creation while living in the fallen world, and that we are in the position of people who are indebted to each other even among the couples in the family.
\n\nWe did not know that we are in the position of indebted people in relation to our parents, also, and we did not know that it goes without saying that we are greatly indebted to you, the eternal God, as well.
\n\nEven if we look at it from the viewpoint of the fallen world, we are indebted people who rightly deserve to die; we are indebted in relation to the things of creation, and we have been people who are indebted also in relation to Jesus Christ who established the concept of the bride and the bridegroom.
\n\nWe are people who should repay our debts while representing the love of the eternal God, but without knowing that we should repay those debts, we worried and lamented centered on ourselves alone, we were people who cursed the earth, who cursed the things of creation, and who cursed heaven.
\n\nIn order to reestablish these kinds of human beings, Jesus struggled without minding even the way of death, and he was crucified on the cross. Because of that, the struggle of two thousand years in order to repay the debt formed in relation to heavenly morality has still not been resolved, and the word "judgment" came to remain.
\n\nPlease allow us to be able to settle all the debts made throughout the course of history so that we may go over the peak of judgment. Please allow us to understand that we can stand before our eternal Father only if we become people who are more than able to repay all those debts.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you still quickly lead us into lives through which we are able to repay our debt to the life that you desire, our debt to your love, by having cast off the conditions of the satans, as people who have repaid our debt to the True Parents, who have repaid our debt to the true couples, and who have repaid our debt to the true things of creation.
\n\nPlease allow the battle being fought in heaven with Satan to be brought to victory through us on earth, and please let the works being done in heaven be realized on earth. And we earnestly ask and desire that you will please allow us to become your eternal children who feel the love of our eternal Father as joy and glory.
\n\nAnd we earnestly request that you will establish us as your true sons and daughters who are able to take dominion with dignity over all the things of creation as your beloved children who are not ashamed in relation to you, to Jesus and the Holy Spirit, to the many saints and sages, in relation to all the people on the earth, and in relation to all the things of creation.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 10, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_2t">
We, who have been tormented by death, have longed for you and have gathered again today. Now please allow our minds to be able to dwell in your mind. And please let our minds and bodies be able to move as yours.
\n\nYou did not avoid endless toil, and you must have gone through so much effort in order to accompany our ancestors while going through each age and each century, and you must have toiled so much in order to pioneer the way of our ancestors! Please pardon that, in spite of that, our ancestors trampled upon the achievements of the hard work of heaven, and were people without honor, who have caused you to have a heart of concern.
\n\nWe know that the sin committed by our ancestors has remained as the grief of thousands of years, and due to the grief-filled act of the fall, so many people have been driven into misery for six thousand years.
\n\nWe are afraid that we might inherit once again the minds held by our historical ancestors who betrayed your heart and caused you grief. We are faced with the Last Days, when it will not do unless we tread upon and go beyond the grief left by our ancestors and unless we go over the peak of grief due to the fall. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow our minds to be captured by your mind, and that you will allow a time of glory in which our bodies are able to represent your body.
\n\nWho is the person who will fight representing your heart, the person who will shed tears and appeal having united with your heart? There are many people living on this earth. And the human beings who are alive have many different shapes, but there are very few people who know that you are a Father who has gone repeatedly through a history of sorrow and lamentation because there was not a single person who could be an object partner with whom you could discuss and share, to your heart\'s content, the heart that you have had in your breast. Since we know the kind of lonely, greatly indignant inner situation of your heart, please let this become a time today in which you are able to open your mind and engraft everything as yours.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 5, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_3t">
We know that the historical course of heaven is the historical course to straighten things out. And we have come to know that in relation to the historical course that heaven is straightening out, multitudes of invisible satans are acting in opposition in order to entangle things.
\n\nPlease let us realize that although we have said that history is a history to straighten things out, there is also the aspect of acts which are entangling things, the entangling of things by the world that opposes us, in order to keep us from going to a new place again.
\n\nWe are facing an environment where the history of sorrow for the sake of entangling things and the history of joy for the sake of straightening things out are at a crossroads. We are in the realm of lamentation where our bodies are looking forward to things being entangled, and our minds are looking forward to things being straightened out.
\n\nWe are looking towards the final stop of the sorrowful history where we must have a time of joy in which our bodies are subjugated to our minds by raising up our minds and striking our bodies. Please do not let us forget that we are people like this; please do not let us forget that we are in this kind of realm of heavenly destiny, and please do not let us forget that we are standing on the course that is for the resolution of this kind of providence of restoration.
\n\nAmong the people who do not know you today, there are people who hope to be tied to a concept, and there are people who want their consciences and bodies to be tied to an ideology, a thought, or to human morality. But please let us know that when we consider them through the original nature, they are faced with the sorrowful situation of not being able to stand before you eternally, Father.
\n\nAmong humankind who are going forward on this kind of course which is before them, there are many people who, without their even knowing it, have experienced and felt keenly hearts permeated with anxiety, uneasiness and loneliness, but there is no one to block that.
\n\nTherefore, Father, who will take responsibility for exhausted humankind who cannot rejoice together with history, with the time, or with the ideology, and who do not know fundamental rules of life, who do not know the direction of life, who do not know the course of life, and who do not know the purpose of life?
\n\nWe will have to straighten things out between ourselves. If there are tangled things, straightening them out is a fundamental rule of the course of history. Therefore, in a position where Jesus could have shown a tangled heart of indignation in relation to his enemies, he wanted to straighten it out. Accordingly, we know that he became qualified as a person who could build the garden of the resolution of grief which straightens out the world of enemies.
\n\nWe know that heaven was also happy about that and established Jesus in the position of the resurrected Jesus. Even if we are ostracized by the people and the people stand in the position of our enemies, please do not let us become persons who consider the people as our enemies. We earnestly hope that you will please let us become sovereigns of life, and please let us become leaders of heavenly life, and even if the world opposes us, please let us become people who have heavenly hearts which are able to go beyond the hearts of the enemies and not consider them enemies, in order to leave behind for them only the open heart of heaven.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 14, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_4t">
Oh Father, who is the majestic Lord of heaven: We know that everything that you created must be together with your ideal forever. A long time ago we realized and for a long time we have been regretting that the terrible grief exists that we have not become human beings who live surrounded by glory, by becoming your true sons and daughters for eternity, together with the praise given to you by the cosmos as your object partner of joy, and together with glory, while we attend you with overflowing joy, having gathered together before your ideal.
\n\nEach time we call you, we cannot help but feel the situation of our Father who is sorrowful, and we are mortified, and we regret deeply that we cannot help but confess that we are descendents who have held up the banner of sin, who have betrayed heaven, and whose minds cannot help but feel anxious each time we look up at your holy majesty.
\n\nYour order to hold on to your children who had become sinful like that, you left your heart of glory as hope, and you have endured and waited impatiently throughout six thousand long years. When we think about the holy grace of our Father who has toiled not just for a day but for six thousand, long, grief-filled years, because of us, because of our ancestors, because of the many people who are living on the earth today, and because of the many spirit people who are staying in the realm of lamentation in the spirit world, we cannot help but confess once again that we are unworthy sinners, who are awe-struck before you.
\n\nFather! Before the love of our Father, who is great and mighty, before the touch of our Father, who has worked so hard, before the footprints of our Father, who has been wounded and has come to us, we are unworthy children who cannot raise our heads. You have walked a way of tears and blood like that. You have waited impatiently for humankind to participate in the way that is like that, but humankind have avoided that way.
\n\nIt was your heart to want to be together in this kind of miserable situation, but humankind, who should have become your children, did not know that Will of hope and were always pounding nails into your heart.
\n\nAs extremely unfilial children like that, we have once again come before you, have knelt down, and are calling you our Father. We know that the voice of our Father is filled with infinite sorrow, and the heart of our Father is filled with bitter lamentations, and his heart has been mistreated, and it is all pent up in his breast. We know that you are a Father to be pitied. But your Will still remains, and as long as you do not cast away that Will, we also must hold on to you once again while going this way.
\n\nToday also without resting, the waves of death are making our living environment muddy, and they are covering the glory of heaven by occupying the area around us. We know that at this kind of time we must once again bear in mind what kind of position we are in and what is the location of that position.
\n\nToday we have been called before the Will of this kind of great providence. We were called without having any kind of achievements. We have come to this place without even any contributions of work. We have come to this place without having anything to give to you. But we have brought earnest hearts which want to hold on to you again, by confessing our evil with repentance and our inadequacy with tears.
\n\nKnowing the historical destined relationship of the work of our Father who took pity on the situation of these prodigals, we are hoping for that destined relationship and we have come anticipating that heart of compassion. Therefore, please bind us tightly once more through your deep heart. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will establish us to be able to go out and fight in the world.
\n\nIt will not do unless we are once again awakened to the fact that we must inherit a new world-level role and mission from you at this time, and we must shoulder the responsibility and the mission from the position that it will not do unless "I" do it.
\n\nThe time is approaching when it will not do unless we indemnify all of the history of the past days of struggle together with the sin of this world. And it will not do unless we form ranks, and we all march forward as the fully-equipped, elite troops of heaven towards the enemy world, while holding the banner of judgment, after having straightened our minds and bodies once again, and while looking towards the new garden of hope.
\n\nWe earnestly hope that you will let us become true sons and daughters who pledge to become filial children of heaven, and that you will let us become brave people of heaven, and that you will let us become the true, elite troops of heaven who are able to give everything we have to the battle, while not wasting a single hour of any day, bearing in mind that we are carrying this kind of responsibility and mission on our two shoulders.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nAugust I1, 1963
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_5t">
We know that the foundation of glory which you were looking forward to was a place penetrated by the destined relationship of True Parents centered on your love without indignation, without lamentation, and without sorrow. The True Parents are the center of the ideal of creation and are the hope of history. From the day they were lost due to the mistake of Adam and Eve, who were the first ancestors of humankind, we became orphans, and it became our lot to moan, held in the embrace of the enemy.
\n\nWe know that you have worked hard in order to establish the individual, family, tribe, people, nation, and world-level destined relationship of the parents, while going through the course of history, and you have prepared the cosmic period of the Last Days by laying down the bridge of the six-thousand-year history, and you have been going through the grief-filled course of restoration in order to find and establish once again, horizontally, the value of the substantial parents of the individual-level victory, the value of the substantial parents of the family-level victory, and up to the value of the substantial parents of the tribe, nation, and world-level victories.
\n\nWe have come to know that the True Parents, who were to come without our knowing, have lived a grief-filled life in the position of pioneers.
\n\nWhen we think that you have prepared in reality a stage where we can struggle for the sake of the individual, the family, the tribe, and the people, we are grateful.
\n\nFather! We thank you for having taken responsibility for the history that remained. Father, we are filled with awe by the fact that you have established the True Parents before us here on the earth, by your having worked hard as a pioneer, going the way before us until now.
\n\nWe have come to know that your having given us suffering was in order to connect us to the level representing the people of the world, and your having given us the suffering of the True Parents was in order to subjugate the satans covering us. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow this to become a time when we swear to fulfill that responsibility.
\n\nWhen have we knelt down and attended individual-level parents, attended family-level parents, attended tribe-level parents, or attended people-level parents? And have we become people who are able to attend such parents?
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to determine that we will prepare the way on which the parents will come, by your letting us take responsibility for the way that is heading towards the enemy world, the way of tears, the way that restores that grief at least today, by repenting for the past in which we could not become people like that, by pioneering the way of the people-level cross, and by pioneering the way of the national-level cross.
\n\nSince we now go the remaining way in joy, oh Father, please do not worry. We earnestly request that you will let us be able to take responsibility for the cross, to devote ourselves for the sake of taking the world away from Satan, and to prepare a way on which you can follow us in joy.
\n\nSince the proclaim that all the good people in the spirit world and on earth, who are hoping for truth, will become the people of heaven for the sake of the Will, and will assist us, please let heaven and earth officially recognize this.
\n\nSince we are hoping that a world of peace, centered on the glory of the victory, on praise, on joy and on love will be accomplished through us in the name of the True Parents, Father, by that day coming quickly, please allow us to restore the day of the cosmic victory entirely and to restore a cosmic day for you, Father.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nApril 17, 1964: the fifth Parents` Day
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_6t">
Father!
\nToday at this time we dare to consider your heart when you were creating all the things of creation. It is the purpose and the hope of the original creation that the destined relationship of one family be formed in relation to the entire universe on the foundation of your heart which is the center of happiness and rejoicing and is the center of all things.
\n\nWhen we think about that, we realize that today this earth has repeated the history of the fall without having become united, centered on your heart, on your hope, or on your situation. Please guide us to become people who are able to repent once again for all our historical inadequacies, while thinking about all these kinds of things.
\n\nPlease have compassion, Father, for the many people who must run along the way of the battle for the sake of the hope of tomorrow, while not having been able to cast away the world of death as vet. And we earnestly hope that you will have compassion for the many believers who, kicking aside the present age, are rushing forward today in the direction of the land of the original homeland which is the land of the ideal of creation which you wanted to accomplish.
\n\nWe know, Father, that there is a great deal of grief in your heart, in the heart of our Father, who has gone through the most adverse situations among adverse situations, while acting and taking responsibility for the past, the present and the future.
\n\nWhen we consider the sorrowful past in which people ended up pounding nails into your heart, in spite of the fact that they should have sung songs praising your eternal idea and heart in front of your heart and your ideal, please let us bear deep in our minds once again that we are people who must bow our heads and kneel down before you, while feeling how sorrowful your heart must have been, and who must raise up an altar of atonement.
\n\nFather! In the long course of history, many days have flowed by, but were you able to be happy for even a single day among them? In this kind of flow of history, you have sought and established a true day of parents on this earth, and you have found and established a true day of all things. Father, today is the very Day of All Things which you sought by working so hard.
\n\nFather! We cannot help but have minds that are filled with deep emotion as we greet this day today, while reflecting once again on the providence which you have worked hard on and carried out.
\n\nAlong the course that has flowed by, you have walked forward through the miserable adversity of sorrow and anguish, we come to feel once again that these were days that you prepared while promising the one day of certain victory in relation to the Will of your mighty providence.
\n\nFather! We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will awaken us to the fact that we are people who must be grateful thousands and hundreds of thousands of times when we think that the greater the adversity was in the past, it appears as a condition for greater gratitude today. Desiring that you will fill all with ample grace today on this day which is a day of joy and glory, we have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJune 19, 1966: the fourth Day of All Things
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_7t">
Father!
\nFrom the day when the struggle of Cain and Abel began, from that time when the foundation of death established itself until now, the world of death has not disappeared. Today we feel that the history of your struggle has continued down through the age with humankind being unable to remove the yoke of this kind of environment.
\n\nWe must feel once again that if conditions of lamentation still remain, those conditions must be straightened out, and if labor that we must do still remains, we must put in order this foundation which is wrong, and settle the accounts of that work.
\n\nWhile continuing along this way of peaks, which has good as its basis, the history of sorrow has continued on down until now, by collapsing and getting up again, and then crashing into sorrow again, as a history of collapsing over and over again and then getting up again and crashing again. We have come to think that this wall of sorrow which has appeared before the present age is the remaining world-level wall.
\n\nOh Father! In order to remove this wall, an individual will not be sufficient. And a few people who have a common will, will not be sufficient. In order to do that you called and gathered individuals, and established the family; you called and gathered families, and established the tribe; you called and gathered tribes, and formed the people; and you called and gathered peoples, and formed the nation. And even when the nation was established, it was your hope to march forward farther towards one united world.
\n\nBut we must think about the fact that it will not do unless there is an individual, a family, a tribe and a people who are able to settle the accounts of sin and take responsibility for your work according to the purpose you have willed.
\n\nIn spite of the fact that history became one of external sorrow due to people, how many sons and daughters do you have who are struggling for the sake of the world and who are taking responsibility for all the things on earth?
\n\nPlease let this become a time in which we examine ourselves again through each of our hearts, and we have a new attitude in relation to you. Please let this become a time in which we are able to realize once again whether we have become people whom you can remember as having attitudes of compassion and conditions of compassion.
\n\nOh Father! We must come to know the fact that you are a Father who is waiting for the time when you can give us a blessing, while responding to our requests even when you are in agony.
\n\nWe have been thinking about how severe the suffering of your heart must have been and how severe the wounds must have been in the mind of our Father who has faced that sorrowful history for six thousand years while days like that continued on and on.
\n\nWho is there to remove the heartistic grief which is twisted and tangled like this? It will not do unless it is a true son of filial piety; it will not do unless it is a true daughter of filial piety.
\n\nBut we know that it cannot be done by a filial son who is centered on the family; it cannot be done by a filial son who is centered on the tribe; and it cannot be done by a filial son representing the people.
\n\nPlease act to let us know the fact that you cannot reveal your heart which permeates and is hidden in your mind, unless to true sons of filial piety, who represent the world, and represent heaven and earth, and whom you can show off to Satan and boast about.
\n\nWe earnestly hope that you will pardon the past in which we could not think about your being in a position of having such a terrible predicament.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJune 8, 1967
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_8t">
We have come to know that the way we are going, called by you, is not a smooth way. Please let us realize the fact that before our eyes today the world of life and the world of death are reaching a crossing point.
\n\nWe, who know that at this point when the historical crossover is confusing the direction we should go, at this point when the religious people throughout the world are being broken, we know that when heaven breaks them, it is striking after having established a standard of goodness, and we know what kind of standard the time of heaven has reached.
\n\nNow we will call out to you under the bright, blue sky, having straightened up our expressions and attitudes. We think the heaven and earth of freedom are approaching when we will be able to run to you swinging our arms and dancing while saying that our time has come.
\n\nWhen we have thought about the fact that the sorrowful past is able to turn into joy, and regrettable, grievous facts are being changed into a time which is approaching which can boast about the brilliant power of heaven, we have realized that all those things that drove us into this kind of position, all those things were your love which wanted to bequeath your heart to us.
\n\nIn this moment when life and death are crossing over each other, please let us become your sons and daughters who are able to subjugate the dominion of death with the authority of life.
\n\nWe are trying to break through to that position in order to harvest, in order to gather in the fruits of goodness which you have sown. We know that we are doing that in Korea, we are doing that in Japan, and we are doing that in many nations of the world.
\n\nSweat will have to flow from the foreheads of such unification workers, and tears will have to flow from their eyes, and we know that the mission still remains that they will have to fulfill for you through their hands and bodies shedding blood.
\n\nTherefore, please let us become sons and daughters who anticipate dying over and over again until the day comes when you can rest after we have gone this way to the end. Please let us become your sons and daughters who determine to fight again and again and who determine not to become people who become exhausted during the battle. Father, we earnestly hope for and desire this.
\n\nPlease let us become your sons and daughters who are able to forget the anguish of the grief-filled history; who are able to embrace the deep heart of life; who are able to boast before all the people of the world by having the day of joy come on earth when we can call you "Father!" until our throats burst in the heaven and earth of freedom; and please let us be able to raise you up and to sing the song of victory.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJune 9, 1968
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_9t">
Father!
\nToday is November 20, 1968, by the lunar calendar, October 1. Nine years ago today, this new Children`s Day was proclaimed on this earth.
\n\nDuring that time we have seen many days go by; and several years have passed. Along this course following the Will, each time we attend this kind of event longing for the aspect of the true children you are seeking, when we look from the viewpoint of the standard you are hoping for, we see that we are still too different from what you are hoping for. The more we think about that, we feel we do not have the dignity to meet you. Oh Father, please look on us with compassion.
\n\nFather! We know that in order to commemorate this day, today, facing this headquarters, many children, who are spread out in each area of South Korea, are bowing down to you respectfully with earnest hearts. And we know that not only in Korea, but your many children, who are spread out overseas as well, who are dragging their exhausted bodies along the lonely course of the pioneer, are thinking deep in their minds about the value of attending a day like this. These children are eagerly looking forward with earnest hearts to being able to greet this day themselves in the land of Korea, and they are praying, shedding tears for the sake of that day.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will resolve their grief, and that you will look upon their concerns, by being together with them personally even though all of their situations and environments are different.
\n\nSince there are many religious people on the earth who are going the way of morality and are offering devotion, please let them have the glory of children by finding the place they are hoping for. And since the hopes of the people, who are professing a day of liberation, must by all means bear fruit on the earth, we earnestly hope and desire that you will let them participate in an occasion that celebrates this kind of day together with us by their meeting you substantially on the earth and by your having dealt with the minds of the people who long for that place.
\n\nWe know that not only those on the earth but also our ancestors and the many saints and sages, who are in the spirit world, have walked the course of the indemnity of restoration for the sake of this earth until now. And we also know that you have pioneered the course of restoration through indemnity by setting up the next descendent if an individual could not fulfill his responsibility.
\n\nAlthough our many ancestors who have gone to the spirit world worked hard, following the Will, and established the foundation of public righteousness, they were not able to have a day of the resolution of grief while on the earth. But when we think about the fact that today we are able to have the resolution of grief due to having Children\'s Day on the earth, we earnestly hope and desire that you will let us clearly realize that our having Children\'s Day today has universal significance.
\n\nEach time we attend a ceremony like this, please do not allow us to think of it as a formality, as a ceremony or gathering like the ordinary ceremonies of the world. We are sincerely grateful, and we sincerely commemorate that this kind of commemorative day has appeared for the first time since history began.
\n\nWe earnestly hope that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who, while groping for the heart of love, are able to be grateful that you have worked terribly hard until now, and you have pioneered the way of the providence of restoration.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 20, 1968: The ninth Children\'s Day
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_10t">
Oh Father!
\nNow please let us know clearly at what stage the responsibility is that we must fulfill through this people, and at what moment the circumstances of the world and heaven and earth are, while going through this point.
\n\nEven though we have minds, we have wills, we have bones, and we have flesh, we have not been able to think about the duties of heavenly morality with proper emotions. Father, please allow us to be able to set a standard that will allow you to set us up and boast about us through our having established the duty of loyalty to heaven, the duty of filial piety to heaven, and the duty of virtue to heaven. In order to do that, please let us have minds that are able to bear fruit throughout the world by surpassing the standard that can connect to the heart of the parents.
\n\nWe know that until now, it has been the age of the parents who could love only Abel. But we know that because we have hearts such that it will not do unless they love Cain as well, a new heart of the parent is budding out here, which has not existed in other ages and which can save this world. And please let us clearly know the fact that you are establishing a new historical, substantial foundation here, and please let us be unchanging people.
\n\nPlease let us know clearly the fact that it will not do unless we stand in the position of being able to love ourselves and at the same time love the world more, and to love Abel and at the same time love Cain more.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will let us know clearly the fact that without Cain, Abel cannot exist, and that we cannot prepare the destined relationship of the blessing on this earth without standing in a position of being able to make Cain submit to us, and that you will let us go the way we must go on our own.
\n\nPlease let us understand the fact that in the future one will not receive prizes from you or be recommended for positions according to the knowledge or accomplishments one has on one\'s own; rather, one will receive prizes from you and be recommended for positions according to how much one has prepared a foundation of education as your sons and daughters in the family, and according to how much one lives a heartistic life in relation to heaven centered on the family.
\n\nPlease let us realize that that is the foundation being established on the earth of the Kingdom of Heaven you hope for, by connecting the destined relationships of new horizontal families which have not existed in history on this earth until now.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMay 25, 1969
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_11t">
Father!
\nWe know that our human ancestors should have become one flesh by realizing the love of the couple together with the destined relationship of your love.
\n\nWe know that centered on the love through which you and our human ancestors became one, all the things of creation should have become one in the midst of the destined relationship of the four position foundation at that point. But we know the fact that because of the fall of the human ancestors, all the things of creation entered a realm of lamentation and God also is lamenting.
\n\nWhen we look back on the course of the history of the providence of restoration, we see that the things of creation were always placed in the forefront in order to restore humankind. By becoming one with those things of creation, centered on God at that point, humankind and the things of creation were connected so that they could become one.
\n\nYou connected those kinds of destined relationships centered on each individual, but today it will not happen only with individuals. We know that because the first ancestors of humankind fell before realizing the couple, it will not do unless one standard is established that is able to connect us with God centered on couples.
\n\nPlease allow us to know clearly that a new task remains such that all of the things centered on that couple must absolutely pass through the name of God, and must pass through the name of the True Parents.
\n\nWe must know the fact that without going through that, we of today could not have been created. And we know that the grief of all the things of creation is resolved only at the point where they become one with the True Parents; and all the things of creation are able to become one with God through all the things of creation which belong to God, and through all the good things of creation which were formed just as we were formed by him.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to realize clearly the fact that the origin of the world-level standard is realized centered on the family in the horizontal world of today.
\n\nPlease let us feel once again today that until now we have not been able to offer devotion in order to have them be able to be things like that, and we have not lived lives of offering devotion for the sake of a day when we will offer those things to you completely as people who eat them, use them, leave them as leftovers, and manage them.
\n\nWe know that there definitely must appear on the earth a day of dedication which is able to dedicate them in order, by forming the destined relationship of the family, and by passing through the destined relationship of the nation up until the destined relationship of the world.
\n\nWe know that a day of celebration must be realized in which all humankind offer to you our entire family and everything we own through our families, through our tribes, through the peoples, the nations and the entire world. In other words, we know that it will not do unless a day is established in which we are registered as families in the family registry of heaven.
\n\nFather! Please allow us to offer everything we have to you completely, and to offer ourselves and our families to you in order to welcome that day. And please let us know that by forming a destined relationship with the parents of heaven, that is to say, the True Parents, and by having it all redistributed to us through their embrace of love, we must remain as the successors of the eternal enterprise, and please let us come to know that we have this kind of amazing mission.
\n\nWe know that this kind of thing must happen on the individual level, and it must happen on the levels of the family, the tribe, the nation and the world. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become children who know clearly that everything must be connected as a thing of heaven by our carrying out a ceremony of purification in order to accomplish this on the world level.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJune 15, 1969: the seventh Day of All Things
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_12t">
Father!
\nWe must feel once again the fact that humankind has infinite value and a destined relationship.
\n\nChildren who seem inadequate to you have come here and are calling out to you. We must not forget that in order for our individual selves to become the beings of the age today, behind the scenes there have been destined relationships of tears between our many ancestors and you.
\n\nWhen we think about the fact that among the many people of the world today, we have been called, centered on the destined relationship, we earnestly hope that you will allow us to discover that although it seems that we look like beings who are nothing special, and who are very shabby, we are awesome people who are representing history and who are representing the present age.
\n\nWe have come to realize that heaven exists in order to love people, the earth exists in order to love people, and you created humankind in order to love them. Accordingly, is not your highest goal the realm of love where your mind, which wants to embrace and love all humankind, can reach everyone in an environment of freedom, in the heaven and earth of freedom without being restricted?
\n\nWe must become people who inherit your providential matters like this, and who are able to directly cry out and shout about it to all humanity. And we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to clearly know the fact that we provide the motivation so that the work of heaven can be spread from here to the whole world.
\n\nToday, centered on a new historical destined relationship, our church is accomplishing world-level development by realizing new relationships. All of this is not boasting about the past, and it is not boasting about a present social organization or form. Please allow us to realize that we have begun walking this way from a position of seeking to love the people of history, to love the people of the present age, and to love the people of the future.
\n\nIn our one generation we must resolve the grief of our many ancestors and the saints and sages of history who were not able to receive true love, and we must become the center which all people are seeking, from a position of being able to love the people of this age today to compensate their not having been loved. We hope that you will allow us to begin with the basic matter of our loving people as a decisive condition which will allow us to connect here the destined relationships of the new beginning of the future.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 5, 1965
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_13t">
Beloved Father!
\nToday is the ninth anniversary of Children`s Day. Please let your love dwell with the children who are sincerely praying throughout the nation facing this place.
\n\nFather! Please bless all the people by reaching out with your holy love from this day on. And please bless not only the people who are on earth, but also the many people who have followed your Will and the many spirits who died for the Will in the course of history up until now.
\n\nSince we know that the way of the absolutely necessary destiny remains, which is the course of indemnity that must be gone by being resurrected on the earth, please let them form invisible destined relationships with us, centered on the activities of the Unification Church today, and centered on our work.
\n\nAnd we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow the many spirit people in the spirit world to become one with us, and even their descendents to become one with us centered on the physical standard, so that we may establish the nation of unification which you desire.
\n\nFather! We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow what is realized on earth to be realized in heaven as well by your personally carrying out works of liberation for our many ancestors who have lived and died while taking responsibility during the course of restoration for the sake of your Will.
\n\nPlease allow us to be able to go forward centered on you, to become true children centered on the destined relationship of the True Parents, and centered on the destined relationship of true children, please let us realize true families, and through true families, please let us realize true tribes, true peoples, true nations, a true world and a true cosmos.
\n\nWe have earnestly prayed in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 10, 1969: the tenth Children\'s Day
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_14t">
We have come to know your heart which was indignant when Adam fell in the Garden of Eden. And we know that you walked over peaks of hard work for four thousand years in order to restore that. And furthermore, we know your deep mind which sent Jesus Christ as the torch of hope, as the torch of sacrifice to the people of Israel on this earth.
\n\nWe know that you sent Jesus in hope, while looking forward to the day of restoration, but because the people opposed him and the environment did not welcome him, we know your heart was indignant as you had to watch while he died on the cross.
\n\nThe history of blood, which has continued down since that day until now, has stained the history of this earth, and it has left traces in the minds of humankind. And in the spirit world, the many saints and sages and martyrs who have come and gone in the course of history, are looking forward eagerly to the day of victory and the day of the resolution of grief.
\n\nWe must realize that the time of hope that they are looking forward to eagerly is this very age, this very moment, and we must be truly grateful to have been born in this awe-inspiring, amazing, historical age. And then we must become your sons and daughters who determine to fulfill the duties of loyalty and filial piety by being on fire with a serious sense of mission.
\n\nNow the Unification Church has laid a foundation such that it will not disappear from this earth. There are many children who worked hard during that time for the sake of this. Until now we have overcome many things for the sake of the way the world must go, centered on the thirty million Korean people, on this nation, and on this land, and they have hearts that have been mistreated historically and which could not share their situations with anyone at all. How very hard you must have worked in order to protect us in the midst of that! We sincerely thank you.
\n\nSince we all have gathered together our weak hands, and our weak bodies are all bent down before you, please command us anew. While remembering the past days when we carried the responsibility of heaven and shed blood and tears in each part of the entire country, we have realized that our whole religious group must move forward once again in the future as well, representing this people.
\n\nTherefore, please let us realize that now the time has indeed come when we must work. Please let us realize that now the time has indeed come when we must fight. And we earnestly hope and desire that, after we offer everything to you, you will let us run out without hesitation for the sake of the liberation of this nation and this people.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 1, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_15t">
Father!
\nPlease let us awaken to this historical mission which is that it will not do unless the Will you have hoped for bears fruit through us today, and that it will not do unless the Will Jesus has hoped for bears fruit through us today.
\n\nWhen we consider that this mission has been bequeathed to us through the price of so much blood, please let us know the fact that we have the responsibility of having to open the gates of the new Kingdom of Heaven of brightness and to enter triumphantly starting from here.
\n\nPlease let us come to know that you have endured up until now by hoping for this, and Jesus and the Holy Spirit endured and went the path of death, and many saints and sages also looked forward to this day and endured, while shedding the blood of martyrdom at the hands of diabolical enemies.
\n\nPlease awaken us to how important and great our individual missions are as we face this kind of crux of history. We know that even Jesus who was born in a lonely manner in the village of Bethlehem had a destined relationship with you.
\n\nAs we think that today we have the responsibility of spreading that Will, which is now centered in the land of Korea, horizontally throughout the world, please, awaken us to how tense and serious a position this is.
\n\nAs we reflect on the six thousand years of your holy history of the providence of restoration through which you sought to have your bear fruit through Jesus by carrying out restoration through indemnity of all the things lost due to the mistake of Adam in the Garden of Eden, we earnestly request that you will let us remain as children who are able to become completely one with your Will by having new minds and new bodies today.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 3, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_16t">
While going forward until now with inexpressible matters in your heart, how very much you must have wanted to express those matters! We have gone forward looking for the aspect of Abel with a humble attitude today also before you, our Father, who has endured and gone forward while hoping for the day to come in which we can raise up glory with praise, and we can praise the victory together with all nations; therefore, please remember us.
\n\nWe have come to know that the purpose of Abel is to attend you alone with his entire mind, and his purpose is to restore his elder brother, Cain. We have come to know that what is needed for that is not awareness about oneself, but a new awareness about you, and a new awareness about the world.
\n\nFather, we know that you are an absolute being, and you are the center of the world. But we have come to know that unless Abel can make Cain submit, you cannot stand in a position at the center of the world. We have come to know the fact that it will not do unless Abel creates the motivation to be able to attend you as the center of the world from a position of awareness. It is said that this is the starting point of restoration.
\n\nFather! Is the Unification Movement standing in an Abel-type position in relation to this people? Now more than a consciousness centered on our movement, we must have a strong consciousness of living for you. More than a consciousness of living for our movement, we must have a strong consciousness of living for the nation. And we must know that when we are able to attend you and that nation in our minds, the fact that we are able to attend you and to make Cain submit as well, that is the starting point of restoration.
\n\nWhen we look at the world dominated by Cain, oh Father, we see that the world has lost its way. Even America, which is standing as the spearhead of the democratic world, has lost its way. The advanced nations are in that situation, too,
\n\nBecause of that, the world has run into a wall of disruption in which from the youth, to those in their prime of life, to the elderly, people cannot find their center. Here we must be able to make Cain submit voluntarily by having become subject partners of the new Abel-type belief.
\n\nPlease allow us to realize that you are very happy when you see an Abel-type person who has a new world viewpoint, and when you come to know that this kind of environment is coming to this world. Please allow us to become one with this Abel.
\n\nThe Cain world submits itself when our individual selves become one with you, and our families become one with you. Since we knew that, the Unification Movement has held up the word, "blessing," and has gone forward fighting until now in order to become the heavenly side by bonding individuals to you and by bonding families to you.
\n\nWhen these families become one with you, the satanic world can submit itself voluntarily, and when we go forth holding up a banner in order to build an Israel centered on these families the world can submit itself voluntarily.
\n\nFather! Since the environment that allows Cain to submit himself voluntarily is arriving right in front of us, it will not do for us to become disappointed here. We must become people who know clearly the fact that we cannot make the world into one unless we, of course, awaken ourselves, and become people who are able to awaken the Cain world.
\n\nWe must realize that this is the position of Abel. Please let those of us who know these kinds of facts know what the position is like where we are able to live together with you, and what dignity Abel must have, and what authority Abel must seek.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 15, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_17t">
Father!
\nThe way we must go now is not an ambiguous way. We know that the people who live, seeking a more public way, become the victors who have dominion over historic  We know that even if they could not take the sovereignty on this earth, they are given a special privilege to be able to have dominion over eternal history.
\n\nWhen we think that these kinds of serious moments are being decided on the stage of our daily lives, we feel that this position we are standing in is a frightening position which makes us tremble, and the course of our lives is a frightening one, which makes us tremble.
\n\nFather! Today we must go the public course of indemnity. We must cast away our individual selves and go the public course of indemnity. You have taught us to go the public way in order to leave behind only the way that brings the greatest victory. Because we must transcend our circumstances in order to go this public way, we know that it will not do unless we serve each other and live for each other.
\n\nWe know that, even if we meet persecution and suffering on the absolutely necessary course as we go towards the purpose, when we stand in a more public position, you let us overcome that by definitely giving us more strength. Please do not allow us to forget that we have that kind of eternal backup and we have that kind of eternal frontline.
\n\nWe have realized that, even if we die, you are our Father who will embrace us and bury us with a glory that is thousands and hundreds of thousands of times more valuable. When we realize that our future is a way that can only be victorious, we cannot help but thank you.
\n\nNow please allow the Unification Movement to become a holy group that is able to handle this final public mission by representing the destiny of this people and by representing the destiny of this world which remain through the entire Unification Movement being united together.
\n\nPlease let those of us who are going forward like this become a movement which increases in strength in front of the hope of tomorrow and not one that loses strength as the days pass.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the TrueIrate Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMay 24, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_18t">
Father!
\nWe find ourselves reflecting once again on that time when we had to decide the destined relationship of indemnity, whether we would go to the right or go to the left at the crossroads in the battle, which no one could know, centered on the 1960s, until the time when the Day of All Things was established.
\n\nAt that time, the place where the blessing was given and at that time, the place where destined relationships were formed was an anxious place, and it was a deep valley among deep valleys. It was a place that beloved parents opposed; brothers and sisters opposed, and relatives who had destined relationships of love opposed.
\n\nStanding in a valley, where we had lost everything like this, we attended you, and we possessed a value that we had found instead, and in the midst of hope, centered on you, the history of the families of the Unification Church began.
\n\nFollowing that destined relationship, Parents` Day, Children`s Day, and The Day of All Things were established. The day that was established on the foundation of these days is God`s Day. In spite of the fact that this God`s Day should have become The Day of All Things right away, should have become Children`s Day, and should have become Parent`s Day, we have come to realize the fact that we possess these days of glory which should have been realized in one day by having patched them together piece by piece over time.
\n\nPlease let us become people who are able to pledge, while gritting our teeth and biting our tongues, that, even if other people do not have filial piety, I alone will fulfill filial piety, and who are able to sympathize with your pitiable mind while kneeling down and shedding tears each time this day comes.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will let us become your sons and daughters who realize the truth that there is an original meaning why we are commemorating this day on which many people are making this kind of pledge each time this day comes.
\n\nToday please do not let your sons and daughters who are gathered in this place know The Day of All Things only by its literal meaning. Please let us realize that the things of creation are not the problem, the person, whom the things of creation are able to follow, is the problem, and whether that person can follow you is the problem.
\n\nPlease let as realize that the things of creation want to be taken care of and governed by a true person who can do that. Please let as become your sons and daughters who love the world and who love all the things of creation. Earnestly requesting that you will please let us become your sons and daughters who are able to be more deeply aware than anyone else of the value of the things of creation, and who are able to care for the things of creation, we have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJune 4, 1970: the eighth Day of All Things
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_19t">
Oh Father, who dwells in a place of glory in relation to this point at which God`s Day comes! Oh Father, who is the Lord who leads everything! Oh Father, who is the essence of omnipotence and an absolute being!
\n\nOh Father, who is the ideal of life and love! Since you have already established this inadequate group which is on earth today as your descendents, and you have already chosen us as your blood lineage, please embrace and love us in your mind. We earnestly hope and desire that you will not cast us away.
\n\nBecause you have not cast these people away, the Unification Movement will become an Abel-type movement, won`t it? Because of that, we will embrace the established churches. Due to our movement and the established churches becoming one, please embrace this people to your heart through this Abel-type standard.
\n\nThen the Korean people and the Korean Peninsula must become able to erect the foundation of liberation for this nation. In order to do that, today the Unification Church members must become one, centered on their teacher. We must not become a group of people who were born for our own ambitions, or who live for our own ambitions.
\n\nWe earnestly request and desire that you will allow us to become holy sons and daughters who are able to live for you and to live for the sake of the future world because we were born for your sake and we were born for the sake of the future world.
\n\nSince we bind our inadequate minds together into one today, and offer them to you, please accept them. Since today at this time, we have gathered together with minds that pledge that we will become one by going beyond our lives and centering on you Father, please be together with us here.
\n\nSince it is said that in the place where there is give and take, there is multiplication, and in the place where there is give and take, you dwell, oh Father, through the unity and give and take between the family of the teacher and the families blessed by you, please let this nation, which has not yet awakened, receive the destiny of the new age, and please let the foundation of the blessing, which can open the gates of liberation, be connected to the religious world and this people, and please connect it to this nation and this land. We earnestly request that you will quickly accomplish the course of world-level indemnity centered on American and Germany by blessing Japan and China in Asia.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 1, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_20t">
Father!
\nPlease let us become people who know the age. We know that it is truly difficult to know the age of the providence. We know that in order to know the age, it will not do unless we appear as the sinner among sinners, and it will not do unless we appear as lonely people.
\n\nI myself know well that it is very difficult to conform to the age unless we have hearts that are in the position of a lonely person, in the position of a hungry person, as a hungry baby yearning for its mother`s breast.
\n\nPlease let your sons and daughters, who are gathered here, realize how many times we have conformed to the age of heaven in our lives, and how many times we made you, who had come to us, shed tears and turn back.
\n\nPlease let us become your children who are able to struggle, saying that we will now become sons and daughters of filial piety and settle the accounts of the past when we were unfilial children. We earnestly hope that you will let us know sincerely that your sons and daughters must inherit the mission of the age, which means to follow you.
\n\nIt is a mission such that it will not do unless we at least determine that we will remain as people who are struggling before you and who forget ourselves while longing to become filial children, even if we cannot become filial children.
\n\nSince humankind cannot know what decides the issue of our living and dying in a certain age, we must realize that only the way of going forward with a mind that is seeking to be careful always, to be humble always, and to sacrifice always will guarantee and protect us.
\n\nIf one age passes by, then once again an enemy in the position of Cain denounces us and blocks our way. But when we go forward offering devotion, when we see the proven developmental course of being able to go forward taking things away after being struck, we feel that you are indeed a being to be pitied, and the people who know the age of heaven and who are shouldering the mission of heaven are indeed a group of people who are to be pitied and whom you cannot help but love.
\n\nBecause you are like that, we have come to know that you always sympathize with your son, if it is a son, or your daughter, if it is a daughter, who is in that kind of position, and you seek to be together and to act together in that realm of the environment of the same destiny.
\n\nWhen we realize that humankind today have the responsibility to attend our Father who is like that, not from a position of being indebted, but rather from a position of comforting you, we must realize that we are people who have the mission of having to fulfill this kind of responsibility.
\n\nThrough our becoming people who know the age and conform to the age, we earnestly hope that you will let many precious people appear from among the Unification Movement members, who are able to be remembered and whose names can be praised on this earth, by your praising us and by our many ancestors of the spirit world returning glory to us.
\n\nWe request over and over again that you will bless us to be able to remain as a movement that heaven and earth can remember and that absolutely does not miss the age by becoming people who know the age.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 31, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_21t">
Beloved Father!
\nThrough the Divine Principle we have learned that the foundation you are seeking is the restoration of the four position foundation. We have realized that the four position foundation is realized when something that has been divided from the complete origin forms a union once again.
\n\nThrough the Divine Principle we know that the world of the ideal of creation which you desire cannot be realized by anything else outside the realm of the four position foundation. When someone asks, "What is the perfection of the purpose of creation that God desires?" we say that it is the perfection of the four position foundation.
\n\nFather! We know that the husband and the wife must be in a position of having become one in order for their sons and daughters to become one. Since the mission to fulfill the responsibility that can be offered to you carefully has been entrusted to the Unification Movement, Father, please love this movement.
\n\nOh Father! The families of the Unification Movement must become families you can trust. When we think that the reason you have overcome the way of suffering for thousands of years was in order to find a decisive object partner who could be victorious as a family by establishing this kind of family, we sincerely thank you that you have allowed the time to come in which the families of the Unification Movement are all able to be mobilized today.
\n\nWe have clearly understood that only when the course of indemnity that must be gone over as a family is gone over, only then will the branches of the family spread out in the heaven and earth of freedom in which you can rejoice. It is a joy that the final age has come in which an age of rewarding value can be concluded in our own lives, no matter what situation we are in, whether we are sleeping or awake.
\n\nWe know that many saints and sages died while going forward with hope for this age, and the fact that they died without fighting together with the Will for the sake of the nation and the world has been their grief for thousands of years.
\n\nTherefore, please let us become sons and daughters who are able to be exceedingly grateful that we are families who have the destined relationship of victory, and we are families who are standing in a position of being able to be blessed more than anyone else.
\n\nYour beloved children who are out fighting on the frontline must be able to think of you alone, and to offer everything to you alone. Having left behind their husbands and children, they are taking responsibility for the frontline, and they are going out day by day to pioneer in order to have concrete results which are proof. Therefore, you will absolutely have to be together with them here. We must realize that there is more value in their offering filial piety to you than in witnessing.
\n\nFather! As they go on their way to the world of the enemy while representing all humankind and representing this people, please let them be holy daughters who know how to be decisive about forming and breaking relationships.
\n\nWe earnestly hope that you will let them know the fact that through this period the  will receive from you the special privilege that lets the day of victory come by their now treading upon and standing upon the history of shame in which women could not find their dignity due to the grief of six thousand years.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 1, 1972
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_22t">
Father!
\nWe know that it is not because of someone`s strength that the Unification Church has continued to exist until now. We know that it is due first to your power, and it is due to the foundation of the public accomplishments of the many saints and sages who have paid the price of blood in the historical ages.
\n\nWe have come to think that these kinds of destined relationships have been formed today because the foundations of the duties of loyalty and filial piety that Jesus Christ offered in his life still remain. And furthermore, we know how very hard you worked before us on the way of suffering in the course of history. I know well that before I was lonely, you were lonely first, and before I faced a sorrowful situation, you are my Father who experienced sorrow first.
\n\nNow we must realize how precious it is that we are standing in a position to be able to know the destined relationship of true families in relation to your Will today, and that you have gone through those kinds of adversities, and have formed the Unification religion and have formed the Unification tribes through many families.
\n\nThrough realizing the true family, that true family you longed for so much, a true people is formed. And through the traditions of the true family spreading out a true nation is formed. And when, through the destined relationships of the true family, the traditions go beyond the nation out to the world, a true world is formed.
\n\nWhen we think about this amazing fact, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will let us realize clearly at this time that we must prepare a firm foundation of true families which you can remember, and in which you can rest.
\n\nWhen we think about how much value we will have when we ourselves collapse, please let us know that the position of blessed families today is an amazing position which determines the internal conditions of the accomplishment of the three-dimensional hope, which is able to resolve the grief of heaven, resolve the grief of earth, resolve the grief of the True Parents, and not only resolve these three great griefs, but rather resolve the grief of this people, and resolve the grief of our descendents in the future generations, by our giving ourselves.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nApril 29, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_23t">
Beloved Father!
\nWe know that your children who are spread throughout the nation are commemorating The Day of All Things by offering devotion in the places where each of them is. Your children who are at the headquarters have come to this place also in order to commemorate The Day of All Things which we are holding for the ninth time.
\n\nWe have come to commemorate this day each year like this because of the grief-filled history of restoration. Through the Old Testament Age, you connected with people through the conditions of offerings. After that you established the New Testament Age by sending your son, and through the New Testament Age, you sought to establish the destined relationship of the parents of the new Completed Testament Age.
\n\nWhen we think that all the things of creation carried out the mission of the offering in the middle from a position closer to heaven than humankind, we come to feel that human beings are standing in a more shameful position than the things of creation.
\n\nIn accordance with this kind of vertical, destined relationship, from the position where the things of creation were the mediators, the son was made the mediator; and from the position where the son was the mediator, the parents were made the mediator. And the realm of this age came in which we can see today the horizontal beginning of the vertical history centered on the love of the parents.
\n\nTherefore, when we come to understand the fact that it will not do unless we connect them in the opposite order to the proper order which is from the parents to the children and from the children to all the things of creation, we come to feel once again how precious the created world which you created is.
\n\nToday in our age it will not do unless the destined relationship of Cain and Abel is reversed by going through this kind of way of suffering, through the family, through the tribe, through the people, through the nation and through the world. When we think that the grief of the parents cannot be resolved unless we do that, we must realize clearly that having to distinguish and go this way is the mission of the Unification Church, and this is the philosophy of life of the Unification believers.
\n\nInadequate people have gathered in this place, but we know clearly that this place is a place that is being watched carefully by the world, and it is a place that is being watched carefully by the entire spirit world. Since it is a place that must not become an object of worry to you or a factor of sorrow for you, by becoming something that is not good, Father, please let this be a blessed day.
\n\nPlease welcome this day happily. We know that this place which is holding a ceremony where we are offering our inadequate devotion is a place that represents history, a place that represents this present age, a place that represents the cosmos, and a place that is able to raise you up and where we are able to form a parent-child relationship and have a destined relationship.
\n\nFurthermore, this day is the day that our many ancestors, who have come and gone in the historical ages until now, have longed for and hoped for. And it is the day in which all the things of creation, which have been lamenting in the realm of sacrifice, can reveal their glory by being liberated.
\n\nAnd it is a day in which the whole world, is able to have a new dignity and is able to bow down respectfully, while calling you, "Father," with a serious attitude, having cast off its shameful attitude on its own, with bright new light after having been in darkness.
\n\nWhen we think of all this, please let us feel deep in our minds at this time the fact that we must celebrate this day, truly giving our minds completely and offering all our devotion, and we must become people who fulfill the duties of filial piety to you and who have the authority of having become a son and the authority of having become a lord.
\n\nFather! Please receive this day today in holiness. We have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMay 24, 1971: the ninth Day of All Things
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_24t">
Beloved Father!
\nWe know how very many rugged peaks there were in the flow of the grief-filled history of the many ages which have come and gone. In the midst of that, many of our ancestors died while they embraced the true Will.
\n\nWhen we reflect on each historical age in which people believed that a day of victory would come, and they determined to, all the while looking up to heaven and while shedding their blood of goodness, and when we think that the leaders of the Unification Church, who are gathered here, and I, who are responsible for the Unification Church, have the responsibility of the actual mission of having to horizontally indemnify completely the vertical history of today, we must realize that this place is not adequate before you and is one we should apologize about.
\n\nIf the positions of joy today are positions that cannot be connected to the destined relationship of heaven, then we must avoid those positions of joy. We have come to know that no matter how ghastly and miserable our lives of today are, if it is a foundation on which the destined relationship of your blood lineage can be connected and moved, we have the mission of having to keep those positions by clenching our teeth and overcoming.
\n\nIt will not do unless we bring to a conclusion the moment when we are able to conclude the mission of the three ages centered on one point, but at this time we must feel once again that we have been people who have not been able to bring this conclusive chance to a decisive conclusion in this serious and determined resolute position of our lives.
\n\nWhen we come to think that you have always coped with history from that kind of position until now, and you led our many ancestors, we realize that you alone are indeed a being to be pitied. We know that the sorrow that is flowing down from the recesses of your mind, and the pulse of your heartbeat which is pounding out must also pound out through our minds, through our inner hearts, and through our physical hearts.
\n\nOur blood must become blood that is able to move because of your blood. And furthermore, our emotions must not move because of our own emotions. We must discover in ourselves, selves who are able to move, having adapted ourselves to your holy emotions.
\n\nFrom our miserable position of tears, we must embrace your mind and appeal to you in order to resolve this grief by hugging you and rubbing ourselves against you, and we must have a position where we can discuss together, and where you say, "I have been looking for you!"
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to definitely realize at this time that without having that kind of position, your beloved sons and daughters will not be able to establish their dignity on their own even if they go to the spirit world.
\n\nPlease allow us to clearly understand that we are pitiful people who cannot go back without having achievements that give you joy in relation to the realm of value of the present in which we must determine to fulfill the responsibility by having the realm of resurrection of the three ages.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nAugust 13, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_25t">
Oh Father!
\nWe know that we have come to stand in this kind of position not because we are so outstanding, but rather it is because behind the scenes our good ancestors paid a terrible and amazing price of blood, sweat and tears.
\n\nWhen we think that we have received the grace of being able to meet with you in this kind of position in the destined relationship of the present age today because of that, we must truly, truly thank you.
\n\nFather! How very much you must have looked forward to this age! How very much you must have longed for the family you desired! And how very hard you must have worked in order to embrace your children!
\n\nWhen we think about these things, we cannot help but worry that our not being able to offer you more brilliant, more valuable, more glorious selves will become not just the grief of one generation, but rather the grief of thousands of years.
\n\nFather, your having gathered these childlike people together like this is not because they are outstanding in themselves; rather, it is because they have precious historical destined relationships. Therefore, we hope that you will mobilize their ancestors and let them cooperate and not rest in relation to their urging forward the mission of this age.
\n\nToday, please let us realize that we are carrying on each of our shoulders the serious mission that heavenly fortune is hoping for, representing our tribes, and representing our people. We know well that it is our responsibility, our mission and our duty, that we must fulfill, even if we die, we who pride ourselves in the name of the true family members.
\n\nAnd the mission of the Unification Movement is the resolution of the three great griefs: the grief of Jesus, the grief of humankind, and the grief of heaven, as elderly people who are old, as the youth who are young, and, it goes without saying, as men or women, young or old.
\n\nWhen we think that the infinite world is moving in order to be included in that value because that value is infinite, before we call out to you, we must feel filled with awe and we must feel a sense of being sorry, such that we cannot even think of the name, "Father." We did not know until now that you are a Father who is difficult to attend, and you are a Father who is difficult to call.
\n\nYou have a warm mind in relation to us, a mind of broad and deep love, and a heart of forgiveness, and you do not lament your billions of sacrifices; rather, you worry over our inadequacies. Each time we discover our inadequacies in relation to your grace, which is like that, we will have to be filled with an apologetic mind and an awe-stricken mind.
\n\nIf we could receive the glory of victory in that kind of position, receive your love as sons, and receive your love as daughters, what more could we want as human beings? Please allow us to clearly realize that a position where that can happen is a position of more precious value than any kind of value represented in human history.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nAugust 22, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_26t">
Please remember, of course, the Unification Movement which is on the earth, but also our many ancestors who are in the spirit world, who worked in the course of history in order to realize the Will, and our many ancestors who shed blood and died while following their inner relationship with the Will.
\n\nThe more that we realize that you are calling upon our inadequate selves to carry out the victorious liberation of the spirit people who know that they cannot dwell in your original world without going through the base of this earth, the more we must feel how important a responsibility we are carrying. And we must more clearly realize the fact that our daily lives are not daily lives that we are living for ourselves; rather, they are daily lives for the sake of the three-dimensional world.
\n\nWhen we think that the many spirit people and the angels in the spirit world have gone forward overcoming a difficult course while hoping until now for your one day of victory, we come to think that we must harvest the fruits of their labors, and the hope we have must be brought to fruition together with all the people of the world. And we come to feel once again that it will not do unless we, who are living on the earth at present, fulfill the responsibility which is able to be linked up and down.
\n\nFather! We come to think that if we do not experience and feel your heart keenly and bring to a conclusion on this earth the way that is able to raise up the destined relationship of your life, you and the many good people will not be able to form a relationship.
\n\nWhen we think that your many children, who are isolated from one another, are on this earth, but there is not a true leader who is able to connect them to life, and when we realize that they do not have a foundation for the daily life in which they must attend heaven and live, while going together on the way they must go to the front, back, right and left, even so, please let us feel that this inadequate Unification Movement, which is unworthy, can have the foundation of the hope of heaven and can become an object partner which is able to comfort your mind.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nAugust 29, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_27t">
Our having remained until today is not due to the hard work of someone. We know well that it is entirely due to your infinite love. It was so in the past, it is so in the present, and we hope that it will be so in the future.
\n\nWhen we think that the area of the providential mission coming in the future will gradually get wider and bigger, it will not do unless, when we offer devotion to you, we offer it with still higher and larger hearts in the future than in the past or in the present. We who are at this kind of point ourselves must not become a movement that criticizes the present reality while wanting to go hack to the past as deficient people.
\n\nWithout forgetting the past, having great hope in our hearts, pushing over all the barriers we run into in the present, and becoming people who are able to be busy handling everything, we cannot become a movement remembered by heaven.
\n\nSince that is a natural fact, please do not allow us to have any inadequacies but let us appear as soldiers in whom you can have confidence, as brave people of heaven, who have completely prepared ourselves to be able to lead the final great battle to victory by confronting the world of evil while being brave and courageous today.
\n\nHow very, very much you must have looked forward to being able to entrust this nation and this people to us, to put your mind at rest, and to entrust the course of suffering of this world to your son by establishing him on this earth, to put your mind at rest!
\n\nWhen we think about this, we realize that our ancestors were always terribly unfilial and inadequate. It absolutely will not do if we also become people who are accused by our descendents in the future of not having been loyal to the way of heaven.
\n\nTherefore, we earnestly request that you will allow this to become a time in which we determine to become sons and daughters who will shine brightly in the final day by our offering the rest of our lives to you completely and who are able to go before you after leaving this world. And please let all this that we desire be able to become the request of the rest of our lives and to become the course of our lives.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 24, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_28t">
We think that the Will of your providence for the course of history which is flowing along was the course of the providence of restoration which cannot avoid a destiny of constant complications. We did not know that in the restoration through indemnity centered on Cain and Abel, the representative dealing with the mission of Abel had to cope with Cain on this earth.
\n\nWe did not know that he had to expand the foundation of liberation which the parents were hoping for. We did not know that he had to possess and offer God`s heartistic liberation which can unite heaven and earth.
\n\nFather! Please let us know that the fact that the members of the Unification Movement are living on the earth today is not an accidental result of your labor. We cannot help but think that, in relation to this serious mission, the Unification Church, which has inherited the traditional history of Abel, has the mission of having to demand the people-level liberation, and at the same time, to accomplish the dominion of goodness and to perfect the world-level liberation.
\n\nAlthough the way we have walked until now was also difficult, we come to feel more and more how vast the course of the mission is which we will have to run in the future. Now the time has come when, having broadened our viewpoints, we must not appear as shameful people before the standard and the ranks which are rushing towards the world.
\n\nFather! The way of destiny which we must by all means go is for the sake of the restoration of the world. Since this way began together with your Will, please give your blessings forever. We earnestly hope that you will allow us to become the heroes needed in the liberation of your victorious Kingdom of Heaven, by always being victorious on the field of battle where we are going.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become children who, at the same time as we awaken the people, also arouse the world, and who carry out the central mission in relation to opening the gates of the future Kingdom of Heaven. While praying that abundant grace and love will always be together with the people who are concerned about your Will.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMay 18, 1972
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_29t">
Beloved Father!
\nWe sincerely thank you that you have awakened us, who had not known, to how tangled the course of history is, and that you have established us in a position where we are able to seek the way of grief-filled restoration that you sought.
\n\nNow we must know clearly that you exist, and we must know clearly what the original standard was like of our ancestors before they had fallen, as you had originally created them. When we think about what the family, the people, the nation and the world are like, we realize that we are placed in the realm of your enemy Satan. We know that we became children of that parent; we became part of that blood lineage, and we became the people of that nation and that world.
\n\nIn this regrettable and mortifying position, it will not do unless we make a resolute decision to cut off from this world and go forth. Having done that, a standard of value just like that does not appear immediately in the good world in place of what was cut off. Therefore, we must clearly realize that when we go out and cut off from the evil world, at first we remain alone.
\n\nEven if we are lonely, we will have to hold on to heaven and be lonely. Because the way our ancestors went in history was like that, please allow us to be able to solidly keep that kind of lonely position ourselves, to know clearly what the hope is that heaven desires, and to run along the way we must go.
\n\nWe must restore the way where we were not able to be loyal to you as servants; we must perfect the restoration of all the things about which we could not fulfill our responsibility as adopted sons. And as sons and brides and bridegrooms, we have not yet gone to the position of parents which is able to inherit your love, but we must inherit it. Since we have clearly realized that this is the way desired by your Will, that is unique, please allow us to go this way purely.
\n\nNow when we feel our bodies and seek to understand them, we must feel that our hands represent the hands of Adam and Eve whom you personally formed. We must realize that our hands are filled with your devotion. We must know clearly that your hope and your ideal dwell in us. We must become people who consider ourselves as precious and who are able to know that your fingerprints of love remain in all our limbs and body, and all of your devotion and love are dwelling there.
\n\nPlease allow us to discover that we cannot connect ourselves with evil because our value is far too precious. And while earnestly hoping that you will allow us to remain as people who belong only to heaven and who honor only heaven, we have humbly prayed in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 22, 1972
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_30t">
Father!
\nNow the final stop at the end of the century is approaching us. Now we know that this being called "I" does not have enough power to be able to solve things through just my destiny alone. Right before our eyes, we are looking straight at a decisive age where it will not do unless the way of victory of the individual passes through the people; the way of victory of the people passes through the world; the way of victory of the world passes through the victory of the cosmos and your victory.
\n\nWe have come to think that in this age when a scene is approaching us where we will be panting and out of breath, if we ourselves do not stand in a position that is able to be one with the purpose you are looking towards, we will become pitiable people, a pitiable nation, and a pitiable world.
\n\nTherefore, we will have to long for you with loyal hearts, and it will not do unless we discover selves who are able to make serious efforts in order to go towards the final stop while believing in and attending you.
\n\nWe know the reality that the evil world and the good world are all tangled together. We know that it is the way of restoration that it will not do unless we, who were born as the descendents of evil people in an evil land, settle our accounts for having gone an evil way and enter into the way of goodness.
\n\nThat way cannot help but be a way of suffering because there is no way to go around it. On the way we are going, individuals are blocking the way, and families, nations and the world are blocking the way, and not only that, even the power of Satan, who has taken the spiritual sovereignty, is blocking the way we are going.
\n\nWhen we think about those realities, and the more we think about how very nearly impossible it is to go against this current throughout our whole lives, we come to realize that we have a duty and a responsibility such that it will not do unless we overcome this way even by determining to die, while having offered all the devotion we have with our entire minds.
\n\nHowever high the peak that we must go over is, when we think that our ancestors were destroyed, and all the nations that came before us were not able to go over this peak and passed away, we know that it will not do unless we, who are running towards that peak, make the greatest determination that has ever been made in history!
\n\nBecause of that we will have to love you with our entire mind, will and devotion. We will have to be crazy about you. We will have to become one with you. Because we know that at this almost impossible stage you are hoping for all the acts that are possible to occur, in our minds we are looking forward to becoming sons and daughters who are dignified enough to receive your love and your praise and who are able to overcome and break through all this.
\n\nThe position of looking forward to this in our minds may be easy, but when we think that in order to go beyond this reality, it will not do unless we conclude the final battle and we bring to a conclusion the final battle of life and death, the more we reflect on whether the mental attitudes that we must have are ready, and whether our bodies are armed, we find that we are inadequate, and we are like naked people.
\n\nTherefore, Father, please dress us in the armor of your strength and your power, and please unite our minds with yours. When we think about the fact that we cannot determine to overcome and to have the victory without becoming substantial beings representing you, we must realize the fact that if we cannot do that, there will be no group as pitiful and miserable as we are.
\n\nWe know that this is a position where victory and defeat cross each other because this is a position where we can cooperate the most with heaven because we have stood on the highest peak in front of Satan.
\n\nWhen we think about the fact that if we end up standing in the position of the loser, we become an enemy to heaven as well, we earnestly hope that you will let this become a time in which we clearly realize the fact that each of us has a responsibility such that it will not do unless we go beyond the standard that you have believed, by absolutely bringing a result of victory, while knowing that we are in a position in which we must not lose.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nNovember 5, 1972
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_31t">
When we consider the problem of who can guarantee history, who can take responsibility for this age, and who can open the new gate of the future, we come to think that it will not do unless I, and not any other person, do it.
\n\nWhen we think about this kind of important starting point, we feel that we are far too weak, far too inadequate, and we are not equal to resolving this. Without a doubt, we are going through our present destiny, the destiny of our daily lives, and the course of our lives looking like that, but in view of this fact of our going up and down, we must realize that if we are not able to resolve the will of the course which we must discern and go as those kinds of people, it is not just a personal tragedy; it is a historical tragedy.
\n\nNow we clearly know the fact that the ruin of one person is not something that finishes with the ruin of that one individual; it has a relationship to history and it has a relationship with the present age and the future.
\n\nWhen we think that the awesome task that is called "the responsibility for the three ages" is related front and back, right and left, and above and below, centered on the one person, "me," today, we realize that if God exists, we must find Him. We must form a relationship with God.
\n\nBecause God has a relationship with the central point of the present, and has a relationship with the starting point of the past, and with the point of the goal of the future, we have come to think that there is no method to break through this way without difficulties, other than going this way holding on to God.
\n\nEven when we are in a bad situation, we must seek God; even when we are sad, we must seek God; even when we are frustrated, we must seek God; even if we go into deadly circumstances, we must seek God.
\n\nWe must handle everything together with heaven, we must adjust everything to heaven, we must forth a relationship with heaven, and we must discern things and go forth together with heaven. Until now we have not known how brilliant this kind of course would be if this kind of valuable course existed.
\n\nWe have learned about the heart of God in the past. We are learning about the heart of God in the present. We have learned about what the heart of God would be like in the future. And not only that, we have discussed even the heart of God before the creation. When we think about those kinds of things, we know that it is truly an awesome place.
\n\nWe must know the fact that if we cannot keep this awesome position in spite of having been entrusted with this kind of awesome position, all these blessings will strike us as misfortunes and go away.
\n\nWe must clearly realize that we must become a movement of people who give all our effort and all our devotion to go forward matching the focus of our lives day by day while always thinking that at the same time that this is an extremely blessed position, it is also an extremely frightening position.
\n\nWe must always feel that we must live in a position representing the three ages. We must clearly know the fact that if I as one person make a mistake, the way of the spirit world is blocked, the historical direction is blocked, and not only that, all of the ways of the past are blocked.
\n\nWhile having hearts that represent history by ourselves, we will have to comfort you, and with hearts that represent the age, from a position of this age, we will have to comfort you who are experiencing loneliness, and from a point in the present time that is surrounded by disappointment and despair about the future, we will have to get rid of those things for you.
\n\nWe earnestly request that you will bless us to be able to become sons and daughters who shine in the past, who shine in the present, and who shine in the future, who are not only loved by you, but also are sons and daughters who are worthy of being set forth and boasted about; that is to say, who are able to be remembered as sons and daughters who have the condition of victory which is able to shine forth in the three ages.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nAugust 1, 1973
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_32t">
Beloved Father!
\nToday, February 5, 1976, January 6 by the lunar calendar, is the fifty-sixth birthday of this son of yours, and the thirty-third birthday of your beloved daughter.
\n\nOur family, which made a new beginning on earth in 1960 in the name of the True Parents, first thanks you that you have let us celebrate this birthday today in the historical year of 1976, having welcomed the day of victory, having followed the administration of the Will you desired in the period of 16 years which have passed since we were established in the center of your Will.
\n\nPlease enjoy this situation and this ceremony. We know that it is grievous that the many human beings living on this earth are not able to celebrate the day that the True Parents were born. We know that it is grievous that the many spirit people who are in the spirit world also are not able to celebrate the day that the True Parents were born.
\n\nThis day today is a day of parents through which a connection between heaven and earth is made, more so than on the days on which many people were born, and more than on any day in history. When we think about the fact that this is a day in which we are celebrating and commemorating that the parents were born, we know that this is a place that heaven and earth know and are bending down to watch; it is a day representing the new historical transitional period in which the spirit world and the physical world become one.
\n\nFather! In view of how very much you must have looked forward to this ceremony, please celebrate this day joyfully. Please bless the many good spirit people who are in the spirit world centered on your name. Please bless their many descendents who were born on the earth, having inherited their achievements.
\n\nAt this time, please let them resolve the grief of their not having been able to commemorate personally on this earth, the day that True Parents were born. Even though all their descendents born on this earth do not know the day True Parents were born, please give them the grace of being able to celebrate this day together on this earth, on a foundation centered on their ancestors, and centered on God.
\n\nThis is a new historical time in your Will in which you have wanted to complete the ideal of creation which you desired, centered on humankind and the entire spirit world in the midst of the love of the True Parents, and centered on the True Parents in the midst of your love. As we think of that, we ask you to please rejoice, Father. We earnestly request that you will allow the entire spirit world to rejoice, and that glory to reach even the earthly world, and the heart of each person to be moved and to be happy.
\n\nPlease bless your children who have gathered here. Please establish this joy of celebrating the day the True Parents were born in a place where we have become one, representing all the nations, representing all the people, and representing the entire cosmos, as a condition of indemnity for the grief of the people on the earth who do not know the Will and all the spirits in the spirit world.
\n\nNow please extend your authority as the subject partner so that they may be governed within the realm of the name of the True Parents. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will transform this age into an age in which we are able to work with the authority of the eldest son by having the descendents of evil parents become restored before the descendents of the good parents by Cain and Abel being switched directly.
\n\nToday, here on this day, born with the name of the True Parent, with your permission, I proclaim that all the spirits in the spirit world and all their descendents on the earth shall become one.
\n\nTherefore, we earnestly hope and desire that by calling together enemies, and by the divided tribes and nations becoming one, you will take direct dominion of them spiritually and physically so that they will be able to advance and march forward to the world of unification, following the destined relationship of the one family as a whole, following the destined relationship of the family of the True Parents, following the destined relationship of the love of the True Parents who represent God.
\n\nPlease realize everything according to your Will, and we earnestly request that you will let this become a day we are able to commemorate while receiving your blessings in the midst of glory, and in the midst of your personally and the whole cosmos rejoicing over this day. We earnestly hope and desire that you will add millions of times of blessings onto all the people who are admiring and praying for this day.
\n\nWhile thanking you for allowing us to welcome this day in joy in your name, we have prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 5, 1976: Parents\' Birthday
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_33t">
Beloved Father!
\nThis son of yours knows well that the history of restoration is a history that has been linked by tears. From the day I groped for and found the world of heart which no one knew, I have come to this position while longing for the day of hope, which I could not speak to anyone about.
\n\nOn February 23, 1977, January 6 by the lunar calendar, we have established the way of hope you desired, we have defended ourselves against the world of Satan, and we have met the new age of a new offensive.
\n\nWe are at a new historical point where the tides that have flowed down must flow the opposite way. We celebrate your having worked so hard throughout the historical ages in order to find the original standard where we are able to boast about your love and your realm of inheritance, where we are able to boast about having become your sons, centered on your love, by you, Adam and Eve, and the angelic world having become one centered on your ideal of creation.
\n\nNow in your name and in the name of the True Parents I make a new proclamation that defends against the standard of accusation of the satanic world, by the entire spirit world, including Jesus, becoming one with the world standard of the Adamic realm, and the world standard of the angelic world which is centered on the Adamic realm, in the ideal world of creation that you hoped for. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will receive this day joyfully, Father.
\n\nSince I have proclaimed that now the people of the Unification Movement, the people who follow the way of the Divine Principle and who know this content, will be blessed with a way of defending themselves against the accusations of Satan, please permit this to happen before the people of the world.
\n\nDue to this, please shine the light of your bright love and the light of the love of the True Parents even to the bottom of hell by your granting a special pardon today. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow that world to praise you, too.
\n\nSince we forgive with love and forget all the sorrowful things along all the historical course we are going, please embrace humankind, and please embrace even the Christians who opposed us, Korea which opposed us, the world which opposed us, and the communists who opposed us.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will please make them one through your love, please let them remain through your love, and please forgive them, especially. And we thank you that we have been able to open the gates and enter the Kingdom of Heaven which can be governed by the dominion of your goodness by realizing one extended family by realizing one nation, and by realizing one world in human history.
\n\nI thank you and proclaim this in the name of True Parents.
\nAmen. Amen. Amen.
\nFebruary 23, 1977: Parents` Birthday, The Proclamation of The Day of Victory of Earth and the first Day of the Kingdom of Heaven
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_34t">
Beloved Father!
\nThe flow of history was full of pathos, and your providential history was a history of despair. What caused this was not God or the things of creation. This miserable flow of history was left behind only because of the mistake of Adam and have, who were the lords of creation, and the Archangel, who was responsible in the angelic world to take care of and raise Adam and Eve. When we think about how sorrowful you must have been while thinking about these facts, we cannot help but lament bitterly humankind`s unforgivable destruction of your nation.
\n\nBut because you are love, in order to establish the standard of the original ideal of creation by letting us go through the history of re-creation, even though you had to go back thousands and hundreds of thousands of times, you did not cast away the way of sorrow of the historical ages which came over and over again, and even if your mind with its traces of love was divided out onto thousands and hundreds of thousands of paths, centered on the position of investing and investing again, and living for the other, and living for the other again, your mind has endured until today, forgetting itself.
\n\nWe cannot help but thank you that such a great God exists. Because this kind of heart of the providence has occurred because of the mistake of humankind, humankind has the responsibility to understand it. In the ages of history many prophets and saints appeared, and many religious leaders came and went, but they were not able to uncover the hidden situations in the recesses of this heart.
\n\nBecause no one knew what the cause of the sadness of heaven was, or what the motivation of beginning of the devil was, or what the condition was for all the attacks of Satan`s accusations throughout history, until now in the religious world there was no way that was able to eliminate and defend against this.
\n\nWe know the fact that many people, who had put their lives on the line and gone forth fighting, having determined the dutiful way of loyalty and filial piety, and who had worshipped heaven and believed in religions, at the very end fell into traps and disappeared as offerings to Satan, and on the rugged, steep way of indemnity, on the rugged peaks of the eight stages which had to be gone over, many people were sacrificed.
\n\nTherefore, please awaken the spirit world of the people who were sacrificed while going forth crossing the gateways of the religions in the ages of history. And then by letting them once again have minds that are able to be loyal to the parents on the earth by finding once again their innermost hearts which related to heaven, please let them become one with the parents` family.
\n\nAnd due to their contributions to the moral principle of the parents` nation, of the parents` world, and of the Kingdom of Heaven of victory, which the parents established, please let the work of being engrafted come about centered on the destined relationship of the parents` family members and the parents` children, by settling all the accounts for everything about the blood lineage which was severed.
\n\nPlease let us have the concept of a total, internal, heartistic bond, which is able to earnestly request to heaven, to the parents, to the brothers and sisters that the family of heaven will bring them to the place it is going, and that the family of heaven will not lose them, by taking as a condition whatever cannot be forgotten, everything they had been devoted about in relation to heaven, and the hard work they did. Since without doing that, that kind of work cannot be realized, we earnestly hope that you will bestow the destined relationship that can do that.
\n\nSince all the ancestors who have gone to the spirit world before us seem like elder sons, and we who are living on the earth today seem like second sons, please let us become one. We know that your way of seeking for the truth of the liberation will be connected by having a victorious foundation in the vertical realm of Cain and Abel which establishes the original realm of the eldest son by Cain and Abel becoming one and by having the spirit and the body become one.
\n\nTherefore, please call and awaken all the grieving spirits who were sacrificed while going the way of religion, and please let them be able to pay indemnity again in relation to all the religions on the earth. And please let them become one with those religious leaders.
\n\nAnd through the cooperation of heaven, and through establishing a standard that is able to restore the realm of the eldest son through Cain and Abel, and a domain that is able to attend the parents, in accordance with this, liberation and resolution will be able to be achieved. Since the parents want them all to have the authority to be able to return to the earth and become one like this, we earnestly hope and desire, rather, that you will bestow that authority upon them.
\n\nOh, all the good people, all the people of conscience, who struggled and sacrificed in order to live according to the way of the ancestors who left behind the way of righteous morality historically, and in order to live according to your consciences while going forth with the morality of your consciences on earth, may all of you, not just let the pitiable religious leaders be liberated, but please come to the earth again.
\n\nThen please open the door through which we can attend the parents and follow them into heaven through the cooperation of you spirits centered on your substantial object partners on the earth. Please deal with all the people, who have been in the realm of the religions, and in the realm of conscience, and not only them, but also all the people who have been in the embrace of the satanic world until now.
\n\nAnd since the age has now come in which Satan can retreat, please establish all of them as family members in the realm of God\'s love. And please establish them in the world-level realm of fortune which is able to receive the benefit of moral principles by having formed destined relationships in the blood lineage of the True Parents.
\n\nWe hope that the external liberation and the internal liberation will go forward into the realm of unification, centered on the domain of the victory of the Cain and Abel realm, by having become one with God\'s inner heart today, just as the internal and external foundation became one in the Republic of Korea during the Seoul Olympic period. Therefore, Father, please be together with us today at this time.
\n\nUntil I your son, who has the name of the True Parent, came to this point, I have struggled for more than forty years. How could I relate to the standard of your hard work, or how could I act in relation to the standard of hope which you desired?
\n\nFeeling, of my own accord, my inadequacy which could not do that, I have lived while growing up in the shadows. I thank you for not having cast me away, and for your day and night having straightened the way I had to go, and for the blessing of your many hidden works through which you let me pioneer the way through the difficulties of the environment and go over the rugged peaks.
\n\nFather! How very much you must have worked to guide me to this place! Please forgive this son of yours. And in the same way, please forgive, at this time, the mistakes of the Unificationists who have followed me in the course of my establishing the Unification Church. We will now repent in prayer for seven days. Please forgive them together with me.
\n\nPlease establish them as your children who are not ashamed to live receiving the blessings of heaven, as the princes of love whom you desire, and as heroes who are the standard-bearers you desire, by embracing them and not leaving them in a pitiful position. We earnestly hope that you will cover over my shame at having held out my hand and given the blessing in the name of the parents, while representing the heart of God.
\n\nOur Father, who knows the situation of our struggling because we do not know the way which is able to deal with the things that happened; oh Father, who knows that we cannot go a way on that we can be comfortable on our own, we earnestly hope and desire that you will broaden the way of moral principles and you will take charge of our future by embracing us with the love you give.
\n\nThrough the love of the True Parents, I declare that everything will be forgiven, everything connected to the five billion people on earth and their ancestors, who are outstanding, starting from the standard of all our ancestors in the spirit world which we must go over, and going beyond the communist world, to the leader of the communist world, Gorbachev, and next to Deng Xiao Ping and the American President Reagan, and it goes without saying, to everyone.
\n\nTherefore, since we have presented the necessary conditional objects to heaven, please do not let this be in vain. And we earnestly hope and desire that, together with the content of the proclamation which is able to unite both worlds, you will receive them as the driving force that is able to rush to the world of liberation by their being fixed in the realm of your heart.
\n\nWe have passed through the Transformation Ceremony of Unification which will be able to go through the providence of restoration, and I have proclaimed this day, which is able to let North and South Korea be unified, to let the world be unified, to let the Kingdom of God on earth and the Kingdom of God in Heaven be unified now within a week, and, centered on this amazing point, taking the heartistic realm of unification of the True Parents as the center of all heaven and earth, on the foundation of that, I have proclaimed the liberation of all nations, "The Foundation Day for the Nation of the Unified World."
\n\nTherefore, please lead all the people in heaven and on the earth who have ears and eyes to listen, to know, and to cooperate with this work and to come into the liberated world of unification.
\n\nPlease let the liberation of North and South Korea be accomplished first, and the liberation of Asia, the liberation of the world, and, of course, the liberation of the world on earth, and even the liberation of hell in the spirit world.
\n\nAlong the course of unification which remains, we must go forward fighting centered on love, by offering everything in order to reach even God\'s world of true liberation together with the liberation desired by True Parents.
\n\nSince we have been entrusted with that kind of task, since we raise up the banner of love in 120 nations, and we set up new lighthouses of unification and light their lamps, and since we determine to go forward to the Unified World Kingdom together, so that our minds of love, that we have pledged before you, will not go out just as those lamps will never go out, please accept everything, Father.
\n\nI proclaim once again, in the name of the True Parents, that God will receive what was proclaimed today as his own proclamation at the same time, as a unified proclamation of the spirit world and the physical world.
\n\nMay that nation last for thousands, and hundreds of thousands of years, and forever, and may it be one that can be governed forever and ever, and in which we live forever and ever, centered on the True Parents and the True Children!
\n\nTogether with prayer, I proclaim all these things in the name of the True Parents!
\nAmen. Amen. Amen.
\nOctober 3, 1988: The Foundation Day for the Nation of the Unified World
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_35t">
History has flowed and flowed until now, and has arrived at this point. Due to the appearance of false parents, the ideal of creation which started with true parents left behind many miserable situations in the course of history, and history continued on as a bloodcurdling conflict filled with death in back of the many human beings.
\n\nWhile reflecting on these facts once again, we come to realize that at the same time that heaven exists, which seeks to deal with those realities, the devil also exists, who is seeking to destroy God`s dealings with those realities, and the devil has occupied the earth as his domain. And we have realized how lonely and solitary the situation of heaven was.
\n\nWe could not fulfill our responsibility of having to return glory to heaven as attendants, by leading and dealing with even the angelic world, with the horizontal, even authority of the parents on earth. Because of that, humankind became the servants of Satan, and by our having become sons and daughters who inherited the blood lineage of Satan, history has continued down as a history of grief; and more grief, and even more grief, from which we could not escape even if we wanted to.
\n\nWhen we think once again about that fact, we come to realize that human beings, who were born as the descendents of the fall, are people who have inherited the fruits of grief, and that a course of grief remains before us as well in order to recover the destined relationship of the blood lineage of the True Parents, by our dealing with ourselves on our own, with minds that respect the position of the family members of heaven, while admitting that we are people who have inherited the blood of the traitor of heaven.
\n\nHumankind was born in the position of the child of the devil and in a position like an orphan who has lost his parents. Human beings have stood in the position of the children of the devil, but the devil has not loved them, and has driven them along a path where they are able to betray the way of heaven.
\n\nBecause of that fact, hell on earth and hell in the spirit world came into existence, and they did not know heaven which thought of that as grief, and all of the people of history were unfilial and disloyal. We earnestly hope that you will forgive everything human beings have done in history.
\n\nThis was because Adam and Eve, who became false parents, could not live according to the destined relationship of true love, and were connected through false love, and grew up like a tree which bore many fruits on this earth.
\n\nIt is nearly impossible to gather all these fruits again and return them to the original standard. But heaven linked that again through a group of people who sought the realm of the chosen people, by starting from the brothers, up to the original position which is the world of the womb, by representing the individual, the family, the tribe, up through the people in terms of the blood lineage.
\n\nWe know how great the labor of heaven was in order to have the dutiful way of the destined relationship of the True Parents appear on this earth. The people of Israel walked a grief-filled, historical course which was a continuation of bloodcurdling conflicts and the blood of martyrs for two thousand years.
\n\nAfter that, the day in which Jesus could be sent to the earth for the first time from heaven, with the authority of the only son, in the position of an original, sanctified child, that day must have been such a day of hope, such a day of liberation, and such a day of joy for humankind.
\n\nBut because the people of Israel did not know that and nailed him to the cross, they once again added to the grief of heaven, and at the same time extended the foundation of Satan. Because of that, the course of history became one that had doubly difficult, rugged peaks that had to be gone over.
\n\nIn order to work through this, the Christian believers inherited the blood of martyrdom. And in order to represent the Chief Priests, the Christians have sacrificed much and have shed much blood, while wandering everywhere as a people who had no nation, who had lost the realm of Israel, and as a people without a nation for two thousand years, while enduring the solitary way of sorrow and persecution.
\n\nThe Christian cultural realm inherited that kind of blood of martyrdom, and extended the world foundation where the historical age of today could once again be connected to the realm of heaven. Centered on the Second World War, the Christian realm was in a position that was able to have, together with the age of the Second Advent, a nation with the sovereignty that is the final destination and that represented the world. But, Christianity, and the United States, which was leading Christianity, did not fulfill their mission, and fell down to the earth.
\n\nFor that kind of reason, the people of our movement, who have been called to the Will of all the historical hopes, in accordance with the destined relationship of the True Parents and the Unification Church today, have lost their nation, have lost the world, and have lost their place to stand, and have been driven out into the lonely wilderness.
\n\nBut through the protection of heaven until today, we have established the church again; we have liberated the people again; we have connected again with Christianity, which represented the realm of world dominion; we have gone to America, which represents the free world, and have been victorious; have not collapsed along the course of persecution even while going against the current to the communist realm, and we have been victorious.
\n\nNow as of July 1, 1991, we will clear away the grief-filled historical course of indemnity; we attend anew the horizontal True Parents who are able to be the original parents together with the Lord of Creation, God, and the right and the left will become one; north and south will become one; and by the religious realms and political realms all becoming one, we will inherit the authority of the eldest son, inherit the authority of the parents, inherit the kingship, and we know that all these circumstances are needed to find the realm of liberation of the original world.
\n\nAnd not only that, we follow the dutiful way of true love which is the center the individual, the family, tribe, people and entire nation centered on the original nature, centered on true love. And we know that it will not do unless in accordance with the one absolute direction, the original Kingdom of Heaven, which is the final, absolute goal, becomes the foundation of the family where we live on earth, representing the earth.
\n\nTherefore, the Unification Church has received from heaven the command to move forward in relation to the task of the sacred mission that it will not do unless we proclaim tribal messiahs, settle down, and break through on the local and neighborhood levels.
\n\nWe have come to know that the positions where we must stand are not as the leader of some church or the chairman of some federation; rather, now we must find the position of the filial son who is able to attend the parents; we must find the position of loyal patriots who are able to attend the nation; we must find the position of saints who are able to attend the world; and we must find the dutiful way of the divine sons who are able to attend heaven and earth.
\n\nThe age has come in which it will not do unless, beginning from the family, we plant that kind of tradition, in which we can declare the completion of the grave five percent portion of responsibility of each individual. The activities of the parents for the mission have already been completed.
\n\nAs of today I have completed the responsibility I had to fulfill in relation to the free world and the communist world and North and South Korea. Now what is left is that the people of the Unification Movement, the children, and the children of the blessed couples must inherit the tradition and be very thorough in carrying it out.
\n\nThe stage on which that can be accomplished centered on principled education, is not the nation or the world. This is the time in which I clearly proclaim that the course of the portion of responsibility in which we must complete our five percent of responsibility, is the establishment of the foundation of the family.
\n\nTherefore, Father, please accomplish this solidly. The person who does not have a victorious dominion over his family, cannot stand before his tribe; the person who does not have a victorious dominion over his tribe, cannot stand before his people; the person who does not have a victorious dominion over his people, cannot stand before the world; the person who does not have a victorious dominion over the world, cannot stand before the cosmos; and without having a victorious dominion over the cosmos, a person cannot stand before heaven, nor attend events before your throne in the heavenly kingdom. Please let us accept all these things as the solemn truth.
\n\nThe age of the completion of the five percent portion of responsibility has come in which each individual must act on his own authority. Now even the persecution of Satan has disappeared completely from our right and left.
\n\nThe Unification Movement is being gathered into a situation where all humankind should respect it as a symbol to be respected highly by the whole world. In order to attend and to accept this, we will have to prepare the place that is able to become the foundation of the Kingdom of Heaven starting from the foundation of heaven\'s blood lineage on a revolutionary foundation, by making the family foundation anew, and by changing the blood lineage through the destined relationship of the blessing by becoming a movement that is able to represent the whole clan as the original family of Adam and Eve.
\n\nUntil now, none of the members of the Unification Movement knew that the beginning of a new base is possible only where each individual becomes one in mind and body so that he or she will not be ashamed; where men and women, and couples become one; and where families are found and established in which the parents are one.
\n\nPlease let us know that now from July 1 on, the world-level age of history is coming in which we must march forward in order to deal with our families and our clans, and in which we must go forward towards this decisive peak.
\n\nOn the first of July, this day was decided as a day in which one could make this kind of application, in which tribal messiahs are declared throughout the world. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will not allow us to forget the mission of blessed couples to establish the dominion of victory which no one can shake.
\n\nStarting from the family, we must pound in, like steel pillars, the standards of the restoration of the authority of the eldest son, and the standards of the restoration of the authority of the parents, and of kingship, which Adam and Eve lost. Please do not let any of the people who applied for that look around to the right or to the left while pursuing their destined relationship with the family of heaven.
\n\nBecause this origin came into existence, through which this standard of the family can be kept, we want to open the way that is able to arrive even at heaven through this foundation, by linking the tribe, linking the people, linking the nation, linking the world, and linking the cosmos. Therefore, heavenly Father, please allow such a time.
\n\nNow please appoint, just as they are, all the representatives who have bowed down respectfully, three people by three people, for the sake of heaven in this ceremony.
\n\nSince I proclaim this to the entire universe in the name of the True Parents, may heaven please directly take authority over everything. Please allow us to pass over from the grief-filled age of history to the age in which the inability of heaven\'s almighty omnipotence to act and to do everything is restored through the True Parents, through the standard that established the condition of the perfection of the True Parents, and to the age in which you can have dominion over all nations.
\n\nBefore heaven there cannot be a free world and a communist world; there cannot be a north and a south; and there cannot be a Satan. Since I proclaim in the name of the True Parents to the earthly world and the heavenly world that the Kingdom of Heaven of victory and liberation will come to the earth by settling the accounts of all the roles of evil, and by burying them together with history, please take it as a shield and lead it eternally.
\nAt this time today on July 1, I proclaim this in the name of the True Parents. Amen.
\nI proclaim this in the name of the True Parents. Amen. I proclaim this in the name of the True Parents. Amen.
\nJuly 1, 1991: the first July First Holy Day, the Declaration Day of God\'s Eternal Blessing
    </string>

    <string name="pr_restoration_36t">
Beloved Father, As of two o`clock in the afternoon on the Day of All True Things, today May 26, 1998, centered on the parents, all the peaks of indemnity that had to be gone over on the earth as the parents have been gone over.
\n\nStarting on June 13, the 360 million couples will be blessed, and one year and seven months later, the age will come in which the entire 360 million couples must take the highway that is able to go towards the Kingdom of Heaven by finding a nation, a central nation, in which direction all the world must go, by uniting representatives of the nations, the nation of the parents, and the nation of the realm of the eldest son.
\n\nAt this point, you have let us have an age that is able to liberate all humankind who are lamenting in hell, and the people of the spirit world and the earth. Through heavens love and the favor of the parents, now the nation of the parents is established, and beginning with twelve Korean people and forty Japanese people, the responsibility of the mother nation, which has not been fulfilled, has been connected to the Eve nation.
\n\nThrough their having become one, saying that they are determined, the condition of the four position foundation is restored, and for the first time, the age has come when America can be blessed. Because of that, now, centered on Korea, Japan, Taiwan, the Philippines and Canada, they have been connected.
\n\nWe sincerely thank you for having helped the hard work of the parents, who are pioneering the way of blessing in order to form the family-level kingdom which could have opened the age of the unified kingdom centered on the True Parents right after the Second World War after all the Abel-type nations, including England, were victorious.
\n\nI know the days in which you pioneered, through your hard work, the course that let me pioneer dream-like realities, and I lived completely for the sake of this work, and I crossed mountains and seas, Father, along this way no one else knew about.
\n\nUntil now the people of the Unification Movement have been treated contemptuously and have walked their course shedding tears. Due to the merit of their tears, they could conditionally offer the nation of the parents instead; they could conditionally offer the nation of the children instead; and could build the liberated world, which could establish the realm of the unified kingdom, centered on Christianity.
\n\nBy doing that, of course, North and South Korea will unify, and Japan and Korea will become one nation, and Taiwan, the Philippines and Canada will become a standard that has transcended race. On that standard, we will establish the destined relationships of children as one family, centered on America.
\n\nThe parents proclaim the foundation on which you can arrive and settle down and the realization of everything that had not been settled centered on the ideal standard of love in the family, the love of front and back, the love of right and left, and the love of above and below that received your love completely, centered on the nation of heaven and earth, we offer before you the foundation that accomplished this. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will receive this.
\n\nNow True Mother will combine the twelve people of Korea with the thirty-six Japanese people centered on Japan, and stand in a position of becoming one. Through that, for the first time, the promised age comes, which is able to go beyond the boundary line of conditional victory of the whole, by the parents and the children having become one before the True Parents and before God.
\n\nSince we are having this kind of ceremony, we earnestly hope and desire that you will receive it in joy. Please let the conditions that are being carried out become historical declarations, and become the realm of the shield of historical victory of the providential history. I earnestly request and desire that you will allow us to become great kings of love who are able to put it into reality and to have a dominion that has eliminated all traces of the satanic world, and that has the supremacy of love in the entire realm of liberation, and where God is able to go back and forth freely, going beyond the families, going beyond the nations to the entire cosmos, to the world of the perfection of the sovereignty of love.
\n\nSince I proclaim this kind of dedication ceremony, Father, please receive it. I proclaim, proclaim, proclaim, this again and again and again in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen. Amen. Amen.
\nMay 23, 1998; The Day of All True Things, The Dedication Ceremony of the Transformation
    </string>
</resources>