<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="pr_devotion_1t">
Please allow this time of our bowing down respectfully before you to become a time of earnestly giving you offerings just as the blood of Abel cried out. Please guide us not to become people who gather centered on our bodies which will decay. Please let us raise up an Abel-type altar representing this people by becoming a sanctified altar just as Abel was a fragrant offering before you and all the things of creation.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will establish us as children who are able to bow down respectfully to you, as offerings that are bowing down meekly and humbly, as offerings that are being given to you, and as offerings of joy that are being offered.
\n\nFather! Please awaken this city which is sleeping. Please take pity on this people that does not know the direction and is wandering in darkness. For their sake, please establish quickly the children you will establish. Please call quickly the children you will call. Please allow us to quickly realize a center directed towards heaven as a beloved altar which is able to represent the whole.
\n\nFather! Please allow us to be able to become meek and humble offerings before the heart of our parent and to frankly lay before you all our concepts, ideologies, and things we insist on. We earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to be able to fully realize our inadequacy, and to basically lay out everything about ourselves before our majestic Father.
\n\nPlease do not allow us to become people who would receive blessings through a conceptual attitude of faith. Please do not allow us to become people who have minds that only seek to receive grace. A history of crying out, "Save me!" has gone on for six thousand years.
\n\nTherefore, please allow cries of prayers which are able to say, "Please accept me!" be heard upon the earth, and please allow this to become a time in that we are able to pray, "Since the time has come to report to heaven, oh Father, please accept me. Since I give you everything I have, please accept me."
\n\nPlease let us be able to examine of our own accord whether we are appropriate gifts for you, and please guide us to be able to bow down respectfully and bow our heads to you, while feeling of our own accord that we are sinners, and feeling clearly our own inadequacies each time we stand in the holy presence of our Father who manifests himself.
\n\nPlease allow this to become a time in which we are able to bow down respectfully to you while embodying your glory by feeling the original nature of goodness and feeling the essence of goodness, and please let minds of repentance arise by awakening us.
\n\nThis work is the work heaven is hoping for. Since we know that heaven is mobilized for the sake of this one Will, please take charge of all activities, and please hold everything in your hand through the Holy Trinity moving, and the works of the Holy Spirit appearing.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will guide us to be able to raise up an altar of saints who are able to offer everything to you alone, Father, and who do not have any ideas or perceptions that are different from your Will.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMay 16, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_2t">
We will have to determine the victory through the process of the sacrifice in order for us to inherit the way of the tradition of Abel. Originally humankind should have had one united standard by becoming one son centered on God`s love in the position of God`s unchanging love.
\n\nBut we already know that due to the fall, we could not have that standard, and because that brought about two results of love, until now you have been going forward shedding blood in the historical course of struggle in order to unite that into the one original standard.
\n\nThe way Abel must go is to find Cain. Then at the point when he becomes one with Cain and offers it up, the parents can manifest themselves, and when, representing the world, centered on the parents, he forms a four position foundation, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow a course of life for the lives of each individual, for the lives of each family, for the lives of the tribes and peoples to occur, that is able to be one in relation to the rules of the Principle which God manifests Himself.
\n\nThe destiny of the Unification Church, which has gone forth fighting for scores of years for the sake of this way, has been miserable, but now the dark night which was pitch-black, has passed, and we have met this age when the morning is coming in which we can face the bright new sunlight.
\n\nWe must all change into new clothes, take on a new mission, have new hope, and march forward with three-dimensional hope rather than a two-dimensional hope. When we understand that those kinds of ranks are now coming in, connected from the world, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow many people to be able to be sincerely grateful for what you have allowed to the people of the Unification Church and to this people of glory who are able to participate by going this way at this time.
\n\nWe must go paving the way of Abel which we must go without caring whether it is day or night. While doing that, it will not do for us to be destroyed along the way, and it will not do for us to become a group that drinks the bitter, sorrowful cup of the defeated in relation to going over this peak. After having gone over peak after peak, we do not receive the laurels of the final victory from God; rather, we must be able to present them to God.
\n\nWe must go forward knowing that of course individuals, and families, tribes, peoples, nations and the entire world must do that before you as their continuous missions. Since we know that the heroes of Unification who stand centered on Unification Thought are this kind of movement, we earnestly hope and desire that yon will allow us to become sons and daughters who are praised and boasted about by you as having that thought until the end, and as having attained the beauty of consummation.
\n\nPlease remember the many Unification Movements that are spread throughout all the nations; please bless the many religious people who are praising the name of God in many places, and please remember all of humankind who are living in misery.
\n\nWhen we think that we have the mission of having to restore through indemnity all the sorrowful spirits that are in the spirit world, we ask you over and over again that you will allow us to realize that the fact that this heavy three-dimensional responsibility is connected to ourselves today means that we are standing at an awesome historical focal point, and please allow us to be able to go to the end as a movement that is able to praise the victory of tomorrow in a grand manner on the pilgrimage that we are going today.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nMay 14, 1972
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_3t">
Oh Father!
\nWe have related to the Will you have allowed wanting us to live in your embrace, but through our minds and through our bodies, there have been many moments that the Will does not allow. If there are conditions that can be accused before heaven and earth or before Satan through our inadequacies, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will fill in our lack through the touch of your power, and that you will block those conditions through the power of your love once again.
\n\nPlease let us have minds and bodies that are thirsting, and please allow us to be able to adore the love that has been locked in heaven, and we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will lead us to be able to be offered as offerings that will give heaven joy.
\n\nPlease take dominion so that our bodies and minds may be offered on an altar and bring you joy, and please guide us to be able to become children who are appropriate for you to have personally.
\n\nAnd please allow us to be able to receive completely all your commands and all your advice. Please take charge so that there will be no one who reluctantly receives your advice and your grace, and we furthermore earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will lead this to be a precious time in which we are all able to become one with one mind and one joy by embodying your mind.
\n\nFather! If there are any kinds of situations centered on ourselves, please discern that with your eyes like fire and let us win over them. Please lead us to realize that you really exist by raising up peace and gratitude in our hearts. Please allow works of inspiration to appear through which we can reveal our inadequacies and repent.
\n\nFather! Please let our minds and bodies be mobilized by that inspiration, and please let everyone be mobilized, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow this to become a time in which we are able to offer ourselves as offerings of glory; and as offerings of gratitude to you, Father.
\n\nOh, Father! Please allow the altar of Abel, which represents the people having the condition of victory, to be able to be offered as an altar of the victorious Abel which is able to restore everything through your having added your power of salvation to this people. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will lead us to be able to raise up the altar heaven has requested.
\n\nWe know that, unknown to others, there are many children who are raising up altars of atonement by representing all the people at hidden altars with hearts that are broken and looking towards heaven. And since we know there must be many lonely children who are shouting out representing your heart in caves, on mountains, or in the wilderness, oh, Father, please let the Will you promised in the last days appear before them.
\n\nPlease allow us to raise up an altar of glory by this people quickly kneeling down next to each other before heaven, and by your pouring out the grace you promised, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will let this people appear holding up a beacon of eternal truth before heaven and earth by building an altar that represents the totality of this people's altars so that this people may sing of joy and victory.
\n\nWe have prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 3, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_4t">
Oh, Father, who has gone forward unfolding a history of toil until today for the sake of all humankind who are shouldering the mission of having to tear down the walls of the indignation that has penetrated heaven! We have realized that now our minds must tear down the walls of indignation that have penetrated heaven, and we know that through resolving that indignation on earth, we form a relationship with heaven.
\n\nHeaven is not forgetting us at this time, either; it is calling to us and is giving commands about the Will of hope which it desires in relation to us. But when we think about whether today we are such that we can respond to that call and whether we are such that we can become offerings of harmony in your presence, we must ask you to please bear with our not having become beings like that, and our being in an position where we are still falling short, are incomplete and are insufficient.
\n\nNow please allow the indignation that has penetrated heaven to be resolved through us by our becoming sanctified offerings by having opened the gates of our minds and having repented again. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become your sons and daughters who are able to greet that kind of day of joy.
\n\nThe final walls of difficulties of the Last Days are blocking the way in front of us, and the course on which we must fight putting our lives on the line blocks our way, but we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will not allow us to become immature, unmanly people, who collapse resenting heaven in our hearts along the course of this battle.
\n\nSince we have already decided to give our minds and bodies as offerings, please accept them and do not consider them inadequate. We earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to hope for your command and who, as the offerings we have made, entrust everything to you.
\n\nFather! Please allow there to be many sons and daughters who are able to tear down the walls of indignation. And, Father, please allow us to have victory in the universal battle by becoming altars which are revealed at the same time as being hidden altars in each place we gather. And we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become able to respond to the direct commands of heaven, to have victory in the universal battle, and to raise the beacon of victory up as far as you.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 2, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_5t">
When we think that you have given us grace which allows our unworthy selves to be able to come before you, our Holy Father, and call you, "Father," we sincerely thank you, Father. We cannot help but be truly grateful that you have extended the grace of salvation to us, a people who have to live filled with indignation without a day in which the moans of death end.
\n\nPlease allow us to become children who are able to offer gratitude for that grace by first giving our minds and bodies to the work of our Father who has shone the light of brightness on this earth of darkness, and to the grace of the Trinity which has toiled consistently while passing through thousands of years of history for the sake of this work.
\n\nWe thank you for the grace you allowed for our bodies, which had been submerged in death, to be able to lie connected to the pulse of love of our universal Father, and for our bodies, which had been submerged in darkness, to be submerged in the flow of life which had been hidden in heaven, by experiencing and feeling keenly your amazing grace through our minds.
\n\nFather! Please let us experience and feel keenly at this time that there is no way to repay your grace even if we give you all our minds and bodies. Please allow us to become people who feel our insufficiency of our own accord, and please allow us to become people who feel overwhelmed of our own accord, even though we give you all our minds and bodies.
\n\nFather! Since we have come before you offering all the strength we have, all the devotion we have, and our entire minds and bodies, please take pity on us. In spite of the fact that we should have offered ourselves as living offerings to you, please pardon that we have not been able to do that even up until now today, and please guide us so that we may quickly be able to appear as offerings that you can be proud of eternally and you can rejoice over and be pleased by.
\n\nFather! Please allow us to realize that you are requesting this people to become an offering of victory, and please allow us to realize that many offerings are required in order to block this people from being swept away by the waves of death.
\n\nWe have bowed down with grateful minds before the grace with which you have led us and established our unworthy selves as offerings that are able to return the glory of victory to heaven, to settle accounts on the battlefield of good and evil, and as offerings that are able to resolve the sites of your work, and as offerings that are able to take responsibility for all areas that you are worried about, Father.
\n\nFather! Please accept us happily as living offerings. After that, please guide us to be able to raise up the altar of victory you have been seeking, and furthermore, we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will let your Will of compassion appear to this people and to all humankind.
\n\nFather! Even for your pitiful sons and daughters who do not know the age and the time, please let your beacon of love and compassion appear, and please let your beacon of words of compassion appear. We earnestly request that you will quickly establish an altar of glory that is able to subjugate Satan, by having an altar of victory, and that we will return glory and joy as unified beings by being quickly embraced in your bosom of love which wants to embrace us.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 23, 1956
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_6t">
Father!
\nHas there been any time that we have offered our minds, will and strength to you as pure things? If there has not been that kind of time while we represent humankind, the people, the world, and the cosmos, please allow us to become sons and daughters who fully realize our own inadequacies before you, and who repent for this of our own accord.
\n\nNow we must offer you everything about our daily lives as pure things; we must offer you all the strength we have as a pure thing; we must offer you our bodies and minds as pure things, and we must offer you our characters as pure things.
\n\nEven though we know your situation of not being able to take things unless they are pure, we have offered to heaven things that are left over after we used them, and since we have lived our lives in just any old way, please bear with our inadequate selves.
\n\nSince now, by taking the example of Jesus who toiled to realize the Will of heaven, we will give everything to you as pure things in terms of our hearts, we earnestly hope and desire. beloved Father, that you will bless us.
\n\nOh Father! Please allow us to take the example of Jesus` mind and experience and feel keenly the heart of Jesus, who worshipped heaven and was not concerned about life or death.
\n\nPlease let us become Israel centered on love by our taking the example of the Will and character of heaven which are centered on the new love, and please let us attend heaven and carry on heavenly lives centered on love.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will awaken us and not let us become people who do not know that we must become true brides of victory who are able to stand proudly before you by having subjugated Satan, and we must become saints who must build the ideal world which heaven is able to enjoy, and at the same time Jesus and the Holy Spirit are able to enjoy, and the myriads of saints are able to enjoy, and even all the things of creation on the earth are able to enjoy eternally.
\n\nNow we earnestly hope that you will guide us to be people who, even if we repent and shed tears, are more than able to shed them on the world level, and if we give our entire mind, to do it on the universal level, and if we give everything for the Will, to do it on the universal level, and if we give our entire character, to do it on the level of the cosmos.
\n\nFurthermore, please allow us to attain the glory of being able to gather together individual things, and as things belonging to the whole to offer those things by our representing the tribe, the people, the nation, and humankind, through living lives which we offer to you as pure things.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 24, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_7t">
Father!
\nWe have now realized that we must go this way for the sake of becoming victors for God. We have come to know that this way is a way of tears; it is a way of sweat and blood; and this way is the way of the offering which is shared with all the people by dividing one`s flesh and blood into all its elements.
\n\nWe have come to realize that if we depart from this way, we will not be able to live in the universal garden of victory that you are hoping for.
\n\nFather! We know that our lives are not our own; our love is not our own; our children are not our own; and all of our things are not our own, either.
\n\nWe know that if, through our greed, we want to possess everything for ourselves, there is nothing that will be possessed by us. Therefore, please allow us to stand in the position of having become offerings who are able to give everything we have to you.
\n\nSince we know that everyone who is a human being must indemnify the grief of six thousand years and become a victor, Father, please allow your sons and daughters who have gathered here today to be able to sing of your glory from a restored position by having accomplished their world-level and cosmic missions while representing only you and not minding this way of tears, this way of sweat, or this way of death, in order to go this was.
\n\nAnd we earnestly hope and desire that you will establish us as children who are able to return all the things of creation to you with tears of joy, and to dominate the enemy Satan.
\n\nSince we have committed all these things to you, Father, please let us go the way of tears, the way of sweat, and the way of blood for the sake of victory. Since the responsibility of having to pioneer the way of victory, has been given to us today, please allow us to give ourselves as offerings on the cross by fulfilling this historical mission of victory.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nJune 30, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_8t">
We know that the day of victory you are hoping for has not yet appeared. When we think that for the sake of the final victory you have been walking a course of struggle covered with blood until today, we don`t know what to do with ourselves.
\n\nWe know that we must arm ourselves with truth and safeguard your Will, and we know that we must offer everything we have in order to go forth fighting for the sake of carrying out the Will of goodness which you desire. Therefore, please let our minds and bodies be mobilized, and we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow the day to cone quickly when we are able to return glory to you.
\n\nIn order to find this one day, while going through the course of history, our ancestors were exhausted, went through suffering, and eagerly waited for the age of the Lord. But we know that due to humankind, the sorrow of not having been able to realize that yet has pierced heaven and earth.
\n\nPlease let us know that in order to find that day of glory which you are hoping for, there have been blood-curdling complications through your having called our inadequate selves, our worthless selves, our incapable selves. We are grateful for your grace of having let us determine and decide that we would offer all our minds and bodies in order to be able to fight for the Will.
\n\nFather, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become sons and daughters whom you alone can boast about, whom you alone can possess by your separating us completely from conditions of the accusation of Satan, and by your receiving us as offerings through purifying our minds once again.
\n\nNow in relation to the Will you desire, we will have to fulfill loyalty through our minds and bodies, and please allow us to feel a new grace through our minds. Please act, Father, so that we may experience and feel keenly the grace of your glory overflowing in our minds and bodies.
\n\nPlease allow us to bow down before you and to place before you the content of how we have lived until now and the responsibilities we have not been able to fulfill. If we acknowledge that the contradictory knowledge of contradictory humankind cannot replace your truth, we earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to place everything about ourselves before you, and to be filled with your grace.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 23, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_9t">
Since we are in such an inadequate position that it will not do unless we request each and every thing from you, Father, please reach out to us and lead us with your compassion. And since the strength and character of sin inherited from our ancestors has closed the doors of our minds, we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will open the doors of our dark minds by revealing the grace of your power and that you will guide us to be able to dash forward towards goodness.
\n\nThe mission that heaven has entrusted to us is not a mission for the sake of our individual selves; we have realized that it is a mission which is for the sake of the people and for all humankind and which has to even resolve the indignation of billions of saints.
\n\nSince it is a mission such that it will not do unless we, who are so unworthy, accomplish that kind of Will of heavenly morality, we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will accomplish that universal Will which you desire by accepting as offerings the minds and bodies of your sons and daughters who are bowing down here, and that you will establish us as people who are not lacking in the least in relation to accomplishing that Will.
\n\nSince there are many kinds of difficulties blocking the way in front of your sons and daughters who want to go towards the Will of heaven, oh Father, please allow us strength; please reach out to us with your power and hold on to us; and please allow us to win by your having entrusted to us the entire battle you have been carrying out. And we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to praise the Will of God highly in front of billions of satans.
\n\nWe thank you that you have entrusted to our unworthy selves the mission of heaven of being able to fight representing this people. Since we have a universal responsibility such that it will not do unless we go forth towards heaven holding high the banner of the battle, oh Father, please give us your might.
\n\nPlease guide us to be able to dash towards the eternal, unchanging course by revealing through our lives your works of inspiration and your direct movements so that we cannot help but go towards your Will even if we don't want to. And we earnestly hope that you will lead us to be more than able to testify in front of all groups of people that we are the sons and daughters with whom you dwell, after having battled and won over billions of satans.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nFebruary 17, 1957
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_10t">
Father!
\nPlease do not cast away your sons and daughters who are bowing down before you in this place, and please allow us to become sons and daughters who do not hesitate to give you all our minds and bodies. We have many points that, in your view, are inappropriate, points that are inadequate and disloyal, but since, depending on your historical heart which has gone forth toiling in order to find us, we offer all our minds and bodies to you, please personally take dominion over us.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will purify our imperfect parts by burning them away with the fire of the Holy Spirit, Father, and that we will become appropriate for you to take. Please allow us to be able to tie all our minds and bodies into one and to offer them to you.
\n\nFather! The rugged footprints of your sons and daughters who have followed coming to this point are footsteps embodying the traces of your tears, and are footsteps, filled with loneliness, that embody your course which has torn at our flesh and blood.
\n\nTherefore, Father, since you know what we have determined in our minds and what we do with our bodies, at this time, please embrace us personally with your deep heart of love, and we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will not allow a single life to be caught by a condition of the accusation of Satan. We know that it is your Will, Father, to convey a new message to this people by establishing us, but we are very anxious that we might cause you sorrow by not being able to handle the responsibility and mission that you desire because of our imperfections and disloyalty.
\n\nTherefore, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will look carefully at the fact of our imperfection in relation to your Will until now, and that you will add the power of your love and the power of your life which are able to supplement that, and that you will pour down on us your personal grace which allows us to be able to handle any kind of mission or responsibility whatsoever.
\n\nSince billions of satans will be active to block our way on the course we are going, please lead us, Father, so that by completely determining our minds and bodies in preparation for that, by offering our lives to you, and by persevering and enduring to the end, we will not fail in the battle with Satan.
\n\nEarnestly hoping that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to fight and go forward for the sake of revealing your glory alone, Father, by going ahead with the determination and decisiveness we had in the beginning, we have appealed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 12, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_11t">
Father!
\nSince you know our minds and you know our bodies, if there is anything inadequate about our minds or our bodies which are bowing down before your majesty at this time, Father, please reveal your power, and please let us become purified through your reaching out to us, and through your bringing about the work of re-creation.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow only you to be able to act, only you to be able to take dominion, and only you to be able to advise.
\n\nSince we are worried that we might not be able to handle the responsibility and mission before you, who called us though we are nothing special, and chose us, though we are unworthy, from among the many people living on this earth, oh Father, please advise us at this time.
\n\nWe know that when Moses stretched out his hand over the Red Sea, it split. We earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to become like rods of heaven which are able to move as you reach out, and that you will become the rod that guides us.
\n\nSince it is already the final time when it will not do unless we march towards the battlefield, please allow us to consider ourselves and to discern what place we are at now. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will guide us to become people who are offered as yours, and that you will allow us to become sons and daughters who are given as offerings to you in each place that we are, and in each one's position.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that, through our becoming new bombs of life which are thrown, you will allow a day of joy to appear quickly in the midst of this people; that you will allow a day of joy to appear quickly in the midst of this global village, a day of joy in which we are able to find a foundation of rest for you, and a day of joy in which people who had died can come back to life.
\n\nNow since we want to offer before you our disloyal minds and bodies tied into one, please bless us to be able to cast away all the elements of sin, of our own accord, and to be offered as pure minds and bodies as yours alone, and please do not allow Satan to attack.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 14, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_12t">
Beloved Father!
\nHumankind, who should have seen the ideal garden of love and worshipped your love, excluded the heart of our Father, who wanted to build the ideal garden of love. Since then they have left behind footprints of lonely blood and tears while going through the course of history of thousands of years. Please bear with humankind who are like this.
\n\nWe know that the time has come of having to long for the lost love of our Father, and the final day of restoration is at hand, when it will not do unless we stand on your side and grope for your heart. Father of love, please establish us today and advise us anew. Since you have called us, please reprimand us anew. We earnestly hope and desire, Father that you will allow us to be able to eliminate the sorrow of restoration and to become people of glory and joy- who are able to bow down respectfully to you.
\n\nNow please do not allow our minds to remain as our minds alone, and please do not allow our bodies to remain as our bodies alone. Please do not allow anything, from the feelings we experience, to the concepts, the ideologies, and the things we insist on, to be ours. We know the truth that there is not a single thing that has started from us, and everything has heaven as its basis.
\n\nTherefore, we earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us to become people who are able to put forth everything as yours at this time, and who are able to return everything to you as yours.
\n\nPlease let us realize that we are beings who are not able to appear before all people with pride with just our own bodies alone, and who are not able to appear before all things with just our minds alone even if we want to show off our minds as individuals. Please let us recognize that we are beings who cannot appear proudly before the entire universe of our own accord, no matter what we have.
\n\nThen please let us place everything that is ours before you, and please transform us through your heart by our receiving your heart of resurrection, and please guide us to be able to penetrate deep into your heart. We earnestly hope and desire, beloved Father, that you will allow us earnest minds which are able to receive your commands of re-creation with hearts of joy. Since all we have to offer you are our earnest minds, please receive these minds as yours, and since we offer our bodies to you, please let them become living offerings.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 21, 1958
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_13t">
Father!
\nHow many tragic situations have you had as you sought to restore the people on earth who should be living for you? Father! Since knowing the Will we have had earnest minds which want to live for you, and even though our hearts are filled with aching and loneliness, I think that there are not many people on earth who have fulfilled their duty of loyalty to you according to that word. Who could have imagined that you, who created heaven and earth, could be in such a situation?
\n\nOh Father! We thank you sincerely that among the many peoples you have protected this pitiful Unification Movement. This way we are following, this way others ostracize, and this way others say is not right, is a way that cannot be gone without tears, and it is a way that it will not do unless it is gone by those having determined to die.
\n\nWhen we think that we are people who have come forth, even though late, appealing to you with tears, on the one hand, we feel sad and mistreated, but when we think that we can stand in a position near to your heart, we thank you sincerely. Father!
\n\nNow this final period is changing rapidly. We know that we have been gathered through a historical destined relationship in this kind of age. Since because of that we must win today, and we must pioneer tomorrow, please let us become brave heroes of heaven who are able to pledge the victory of today and the pioneer work of tomorrow. Father, we earnestly hope for and desire this.
\n\nOh my Father, who has protected me even in the midst of difficulties! I know clearly that you exist, Father, you, who have commanded me to go again, saying, "Since I am here, go again," even on the road of despair, and you gave me orders in the midst of difficulties. Now I have fulfilled my duty of loyalty to you, and I have already gone through cruel situations, while following your commands, but I cannot help but say that the «ill you are carrying out is profound, and your providence is mysterious.
\n\nOh Father! We have realized that when we run into difficulties, behind the scenes you are always bringing us a present. Since we have realized that you love the person who is being struck, and you bless the person who endures and wins over persecution, Father, please remember our members' absolute sincerity as they look at you while doing their best today, and please do not cast them aside.
\n\nWe earnestly hope for and desire this. Please let the tear-filled road they are going blossom as flowers in the garden of your heart, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will please act to let them be able to become shields of victory on the path of the cross which you left behind.
\n\nSince we have now stepped onto the way of restoration which we must go, we must go even if we die, and we must go even if we live. Please let only you be together with us here, Father. We earnestly hope and desire that you will let us become your sons and daughters who are able to testify about you, and who can be testified about by you, even if we collapse.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nOctober 3, 1964
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_14t">
Oh Father!
\nPlease look with pity on this people of thirty million persons. Please allow us to convey heaven`s righteous, new message to this people which has become exhausted, unable to know the destination it must go to, even while wandering, having lost its way, having gone through valleys of sorrow and having gone through a long course of history, and please allow us a day in which we are able to raise up a new altar or resurrection. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow a new time of glory to this people.
\n\nSince we know that you have gathered our inadequate selves and ordered us to become offerings in front of this people, we earnestly hope and desire that you will let us become sons and daughters who are able to charge into the capital city of Satan like bombs and explode, as offerings who give everything for your Will, rather than staying in a position of grieving to ourselves that we are inadequate people who cannot handle this responsibility in front of heaven.
\n\nSince it is not just this people who are wandering and do not know where to go, please ring the bell of the new dawn for the many people who are living on the earth as well, and reveal the light of life. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will let the time come quickly when we can introduce your day of glory.
\n\nOh Father who has taught us the entire Will of the providence of heaven by calling us and establishing us! Since we have come to know your Will today, Father, please act with your direct power so that we are able to act for the sake of that Will.
\n\nWe earnestly hope that you will allow us to become heaven's sons and daughters who are able to go forward and go forward again with new decisiveness and determination towards the blessed land of goodness you desire by your stirring up our bodies that are hesitating and by your urging on our faltering footsteps.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 8, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_15t">
Please let me be able to say, "I am a person who is going towards the garden of goodness which you left behind, and I am a brave person of heaven who is fighting for the sake of the mission which you left behind." Please let each one of us become an individual who is able to state clearly before you that we are making efforts to be found, knowing that we are the people you are looking for. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that we will become people who are able to make a determination of our own accord, and be purified on our own.
\n\nFather! Please add to us your touch of re-creation which will enable us to long for the original homeland by coping with our scattered minds, and we earnestly hope and desire, Father, to become people who decide and determine to assure you and go forth by having become masters of sorrow through having inherited your sorrow, before inheriting your blessing.
\n\nToday with the idea of unification you have gathered us together in this place which others say is not right, Father. You have gathered us together to urge on our footsteps to that place we do not want to go. You are the one who has started this work of goodness. And we know that you are the one who will accomplish that work of goodness. Since we know that without going through your Will, the Will for which you called and gathered us cannot be accomplished, we earnestly hope and desire that we can become humble offerings before the Will today and tomorrow also, by being able to become water before the Will, to become fire, and to become oil.
\n\nWe know that we must become oil which can burn the evil world, and we must be mild and humble in relation to goodness. We know that because you have sought us through this kind of law, Jesus said that "Whoever exalts himself will be humbled, and whoever humbles himself will be exalted," and you have gone forth establishing the way of heaven through sacrifice, service, mildness and humility.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to know our own inadequacies while being filled with that center, and to be able to be infinitely humble before you, and our hearts, that are able to give themselves entirely to you as offerings, to be able to affect even the heart of heaven through each of our minds communicating.
\n\nNow please let our minds grow endlessly in your direction, Father, and please let all ideologies, all concepts and all consciousness which are stained by sin depart from us, and please let us become people who are able to worship you endlessly, with hearts like little children and minds which long for you and want to hold you.
\n\nWe pray that at this time you will lead us so that our original nature will be revealed, our original character will be revealed, and our original appearance will be revealed. Please act to let us become people who are able to make you happy, whom you can embrace once again, and whom you can set forth and of whom you can be proud before the entire universe and Satan. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that going beyond that level, you will let us become people who bow our heads before you.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become people who fight without yielding as the established elite troops of heaven and as pioneers of heavenly morality, even if our bodies are laid on the altar, with hearts of righteous indignation which burn with rage and cannot endure in relation to unrighteousness and evil.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nApril 12, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_16t">
Having gone forth along the way on which you called us, we thought that the way was a way of joy, but as we went along it, we came to realize that it is a way that must be gone while shedding endless tears. And we came to know that it is a lonesome, lonely, worrisome way on which it will not do unless one embraces a heart of indignation while representing heaven and earth unknown to others. We cannot help but experience and feel keenly that it is a way that a person who wants to live cannot go; it is a way on which only a person who wants to die can remain.
\n\nFather! Please take pity on your lonely sons and daughters who have gathered here. Is a heavenly idea moving in their minds? Please let them realize that this idea is not an idea centered on themselves, it is a historical idea. Is there a heart that is moving through this idea? Please let them realize that their hearts are not hearts that remain in their one generation.
\n\nIf they have experienced the grace that they are to receive, and the grace that they are to feel, now please let them realize that they do not accomplish and live in the Kingdom of Heaven alone, centered on themselves. Since you are the one who started this work, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become people who are able to offer everything we have as yours. When we went forth on the way you called us, we had already given everything we had to you, Father. We had given everything we had as yours, even our hearts.
\n\nYou are longing for a person who is able to be happy even when giving everything; please bear with our being sad seeing something disappear. Please let us have minds that are able to be infinitely joyful even after committing everything to you. We know that the person who possesses a mind like this is the person who will possess everything of yours, and the person who has in his bosom an earnest heart like that in relation to heaven, will be victorious in heaven and on earth.
\n\nFather! We have come to realize that your having taken everything away from our living environment was not for the sake of your joy; rather, it was the Will of the providence in order to bequeath to us everything that you have.
\n\nWe have come to understand the heart of our Father who could not help but tell us to come, call us, who could not help but seek us with the Will of those kinds of complications. If there still remains a feeling or a consciousness centered on ourselves, please let us now place them before you. Then we earnestly hope and desire that you will fill our minds and bodies only with minds of infinite gratitude to you as we look at all the things of creation that exist in heaven and on earth.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMay 17, 1959
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_17t">
Father, if you are not there for me, I can say that I am truly a pitiful person. Then when I say I am lonely, I know that there is no place more lonely than this. I have come to understand your gaze, Father, as you looked at me with the heart of looking at an orphan when you drove me out without a friend to the vast wilderness in which my situation could not be understood.
\nI have seen how my Father looked as he struggled to find his children with the heart of a parent who had lost his children. When I think that because of that, I have not collapsed and have come to this point today, I am awe-struck, Father.
\n\nEven if no one of the world gives me recognition, I am proud that I have my Father. You were my Father when I was sorrowful, and you were my Father when I was happy. But because I have realized that you are in a more sorrowful situation than I, I will have to give all my strength…
\n\nPlease do not let depart from myself a mind that is sorrowful from being worried that I will leave behind the grief of not having been loyal from a position where I still have strength remaining, while looking back on the way I have come. You know that I am longing for the time when I can call you my Father, shedding tears, while embracing your heart having pushed myself even on days of rest, and it is so today, and it will be so tomorrow.
\n\nAmong the people kneeling down here there are miserable, lonely people. Father, they are in the prime of their lives. I know well that it is the nature of youth to want to eat more than other people, to want to be prouder than other people, and to want to be more respected than other people. But these people are your sons and daughters who have buried all the ambitions of this time of the prime of their lives and while struggling and longing for your embrace, they have rushed here.
\n\nNow we earnestly hope, Father, that you will become our Father who is able to hold our hands and call us, "My sons and daughters… and please protect the way we are going by participating directly.
\n\nThe remaining mission on the level of the people and the remaining mission on the level of the world are before us. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will please allow us to become sons and daughters who are able to sing songs of the freedom and glory of liberation in the presence of your majesty, by having been people who do not collapse here and who remain to the end.
\n\nIt will not do unless we become people who go towards the foundation of our mission which we cannot help but go towards whether we want to or not because we still have the way which remains for us who have to go it, since we have the moral responsibility of children to complete the mission of restoration.
\n\nTherefore, we earnestly hope that you will protect us along our way. Since you protected me in that kind of position, I know that you are a Father who will protect these people, too, when they are in those kinds of positions. Since you are the Father who was concerned when I was having trials like that, I know that you will protect them when they are in the positions of trials like that.
\n\nI know that when, in the midst of such trials and misery, we offer a position of victory before you, you are the Father, who, after giving us thousands upon thousands of blessings, asks us whether we want more. Therefore, I earnestly hope and desire that you will bless them also in those kinds of positions.
\n\nFather, we know that this age will not last long on the earth. We have met a period of infinite value which occurs only once. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will not allow anyone to become a person who misses this valuable way and laments for thousands of generations, or in the eternal world.
\n\nPlease let us become sons and daughters of filial piety during this time when we are alive in our physical bodies, and by letting us become loyal followers and virtuous women. Please let the way we have gone be called the way of filial piety, and the way we have gone be called the way of loyalty on this historical course of the new heaven and earth.
\n\nAnd we earnestly request and desire that you will allow your eternal glory to dwell forever and ever on our foundation.
\n\nWe earnestly request that you will gather together our movement and all of heaven and earth on the new foundation of glory by revealing the benefit of the special privilege, and please let your glory and blessings and authority of the ages be together with these people, your beloved children, and your sons and daughters who are spread all throughout heaven and earth, and in the future, all the myriads of people who must be established before the Will, and even the billions of saints who are in heaven watching for the resolution of the grief of restoration in heaven with sorrowful hearts.
\n\nIn that way please allow a world of oneness to be quickly realized in which we are able to realize heartistic oneness with you as the center of the true parents, the true children, the true family members, and the true heaven and earth.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 25, 1963
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_18t">
Father, we know that the way of grief-filled restoration is complicated like this. But we, who have been treading along and fighting and have gone over a peak which will allow you to be able to rest, can now feel vaguely that the time is near when we will be able to praise the day of hope.
\n\nWe know that all this is not because of our hard work; it is because of your hard work in order to establish us on the foundation of your endless hard work without others knowing. In this age, you have given us Parents` Day, and you have given us Children`s Day, and we thank you for having established us in the realm of this amazing destined relationship where we are able to attend you, focused on a family that represents a tribe, a people, the world and the cosmos, on a foundation that is able to communicate with hearts centered on you, Father, who are able to create all things.
\n\nPlease do not allow us to become people who lament in the position where this destined relationship is able to lead us. We have realized that it will not do unless we become responsible persons who are able to cope with this destined relationship and who are able to lead this destined relationship and go forward, and we have realized that these kinds of days were necessary in order to accomplish this purpose.
\n\nWe have realized that it is our mission to have to cope with the responsibility of sons and daughters which is to receive written surrenders from the enemies and to restore the billions of enemies of God, the enemies of humankind, the enemies of all things of creation, and the enemies of heaven.
\n\nNow we have realized that it will not do unless we carry out responsible activities to restore of our own accord the entire content of what we have to establish within the realm of all the things of creation which were lost. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become able to let you rest from now on, to take responsibility for the entire history of sorrow in our age on a horizontal level between humankind, and to be able to return only glory to you on a vertical level.
\n\nNow here in this place, please let heaven and earth and all the things of creation become one in this time when we are heading towards and going over the last peak of the providential course, and we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to appear in victorious glory according to the eternal standard of your glory by your preparing the decisive basis for all victories centered on where the heart dwells.
\n\nSince many of your sons and daughters are fighting today also for the sake of this, and at this time also are appealing to you, we earnestly hope and desire that you will personally listen to these hearts and all of the content that is being appealed, and please establish a day of the accomplishment of victory in relation to the entire Will.
\n\nPlease protect all your sons and daughters who are spread throughout the world for the sake of this work in this same realm of grace, and please do not allow them to become exhausted while facing this brutal battle. We earnestly hope and desire that you will allow them to be people who endure and remain to the end until they greet the final day of glory together.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will let us make sincere efforts in order to find ourselves who are not inadequate to stand as victorious, brave people of heaven once again, who embody glory on the foundation which we have coped with, anew by each of us determining ourselves once again through our minds and bodies which are returning home, and we thank you for having been with us until this time today.
\n\nPlease accomplish everything according to your Will. Please allow only the glory of the victory you planned to be realized in the entire cosmos.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMay 15, 1963
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_19t">
Father, Please remember the people here who are in the flower of the prime of their young lives. Their lips have not been defiled. Their eyes are still in a position that does not like the sorrowful color of the sky.
\n\nThe heartbeat that pounds out of their hearts and their pulse and flesh and blood which spread out from it have not yet encountered the Satanic world. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will accept them as yours, Father, and that you will allow them to become your sons and daughters, who are able to sow for the people, to watch for the people, to speak for the people, and to fight for the people.
\n\nAs they go past thirty and go past forty, human beings worry about the time until their final day of their lives being reduced. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow these young people to be able to not worry about the place they are going and to imagine it with hope, to have their hearts brimming over with the great hope of their youth, and to live profoundly, nobly and broadly while living together with you endlessly, and whispering quietly together with you endlessly.
\n\nFather, please remember the youth of the Sunghwa Association who are here. Please let them become living offerings who are able to represent the Unification Church, living offerings who are able to represent the thirty million people of Korea, and living offerings who are able to represent the three billion people of the world.
\n\nAnd we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will let this become a time in which they will be able to pledge anew that they will become living offerings who can become examples for the many people of later generations, and please let them become people who are able to begin as new beings from tomorrow by letting this become a time in which they are able to re-determine themselves.
\n\nPlease allow us to realize that now the Unification Chur ch, the Unification Movement, holds the rod of victory or defeat in relation to you in the future and that we are facing this kind of important great age which will decide whether we can fulfill the responsibility or not as the final shields.
\n\nPlease let us realize that it will not do unless we are on this earth. We are insignificant, but we have stood together with heaven by representing the mission of humankind, and we have stood together with heaven in a destined relationship. Therefore, please allow us to realize that even a small person is strong and courageous, and we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow us to become people who are able to realize that even people who are powerless are valiant.
\n\nWho is going to take responsibility for the thirty million Korean people who remain, for the three billion people of the world who remain, and our many ancestors in the spirit world? How very much you must have longed for a group of people who could say, "Please send me!" while looking up to heaven together with a burning desire to advance forward boiling up in our minds, which is able to mobilize our blood and our flesh, as we weep, kneel down, and join our hands in prayer!
\n\nThis son who is appealing to you has waited impatiently for that; therefore, you have waited much more impatiently, haven't you? Please do not allow your sons and daughters who have bowed down before you here to become people who just put on outward appearances. Please do not allow them to become a group to be hated. Please do not allow the sound of the prayers they are offering to you as they bow down before you to be sounds that can be accused in the future.
\n\nThese are people who have received blessings. Even if they have been in sorrowful positions, they have not been sorrowful people. They have not been sorrowful people because they are people who are able to make the thirty million Korean people weep loudly, and they are people who are able to make the three billion people of the world weep loudly if they come to shed tears out of sorrow.
\n\nEven if they go out to a position of death, even if their individual selves die, they are individuals who are able to make the thirty million people of Korea die for the Will, and they are people who are able to make the three billion people of the world die for the Will.
\n\nTherefore, we earnestly request and desire that you will allow them to become your sons and daughters whom you are able to believe and love, about whom you can believe and boast as the very beings heaven has sought for so long in relation to the stage of the remaining responsibility and mission, and please let them realize that they are not people to be pitied no matter what kind of position of suffering they go into.
\n\nPlease let your glory of the ages be together with them on the shoulders of these young people who are growing, and please form a destined relationship between these people and the new destiny of the world, which will come to the thirty million people of Korea and all humankind.
\n\nWe earnestly request that you will protect and guard them, Father, so that they will be sons and daughters who have no inadequacies and whom you are able to establish to represent the entire universe by being embraced in your bosom of pride, and by being embraced gently in the garden of the Will you had as your purpose.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 15, 1963
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_20t">
Oh Father, who has gone through the histories of countless areas, with countless persons and with countless nations! We have come to understand your history of toil to find one person by having established one people and one nation among them. You have remembered this people among the many peoples, and you have remembered our individual selves today among the many peoples.
\n\nAnd we have realized that you desire to spread the Will of a particular heart which heaven desires to remember again particularly among the individuals. We have realized that until now we have not been able to become substantial beings of joy in relation to that Will.
\n\nNow in relation to this one standard, we will have to determine once again and pledge once again before heaven that we must become sons and daughters of heavens victory who are able to offer ourselves to you as substantial beings about whom you are able to be happy.
\n\nWe know that you need sons and daughters who are able to take the Korean Peninsula as their stage and who are able to begin powerfully and take as their goal of hope having in their hands this planet earth, where so many people are living.
\n\nIn these chaotic circumstances of the nation, we will become able to state clearly the way we should go by revealing our hearts before this people and by at least even ourselves uniting together today.
\n\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will allow us to become people who have no inadequacies to offer ourselves as substantial beings before you, Father by gathering the value of having become the offerings which must be given before this people which still exists, and of having become the altars which must be maintained before this people which still exists.
\n\nWe thank you that you have protected this entire day, and you have worked endlessly in order to have us remain in the providence you have willed. We earnestly request that you will bless us to be able to participate in the midst of joy in the position of people who are able to remain when the Will is realized, as long as we do not betray the Will which has been leading us.
\n\nEarnestly requesting that you will protect us in the embrace of your warm love until we meet again, we have humbly prayed in the name of the Lord.
\nAmen.
\nMarch 3, 1963
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_21t">
Father!
\nHow could the way that you are going be the same as the way that we individuals are walking? And how can we feel that your internal feelings and our individual feelings can communicate with each other?
\n\nOur Father, who has endured and gone forward even in the midst of sorrow and grief-filled complications! We are people who cannot even look up at you. We earnestly hope and desire that you will pardon the days of our foolish past when we rushed forward without knowing you.
\n\nNow we know the attitude of life that we must have as individuals and the direction we must go, centered on the immense mission of having to judge the world and of having to create a new history. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire that you will not let us forget the heart of our Father who has been waiting impatiently for that kind of day.
\n\nFather! You have worked very hard in order to drive the Unification Movement to this point, haven`t you? Now we know that there are many trials left on the path that we must go. Each time we grope for the heart with which heaven endured in the midst of such complications, even though we hold on to you and struggle, we know the fact that we are not able to keep it, and we are calling out to you while shedding tears.
\n\nFather! Please let your many children become able to understand your situation. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will not let us forget how impatiently you have been waiting for children who can be proud after having received the blessing as princes and princesses of victory by having followed the movement you established and having subjugated the enemy.
\n\nEven if the seat of the religious services of the Unification Movement doesn't look like anything and is very shabby, please let it become a place where people are struggling to be centered on your heart. And we earnestly hope that you will let dwell, here in this place, a destined relationship that we cannot avoid and cannot separate from if we are centered on your situation.
\n\nEven though we are naked people who have nothing at all, even if we collapse due to the groups that are ostracizing us on this earth, we know that if this becomes a place where we fall on our backs, while holding on to your idea, your heart and your love alone, that is a place where you will be able to come to us without fail. Therefore, earnestly hoping and desiring that you will not let a single one of your children who are following this destined relationship, fall away, we have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 4, 1966
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_22t">
Father, when we think about how hard you worked in order to cause this Unification Church to progress on earth, we cannot think about it without tears. Until standing in this position today, I have not requested any kind of glory. I have not had any mind to want to brag, to excuse myself, or to put myself forward and advertise.
\n\nBut one thing I am afraid of… I have said that I have gone forth following your Will until now in my life of scores of years, and with a mind that laments that, while going through the past, present, and future through positions of holding the new historical responsibilities, there has been no person who shed tears while embracing your heart in the past, and with a mind that laments that there is not a person like that in the present.
\n\nI am not ashamed before you, Father, because in order to establish your authority, it is evident that you gave up human authority, and in order to establish your prestige and dignity, I gave up completely any kind of location, any kind of environment, and any kind of position.
\n\nYou know that very well. In relation to the historical course where I struggled saying I would find the way of matters that none of the people of the world had gone, you comforted me in every case, and held me in every case. I cannot forget the voice of my Father who encouraged me, saying, "There is no one on the earth who is more lonely than you who are going this way. But there remains more loneliness that you must go through."
\n\nEach time the sound of opposition became louder and I collided with the complicated environment around me, the more I shed tears in the midst of that, and the more I was in places where I vomited blood, I embraced those tears, and I embraced those streams of blood.
\n\nPlease allow your sons and daughters who have gathered here to realize the fact that those matters about which I struggled, saying I would not become a person who resented you, while looking up at heaven, and shedding tears, are what have raised up the Unification Church of today.
\n\nThat is because we knew the situation of our Father who could not speak. It was as though his stomach was cramping and as though his breast would rip apart. You know very well that we are sighing sighs of grief since we could not resolve all the origin and circumstances of the matters of thousands of years, and even today we still are not able to resolve the origin and circumstances of those matters about which we could not help but determine to fulfill our duties of loyalty and filial piety to you.
\n\nPlease bend down and gaze upon your sons and daughters who express these minds completely; who resolve those kinds of hearts; who are able to boast of victory in all nations as your sons and daughters; who say they will fulfill the duties of loyalty and filial piety; and who bring about the day about which you can boast, the day in which you can rejoice, by greeting the day that they can praise for eternity.
\n\nI thank you that you have not cast me away even though I was in a miserable position. And because those who have gone forth following behind this lonely person, are certainly lonely people, since you have protected them with a tear-filled breast, we cannot help but sincerely thank you who have worked harder than I have.
\n\nEven if this kind of heart goes beyond the people and goes beyond the destiny of any satan of the world, we want to be proud that it is the source of life that we alone have, it is a pride that we alone have; it is an asset that we alone have.
\n\nThe things that we are hearing around us inspire our minds for a moment, but please do not allow that to end. And we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will allow this to become the motivation for a new promise which is able to make us determine once again that we will fulfill our duties of loyalty and filial piety, and we will promise tomorrow to you once again by regaining the motivation of life and the source of life.
\n\nPlease allow this to become an opportunity for your children here to go back home with a new fire of life in their breasts while heading to the new world.
\n\nAnd we earnestly request and desire that you will let them become your children who are able to struggle, saying that they will acquire gifts that they are able to bequeath to their descendents by fulfilling their responsibilities of today, and which they will be able to boast about before the later generations, by their having accepted this son as a living testimony.
\n\nNow throughout the time that your beloved son is staying, please personally take dominion over everything. And please let this movement become one that must absolutely exist in relation to resolving your grief and accomplishing your wish on the earth by your widening the foundation of victory through your adding still more of your blessings and protection to the way that the Unification Movement is going.
\n\nIf you need us, please send us into a position of tears, and send us into a position of persecution. We earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will please let us become the elite troops of heaven, and that you will please let us become sons and daughters of heaven who cope with the mission of world history, and who are able to carry out the holy thought of Jesus who prayed for his enemies while dying on the cross and was able to ask for blessings upon them by representing you in a position of being trampled upon and driven out, and by representing the people.
\n\nWe earnestly request that you will let us fulfill all kinds of duties of loyalty and filial piety in order to have the heavenly Will remain, which can be raised up forever and ever, and praised forever and ever, as a mission that goes through the tribe, and is not just a mission in relation to one generation, which can be left to our descendents and our world, and that, as individuals, you will let us attend you as our Father, by quietly keeping all these matters deep in our breasts forever.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed about all these matters in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJanuary 28, 1968
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_23t">
Father!
\nWe don`t have anything. When we see how we look in front of you, we are like naked people, and we are shameful people who cannot raise our faces to you. But we cannot help but request humbly to you that you remember that we are able to understand the innermost heart of our Father who has established the Will of the providence in the midst of miserable situations according to those kinds of matters.
\n\nWe are like naked people who have nothing. With your entire responsibility in front of us, we discover that we are people who cannot go even if we want to, and cannot come even if we want to. We know that the time has come that it will not do unless we struggle in the midst of disappointment and despair.
\n\nIn spite of the fact that we are people who should call you our Father, with both our hands raised up to you, when we consider ourselves, we know well that we are pitiful people who cannot call you our Father when we relate to you.
\n\nThe mission you are requesting is great, but when we realize that we are too small, too cowardly, and too miserable, we cannot help but shed tears feeling deep in our hearts the misery of our Father who called and gathered our inadequate selves.
\n\nBut we earnestly hope and desire that you will let us become your sons and daughters who are able to control our shameful selves by fulfilling the remaining mission and responsibility through becoming people who are able to pray, saying, "We will become living offerings, giving our entire minds and bodies. Even if we die, we will die holding on to the Will, and even if we live, we will live holding on to the Will. Since we entrust everything to you, Father, please accept our minds and bodies."
\n\nWe know that the fact that Adam and Eve came to stand as shameful beings before you, became the grief of thousands of years, and until now they have been derided as objects of reproach by their descendents. Today the Unification Church appeared before the Korean people, and until now it has been ostracized and persecuted, and it has suffered sorrow.
\n\nWe are a group of people who have been driven out by our relatives, our brothers and sisters, our parents and our children. But we have come to understand that this was in order for us to find you.
\n\nWe have cast aside completely the glory of the world and the way that all the people of the world enjoy. We look only at the one great work you have left unfinished, and we have stood in a position of longing for that work.
\n\nBut in spite of that, we know that we are shameful beings who cannot appear before you confidently. We earnestly hope that you will let us become your sons and daughters who determine that we will offer to you our final lives, whether we live or die, while feeling once again that we are shameful beings when we, who are so inadequate, are called before you again and receive orders again.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJuly 14, 1968
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_24t">
We have gone over many peaks of tears in order to break down the standard of the environment of the world which opposes us and the world which does not understand us. The happenings of that time when we went the course of restoration with lonely and grief-filled minds have all flowed into the past.
\n\nBut we, ourselves will remain as the substantial beings of your love, as those kinds of fruits. We must clearly realize that we must not become a movement that collapses and disappears under the opposition of the world, together with history which flows on.
\n\nWe must realize once again that the "I" of today is not an "I" for ourselves. We have come to think that each of us is an "I" who must carry out history, who must pioneer world history; who must take responsibility and testify to the destined relationship of heaven`s love. We are inadequate, Father, but we must become your sons and become your daughters who realize that this being called "I" must offer itself carefully as a gift to be given to you.
\n\nPlease do not let us become your children who add conditions of disappointment and conditions of sorrow in front of your footsteps as you come to seek us. With that kind of heart, how very much you must be looking forward to children who could praise your glory and in whom you could rejoice by your giving them your destined relationship of life and hope, and to sons and daughters who show loyalty to the entire world in order to bequeath without fail, endless blessings to the following generations: We must become people who are able to feel this.
\n\nWe must not become a movement that is destroyed. In order to do that, we must not just watch and assess the things that the enemy is doing. We must fight with the enemy. We know that we come to stand in a position where we cannot be destroyed even if we tried.
\n\nOnly if we strike them and become their enemies. We know that it is not your Will to forgive evil; rather loving and forgiving the people who belong to evil is your Will in order to eliminate evil. Therefore, we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will let us feel once again how very important our responsibility is.
\n\nWe know that it is truth that gives proof of eternity; truth that goes together with eternity, and truth that inherits everything of our eternal Father. Because of that, up until now you have told us to become true people. In order to become true people, we will have to tell the truth.
\n\nEverything we feel through our five true senses will have to become true offerings which can be given to you. Because we are people who have learned through the Divine Principle that it will not do unless it is done that way, in the past we did that, in the present we do that, and in the future we will have to follow the way in which we can offer ourselves like that.
\n\nPlease allow us to become sons and daughters who have lonely hearts having been awakened to sorrow by ourselves, and who feel that we must comfort our Father, and who, even if we have sorrow, know that you have sorrow, and who are able to conceal our sorrow and feel shame.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJune 7, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_25t">
Father!
\nWe earnestly hope and desire that you will not let us forget even in our dreams to become sons and daughters who are able to weep while feeling that our Father who is suffering is to be pitied, when we become more and more frustrated while looking at the way of the Will
\n\nWe have come to know that the course of restoration through indemnity is a way of suffering. Because we have come to know that this is a way we cannot go without tears, we have come to know that we cannot relate to the Will without shedding tears, and we cannot call out to you without tears.
\n\nWe have come to know that if this nation and people were destroyed, you are a Father who would have more sorrow than all the sorrow of this nation and this people, and if this world were destroyed, you are a Father who would have more sorrow than the sorrow of the nations of this world. Therefore, we have come to know that we would not be able to immediately remove your sorrow, even if that nation prospered again and that world prospered again.
\n\nTherefore, we have come to know that you are a being who is to be pitied, and you are a being who is carrying the cross among crosses. We earnestly hope and desire that in the Unification Movement you will let there be many sons and daughters who know that we, who have not established a position to stand in front of our enemies, are beings who lack filial piety, and it is unfortunate that we are not carrying a cross, while attending you as our Father who is like that.
\n\nWe know that the tradition of the Unification Movement is the tradition that you have asserted on earth through the course of history. We have determined that we will follow you as though offering our lives for a day and that we will not mind even a way of many sufferings in order to establish this tradition. But we still do not possess the appearance or the form; therefore, please pardon that we have appeared before you once again.
\n\nIt is natural that we are ashamed of our inadequacy, but the more we think that if due to us this people is destroyed and the world is destroyed, you will have to take the immense responsibility, we come to realize that you are an inexpressibly pitiable being. We, who cause you reason for concern, deserve to the millions of times, but now we must become supports for your Will by becoming offerings.
\n\nAnd then we must stand in a position of being able to shout out that we are those of your children who are able to fathom your mind. We earnestly hope that you will let us come to know that finding the way where we are able to offer ourselves entirely as offerings of indemnity in that kind of position is the way that the unification children must go and it is called the way of victory.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nJune 21, 1970
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_26t">
Beloved Father!
\nToday we are looking for families not so that we ourselves can live comfortably in our families; it is in order to take our families as offerings in order to find tribes. And we are not seeking to live comfortably within those tribes; rather, it is in order to take those tribes as offerings in order to find the people.
\n\nAnd we do not desire comfort in a central position within that people; rather, we seek to take the people as an offering in order to find the nation. It is not to boast before all nations about that nation that we seek the nation in this way; rather, we must give this nation as an offering in order to find the world. We have come to know the awesome fact that after finding the world, we receive the name of your sons and your daughters.
\n\nIt will not do unless we are on the world level. Today we have learned that what is being stressed in the Unification Church is the world level, and the cosmic level, too. We must make a central, united family-level beginning that is able to connect to the heart of the cosmic ideology.
\n\nToday we need a family that is able to represent a family of hope and a world of hope, and is able to awaken the world which has died, and is able to be the pivotal point of the world. Please allow us to become people who are able to have that kind of ideology and thought.
\n\nThen we earnestly hope and desire, Father, that you will let us become a movement that is able to embody the value of God`s sons and daughters who have never existed throughout all of history, and who have minds that are able to love the world more than any other people by having gone beyond our families and people for the sake of the world.
\n\nWe must become sons and daughters who are able to receive love from you by having surpassed the duties of saints. We must realize that that family is more precious than the world, that individual is more precious than the world, and we must meet the day of victory in which we are able to be placed before the whole universe and be praised.
\n\nJesus also said, "For what will it profit a man, if he gains the whole world and forfeits his life?" Please clearly enlighten us to the fact that the position of receiving God's love in this way is the position of sons and the position of daughters which cannot be exchanged even for the world.
\n\nWe must realize that in seeking to fulfill this amazing duty, it will not be just one or two times that we will have to determine to offer our lives. We must realize that we are people who must love the world more than our lives and we must love God more than our lives. Please let us clearly realize that there is no way to go if we avoid this course.
\n\nThe trials and difficulties that are approaching should not be received with discontent and complaint; rather, they should be absorbed with minds of gratitude. We earnestly request that you will bless us to be able to become sons and daughters who, while thinking from your position of the historical ages which were so miserable, praise the joy of today, and can give ourselves for the sake of history, and can create a new age.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the holy name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nAugust 21, 1976
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_27t">
When we think that you have been together with us with love, pity, compassion and forgiveness along the course we are going, we are truly grateful. Father, your children who are gathered in this place are people who are conscious of the fact that they are carrying on their two shoulders the heavy, important mission that will decide the destiny of unification. Father, please consider as holy these people who want to offer themselves to you as offerings as true substantial beings by having realized sincerely the course of truth which has never existed in history.
\n\nWe know that the position where one has gone forth to take responsibility for the people, the position where one has gone forth to take responsibility for the lives of the people, and the position where one has gone forth to take responsibility for the many lives in the place where one is, is the position of an offering which must form a relationship with you alone.
\n\nWe know well that it will not do unless this becomes a life course which we live while having a mind with all kinds of loyalty, and unless we give you all kinds of devotion with minds which hope to offer ourselves as perfect offerings to you, who are an almighty and omniscient being and a perfect being, by our clearly realizing what kind of value we have when we can be offered to you genuinely.
\n\nWe must realize that we are going this way in order to give blessings more than we are going this way in order to receive blessings. We must realize that we are carrying a responsibility such that it will not do unless the people become happy through us more than our going forward for the sake of a position where we are happy through the people.
\n\nWe must know that this is not a way we are going for the sake of our own improvement; rather, it is for the sake of the improvement of the whole. Each time that we stand in a position of being disappointed or being lonely while going this way on our own, we must clearly realize that we are people who are able to be offered representing the lonely people, lonely humankind, and lonely heaven. Therefore, we must necessarily be lonely, we must necessarily be solitary, and we must necessarily go the way of sacrifice.
\n\nWe do not value living better than other people, or being in an environment that is more free than anyone else's. We must come to know that when, standing in a sacrificial position representing the whole, we are miserable of our own accord, we are mistreated of our own accord, and we suffer of our own accord, it is a position in which many peoples and heaven itself are not destroyed at the same time that we are not destroyed.
\n\nPlease let us know that if there is something to beg you, the thing that we beg you must not be something limited to our own individual selves; rather, it must be a prayer for the sake of the realm of the offerings that are able to be offered to you by representing the whole. And then please allow us to clearly realize that when we stand in a position where through our individual selves, our family, and through our family, our church becomes a sacrifice for the whole, at that point a new way can be opened for the people, and a new light of the world can appear, and a new beginning can be made which can liberate your grief-filled historical course.
\n\nWe have prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nAugust 30, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_28t">
Father!
\nPlease let us become offerings as substantial beings, by carefully placing before you our own minds and bodies. The substantial being of offering must not remain as a condition of Satan; rather, it must be offered completely before you as a complete offering, as a resurrected being of victory.
\n\nAnd please allow us to know clearly that it will not do unless we have that day in which you can rejoice, and in which we can rejoice, and that is the way of destiny which the people of the Unification Church must go today.
\n\nUntil now we have gone forward overcoming the way of suffering. Even if we, who are like that, have a course of suffering that doubles the one laid before us, we are people who once again have to have devotion, pledge before you, and go.
\n\nWe know that if we do not take responsibility for this way, there is no one to take responsibility for it. Therefore, please allow us to be able to cope with our forgetful selves in order to go up onto the stage of trials which lies before us, and please let us become sons and daughters whom you can believe and be proud of when you see us, by our having appeared once again as determined, substantial beings.
\n\nWe have come to know that we must become children who are able to comfort your mind along this course where you are seeking sons and daughters of filial piety, who are one with your heartistic inner aspect, and we must become people of the Unification Movement who are able to now ask to take over this way of your hard work, and who are able to inherit the way of suffering. Therefore, we come to think that we are people who must feel that it is worrisome that we could not go a way of more suffering, and it is sorrowful that we could not suffer more.
\n\nThese are miserable people, these are solitary people and these are lonely people. Because they are people who are desperately defending the lonely way of heaven and are following the way of heaven, because they have a common destiny which cannot help but be lonely, I know that you will certainly be with them.
\n\nPlease let us realize clearly that having to carry you on our backs and collapse, and having to attend you and fall down is our life, and please let us be able to sing a song of victory and sing praises strongly, with our whole hearts until our throats burst, while representing you and your eternal glory while gazing on that day of victory. We earnestly request that you will allow us to become sons and daughters of our holy Father, who are able to invest our whole lives, and to invest the time of a thousand years for the sake of that one time, for the sake of that day.
\n\nWe have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nSeptember 5, 1971
    </string>

    <string name="pr_devotion_29t">
Father!
\nThe situation of Korea is at an acute point. Of course, the situation of Asia and the situation of the world, as well, are spinning, having lost their direction in the midst of a whirlpool. We know that it will not do unless we get out of this whirlpool from the top to the bottom by your lowering a line to us, our holding on to that line, and establishing our direction. But this people does not know that it is standing in a position of having to establish its location by waking up and finding its direction.
\n\nWho must help it find its direction? We know that the person who knows the direction must do that. Because I knew the way that others did not know, I have offered my life and endured the way of suffering. The fact is that I knew it was a problem, and it was a problem to live for you.
\n\nSince through your love you have led me to a position that no one else can come to, at this point I cannot drink the bitter cup of the defeated and go the way of sorrow. Please allow us to be able to proclaim that we will unite North and South Korea centered on you by once again equipping and banding together before you the young members of the Unification Movement in Korea. Please allow the division of the East and the West to become one centered on you.
\n\nFather! Through offerings, we must connect everything of the historical individuals that was divided among individuals; through offerings, we must connect everything of the miserable families that was divided among the families; through offerings, we must connect the divided situations of the nations; and through offerings we must connect the divided situations of the world.
\n\nFather, we know the fact that you are looking for a religious movement that must take responsibility for these things. We will have to once again realize that the movement that must take on that awesome mission is this very Unification Movement.
\n\nNow before long, the Unification Movement will lay the internal and external foundation to cope with this amazing mission. Therefore, we earnestly request that you will let this movement become one that determines all kinds of duties of loyalty and filial p1ety in relation to this awesome mission, and we earnestly hope and desire that you will realize everything according to your Will.
\n\nRequesting once more to you, Father, that you will let us become the altar of unification that is able to offer ourselves as living offerings until the final second, we have humbly prayed all these things in the name of the True Parents.
\nAmen.
\nDecember 28, 1975
    </string>
</resources>